- SION, DON'T GRIEVE
FOR YOUR MOTHER.
YOU'VE GROWN INTO SUCH AN
AMAZING YOUNG MAN ALREADY
AND I COULDN'T BE
PROUDER OF YOU, MY DARLING.
AND HOWEVER LOWBORN YOU ARE,
THERE WILL ALWAYS BE SOMEONE
WILLING TO CARRY YOUR TORCH.
SO EVEN IF I'M NOT HERE,
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
- Iris: YOUR MAJESTY?
- SORRY, YOU WERE TELLING ME
ABOUT NELPHA.
- NOW WHERE EXACTLY
DID I LEAVE OFF?
LET'S SEE, THERE'S A VALIANT
PRINCE AND A STUPID PRINCE.
THE STUPID PRINCE ISN'T POPULAR
WITH THE COMMONERS.
- HUH?
- YEAH!
- Iris: THE VALIANT PRINCE HAS
JUST ABOUT EVERYONE'S SUPPORT.
- AND THAT'S
TOALE NELPHI, RIGHT?
- UH-HUH. HE'S EVEN TAMED
THE WILD BEAST!
SORT OF, I GUESS...
MOSTLY BY SHARING HIS DESSERT.
- ( laughing )
I SEE. SO, RYNER AND FERRIS
HAVE SOUGHT REFUGE
IN TOALE'S MANOR HOUSE?
- YEP.
- INTERESTING.
- ( theme song playing )
- Calne: SO FAR, MAJORITY
OPINION CONDEMNS
THE GOODWILL
MISSION TO NELPHA
AS A POTENTIAL
POLITICAL BLUNDER.
- WHICH ALSO REFLECTS JUST
HOW MANY PEOPLE THINK
THE VISIT IS IMMINENT.
- POINT BEING THE PUBLIC
IS TAKING AN INTEREST.
THIS IS DUKE STEARIED'S WAY OF
GOADING YOU INTO A TRAP.
- KNOWING WHAT WE DO,
THERE'S NO SENSE
IN TAKING THE RISK.
- Miran: I RESPECTFULLY
BEG TO DIFFER.
- Calne: YOU DON'T THINK
HE SHOULD GO?
COLONEL FROAUDE, PLEASE...
- A CLEVER STRATEGIST WOULD
SEE THIS LESS AN OBSTACLE
THAN AN OPPORTUNITY.
IF THE THREAT IS HANDLED
WITH A CERTAIN FINESSE,
THE TRAP CAN NOT ONLY BE AVOIDED
BUT SPRUNG INSTEAD ON THE VILE
TRAITORS WHO'VE DARED SET IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
THE BAIT FOR THAT LITTLE
TURNABOUT IS STILL HIS LIFE!
HE CAN'T JUST STROLL INTO
IMPERIAL NELPHA LIKE THAT!
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
THE CONSPIRATORS WANT HIM TO DO!
- THEIR PLOT WILL ONLY SUCCEED
IF HIS GRACE IS VULNERABLE.
- HE WOULD BE VULNERABLE,
SO FAR AWAY FROM HOME.
- NOT IF ON HIS JOURNEY
I AM ALLOWED TO ACCOMPANY HIM.
- Claugh:
WHAT GUARANTEE DO WE HAVE
THAT YOU'RE NOT AN ASSASSIN?
- IF I WERE, NO DOUBT
ELIMINATING ME
RIGHT HERE AND NOW
WOULD HIT THE ENEMY
WHERE IT WOULD HURT THEM MOST.
I ASSUME YOU'VE SUFFICIENT
COMMAND OF YOUR FACULTIES
TO DO SO, ADMIRAL KLOM?
- OH, BELIEVE ME, IF I THOUGHT
FOR EVEN A MOMENT
THAT YOU WERE TRULY A DANGER
TO HIS MAJESTY'S LIFE,
I WOULD KILL YOU ON THE SPOT.
- MY LIEGE,
WE AWAIT YOUR CHOICE.
- WITH LIEUTENANT FROUADE
I WILL PROCEED WITH
THE GOODWILL MISSION.
- Claugh: BUT...
- Royal Caller: HIS MAJESTY
THE HIGH KING OF ROLAND,
SION ASTAL.
- DOES ROLAND MEAN TO
INVADE US YET AGAIN?
- AS IT STANDS NOW,
NELPHA WOULD CRUMBLE EASILY
IF THEY CHOSE TO ATTACK.
- YOUR MAJESTY,
IT IS A PLEASURE
TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
I'VE BUT PALTRY WORDS TO HONOR
SO SWIFT AND
FRIENDLY A RECEPTION.
- UH, FORGIVE MY MANNERS,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
I AM GREAD NELPHI,
RULER OF THE NELPHAN EMPIRE.
INDEED, SIR, YOUR REPUTATION
AS A KING HAS TRAVELED
FAR ABROAD.
YOUR NAME IS SYNONYMOUS
WITH WISDOM.
IT IS TO BASK IN THAT
WISDOM THAT I HAVE TRAVELED
SO FAR FROM HOME.
- Gread: QUITE THE
QUICKSILVER TONGUE, I SEE.
- ON THE CONTRARY, I'VE AGONIZED
OVER THAT SPEECH FOR SOME TIME.
SUCH IS MY HOPE THAT
OUR COUNTRYMEN MAY BE BROTHERS.
- YOUR MAJESTY, I...
- ( laughter )
- IF IT ISN'T SION ASTAL!
WHAT A YOUNG SAPLING YOU ARE!
AND SPROUTING FROM SUCH
DESICCATED CLAY.
- STARNEL! HOW DARE YOU INSULT
OUR VISITOR!
- YOU WILL ADDRESS ME AS PRINCE,
LITTLE MAN!
- CEASE YOUR PRATTLING!
- EXCUSE MY LACK OF DECORUM.
I AM SION ASTAL, KING OF ROLAND.
- QUITE A MOUTHFUL
FOR THE STEWARD
OF A BACKWATER KINGDOM.
DON'T YOU TOUCH ME!
- YOUR MERE PRESENCE
IS AN INSULT! REMOVE YOURSELF!
- HMMM.
- YOUR MAJESTY,
I HUMBLY APOLOGIZE.
I FEAR MY SON IS
INCAPABLE OF DECENT SPEECH.
- PLEASE, DON'T APOLOGIZE.
FOR ALL YOUR SON'S ILL INTENT,
HE DOES SPEAK HONESTLY.
I AM A SAPLING.
AND ROLAND SCARCELY HAS
THE GRANDEUR OF ITS NEIGHBOR.
- WERE I TO REQUEST YOUR
ATTENDANCE AT A BANQUET HELD
IN YOUR HONOR
TOMORROW NIGHT, SIR,
WOULD YOU CONSIDER
STAYING TO DINE WITH ME?
- IT WOULD BE BESTIAL TO REFUSE.
- Fiole: HIS MAJESTY IS
BY FAR THE GREATEST PERSON
I'VE EVER KNOWN.
HE BELIEVES IN DEALING
WITH PEOPLE, EVEN COMMONERS,
AS EQUALS.
HE USES HIS POWER
TO PROTECT THE DOWNTRODDEN.
- YOU HAVE A WEAKNESS FOR
UNDELIVERED LETTERS,
IT WOULD SEEM, SIR.
- YES, WELL, THIS ONE
WON'T REMAIN SO FOR LONG.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THE EAGER HEIR?
PRINCE STARNEL, I MEAN.
AT THE END OF WHOSE STRING
DOES THE MAN DANGLE?
- THAT WILL BECOME
CLEAR PRESENTLY.
MY NETWORK
OF INFORMANTS IS VAST.
- AS IS THE ONE PULLING
THEIR STRINGS,
IS THAT WHAT YOU MEAN?
- I AM AN EXCELLENT MAN TO
HAVE AT HEEL, YOUR MAJESTY,
AS I'M CERTAIN WILL BECOME
PERFECTLY EVIDENT
BEFORE TOO LONG.
- AN ENCOURAGING THOUGHT TO
HAVE IN MIND.
SEE TO YOUR INFORMANTS, THEN.
- I'LL BE BACK SOON.
- YOU WOULD GO FORTH ALONE?
- I AM NOT THE SORT OF MAN
WHOM DEATH IS LIKELY
TO CATCH BY SURPRISE.
- UNDERSTOOD, SIR. I WILL TEND
TO YOUR SAFETY IN ABSENTIA.
- ( yawning )
( gasping )
- Sion: HELLO, OLD FRIEND,
I'VE MISSED YOU TERRIBLY.
I TRUST THE SEARCH GOES WELL?
- OKAY, CLEARLY I HAVEN'T HAD
ENOUGH SLEEP YET.
- ( groaning in pain )
- HUNGRY ENOUGH TO GNAW
AT THE WRITING DESK, ARE WE?
- YEAH, REAL FUNNY HOW
MY MOLARS JUST WOUND UP
EMBEDDED IN THIS THING!
- I HARDLY TOUCHED YOU. BESIDES,
YOU WERE STANDING IN MY WAY.
- YOU COULD'VE ASKED ME TO MOVE!
- WELL, THE TWO OF YOU
SEEM TO BE GETTING ALONG, HUH?
- Ryner and Ferris:
YOU'VE GOT A WARPED IDEA
OF "GETTING ALONG!"
- THIS VICIOUS HARPY'S BEEN
TREATING ME LIKE A WORN OUT
WEAPONS RACK SINCE...
( groaning in pain )
STOP IT.
- DEVELOP SOME CALLUSES
AND WE'LL DISCUSS IT.
I'D SAY SHE'S TREATING YOU
FAR MORE DELICATELY
THAN SHE EVER DID ME.
- ( groaning in pain )
THERE HAPPENS TO BE WORD
FOR PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
BUT, FOR FEAR OF MY LIFE,
I WON'T UTTER IT OUT LOUD.
- REFINED?
- UH, NO. NOT QUITE. THOUGH
"CRUEL" APPLIES TO TWO PEOPLE
IN THIS ROOM RIGHT NOW.
- THANKS FOR WAITING.
SO THEN, UH...
WHAT BRINGS RYNER'S COUSIN
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
- WAIT, WHO TOLD YOU
THIS GUYS' MY COUSIN?
HE ROLAND'S K...
- ( screaming in pain )
- DON'T TEASE THE MAN.
- HEY! WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- Sion: PLAY ALONG.
- OH YEAH! COUSIN, EXACTLY!
BY MARRIAGE.
WHO I REALLY CAN'T STAND.
WAKE ME UP WHEN IT'S TIME
FOR LUNCH, WILL YA?
- HE DOES LIKE TO
SPEND HIS TIME NAPPING.
- HA! LIKE TO, YES, IF SOMEONE
WOULD GIVE ME THE OPPORTUNITY!
- WOULD THIS "SOMEONE"
BE THE INNOCENT YOUNG GIRLS
YOU TRAIPSE ABOUT ON
THE PROWL FOR AT NIGHT?
- YOU'RE STILL UP TO THAT?
- SHUT UP!
- PLEASE DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT YOU'RE
QUITE AN AMUSING TRIO.
- All: TRIO?
- NOT TO PRY OR ANYTHING,
BUT YOU BELONG TO THE
ROYAL BLOODLINE, DON'T YOU?
- YOU MAKE IT SOUND
MORE GLAMOROUS THAN
IT ACTUALLY IS.
- BUT YOU'RE THE ELDEST SON
OF PRINCE STARNEL.
- ONE GENERATION AWAY
FROM THE THRONE.
- YES.
WHICH MORE THAN ANYTHING
JUST MAKES ME A BURDEN
TO MY FATHER.
- AND YET YOU HAVE A
CELEBRATED ACADEMIC RECORD.
IT'S EVEN SAID THE
IMPERIAL CABINET MEMBERS
SECRETLY CONSULT YOU
OVER YOUR FATHER'S HEAD
ON MATTERS OF STATE.
- I WEIGH IN OCCASIONALLY ON
BEHALF OF MY SIBLINGS PERHAPS.
BUT THAT'S ABOUT IT.
- ( gulping )
- YOU KNOW, IT'S A SHAME
HE'S SO MODEST.
HE'S NICER THAN THE
HACK LOUNGING AROUND
IN ROLAND'S PALACE.
- HUH?
- ( groaning in pain )
- IS THERE AN ACTUAL POINT TO
YOU BEING HERE OR DID YOU
JUST COME TO BADGER ME?
- IT IS RATHER FUN
WATCHING YOU OVERREACT.
- I NEED A BETTER REASON
THAN THAT!
- WELL, IF YOU INSIST.
- WONDERFUL.
- I AM IN NEED
OF YOUR ASSISTANCE, RYNER.
- ( gasping )
- Ryner: I'M EXHAUSTED.
AND FOR THE RECORD, THIS SUCKS.
REMIND ME WHY WE LET SION
TALK US INTO THIS FARCE?
- WELL, IT'S EITHER BE HIS
TEMPORARY BODY GUARDS
OR THE WYNNIT DANGO SHOP
WILL BE DECIMATED.
- SO, UH, I TAKE THAT TO MEAN
YOU'RE NOT WORRIED FOR HIM.
- DOES HE LOOK LIKE
HE'S IN DANGER?
- ( laughing )
- Ryner: NOT REALLY.
- Nelphan Guardsman:
THERE'S SOMEONE UP ON THE ROOF!
- UH-OH.
- ( chattering )
- ( footsteps )
- Miran: I AM OBLIGED
TO YOUR PATIENCE, HIGHNESS.
- YOUR REPORT.
- MAY I PRESENT COUNT WEARIUS,
FORMERLY A LINCHPIN
IN THIS AFFAIR.
- Sion: AND TO WHOM
DOES HE LEAD BACK?
- WHY TO PRINCE STARNEL,
NATURALLY.
THE ROOT OF THIS SORDID BUSINESS
WOULD APPEAR TO STEM FROM RUMORS
THAT TOALE NELPHI WILL
SOON BE NAMED
AS EMPEROR GREAD'S
SUCCESSOR.
- SO THE PRINCE ARRANGED
FOR HIS OWN FATHER TO BE
SUMMARILY REMOVED
BEFORE HIS SON'S GOOD FORTUNE
COULD BAR THE WAY TO POWER.
- YES. AND TO THIS END, HE HAS
BRAZENLY SOLICITED THE AID OF
ROLAND'S ILLUSTRIOUS NOBILITY.
- CAN I TRUST YOU NOT TO HAVE
SET THIS IN MOTION YOURSELF
SO AS TO CLEAR THE WAY TOWARD
MY CONQUERING MENORIS?
- IF I HAVE GONE TOO FAR
OR PRESUMED TOO MUCH,
A WORD FROM YOUR MAJESTY
WILL SUFFICE TO STAY ME.
- I MUST APPRISE THE EMPEROR
OF THIS SITUATION.
WE SHALL LET HIM DEAL WITH HIS
TRAITOROUS SON AS HE WILL.
- OF COURSE, MY LIEGE.
( scoffing )
- Miran: A NIGHT FOR
ETERNAL REST IF EVER
THERE WAS ONE, GENTLEMEN.
NOW THAT ALL THE
NELPHAN CONSPIRATORS HAVE BEEN
SERVED THEIR JUST DESSERTS,
BUT ONE TASK REMAINS.
- HEY, FERRIS.
- I SEE HIM.
- AH, AND HERE I THOUGHT
TO MOVE IN SILENCE.
YOU KEEP A VERY SHREWD WATCH,
IT WOULD SEEM, LORD NELPHI.
- HUH?
- MY INFORMATION MADE NO MENTION
OF YOUR HAVING EVEN
BASIC COMBAT SKILLS, HOWEVER.
I'M TAKEN A BIT OFF GUARD.
- AND WHO ARE YOU
TO SPY ON HIS LORDSHIP?
- EXCUSE MY TARDY DECORUM,
MIRAN FROUADE IS THE
NAME I'M MOST KNOWN BY.
- MIRAN FROUADE.
- I AM HERE BECAUSE,
TO ALL ACCOUNTS,
THE GOOD PEOPLE OF NELPHA
HAVE YOU IN MIND TO BE
THEIR NEXT RULER.
FOR WHICH, MY CONDOLENCES.
A WELL-LOVED KING AT THE
TILLER OF A PROSPEROUS NATION
DOES TEND TO POSE
A LITTLE BIT OF A PROBLEM
FOR ONE SUCH AS I.
LET THERE BE DARKNESS!
- CAN YOU TELL WHAT MAGIC
IS HE USING?
- Ryner: IT'S NOT MAGIC.
THE ALPHA STIGMA CAN'T MAKE OUT
WHAT THE HELL IT IS.
- DARKNESS SCOURGE!
- HEADS UP, FERRIS!
- GET ON WITH IT!
- DONE.
I OFFER UP A CONTRACT TO BEAR
THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS
WITHIN THE EARTH!
- HE'S BEEN TRAINED IN
ESTABULIAN MAGIC.
- I SEEK THE BURNING FIELD.
KURENAI!
- ROLANDIAN AS WELL?
DARKNESS, PROTECT!
I SEE... YOU'RE NOT
LORD NELPHI AT ALL, ARE YOU?
BUT YOU ARE HIS
WISELY CHOSEN SENTINEL.
AND THE FAIR ONE'S
SWORDSMANSHIP IS EXCELLENT.
I COMMEND YOU BOTH.
THAT HE WOULD TROUBLE TO
SURROUND HIMSELF WITH
THE LIKES OF BOTH OF YOU
IS RATHER REVEALING.
MY TIMING IS IMPECCABLE.
- ( groaning )
- Ryner: FERRIS!
- WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER.
IZUCHI!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( gasping )
- YOU SON OF A...
- SHE'S QUITE BEYOND HOPE,
I FEAR.
THE WEAK CAN ONLY
PROSTRATE THEMSELVES
BEFORE THE STRONG.
- YOU'RE CALLING FERRIS WEAK?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, PAL.
TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
SHE'S NOT THE SORT OF PERSON
TO PROSTRATE HERSELF
BEFORE ANYONE, LET ALONE SOME
CHEAP, SKULKING COWARD LIKE YOU.
IF SHE'S WEAK,
THEN I'M DOUBLY SO FOR
HAVING HER BOOT TO MY NECK!
- THEN YOU'LL BE LESS OF
A CHALLENGE THAN SHE WAS.
- I WOULDN'T BE
SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
- DO YOU SUPPOSE
YOU CAN VANQUISH ME?
- YEAH, WELL,
WE'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
THAT RING'S HOW YOU CONTROL
SHADOWS, ISN'T IT?
- THERE'S A GREAT DEAL
MORE TO YOU
THAN MEETS
THE EYE, BOY.
HOW DO YOU COME BY
SUCH KNOWLEDGE?
- I'M FAMILIAR WITH THE LEGENDS
OF GREAT EMPEROR KOKUEI,
THE SHADOW KING WHO ONCE
ENSHROUDED THE WORLD.
IT'S WRITTEN THAT HE BESTOWED
UPON HIS CHIEF SUBORDINATE
A VERY POWERFUL RING.
WITH IT, ONE HELD
SWAY OVER SHADOW.
THE RING'S BEARER USED IT TO
ASSASSINATE THE LEADERS
OF RIVAL NATIONS.
BUT A LEGENDARY HERO SEVERED
THE FINGER ON WHICH
THE RING WAS BORNE.
AND IF THE OLD STORIES
ARE TO BE TRUSTED,
THAT LEGENDARY HERO'S NAME
WAS HALFORD MIRAN.
"HE SWUNG ALOFT HIS MIGHTY SWORD
AND BLOODILY CUT OFF THE RING,
"REPELLING ITS POWER
IN ONE BLOW."
- Miran: CAN YOU DO THE SAME?
- MAYBE. AND, THEN AGAIN,
MAYBE I CAN'T. BUT FERRIS COULD.
- DO YOU THINK ALL THAT TIME
MIGHT'VE BEEN BETTER SPENT
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
THIS MAN'S WEAK SPOT?
- YOU THINK I'VE BEEN
TUTORING THE CREEP
ON HIS OWN MAGICAL RELIC
FOR THE PAST FIVE MINUTES?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO DISTRACT HIM
SO YOU COULD RUSH IN
UNEXPECTEDLY AND CHOP
THE STUPID THING OFF HIS FINGER!
- OH, UH, YES, OF COURSE.
SO I TAKE IT THE
RING HE'S WEARING
IS ONE OF OUR HERO RELICS?
- YES.
- THEN WHY ARE YOU
SLUMPED ON YOUR BACKSIDE
LIKE A WET RAG DOLL
WHEN THERE'S CLEARLY
SERIOUS WORK TO BE DONE HERE?
- HEY! YOU'RE THE ONE...
- SO SORRY, IT SEEMS
MY HAND SLIPPED AGAIN.
- YEAH, SURE...
YOU KNOW WHAT? I REALLY
DON'T EVEN CARE ANYMORE,
LET'S JUST CRUSH THIS GUY
TO A PULP ALREADY.
- ( laughing )
I DARE SAY YOU'RE
REALLY AN AMUSING PAIR.
SUCH A SHAME I HAVE TO KILL YOU.
ALAS, I CAN'T LET POTENTIAL
NUISANCES TO MY MASTER
SIMPLY ROAM FREE.
- YOUR MASTER?
- I SHALL LET LORD TOALE LIVE.
FOR THE MOMENT
HE IS FAR LESS OF A CONCERN.
EVIDENTLY I HAVE MUCH
LARGER ISSUES TO GRAPPLE WITH
IN DISPOSING OF YOU TWO.
BUT UNTIL THE MATTER CAN BE
DEALT WITH APPROPRIATELY,
I BID YOU BOTH A FOND FAREWELL.
- ( sighing )
IF HE HADN'T FALLEN
FOR OUR BLUFF
THINGS COULD'VE
GOTTEN SERIOUSLY UGLY.
LOOK AT YOU. I'LL STAY UP
AND KEEP WATCH SO YOU CAN SLEEP.
- IF YOU HAVE EVEN THE VAGUEST
IDEA OF TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF THIS SITUATION...
- WILL YOU STOP WITH THAT?
- THE MAN'S PAST IS LIKE
A STRONGBOX RUSTED SHUT.
I HAVEN'T FOUND A
SHRED OF INFORMATION
THAT GOES BACK FURTHER THAN
DUKE FROUADE ADOPTING HIM.
ALL THE OBVIOUS PEOPLE TO ASK
ARE DEAD.
AND NOW YOU TELL ME
HE'S MASSACRED
THE NELPHAN
CO-CONSPIRATORS
AGAINST YOUR LIFE.
- QUITE SO.
- HE'S DANGEROUS. GET RID
OF HIM WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
- ( knocking on door )
- MIRAN FROUADE, SIR.
I BRING ANOTHER REPORT OF THE
GOODWILL MISSION TO NELPHA.
- BRING IT FORTH.
- FORAGING THROUGH THE ARCHIVES
FOR USEFUL INFORMATION ABOUT ME?
- WE HAVEN'T UNCOVERED MUCH.
- ( laughing )
AND YET YOUR RESEARCH
IS SO THOROUGH.
DOES THE MYSTERY
DISTURB YOU, SIR?
WILL YOU DISMISS ME?
- AFTER YOUR ASTUTE HANDLING OF
OUR ENEMIES IN NELPHA,
IT WOULD BE FOOLISH OF ME
TO DO SO.
- YOU ARE A VERY STRANGE
BREED OF MAN.
- SO SAYS THE WALKING ENIGMA.
- TO BE COMPLETELY FORTHCOMING,
IN YOUR POSITION I WOULD NOT
HESITATE TO DISPOSE OF ME.
- A KING IS ONLY AS EFFECTIVE
AS THE PEOPLE HE SURROUNDS
HIMSELF WITH.
- OR INDEED THE CREDO
HE SUBSCRIBES TO.
MY LIEGE, I AM PROUD TO CALL
MYSELF YOUR MINION
AS LONG AS
IT MAY PLEASE YOU.
- Sion: YOU SPOKE OF
ANOTHER REPORT, I BELIEVE?
- WHILE TRAVELING
THROUGH NELPHA,
MY RECONNAISSANCE
HAPPENED TO BRING ME
TO A PRIVATE
RESIDENCE THERE.
TOALE NELPHI'S HOME.
- Sion: RYNER AND FERRIS
RISKED THEIR LIVES.
FROUADE ACTED ON MY ORDERS,
YES, BUT I DIDN'T INTENTIONALLY
PUT THEM IN HARM'S WAY.
I CANNOT BE HELD
MORALLY RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHERE A MISUNDERSTANDING
MAY LEAD MY SUBORDINATE.
- LET'S GO BEFORE HE NOTICES.
- WHY?
- COME ON.
- Ryner: IF WE STAY,
WHEN FROUADE COMES BACK FOR US
HE'LL PROBABLY KILL TOALE
IN THE BARGAIN, HUH?
- Ferris: RYNER.
- YEAH?
- I THINK MY BACK INJURY
IS ALL BUT FORGOTTEN
NOW THAT I'M ON MY FEET.
YOU'VE A RATHER IMPRESSIVE KNACK
FOR THE HEALING ARTS.
CRUDE THOUGH THEY ARE.
- IS THAT A "THANK YOU"?
WELL, UH... I'M HAPPY
YOU'RE ON THE MEND.
( yawning ) COME ON,
WE'RE BURNING DAYLIGHT.
- Milk: YOU'RE CERTAIN
HE WAS GORGEOUS?
AND THAT HIS
FLAXEN-HAIRED COMPANION
CONSTANTLY BEAT HIM?
YOU'VE BEEN A HUGE HELP!
HOLD TIGHT, RYNER MY LOVE!
I'M COMING FOR YOU!
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: AS IF LOOKING
FOR HERO RELICS
WASN'T A BIG ENOUGH PAIN,
THE CRAZIES ARE
ON OUR TRAIL AGAIN.
WHAT'S WITH "TABOO-BREAKING"?
AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS?
HOW ABOUT I JUST DROP
THE WHOLE THING AND GO HOME?
I'VE SAID IT BEFORE
AND I'LL SAY IT AGAIN.
THIS TOTALLY SUCKS!