( wind howling )
- ( explosions )
- ( clanking )
- HEY! WHAT THE HELL YOU JUST
STANDING AROUND FOR,
YOU LITTLE BRAT?
YOU THE SAD LITTLE ORPHAN BOY
OF ONE OF THESE HIGH
AND MIGHTY ROLAND SOLDIERS,
OR THE BOUGHT-AND-PAID FOR
PLEASURE CHILD
OF SOME ESTABULIAN FOP?
TELL ME YOUR NAME, KID!
- UH, IT'S RYNER LUTE.
- LOUDER NEXT TIME!
FOLKS CALL ME TALROM.
ACT LIKE A DEADWEIGHT AROUND
HERE, THIS IS WHAT YOU GET.
GOT IT, RYNER LUTE?
SHOW ME YOU UNDERSTAND
BY GETTIN' OFF YOUR ASS.
FROM NOW ON, WORK LIKE
YOUR LIFE DEPENDS ON IT.
BECAUSE IT DOES.
- ( theme song playing )
- IRIS JAW-BREAKER!
- HEY, COME ON!
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
STOP TRYING TO HIT ME
EVERY TIME I'M
WITHIN FIVE FEET?
- HANDS OFF, VILE THING!
I DON'T INTEND TO HAVE MY
VIRTUE FOREVER RUINED BY YOU!
- OH, RIGHT... FERRIS PUT
THE IDEA IN YOUR HEAD
THAT THE SLIGHTEST BRUSH
WITH YOURS TRULY
BURDENS A GIRL WITH CHILD...
RELAX OKAY, NOT EVERYTHING
SHE SAYS IS ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
( gasps )
- YET, YOU CLUTCH HER ARM
FOR NO REASON I CAN DISCERN.
- LOOK I'M NOT ABDUCTING,
IMPREGNATING
OR OTHERWISE CORRUPTING
YOUR PRECIOUS BABY SISTER
IN ANY WAY SHAPE OR FORM, OKAY?
YOU KNOW,
I THINK IT SPEAKS TO HOW FAR
WE'VE COME IN THIS RELATIONSHIP
THAT I'M ACTUALLY STARTING TO
FEEL YOUR EYES BORE A HOLE
IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD.
- BIG SISTER FERRIS!
- HOW LOVELY TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
SO THERE WAS NO
MISADVENTURE EN ROUTE?
- NOPE! I MISSED YOU,
SO I DIDN'T WASTE A
SINGLE MOMENT GETTING HERE.
I DO GOOD? TELL ME, I...
- YOU DID.
- HEY, EASY!
- OH, I'M SORRY.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
IRIS IS ALL WORKED UP,
SO I'M JUST COAXING
HER INTO A LITTLE NAP.
- THIS IS THE WAY YOU COAX HER?
- ( chuckles )
COME ON, MY BROTHER
DID THE SAME THING FOR ME
WHEN I WAS A CHILD,
NOW I DO IT FOR HER.
- HOW THE HELL'D YOU
SURVIVE BEING A KID?
- AH, EXCELLENT...
WYNNIT TEA HOUSE DANGO
WILL MAKE THIS A VERY
GOOD MORNING INDEED.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS. YOUR
LITTLE SISTER'S CRUMPLED IN
A HEAP ON THE FLOOR AND YOU'RE
CHOWING DOWN ON PREMIUM DANGO.
- IRIS HAS REACHED THEM
BY NOW, HOPEFULLY...
IF IT WASN'T TOO LATE.
- YOU'RE SO RIGHT!
THIS STUFF IS GOOD!
- SEE?
- YOU'VE BOTH BEEN HOARDING
OVER THAT DANGO LIKE MAD
ALL MORNING.
SURELY THAT'S NOT THE ONLY
REASON YOU CAME HERE, IRIS...
- HUH? WELL NO...
I MEAN... I THINK...
- OF COURSE!
I BROUGHT A LETTER!
- YOU MEAN FROM SION?
- YEAH, I CARRIED IT HERE ALL
THE WAY FROM THE PALACE...
HIS MAJESTY TOLD ME
TO DELIVER IT
AS SOON AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE,
IF NOT FASTER...
THERE WAS SOME REALLY IMPORTANT
INFORMATION IN IT, SO...
- WELL HERE, LET ME GET IT.
- IF YOU MUST.
- HUH. OKAY, THAT'S
A LITTLE BIT WEIRD.
IF I TUCKED IT AWAY
WHERE IT'D BE SAFE...
'CAUSE OF HOW
REALLY IMPORTANT IT WAS...
THEN WHERE'S THE STUPID THING
NOW? IT'S GOTTA BE IN HERE.
- I DON'T SUPPOSE
HE ACTUALLY TOLD YOU
WHAT THE LETTER WAS ABOUT?
- UM, WELL...
I THINK IT WAS SOMETHING ABOUT
A BIG DRAGON BEING ON THE LOOSE.
- IS THAT A FACT?
- OH, YES. OF COURSE.
THE WORTHLESS CREATURE
YOUR RELIC SET FREE.
SION MUST WANT US TO TRACK
DOWN ITS WHEREABOUTS
AND TRY TO REIGN IT IN.
- AW MAN, WHY US?
- THAT SOUNDS
ABOUT RIGHT, BUT...
I DON'T KNOW, I'M PRETTY SURE
THERE WAS SOMETHING ELSE
REALLY CRUCIAL MIXED IN THERE...
- DON'T WORRY, SIS.
WE'LL JUST FIGURE THINGS
OUT AS WE GO ALONG.
- UH, WE WILL?
YOU KNOW, THAT SUDDENLY
SOUNDS LIKE A WONDERFUL IDEA...
- ALRIGHT THEN.
GO BACK HOME AND TELL HIS
MAJESTY WE'LL DO AS HE ASKS.
- I'M ON THE JOB!
- ( yawning )
- Landlady: HMM. WHAT'S THIS?
"CONCERNING THE INCIDENT
LATELY REPORTED
"OF THE DRAGON THOUGHT
TO HAVE MATERIALIZED,
"CONJUNCTION WITH
THE RELIC UNEARTHED
IN THE FORESTS OF NELPHA..."
- Sion: WHILE NO FURTHER
SIGHTING OF THE CREATURE
HAS COME TO LIGHT,
AN ALARMING NUMBER OF PEASANTS
FROM THE AREA HAVE BEEN KILLED.
ABANDON ALL ENDEAVORS TO
RETRIEVE THE RELIC IMMEDIATELY.
YOU ARE TO STAY CLEAR OF
THOSE FORESTS AT ALL COSTS.
- AN IDEAL SPOT FOR TEA.
- NOW THAT I CAN GET BEHIND.
I MOVE THAT WE LEAVE OFF
THE INVESTIGATION ENTIRELY
UNTIL WE'VE HAD
SOME REFRESHMENT.
- COULD THE DRAGON
HAVE DONE THIS?
- Ferris: LET'S FIND OUT.
RYNER, NO BLOOD
HAS BEEN SPILLED.
- YEAH. OTHERWISE WE'D HAVE
PROBABLY BEEN ABLE TO SMELL
THIS PLACE LONG
BEFORE WE FOUND IT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THESE PEOPLE?
- DOWN THERE.
- HELLO! EXCUSE US...
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME...
- THERE'S SOMEONE COMING,
IT LOOKS LIKE THE MYSTERIOUS
MISSIONARIES FROM NELPHA.
- WELL, OUR PATHS
CROSS YET AGAIN.
WHAT A SERENDIPITOUS SURPRISE.
- WHAT ARE THE
TWO OF YOU DOING HERE?
- TRYING TO CATCH A GLIMPSE OF
THE RUMORED DRAGON, OF COURSE.
- SUCH A UNIQUE SIGHT WOULD
ASSUREDLY LIGHT MY
WRITER'S QUILL AFIRE.
I IMAGINE A YOUNG PRINCESS
WRITHING IN ITS
CLUTCHES. HELPLESS...
- DOUBTLESS A KNIGHT IN
SHINING ARMOR THEN RIDES TO
HER RESCUE ON A GREAT
WHITE STEED AND FELLS THE
INFERNAL BEAST WITH A
FLICK OF HIS SHINING BLADE.
CLICHES LIKE THAT
BAR YOUR WRITING
FROM THE POPULAR MARKET,
YOU KNOW!
SO, WHAT DO YOU TWO
THINK'S GOING ON HERE?
- HEY, YOUR GUESS
IS AS GOOD AS MINE.
IT'S WEIRD THERE BEING NO
TELLTALE SIGNS OF BLOOD, BUT...
FERRIS?
- PERHAPS YOU TWO HAVE
YOUR OWN THEORY
AS TO THE NATURE OF THIS BEAST?
- YOUR EYE IS AS SHARP
AS YOUR DRESS, MY LADY.
- DID YOU KILL THEM?
- WE WERE INTERESTED IN THE
HIDDEN RICHES IN THE FORTRESS
FOR MUCH THE SAME
REASON YOU WERE,
IF I'M NOT BEING TOO
VAGUE ON THE MATTER.
- SO YOU'RE OUT TO
FIND HERO RELICS AS WELL.
YOU'VE BEEN TAILING US
TO SAVE THE TROUBLE
OF HAVING TO LOCATE
THEM YOURSELVES.
- THAT ABOUT RIGHT?
- BRAVO.
WE CAN'T TAKE ALL THE CREDIT
FOR OUR SUCCESS, THOUGH,
THE TABOO BREAKER
SQUADRON HELPED IMMENSELY.
AS DID OF COURSE YOUR
INHERENT CLUMSINESS
IN LEAVING THIS
RELIC FOR US TO FIND.
WE WERE EXTREMELY LUCKY...
IT WAS, AS THE
OLD SAYING GOES,
A PERFECT STORM
OF CIRCUMSTANCES.
- YOU'RE A MURDERER...
- ( laughs )
- Ryner: YOU SLAUGHTERED
ANY POOR JERK
HAPLESS ENOUGH TO
HAVE SEEN THE DRAGON.
AND ALL JUST TO KEEP
A USELESS RELIC A SECRET.
- Sui: WELL, IT IS EASIER TO
HARNESS A RELIC'S POWER
WHEN YOU'RE NOT WRENCHING
IT FROM THE RABBLE,
WHICH, I'M SORRY TO SAY...
INCLUDES THE TWO OF YOU.
- IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO BE A THREAT?
- Ferris: WHAT'S YOUR GOAL?
EXACTLY WHO AND WHAT
ARE YOU TRYING TO
COLLECT THE RELICS FOR?
- BIT OF AN INVOLVED QUESTION
FOR SOMEONE ABOUT TO DIE.
YOU'RE TRYING TO BUY
TIME, AREN'T YOU?
- PERHAPS... I CAN HARDLY
BE BLAMED FOR IT.
FORTUNATELY, IT'S AN EASY ENOUGH
MATTER TO DEDUCE WHAT COUNTRY
YOU'RE AFFILIATED WITH.
- I OFFER UP A CONTRACT TO BEAR
THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS WITHIN THE EARTH!
- A SPELL TO INCREASE
YOUR INNATE PHYSICAL PROWESS?
I ADMIRE THE SWIFTNESS...
FROM THE WEST I DRAW THE
EMPTY, THE FORMATION, THE YANG!
- THE EMPTY, THE FORMATION,
THE YANG!
- AN ALPHA STIGMA!
I SUMMON FORTH THE BRILLIANCE!
HE JUMPED MY INVOCATION!
WATCH OUT!
- ( grunting )
- CRAP!
- IT'S NICE TO KNOW
MY LOOKS DISTRACT YOU
EVEN IN THE MIDST OF BATTLE.
BUT SURELY FOCUSING
ON OUR OPPONENTS
WOULD BE A BETTER TACTIC?
- WHAT THE HELL
IS YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU DO KNOW THESE
FREAKS WANT TO MURDER US.
- NO POINT SURRENDERING
OUR SENSE OF HUMOR.
- IS ALL OF THIS A JOKE TO YOU?
- NOT THE PART WHERE YOU
DEFLECTED THE AFTERSHOCKS
OF A HIT THAT WOULD'VE
OTHERWISE KILLED ME, NO.
- ( sighs )
RIGHT. SO LOOK OUT
FOR THE SCYTHE.
- THAT'S A RELIC TOO THEN,
I TAKE IT?
- YEAH. ONE THAT APPEARS
TO RAISE ITS USER'S
NATURAL ABILITIES BY A PRETTY
DAMN SIGNIFICANT MARGIN.
- AND...
- WELL, GUESS THAT EXPLAINS
WHY NONE OF THE BODIES
SHOWED ANY SIGNS OF TRAUMA.
AND WHERE THAT SUDDEN
WALL OF ICE EMERGED FROM.
- A SWORD WEIGHED DOWN WITH
ICE GETS TOO HEAVY TO USE...
THAT, AND AS THE
TEMPERATURE PLUMMETS,
IT'S HARDER TO STAY NIMBLE.
- ALRIGHT THEN...
I'LL CREATE AN OPENING
WITH A GOOD OLD FASHIONED
BOUT OF FIRE MAGIC AND YOU GET
THE SCYTHE OUT OF HER HANDS.
SOUND LIKE A PLAN?
- ONE I'M GLAD TO BE PART OF.
- FORMED AN ATTACK
STRATEGY HAVE WE?
- Ryner: YEAH.
YOU MIGHT SAY THAT.
- THEN THIS SHOULD BE FUN.
IN ALL SERIOUSNESS,
IT'D HARDLY BE WORTH GOUGING
THE ALPHA STIGMA OUT OF YOU
IF YOU DIDN'T STRUGGLE
A LITTLE BIT...
- WORRY NOT, I'LL CRYSTALLIZE
IT TO KEEP IT IN MINT CONDITION.
- CRYSTALLIZE?
- OF COURSE. THAT'S HOW AN
ALPHA STIGMA IS CONTAINED.
DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
- I WOULDN'T BOTHER
PLAYING DUMB IF I DID.
IS IT POSSIBLE THIS GUY
ACTUALLY KNOWS MORE
ABOUT MY ABILITIES THAN I DO?
- CAN ONE TRULY BE SO IN THE
DARK ABOUT HIS OWN POWERS?
I SUPPOSE IT'S TO BE
EXPECTED OF A MAGE
PRONE TO OVERLOOK
A RULE FRAGMENT.
- WHAT THE HELL DOES THAT MEAN?
- THERE IS SO MUCH
YOU DON'T KNOW...
HERE, LET ME BEGIN
BY ILLUSTRATING
HOW THE RELIC YOU
ABANDONED IS USED.
( grunting )
( exclaims )
( screaming )
- IS THAT REALLY HOW RELICS
ARE MEANT TO BE CATALYZED?
- THE DOLWELLY SWORDSCALE
INCINERATES A TARGET
AT THE WIELDER'S PLEASURE,
ACCORDING TO THEIR
STRENGTH OF WILL...
YOU SEE... THE GROUND DOESN'T
POSSESS ANY WILL OF ITS OWN...
SO PLUNGED ABSENT-MINDEDLY
INTO THE EARTH,
THE BLADE HAS NO
POWER TO DRAW UPON...
IN MY CASE, THOUGH,
IT HAS PLENTY.
WHICH ALLOWS ME
TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY
WHAT A HERO RELIC CAN DO.
YOU'RE EITHER VERY CALM
RIGHT NOW, OR EXTREMELY DAZED.
- WHAT I SEEK IS
THUNDER, IZUCHI!
- OH, PLEASE!
- DON'T TELL ME THAT'S
ANOTHER RELIC THAT HE'S USING!
- SO SORRY...
IN ADDITION TO THE AILECRONO
SCYTHE KUU SO DEFTLY WIELDS,
AND OF COURSE THE
DOLUELI SWORDSCALE,
WE HAVE THE ELEMIO COMB.
AND AS YOU HAVE JUST
WITNESSED, MY FRIENDS...
THE COMB NULLIFIES
VIRTUALLY ANY MAGIC SPELL
THAT IT ENCOUNTERS.
- FOR A GRAND TOTAL OF THREE.
- WE MUST RETREAT...
THE ODDS IN THIS FIGHT
ARE NOT IN OUR FAVOR.
- MOVE IT, RYNER!
- ALRIGHT FINE! RUN!
- RUN IF YOU MUST.
YOU WON'T GET FAR.
RESONATE!
- ( exclaims )
- COME ON!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU... HEY...
- Sui: WHY DELIGHT!
YOU WANT EVERYTHING TO
JUST CRUMBLE AND DISSAPEAR.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO HIM?
- DON'T BE CUTE.
I CAN'T VERY WELL STEAL
THE ALPHA STIGMA
WITHOUT FIRST ROUSING IT.
- ROUSING WHAT?
- YOU MEAN YOU REALLY
HAVE NO IDEA?
OF ALL TABOOS, THE ALPHA
STIGMA IS THE MOST HATED.
ONCE AWAKENED IT
KNOWS NO RESTRAINT.
IT ANNIHILATES.
INDISCRIMINATELY... HENCE ITS
BEARERS ARE MALIGNED AS DEMONS.
- ( gasping )
YOU KNOW IT DOESN'T MATTER.
( echoing ) NO. YOU'RE WRONG...
IT DOES...
- THEY'RE MONSTERS WHOSE VERY
EXISTENCE BREEDS DESTRUCTION!
- RYNER!
- ( Ryner exclaims )
IT'S ALL POINTLESS.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE, FERRIS!
RUN AS FAR AWAY AS YOU CAN!
AH! DON'T LOOK BACK!
I CAN'T...
- WHAT IS THIS?
- ( Ryner exclaiming in pain )
PLEASE! GET OUT OF HERE!
I CAN'T CONTROL MYSELF!
I'M A MONSTER!
I'LL KILL...
( gasps )
I'LL KILL YOU...
SO WHAT?
PEOPLE DIE EVERYDAY.
WHAT DIFFERENCE WILL ONE
MORE POSSIBLY MAKE?
( screaming ) SHUT UP!
JUST ACCEPT IT.
THE WORLD IS YOUR PLAYGROUND.
LET LOOSE.
HAVE A FEW LAUGHS.
( screaming )
( laughing maniacally )
- AND, THE FINAL TETHER
HAS SNAPPED...
THE ALPHA STIGMA IS AWAKE.
- WHAT HAVE YOU
VERMIN DONE TO RYNER?
- I'VE FREED HIM TO RAIN
DOWN CATASTROPHE LIKE A GOD...
WE'LL KILL HIM BEFORE
THINGS GET TOO ROCKY, THOUGH.
RECKLESS, YES. BUT THE ONLY
WAY TO BORE OUT A STIGMA.
- ( Ryner laughing maniacally )
- HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED ANYTHING?
I TOLD YOU... THE COMB
NULLIFIES YOUR STRENGTH...
THERE'S NO POINT IN
TRYING TO RESIST US.
- Ryner: ANALYZE EXISTENCE.
AND RELEASE. BE GONE, WORM.
- ( exclaims )
WHAT IN THE HELL?
( screaming )
BURN IT!
- OH MY...
- WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
YOU'RE NOT DYING ARE YOU?
- NO, I'M FINE.
WHAT ON EARTH IS HE...
AN ORDINARY ALPHA STIGMA BEARER
DOESN'T HAVE THIS KIND OF POWER!
- Ryner: YOU REALLY THINK
YOUR KIND OF MAGIC
IS GOING TO GET
THE BETTER OF ME?
- THE ELEMIO COMB MIGHT
AS WELL BE A CONJURER'S PROP.
- RYNER...
- LITTLE WORMS,
CRAWLING IN DIRT.
( laughing )
WRITHE IN A FLASH AND BE GONE!
LET ALL RETURN TO NOTHING!
- WE HAVE TO GET
OUT OF HERE, KUU.
WHATEVER HE IS, WE'RE TRUMPED.
- STOP, RYNER!
- RUN WHERE YOU WILL,
THE VOID AWAITS!
FIRST COMES DESTRUCTION.
I CREATE NOTHING. FORGIVE
NOTHING. SAVE NOTHING.
I JUST ERASE. COMPLETELY.
- DON'T YOU EVER GET LONELY
LIVING HERE ALL
BY YOURSELF, RYNER?
I KNOW I SURE WOULD.
- NOT REALLY, I MEAN
I'VE GOT ALL YOU GUYS.
- YOU KNOW, I COULD PRETEND TO
BE YOUR MOM FROM NOW ON,
IF YOU WANT...
JUST CALL FOR YOUR "MOTHER"
AND I'LL RUN RIGHT TO YOUR SIDE.
- HEY! I GET DIBS
ON BEING HIS DAD!
- EWW...
I'M NOT GONNA BE MARRIED
TO SOME ICKY BOY.
- I'VE BEEN DUMPED!
- ( all laughing )
- Man 1: RUN! HURRY!
- Man 2: GET OUT OF HERE! GO!
- FILTHY GHOULS, I WANT
EVERY SCRAP YOU'VE PILFERED
OFF THE BODIES OF
OUR FALLEN COMRADES!
- Talrom: WE MEAN NO DISRESPECT.
WE JUST DO THIS TO SURVIVE.
- ( screaming ) NO!
- NO PLEASE, SIR!
MY LITTLE GIRL'S INNOCENT...
( gasps )
- ( screaming ) MOM!
- GIVE QUILL BACK!
- WHAT I SEEK IS THE
BURNING FIELDS. KURENAI!
- ( screaming )
- THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU DEFY US.
- WRETCHED SCUM!
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU SAY!
- WHAT I SEEK IS THE
BURNING FIELD. KURENAI!
- ( screaming )
- WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
THAT KID! LOOK AT HIS EYES!
- IT'S ALRIGHT, QUILL...
- THAT'S THE ALPHA STIGMA!
RUN AWAY! JUST RUN AWAY!
- ( whimpering )
- QUILL?
- Quill: MONSTER...
- Man 1: AN ALPHA STIGMA.
- Man 2:
WHAT WAS TALROM THINKING?
WE CAN'T HAVE
A KID LIKE THIS HERE!
- Man 3: WE'VE BEEN TRICKED
INTO TAKING HIM IN...
- Man 4: A CREATURE
LIKE THAT'LL BRING US
NOTHING BUT TROUBLE...
- HE'S A MONSTER...
A REEKING, BLOODTHIRSTY BRUTE!
- YOU SHOULD BE PUT
DOWN LIKE A DOG!
- MONSTER?
THEY WE'RE RIGHT.
I AM A MONSTER.
I BRING ONLY DEATH.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: THIS SUCKS.
THERE'S NO POINT TO ANY OF IT.
YOU PEOPLE FINALLY GET
WHY THE ONLY THING
I EVER WANT TO DO
IS SLEEP ALL DAY?
DAMN IT... WHY CAN'T THE
WORLD JUST LEAVE ME ALONE?