- Ryner: MOM? DAD?
I CAN'T GO TO SLEEP BY MYSELF.
I'M TOO SCARED.
CAN YOU HEAR ME? I NEED YOU
TO READ ME ANOTHER STORY.
MOMMY, WHERE ARE YOU?
- I HAVE TO KILL HIM. THEN I'LL
FOLLOW HIM INTO THE DARKNESS.
- YOU ARE NOT THE ONE
TO DO IT, MY LOVE.
- WHO ELSE, THEN?
THIS IS MY FAULT.
COMMON WENCHES WHO FALL
IN LOVE WITH NOBLEMEN
PAY OUT THEIR
INDISCRETION IN BLOOD.
- IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
- LISTEN TO YOURSELF!
WHAT NEED HAVE WE TO WEIGH THE
WORLD'S SCORN? THIS IS LOVE.
PLEASE. GIVE ME THE BLADE.
- THE WORLD WILL HEAP MORE
THAN SCORN UPON US
FOR BRINGING AN ALPHA
STIGMA INTO IT.
HE'LL LOSE HIMSELF ONE DAY.
I KNOW HE WILL.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS...
( crying )
- I'M SORRY, CHILD. WE
DIDN'T MEAN TO WAKE YOU. COME.
OUR SON WILL LIVE.
AS WILL YOU, MY LOVE.
I'LL SHIELD YOU BOTH FROM
HARM, COME WHAT MAY.
WE ARE A FAMILY,
AND A FAMILY WE WILL REMAIN.
- MOM? DAD?
- Alpha Stigma:
ANALYZE EXISTENCE.
SHATTER.
ERASE.
DESTROY
- NO! NOT AGAIN!
SOMEONE MAKE IT STOP!
- Alpha Stigma: DESTROY.
- I'M SCARED!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
HELP ME, PLEASE!
- ( evil laughter )
- MOM? DAD?
YOU HEARD ME.
MOM?
- Sion: RYNER.
- OH MAN. HEY YOU GUYS.
AM I GLAD TO SEE YOU HERE.
- NO, NOT AGAIN.
DAMN IT, I HATE THIS!
( groaning in pain )
( gasping )
YEAH. AWESOME.
THANKS FOR THAT.
GREAT WAY TO START THE DAY.
JUST WHEN I THINK MY DREAMS
CAN'T BE ANY MORE SCREWED UP.
I START DREAMING THAT
MY PARENTS WANTED ME.
- Lucile: COME NOW.
I'M ONLY BEING CAUTIOUS.
YOU'VE A TALENT FOR
IMPROBABLE DREAMS, AFTER ALL.
DREAMS FOR A WORLD
WITHOUT WAR?
WHAT BASTION CAN YOU HOPE
TO ERECT AGAINST BLOODSHED,
WITH YOUR HANDS DYED IN
THE BLOOD OF INNOCENTS?
SUCH HANDS ARE USEFUL
FOR ONE THING ONLY.
- "IF THE ALPHA STIGMA BEARER
RYNER LUTE LOSES CONTROL,
"OR SHOWS SIGNS OF LOSING
CONTROL, OR BEHAVES IN A MANNER
CONSISTENT WITH AN ACT
OF TREASON AGAINST ROLAND
WHILE TRAVELING ABROAD,
HE IS TO BE EXECUTED."
CAN'T ACT LIKE I'M SURPRISED.
MUCH AS I'D LIKE TO DO RIGHT
BY SION AND FERRIS, I CAN'T
DO IT STANDING BESIDE THEM.
AND HONESTLY, I'VE KNOWN
THAT FROM THE START.
- ( theme song playing )
- YOUR MAJESTY! I BRING NEWS.
FIELD MARSHAL KLOM HAS BEEN
DEFEATED BY THE ALPHA STIGMA!
- DEFEATED?
DON'T TELL ME HE'S...
- HE'S ALIVE, SIR. BUT
ACCORDING TO MY SOURCES,
HE'S SERIOUSLY HURT.
- WHERE IS HE CONVALESCING?
- PREPARE AN ESCORT AT ONCE.
- Soldiers: YES SIR.
- YOUR MAJESTY.
- ( panting )
MY APOLOGIES FOR BEING LATE,
MAJOR GENERAL CALNE.
I ASSUME THE MESSAGE
I RECEIVED CAME FROM YOU?
- IF YOU'RE CORPORAL LEAR
LINKAL, THE ANSWER IS YES.
- SIR.
- I'M ESLINA FOLCALT, THE MAJOR
GENERAL'S PERSONAL SECRETARY.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
- IF I'M NOT STEPPING
OUT OF LINE, SIR,
I'D VERY MUCH LIKE TO
ASK YOU A QUESTION.
- BY ALL MEANS, ASK.
- SERGEANT LUKE STOCK-KART
AND JUNIOR GRADE
LIEUTENANT MILK CALLAUD
OF ROLAND'S TABOO
BREAKER SQUADRON
HAVE BOTH BEEN MISSING
SINCE YESTERDAY.
THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF THEIR
DISAPPEARANCE SUGGEST
THE INVOLVEMENT OF
SOMEONE PRETTY HIGH UP
AND I WAS HOPING YOU
COULD SHED SOME LIGHT
ON THE SITUATION FOR US.
- NO. I'M AFRAID THIS IS THE
FIRST INKLING I'VE HEARD OF IT.
BUT ON THAT NOTE,
STRANGE DISAPPEARANCES DO SEEM
TO BE ALL THE RAGE THESE DAYS.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, RYNER LUTE,
THE ONE YOU LOT WERE PURSUING
HAS GONE MISSING AS WELL.
MY WHOLE POINT IN
ARRANGING THIS MEETING
WAS IN THE HOPE THAT YOU'D
BE ABLE TO SHED SOME LIGHT
ON THAT FOR ME.
- THERE HAVE BEEN SEVERAL
CONFIRMED SIGHTINGS
OF HIM EN ROUTE
TO THE FORMER ESTABULIAN
TERRITORIES ON HIS OWN.
- NOT A BAD START. AT THIS POINT
I WELCOME ANYTHING WE CAN USE
TO TIGHTEN THE NET A BIT.
MY SINCERE THANKS, CORPORAL.
- ESLINA, PLEASE INFORM
LADY FERRIS THAT WE HAVE A LEAD.
- RIGHT.
- NOT TO SOUND OMINOUS,
BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME
THEIR DISAPPEARANCES AREN'T
JUST COINCIDENTAL.
THE SOONER WE CAN GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THIS, THE BETTER.
- BIG SISTER FERRIS!
I BROUGHT YOU A SURPRISE,
EVEN THOUGH I'M PRETTY
SURE YOU CAN GUESS
WHAT IT IS FROM THE SMELL!
FRESH FROM THE
WYNITT DANGO SHOP,
IT'S THEIR CRAZY-AWESOME SUPER
ECONOMY FUN-SIZE DANGO SET!
ALSO, EVERYONE'S BEEN
SEARCHING THE KINGDOM
FOR ANY ROCK THE STUPID WILD
BEAST MIGHT BE HIDING UNDER.
SO ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
SIT BACK AND BE PATIENT
AND THE GRUNTS WILL
SMOKE HIM OUT FOR US!
- I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
- WHY DON'T I GO MAKE US
A NICE CUP OF TEA?
- STRANGE.
MY INSIDES FEEL CLENCHED
FOR SOME REASON.
IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU NEED FROM ME, LUCILE?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
- ALL YOUR LIFE.
AND IF FATE SMILES ON US SO
SHALL I ALWAYS BE.
YOU NEED NEVER ASK
HOW LONG I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU.
- I HAVE TO KNOW.
- YES?
- WHAT EXACTLY DID YOU
SAY TO RYNER?
- I MERELY GRILLED INTO HIM WHAT
GRAVE FOLLY IT WOULD BE
TO MAKE A PASS AT
MY BELOVED SISTER
A NEW EXPRESSION
FOR YOU, I SEE,
TRYING OUT YET ANOTHER EMOTION
FROM YOUR QUICKLY
EXPANDING REPERTOIRE?
MY HEART SOARS AS IT ACHES
AT THE SIGHT OF YOU GROWING UP.
ONE DAY YOU WILL SET OUT AGAIN
INTO THE WORLD AS A WOMAN.
HOW LONELY IT MAKES ME FEEL
TO THINK OF YOU OUT THERE
BEYOND THE REACH OF MY ARM.
- DON'T SAY THAT.
- WE HAVE A GUEST.
- GOOD NEWS, MISS FERRIS!
WE THINK WE KNOW WHERE
RYNER'S TAKEN OFF TO!
- AND JUST WHERE EXACTLY
MIGHT THAT BE?
- A WORTHY SOURCE
POINTS TO ESTABUL.
- ( chuckles ) RYNER, YOU CAN'T
BEGIN TO CONCEIVE OF THE HAVOC
I'M ABOUT TO RAIN DOWN
UPON YOUR HEAD
FOR HAVING DARED BREAK
A PROMISE TO ME!
- ( people chattering )
- I JUST DON'T GET HOW SOMEONE
LIKE HIM COULD'VE BEEN BEAT.
WHAT ARE OUR CHANCES OF REIGNING
IN THAT MONSTER IF KLOM CAN'T?
- ( Noa crying )
- ENOUGH WITH THE HYSTERICS
ALREADY, NOA.
I'M WOUNDED, NOT DEAD.
- I'M AWARE OF THAT.
IF YOU WERE DEAD YOU'D HAVE
MY WRATH TO CONTEND WITH!
- WE'RE EXTREMELY LUCKY
NOT TO HAVE LOST YOU.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT WAS HIM.
BUT THERE'S NO DOUBT,
HE'S THE SON OF A BITCH
WHO SINGLE-HANDEDLY WIPED OUT
MY OLD BATTALION.
- I ASSUME YOU MEAN
THE ALPHA STIGMA.
- YES. AND HE WON THIS ROUND.
BUT MARK MY WORDS,
BY THIS TIME NEXT WEEK...
( grunting )
- I'M HERE FOR YOU, CLAUGH.
TRY NOT TO GET TOO WORKED UP.
- YOUR MAJESTY.
- LET'S GO.
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, SIR,
IF FIELD MARSHAL KLOM HAS
FALLEN TO THE BEAST,
WHAT HOPE TO WE
HAVE FOR SUCCESS?
THE TROOPS ARE ASTIR WITH DOUBT.
- ( soldiers murmuring )
- HEAR ME, MEN!
REGARDLESS OF THE THREAT,
WE WILL NOT SHRINK FROM DUTY!
YOUR KING RIDES WITH YOU.
THE MURDEROUS CREATURE
WILL BE BROUGHT TO HEEL!
WE RIDE TO VICTORY!
- YOUR MAJESTY...
- LONG LIVE THE HERO
KING OF ROLAND!
- ( soldiers cheering )
- I KNOW WHERE YOU'RE
COMING FROM.
DAMN TARIFFS HAD MY FATHER
UP TO HIS EYEBALLS IN DEBT
TO THE TAX COLLECTORS.
- OKAY. SO NOW WHAT?
- ARE YOU ON A JOURNEY?
- SORT OF, I GUESS.
- WELL GOOD FOR YOU.
OUR NECK OF THE WOODS BOASTS
A HOARD OF HOT SPRINGS
AND FIRST-RATE CHOW.
- OH, YEAH?
- A LOT OF ADORABLE
BOUTIQUES HAVE OPENED UP
AROUND HERE LATELY, TOO.
THANKS OF COURSE TO HIS
ILLUSTRIOUS MAJESTY SION ASTAL.
BELIEVE ME, YOUNG MAN,
THIS REGION WAS A NIGHTMARE
FOR TRAVELERS LIKE YOU
BEFORE HE CAME.
AH, THE THINGS THAT GREAT MAN
HAS DONE FOR US HERE!
BLESS MY SOUL YOU
HAVEN'T TOUCHED
A SPOON FULL OF YOUR STEW.
WE CAN'T HAVE THAT,
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO GO WITHOUT.
I'LL GO WARM IT UP
IN THE KITCHEN.
THAT SHOULD KICK START
A GROWING BOY'S APPETITE!
- ( people murmuring )
- THE THINGS HE'S DONE
FOR YOU, HUH?
- ( loud thud )
- OH CRAP.
- I HOPE YOU'VE GOTTEN RUNNING
OUT OF YOUR SYSTEM.
BECAUSE I AM ABOUT TO
CHOP OFF YOUR LEGS!
- PLEASE FERRIS, NO! THIS
ISN'T THE PLACE. COME ON...
- I'M NOT INTERESTED IN TALK!
- OKAY SURELY I'M NOT WORTH
WRECKING A WHOLE BUILDING OVER!
- WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
LEAVE TOGETHER!
I HAD FOURTEEN, FOURTEEN PACKS
OF DANGO READY FOR THE TRIP!
- YEAH! AND YOU EXPECTED ME TO
CARRY THEM ALL BY MYSELF
LIKE A PACK MULE!
- I'D HAVE BEEN HAPPY TO
CARRY ONE OR TWO MYSELF!
- THIS IS OFFICIALLY NOT
FUNNY ANYMORE.
- YOU'VE GOTTEN SOFT.
YOUR REFLEXES ARE SLUGGISH.
GOODBYE, RYNER LUTE!
- OH, OKAY, I GET IT.
YOU'VE BEEN ORDERED TO KILL ME.
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO SMASH THIS
PLACE TO PIECES JUST TO GET ME.
I SURE HOPE YOU GUYS CAN
COVER THE DAMAGE.
- AS IF I CARE A WHIT
FOR THIS PLACE.
DON'T EVADE.
ANSWER ME. WHAT IN THE WORLD
DO YOU MEAN BY SAYING
I MUST'VE BEEN ORDERED
TO KILL YOU?
SO HELP ME, IF I HAVE TO
ASK A THIRD TIME
I SWEAR I WILL CLEAVE YOUR HEAD
FROM YOUR SHOULDERS!
- IT... IT WAS NOTHING.
JUST STALLING FOR TIME.
- GIVE ME A BREAK. DO I LOOK
LIKE I WAS BORN YESTERDAY?
- LOOK, I MADE A MISTAKE. I KNOW
YOU TOO WELL, AND YOU COULDN'T.
- WHAT DID MY BROTHER
SAY TO YOU?
- NOTHING.
- I'M IN NO MOOD FOR THIS.
- JEEZ, GET A GRIP, ALL RIGHT?
HE DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
- APART FROM THREATENING YOU
NOT TO MAKE A PLAY
FOR HIS SWEET BELOVED
SISTER, YOU MEAN.
- HEY, HE WAS JUST DOING HIS
JOB AS YOUR BIG BROTHER.
- IS HE THE REASON
YOU DECIDED TO TEAR OFF
WITHOUT ENLIGHTENING ME?
- NOT EXACTLY, NO.
- MEANING THAT YOU, WHO STALKS
ABOUT IN THE DEAD OF NIGHT
THROWING HIMSELF AT INNOCENT
WOMEN AND CHILDREN,
WHO RESPONDS TO SUCH PLEAS AS
"I BEG YOU, NO! NOT MY
DAUGHTER'S BLESSED VIRTUE,"
FROM PANIC-STRICKEN
PARENTS EVERYWHERE
WITH A GLEEFULLY CALLOUS...
( laughs ) "I AM RYNER LUTE, THE
GRAND POTENTATE OF PERVERSITY!
"THE SOVEREIGN OF SALACIOUSNESS!
ALL VIRTUE LAYS PROSTRATE
BEFORE ME!"
YOU, WHO DOES TEN THINGS
TO PUSH THE LIMITS
OF HUMAN DECENCY
BEFORE BREAKFAST,
SUDDENLY BUCKLED AT THE PROSPECT
OF BEING KEPT TABS ON
BY A PROTECTIVE OLDER BROTHER.
AND SCUTTLED AWAY
LIKE A FRIGHTENED CAT.
WHAT KIND OF SELF-RESPECTING
PREDATOR ARE YOU?
- WHAT WORLD DO YOU LIVE IN?
- ( woman screaming )
- THERE YOU ARE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW LONG I'VE WAITED FOR THIS.
- WHAT IN THE HELL?
- THUS FAR, EVERYTHING
LAFRA'S TOLD ME
HAS BEEN RIGHT ON THE MARK.
WHICH MEANS THAT ONE OF YOU
IS WHO I'M LOOKING FOR.
- ( grunting )
- WITH MOVES LIKE THAT
IT'LL BE NO MEAN TRICK
FIGURING OUT WHICH OF YOU IT IS.
- YOU'VE GOT SOME PRETTY INHUMAN
MOVES GOING ON THERE YOURSELF,
HOT SHOT.
- WELL THAT MAKES SENSE,
SEEING AS I'M NOT HUMAN.
- WHAT?
- WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER.
IZUICHI!
- MY, THIS LOOKS TASTY.
YOU DON'T MIND IF
I HELP MYSELF.
THIS IS PHENOMENAL!
- ( groaning )
- ( choking )
- SO YOU'RE THE ALPHA STIGMA.
- WHO IN THE HELL ARE YOU.
- THE NAME IS TIIR RUMIBUL,
A BEARER OF IINO DOUE.
A MAGIC EYE.
AND YOU'RE THE REASON I'M HERE.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- A FRIEND OF MINE SAW
YOU IN A DREAM
AND FELT COMPELLED TO TELL ME.
HE SAID YOUR WOUNDED
HEART WAS CRYING OUT,
THAT PEOPLE HAD HURT YOU.
AND SPEAKING OF BEING
HURT BY PEOPLE...
- DAMN. WHO DO THESE FOOLS
THINK THEY ARE?
- COME ON!
- HOLD YOUR FIRE!
- SION?
- QUICKLY YOU TWO, GET
OUT OF THE WAY!
- YOU HEARD THE MAN.
HE'S LEADING THE CHARGE?
- ALL TROOPS ASSUME
CASTING FORMATION!
WE LEAVE NOTHING TO CHANCE!
- NO SPELLS. JUST STICK TO
ARROWS FOR THE TIME BEING.
- YOU'RE ALL DEAD.
- TAKE HIM DOWN!
- ( groaning )
- NOW YOU'VE DONE IT.
- ( soldiers screaming )
- NO! SOMEBODY HELP ME!
- ( screaming )
- ORDINARY ARROWS NOT
IMBUED WITH MAGIC.
WISE CHOICE, I'M IMPRESSED.
WITHOUT NOURISHMENT I MIGHT
ACTUALLY HAVE FALLEN TO YOU LOT.
- HE DOESN'T JUST ABSORB MAGIC.
HE DEVOURS THE ESSENCE
OF LIVING HUMAN BEINGS.
HIS WOUNDS HEAL WHEN
HE CONSUMES.
- VERY NICE.
THE GRAY MATTER LOCKED IN YOUR
SKULL LOOKS SCRUMPTIOUS.
- READY ARROWS.
I'LL ASK YOU ONLY ONCE.
DO YOU HAVE AN INCLINATION
TO SURRENDER?
- NOT REALLY, NO.
- BE WISE. YOUR ONLY
OPTION IS DEATH.
- THAT SO? AND WHAT IF I JUST
HAPPEN TO BE QUICK ENOUGH
TO EAT YOU BEFORE
THE ARROWS TOUCH ME?
- A CLEVER RUSE.
BUT IF YOU COULD EAT ME
YOU'D HAVE DONE SO BY NOW.
- NOT IF I DIDN'T FEEL KEEN ON
ROUSING THE FURY OF YOUR LAPDOG.
WOULDN'T WANT TO TANGLE WITH
ANOTHER ALPHA STIGMA.
- HIS LAPDOG?
- DON'T TELL ME RYNER LUTE
IS AN ALPHA STIGMA?
- OH, NO.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
- YOU MEAN WE'RE CAUGHT
BETWEEN TWO OF THEM?
- RUN AWAY!
JUST RUN AWAY!
- HE'S A MONSTER.
A REEKING, BLOODTHIRSTY BRUTE!
- HE SHOULD BE PUT DOWN
LIKE A DOG!
- QUIET, ALL OF YOU!
I WON'T HAVE THIS!
- DON'T SAY YOU'RE SURPRISED.
IT'S THE WAY OF HUMANS.
WE'LL NEVER BE A PART
OF THE FOLD
AS FAR AS THEY'RE CONCERNED.
DEEP DOWN YOU'VE ALWAYS KNOWN.
- ENOUGH OF YOUR LIES.
HOW DARE YOU PRESUME
TO SPEAK TO MY FRIEND LIKE
YOU WERE EQUALS.
RYNER IS NOTHING LIKE YOU!
- WE'RE NOT ALL THAT
DIFFERENT, ARE WE?
OR MAYBE YOU MEAN TO SUGGEST I'M
NOTHING LIKE YOUR FRIEND THERE.
BECAUSE I'M A MONSTER?
YOU MIND IF I CALL YOU RYNER?
SO RYNER, WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE DITCH THESE BRUTES?
SOMETHING TELLS ME THIS PLACE
ISN'T A GOOD FIT FOR YOU.
- COME ON, RYNER, THERE'S
NO POINT LISTENING TO HIM.
HE'S FILLING YOUR
HEAD WITH TRIPE.
- FOREVER SCORNED AS A MONSTER,
HUNTED DOWN AS TABOO.
WHAT'S THE POINT OF GIVING
ANOTHER MOMENT OF YOUR TIME
TO A LIFE LIKE THAT?
DON'T YOU THINK THERE'S A
HIGHER CALLING FOR YOU?
LEAVE THIS PLACE AND
COME WITH ME.
I HAVE MORE FRIENDS THAN
YOU'VE EVER DREAMED OF KNOWING.
FIRE MAGIC DANCES IN
MY EYES LIKE LIGHTNING.
IF YOU JOIN ME, THE
TWO OF US CAN ESCAPE
AND I CAN FULLY RECOVER.
WE CAN BE FREE OF HUMANITY'S
BIGOTRY AND OPPRESSION FOREVER!
- THIS IS ABSOLUTE ROT.
FIRE ON MY SIGNAL!
- YOU WON'T WIN
THE DAY LIKE THAT.
A HYPOCRITE LIKE YOU COULD NEVER
HOPE TO APPRECIATE THE BETRAYAL
THAT DWELLS IN THE
HEARTS OF OUR KIND.
RYNER UNDERSTANDS.
DON'T YOU, RYNER?
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT. I DON'T
BLAME EITHER ONE OF YOU.
I'D FEEL THE SAME WAY
IF I WAS IN YOUR SHOES.
- I DIDN'T SCOUR THE
COUNTRYSIDE LOOKING FOR YOU
TO HEAR THIS KIND OF CRAP!
- PLEASE UNDERSTAND, GUYS.
IT'S NOT LIKE I HOLD
ANYTHING AGAINST YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT I'VE CAUSED
ENOUGH TROUBLE FOR BOTH OF YOU
AND YOU DESERVE A BREAK FROM
HAVING TO DEAL WITH ME.
- RYNER, PLEASE.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I GET WHY YOU GAVE LUKE
STOKKART THE ORDER TO KILL ME
IF I EVER GOT OUT OF HAND.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO EXPLAIN.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT
WHEN YOU'D THOUGHT
I'D BEEN SENT TO KILL YOU?
- ( laughing )
- LISTEN TO ME!
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK!
- YOU'VE GOT A WHOLE
KINGDOM TO WORRY ABOUT.
I CAN IMAGINE WHAT KIND OF
BURDEN THAT MUST BE.
YOU AREN'T IN THE WRONG FOR
WANTING TO PROTECT IT FROM ME.
- RYNER...
- DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE I'M SOME
KIND OF WOUNDED ANIMAL, SION.
THE BLAME'S ALL ON MY HEAD.
WE BOTH KNOW ALL I'M GOOD FOR IS
SPREADING DEATH AND DESTRUCTION.
- DAMN YOU! THAT IS NOT
WHAT YOU ARE!
- YOU'VE SUFFERED ENOUGH
WORRYING ABOUT ME.
SO AS OF THIS MOMENT I AM
NO LONGER YOUR PROBLEM.
- Ferris: DON'T DO THIS.
- SORRY, FERRIS. WHAT I SEEK
IS THUNDER...
- I WON'T LET YOU DO THIS!
ALL TROOPS FIRE ARROWS, NOW!
DON'T SUFFER THE MONSTER TO
LIVE A SECOND MORE!
- DO IT.
- IZUCHI.
- FOLLOW ME AND I'LL INTRODUCE
YOU TO YOUR NEW FRIENDS.
- DON'T GO.
DON'T GO!
- THE MENACE HAS FLED!
VICTORY BELONGS TO US!
- ( cheering )
- THREE CHEERS FOR SION ASTAL!
- THREE CHEERS FOR THE
HERO KING OF ROLAND!
- THE "HERO KING."
- I'M SORRY, FERRIS.
- RYNER WAS RIGHT.
YOU'RE BLAMELESS IN ALL THIS.
YOU'RE MERELY FULFILLING YOUR
DUTIES AS A RULER, NOTHING MORE.
- HIS MAJESTY TRIUMPHED
OVER THE MONSTER
AGAINST INSURMOUNTABLE ODDS!
- ONCE AGAIN THE
PEOPLE ARE SAFE!
- NOT HAVING SECOND
THOUGHTS, ARE YOU?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
I NEVER MUCH CARED FOR
THEIR COUNTRY ANYWAY.
- ( theme song playing )
- I ASSUME YOUR LADYSHIP
IS SALLYING FORTH
IN SEARCH OF THE ULTIMATE DANGO?
- NO.
MY GOAL THIS TIME
ISN'T WHAT I EXPECTED.
BUT THEN FOOLS NEVER ARE.
- OKAY, LET ME BE PERFECTLY
CLEAR, I FRIGGIN' LOATHE KIDS.
THEY'RE LOUD,
OBNOXIOUS, DEMANDING,
IMPOSSIBLE TO REASON WITH...
AND COMMUNAL LIVING?
FEWER THINGS SUCK MORE.
WHAT THE HELL'S WRONG
WITH YOU PEOPLE? LAY OFF!
NOBODY SAID I WAS
YOUR DAMN FRIEND!