- Sion: THE RUNA EMPIRE'S
JOINED WITH GASTARK?
IMPOSSIBLE. IS THIS CONFIRMED?
- Miran: MY LORD, AS OF NOW
THERE'S BEEN NO OFFICIAL
PROCLAMATION FROM EITHER PARTY.
HOWEVER, WE KNOW RUNA
DID WORK WITH DUKE STEARIED
TO ORCHESTRATE
YOUR ASSASSINATION.
THIS FACT MUSN'T BE
IGNORED, YOUR GRACE.
- ( sighs )
WHAT THEN?
DOES THE KING INTEND
TO CARRY ON THE FACADE
OF BEING THIS NATION'S
FRIEND OR WILL HE ATTACK?
- I KNOW NOT.
I WAS UNABLE TO MEET
WITH THE KING, YOUR MAJESTY.
HE'S SHUT HIMSELF INSIDE A
CASTLE WITHIN RUNA'S BORDERS,
COERCED BY THE MESSENGERS
FROM GASTARK INTO SECLUSION.
- A THREAT SO GRAVE,
IT MADE THE KING YIELD?
HOW MANY WERE KILLED?
APPARENTLY, THE ENTIRE GARRISON
IS PROTECTING THE CASTLE.
- ( sighs )
- THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
YOU SHOULD KNOW, YOUR MAJESTY.
ACCORDING TO THE
INFORMATION I'VE GATHERED,
RUMORS ARE CIRCULATING THAT
GASTARK USED A PECULIAR
POTENT FORM OF UNKNOWN MAGIC
IN ITS FIGHT AGAINST STOHL.
- UNKNOWN MAGIC?
- YES, IT SEEMS SO, HIGHNESS.
APPARENTLY, IT WAS USED TO
COUNTERACT AN OFFENSIVE SPELL
FROM STOHL'S CAMP.
IT NEGATED THEIR MAGIC AND
KILLED MANY THOUSANDS, MY LORD.
- ( gasps )
- I MUST ADMIT, I FIND THIS
HARD TO BELIEVE. HOWEVER,
IF THESE REPORTS ARE TRUE,
IT WOULD LEND SIGNIFICANT
CREDENCE TO THE RUMOR
THAT THE RUNA EMPIRE
WAS FORCED TO CAPITULATE
TO GASTARK'S FORCES.
- DOES THIS MEAN GASTARK
HAS BEGUN TO USE THEM?
HERO RELICS.
NO, WE CAN'T LET IT
DEGENERATE TO THE POINT
AT WHICH EVERY NATION
IS FIGHTING AND COMPETING WITH
EACH OTHER TO GATHER RELICS.
WE MUST NOT LET IT COME TO THAT.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( water rippling )
- Ryner: HEY.
- Ferris: WHAT IS IT?
- DO YOU EVER THINK ABOUT
HOW OLD SION'S DOING THESE DAYS?
- ( sighing )
HE'S THE SAME, NO DOUBT.
ACTING DIABOLICALLY
AND USING DUBIOUS MEANS
TO GET WHATEVER HE WANTS.
- YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT
IT, THIS IS ALL HIS FAULT!
- WANNA KILL HIM?
- YES!
JUST YOU WAIT, SION,
'CAUSE WHEN WE GET HOME,
WE'RE GONNA MAKE YOU SUFFER
AND SUFFER AND SUFFER
UNTIL YOU DIE!
SO TELL ME,
HOW EXACTLY DID WE
END UP LIKE THIS AGAIN,
DO YOU REMEMBER?
- AS I RECALL, YOUR TYPICAL,
UNRELENTING NEED
TO MAKE SEXUAL ADVANCES
ON THE FEMALE PASSENGERS,
THREW THE SHIP'S CREW INTO
A BLOODTHIRSTY RAGE.
- COME ON, THAT'S A LIE!
FROM WHERE I WAS STANDING,
IT LOOKED MORE LIKE YOU AND
MILK'S MORON CREW
MADE A MESS OUT OF EVERYTHING
AND TORE THE SHIP APART!
- ( people on board screaming )
- Ryner: AFTER WE SENT ARUA
AND KUKU BACK TO ROLAND,
I THOUGHT THINGS
WOULD QUIET DOWN,
BUT THEY CAME BACK
WITH A SWIFT ATTACK.
OH, WELL, GUESS THEY'RE
SAFE NOW, HUH? WHAT IN THE...
- ( wind blowing )
- AW, NO, THIS SUCKS!
- IT APPEARS THAT
A STORM IS COMING.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SO CALM ABOUT IT!
NO, NO, NO, NO!
GREAT. I'M GONNA DIE.
( groaning )
HEY, WAIT. I'M STILL ALIVE.
( laughing ) THIS IS GREAT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M HERE.
I COULD HAVE SWORN
I WAS JUST DEAD!
FERRIS! HEY, FERRIS!
( sniffing )
SMELLS LIKE SOMETHING'S COOKING.
- Luke: OH, CAPTAIN MILK.
NOT ONLY DID I GET
SEPARATED FROM YOU,
BUT THE WHOLE SQUADRON'S
BEEN SCATTERED
AND THERE'S NO TELLING
WHERE THEY MIGHT BE.
TOMORROW, AS SOON
AS THE SUN RISES,
I'LL GO OUT LOOKING FOR YOU.
PLEASE, STAY SAFE UNTIL THEN.
- OH, NO!
I MADE ENOUGH FOOD FOR
THE WHOLE SQUADRON
WITHOUT REALIZING IT.
I WISH YOU WERE HERE, CAPTAIN,
I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU LOVE CAMPING.
WHEREVER YOU ARE, MILK,
I SWEAR I'LL FIND YOU.
( gasps )
- HE'S A SHARP ONE. THIS GUY
DEFINITELY SAW ME COMING.
DELICIOUS.
THE TASTE HOLDS UP WITHOUT
HAVING ANY OF THE AWFUL SMELL.
METICULOUS TYPES LIKE THESE...
- ( gasps ) YOU'RE RYNER LUTE!
BUT...
- I KNOW YOU. YOU'RE WITH
THE TABOO BREAKER SQUAD.
- Both: HUH?!
- ( Milk sighing )
I WONDER IF LUKE AND
THE OTHERS ARE OKAY,
AND RYNER.
OH, RYNER.
- Young Ryner: TRUST ME.
HOLD ONTO MY HAND AND
DON'T EVER LET GO.
- DON'T WORRY, I'LL SAVE YOU,
RYNER. I PROMISE YOU.
( exclaims )
IT'S HER AND SHE'S ALL ALONE!
THIS IS MY CHANCE, RYNER!
( tripping and screaming )
( grunting )
( screaming loudly )
- Ferris: WHAT IS THIS?
WAIT, THAT'S THE WOMAN
RYNER TRICKED AND ABANDONED.
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
- I HAVEN'T BEEN ABANDONED
BY ANYONE!
YOU'RE THE BIG MEANIE WHO
ENSLAVES RYNER AGAINST HIS WILL!
I'M ONTO YOU, SISTER!
IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD FOR YOU,
THEN YOU'LL LET HIM GO!
YOU ARE MISINFORMED.
I AM THE VICTIM HERE,
NOT RYNER LUTE.
I AM ENSLAVED.
- YEAH RIGHT, MY RYNER
WOULD NEVER DO THAT!
- YOUR MEMORY OF
WHO RYNER REALLY IS
HAS OBVIOUSLY BEEN DISTORTED.
HIS SEXUAL ADVANCES
DON'T EVER END.
HE EVEN SINKS HIS FANGS
INTO MY POOR LITTLE SISTER
NIGHT AFTER NIGHT.
( sobbing )
OH, I CANNOT BEAR TO
SPEAK ANY FURTHER!
- ( gasping )
NO WAY! NO WAY! NO WAY!
RYNER'S NOT LIKE THAT,
I KNOW HE'S NOT!
- LISTEN TO ME.
THE OTHER DAY, WE ENTRUSTED TWO
CHILDREN TO YOUR CARE.
YOU DESERVE TO KNOW THE TRUTH,
THEY WERE HIS SECRET CHILDREN!
- YOU LIE!
- YOU THINK ABOUT IT!
DID THEY NOT TREAT
HIM WITH RESPECT
AND SHOW AN UNUSUAL
EMOTIONAL ATTACHMENT TO HIM?
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
IN NELPHA, HE CONSUMMATED
WITH EVERY MARRIED
WOMAN HE MET.
AND IN RUNA, HE KIDNAPPED
INNOCENT VILLAGE GIRLS
BY THE DOZEN,
ONE AFTER ANOTHER.
HE EVEN WENT AFTER
SOME OF THEIR MOTHERS.
- OH, BOY.
GIVE ME ONE GOOD REASON
WHY I SHOULD
SHARE THIS WITH YOU.
- IT MUST REALLY SUCK BEING YOU.
TABOO BREAKER SQUADRON
IS PRETTY MUCH
THE BOTTOM OF THE BARREL,
AS FAR AS MILITARY POSTS GO.
BUT BECAUSE THE SLAVE
DRIVER KING OF ROLAND IS ALL,
'YOU MUST WORK
FOR ROLAND'S FUTURE!'
SO YOU DON'T REALLY
HAVE THAT OPTION
OF SKIPPING OUT, HUH?
- THAT ISN'T SO. HIS MAJESTY
LABORS AS HARD AS ANYONE
TO IMPROVE THIS NATION
AND KEEP US SAFE.
IT IS NOT SIMPLY
OUR SWORN DUTY,
BUT A JOY AND AN HONOR
TO SERVE SO GREAT A KING.
OH, COME ON. DEEP DOWN,
THERE MUST BE A LOT OF
THINGS YOU WANNA SAY, RIGHT?
LIKE 'I HATE WORKING
LONG HOURS FOR LITTLE PAY,'
OR 'GIVE ME A RAISE
OR ELSE, JERK!'
OR 'EXPAND AFTERNOON NAPTIME TO
OVER TWENTY-FOUR HOURS A DAY!'
- BUT THAT WOULD MEAN
ALL ANYONE EVER DID WAS SLEEP!
I CERTAINLY CAN'T
ALLOW THE CAPTAIN
TO MARRY AN IDIOT LIKE THIS.
- HMM? WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- Milk: RYNER!
- Both: CAPTAIN MILK?!
- EXPLAIN YOURSELF,
RYNER, RIGHT NOW!
THE SECRET CHILDREN,
THE MARRIED WOMEN,
LOVERS IN NELPHA AND RUNA.
YOU'VE BEEN BUSY,
HAVEN'T YOU? FESS UP!
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER! IZUCHI!
- Ryner: WHOA! HEY, CUT IT OUT!
- Luke: PLEASE, CAPTAIN MILK,
CALM YOURSELF!
GET IT TOGETHER!
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, FUNBOY!
- WHERE THE HELL IS THIS
COMING FROM, HUH?
FERRIS!
- INDEED, THE DANGO PREPARED
AT THE WYNNIT HOUSE
ARE ON A DIFFERENT LEVEL.
- THE WYNNIT TEA HOUSE,
BUT THAT'S...
- WHOA! WHERE DID YOU
GET THOSE FROM?
- WELL, I BOUGHT
THEM, OBVIOUSLY.
WE ARE WITHIN ROLAND'S
BORDERS, AFTER ALL.
- Ryner: WHAT?!
- IT'S HOUSE ERIS,
A TERRITORY OF MY FAMILY
POSITIONED ALONG
THE COASTAL REGION.
- BUT HOW CAN YOU TELL?
- YOU CAN SEE PART OF
THE ERIS ESTATE OVER THERE.
DO YOU NOT USE YOUR EYES?
- THERE'S NO WAY I COULD
SEE IT FROM DOWN HERE!
WAIT, HOLD ON A MINUTE...
SO, WE ARE IN ROLAND NOW?
- YES.
- ALL RIGHT! HOW ABOUT WE
DESTROY THE ROOT OF EVIL
THAT PUT US THROUGH THIS TORMENT
AND BE DONE WITH IT, HUH?
- YES. ON THE DAWN OF HIS
DEFEAT, LIKE A SUN RISING,
I SHALL TAKE HIS PLACE
AND I SHALL MAKE ROLAND
INTO THE DANGO EMPIRE!
- COME ON, AT LEAST
MAKE IT THE DANGO
AND AFTERNOON NAP EMPIRE!
- NAPS ARE FINE, BUT
ONLY AFTER EATING DANGO.
- ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
-Both: DEAL!
- I DON'T EAT DANGO.
DOES THAT MEAN I CAN'T NAP?
- YEP.
- WAIT! HOLD ON A SECOND,
RYNER, DON'T DO THIS!
- ( chuckling diabolically )
FINALLY, WE'LL MAKE THAT
ARROGANT BULLY OF A KING
PAY FOR HIS TYRANNY
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
- Ferris: YEAH!
- Sion: "LONG AGO,
THE FORCES OF DARKNESS
CALLED THIS WORLD
THEIR PLAYGROUND.
"DEMONS, GHOULS, EVIL SPIRITS.
"AT ONE TIME,
THEY WERE SO NUMEROUS,
"CIVILIZATION, AS WE KNOW IT,
ALMOST DIDN'T COME
INTO BEING AT ALL.
"THEN THEY SHOWED UP.
"ANCIENT WARRIORS STRONG ENOUGH
TO DRIVE THE DEMON HORDES OUT.
"HEROES WHOSE STAND AGAINST
THE FORCES OF DARKNESS BECAME
"THE STUFF OF LEGEND.
"IF YOU COULD DIG UP FRAGMENTS
OF THAT TURBULENT, PIVOTAL AGE,
"MAYBE WE COULD STAND AGAINST
THE FORCES OF DARKNESS.
"A WORLD THAT HURTS KIEFER, THAT
KILLS TILE AND TONY AND FAHLE,
"IT'S BEST SWAPPED FOR ONE WHERE
PEOPLE CAN CLOSE THEIR EYES
"IN THE AFTERNOON AND NAP."
IS IT BUT A FOOLISH DREAM?
BUT THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
OF COURSE NOT!
IF IT WAS, THEN WHY DID I BECOME
KING IN THE FIRST PLACE?
TO FORGE A PATH TO PROSPERITY.
TO BELLOW THE WINDS OF CHANGE.
TO CREATE A WORLD
WHERE EVERYONE CAN LIVE
A HAPPY, PEACEFUL LIFE.
IS THAT NOT THE REASON
I SO WANTED THIS CROWN?
AND NOW WHAT? WHAT?
SHALL I THROW IT ALL AWAY?
I WILL NEVER GIVE UP.
NOT UNTIL THE DAY I DIE.
- ( maid gasps )
SORRY TO DISTURB YOU,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
- NO, YOU'RE FINE. WE ALL
HAVE WORK TO DO, DON'T WE?
- UH, THANK YOU, YOUR HIGHNESS.
I MUST SAY I'M NOT USED
TO BEING TREATED SO KINDLY.
IN MY HOMETOWN OUR LORD
WORKED US TO THE BONE,
AND PAID US ALMOST NOTHING.
BUT BECAUSE OF YOUR
GENEROSITY, YOUR MAJESTY,
EVERYONE IS ABLE TO
LIVE A DECENT LIFE.
I CONSIDER IT A PRIVILEGE
AND A GREAT HONOR
TO SERVE SO GRACIOUS A KING.
- WELL, MY HUMBLE THANKS.
- Ryner:
LIKE A TRAVELING PLAYER,
HE ACTS THE PART
OF HERO CONVINCINGLY.
THAT WHOLE "NICE GUY" DEMEANOR
AND "CHAMPION OF
JUSTICE" ATTITUDE
ENDEAR HIM TO THE PEOPLE.
THEY DON'T SEE
THE ARROGANT, CRAFTY SLAVE
DRIVER BEHIND THE FACADE.
JUST GIVE ME FIVE MINUTES
WITH HIM AND I'LL SMACK THAT
PHONY SMILE RIGHT OFF
HIS ARROGANT FACE!
- YES, HE'LL BE BUT
RUST UPON MY BLADE!
- OH, RYNER!
WE HAVE TO STOP THIS
MADNESS RIGHT AWAY!
WE CAN'T ALLOW HIM TO
ASSASSINATE THE KING!
- SOMETHING TOLD ME
RYNER WAS MORE
THAN JUST YOUR
AVERAGE TABOO BREAKER,
BUT I NEVER WOULD HAVE
PEGGED HIM FOR AN ASSASSIN.
- EVEN IF HE MANAGES
TO GET AWAY WITH IT,
THE ROYAL GUARD
WILL HUNT HIM
TILL HE'S BURIED
IN THE GROUND!
- WE MUST SAVE HIM FROM HIMSELF.
WE CAN'T ALLOW HIM TO COMMIT
SUCH A HORRIBLE CRIME!
- FEAR NOT, CAPTAIN MILK,
WE'RE WITH YOU!
AS LONG AS I'M STILL STANDING,
NO ONE WILL TOUCH HIS MAJESTY!
( Lach groans )
- ( Milk screams )
- Moe: LACH, NO!
- Milk: PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER!
- Ryner: HEY, FERRIS,
WHAT'S WRONG?
- I JUST FELT A POTENT SENSE
OF DEADLY INTENT IN THE AIR.
OH, WELL.
- SO. WHAT METHODS OF TORTURE
SHALL WE USE BEFORE WE KILL HIM?
- FAIR QUESTION.
HOW ABOUT WE STEAL
SOMETHING PRECIOUS TO HIM?
'NO, NOT MY PRECIOUS THING.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE, FLOP!'
SOUND GOOD?
- YES, I LIKE IT.
NOW WE JUST NEED SOMETHING
PRECIOUS TO STEAL, DON'T WE?
- OH! HIS DANGO, THEN?
- SOMETHING PRECIOUS
TO HIM, NOT YOU!
- Claugh: WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- ( all gasp)
- Luke: CLAUGH KLOM.
- THIS IS A SURPRISE,
I DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE YOU HERE.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD BEEN ASSIGNED
TO THE TABOO BREAKER SQUADRON.
WHAT BUSINESS DO YOU
HAVE IN THE MANOR, LUKE?
- WAIT, SO YOU TWO
KNOW EACH OTHER?
- YES, FROM OUR MILITARY DAYS.
I THOUGHT HIS MAJESTY
HAD DISPATCHED YOU
TO THE NATION
OF ESTABUL, CLAUGH.
- INITIALLY, HE DID.
BUT WIDESPREAD RUMORS OF
ANOTHER ASSASSINATION ATTEMPT
IN THE WORKS STALLED
MY TRIP FOR NOW.
I CAME BACK TO SNIFF
OUT THE TRAITOR.
- HEY, SO DOES THAT MEAN THAT...
- DO YOU THINK THEY'VE
ALREADY BEEN FOUND, CAPTAIN?
- WAIT, WHO IS 'THEY?'
- ( Milk wails )
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- OH, MY POOR STOMACH!
MY STOMACH HURTS, I HAVE
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM!
I DON'T FEEL GOOD!
- THERE'S NO TIME FOR THAT NOW.
FINE, IF YOU INSIST,
THE BATHROOM'S THIS WAY!
YOU'D BETTER HURRY UP!
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'D BETTER GET A MOVE ON!
- HEY! SHE CAN'T
JUST RUN OFF AND--
- OH, IT'S ONLY HER
STOMACH PROBLEMS.
PUTTING THAT ASIDE, I TAKE IT
SION'S THE SAME AS EVER?
- HE'S STILL THE WORKAHOLIC
HE ALWAYS WAS.
SOMEONE SHOULD TEACH HIS
MAJESTY HOW TO TAKE A BREAK.
NOT EVERYONE CAN
KEEP UP WITH HIS PACE.
- RYNER, I WILL PROTECT YOU,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES!
RYNER!
RYNER, NO!
- Ryner: MILK, GET DOWN!
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER! IZUCHI!
- ( assassin 1 screams )
- ( Milk gasps )
- Assassin 2: PULL BACK!
- Ryner: FERRIS!
YOU OKAY?
- BUT RYNER, IS THIS...
- WE CAN'T REALLY BE SURE.
BUT WE HAVE REASON TO BELIEVE
THAT THEY'RE ASSASSINS
SENT HERE FOR A SOLE PURPOSE,
TO TAKE OUT MISTER BIG.
I GUESS BEING THE KING
ISN'T A BED OF ROSES, HUH?
- SO, THEY'RE NOT HERE WITH YOU?
OH, RYNER, THIS MEANS
YOU WEREN'T REALLY
PLANNING TO ASSASSINATE
HIS MAJESTY AFTER ALL, RIGHT?
- NO. NO, I WAS!
AH, THIS SUCKS!
IF I WOULD'VE USED MY HEAD
AND LEFT THEM ALONE,
THEY COULD'VE TAKEN
CARE OF SION FOR ME!
FERRIS, LET 'EM GO!
IF WE WALK AWAY,
THEY'LL KILL SION FOR US!
- RYNER, YOU JERK, SOMETIMES,
I SWEAR, YOU MAKE ME...
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
IZUCHI! IZUCHI! IZUCHI!
IZUCHI, YOU STUPID IDIOT!
- Ryner: CUT IT OUT!
( Ryner screaming in pain )
- SUCCESSFULLY OPPOSING
GASTARK'S FORCES
WILL REQUIRE A
CERTAIN AMOUNT OF POWER.
I MUST PRIORITIZE.
STRENGTHENING MY HOLD
ON ESTABUL IS VITAL.
EVEN IF I ENTRUST THE
MILITARY TO CLAUGH,
THE NOBLES WILL STILL BE...
- ( snoring )
- SON OF A...
HEY, YOU JERK!
- GOOD MORNING TO YOU, TOO.
- GOOD MORNING, MY ASS!
YOU REALLY COULD'VE
BROKEN MY NOSE, YOU KNOW THAT?
- THAT'S THE LEAST YOU DESERVE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
THE OLD BOOK OVER
THE DOOR TRICK?
SO WHEN DID YOU RETURN HOME?
- THIS MORNING.
- WELCOME.
NOW WHAT ARE
YOU DOING IN MY BED?
- IT'S A LONG STORY.
THERE IS SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW, THOUGH.
YOU SEE, I HAD WHAT FERRIS
THINKS WAS AN EPIPHANY!
- IS THAT SO?
- RECENTLY, I FOUND MYSELF
STUCK, DRIFTING IN THE OCEAN.
- REALLY?
- YES.
SURROUNDED BY WATER
AND NOTHING ELSE AROUND.
THE OCEAN WAS SO VAST,
AND THE CLEAR BLUE SKY SO HIGH.
I HEARD NOTHING BUT THE SOUND
OF WAVES CRASHING AGAINST US.
I FOUND MYSELF
REFLECTING ON MY LIFE.
I WONDERED IF I COULD BE
HAPPY WITH THE STATE OF THINGS.
I WONDERED WHY,
DAY AFTER DAY,
IT CONTINUALLY SUCKS TO BE ME.
- IN FULL DISCLOSURE,
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU MEAN.
- BUT THEN IT CAME TO ME.
IT'S HIM! HE'S TO BLAME!
THAT ARROGANT, DIABOLICAL
KING OF THE ROLAND EMPIRE,
SION ASTAL, IT'S HIS FAULT!
MY LORD.
- SO YOU'RE ADMITTING
YOU TRIED TO KILL ME?
WITH A BOOK?
- WITH A BOOK.
YOUR EPIPHANY LED
YOU TO BELIEVE
YOU SHOULD TRY TO
ASSASSINATE YOUR KING
WITH A PIECE OF LITERATURE?
- IT'S BLOWING YOUR MIND,
ISN'T IT?
- ( laughing amused )
YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
MIND-BLOWING INDEED.
BUT, RYNER, YOU'RE AWARE
YOU ACTED RASHLY.
AN ATTEMPT ON THE
KING'S LIFE IS SERIOUS.
PARTICULARLY A 'HERO KING',
BELOVED BY ALL PEOPLE
ACROSS THIS CONTINENT.
- OH-HO. YOU'RE CALLING YOURSELF
A 'HERO KING' NOW, HUH?
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO
ASK YOU THIS FOR A WHILE.
WHERE DOES A BELOW AVERAGE
PERSON LIKE YOU
COME UP WITH THIS SHTICK?
- ASCENDING TO THE THRONE
HAS BEEN MY DESTINY
FROM THE DAY I WAS BORN.
- MODESTY BECOMES YOU.
- THE TRUTH CANNOT
BE HELPED, RYNER.
MY CHARACTER JUST
SHINES DIFFERENTLY.
DON'T YOU SEE?
IT'S A BEACON OF PURITY THAT
COMES FROM A STRONG HEART
AND A NOBLE SPIRIT.
- AH! GOD!
YOU LITTLE ARROGANT BASTARD!
NEXT TIME I'LL USE A
BOULDER INSTEAD OF A BOOK!
- HOLD ON, PLEASE LISTEN
TO ME, RYNER!
- Ryner: SION?
- HMM?
- YOU MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
- YOU THINK SO?
- YEAH. GET SOME SLEEP.
- NO, I'M FINE. I GUESS
I JUST NEEDED TO LIE DOWN.
- WHAT IS WITH YOU?
I COULD SLEEP OVER
FIFTY HOURS A DAY
AND YOU JUST NEED
TO 'LIE DOWN'?
- WOW, FIFTY HOURS, HUH?
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXPLAIN THE
LOGISTICS OF THAT TO ME.
HOW DID YOU CHEAT SCIENCE?
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
SLEEP MIGHT MAKE YOU NICER.
- SLEEP'S FOR THE DEAD.
- YOU ARE HOPELESS.
- ( doors open )
AN ENEMY OF DANGO IS AN ENEMY
OF THE PEOPLE OF THIS LAND!
- RYNER! PLEASE,
DON'T MURDER THE KING!
- Ferris: NO. YOU'VE
BITTEN HIS MAJESTY
WITH YOUR PERVERTED FANGS!
- I DON'T HAVE FANGS!
- HUH? BUT...
YOUR ROYAL MAJESTY,
DID RYNER TAKE ADVANTAGE OF YOU?
- SO, IT'S LIKE THAT, EH?
I'M SORRY FOR NOT NOTICING
WHAT SEEMS SO OBVIOUS NOW.
THOUGH SOCIETY'S WIND
BLOWS COLD ON YOU,
JUST TRY TO BE HAPPY!
STOP IT! YOU'VE GOT THE
WRONG IDEA, ALL RIGHT?
- ( amused laughter )
- Miran: I QUOTE,
"I'VE SPARED MYSELF THE PAIN
OF TAKING A GOOD,
HARD LOOK AT MY PAST.
"BUT IF PAIN AND BITTER TRUTH
ARE WHAT'S NEEDED TO
RESHAPE MANKIND'S DESTINY,
"THEN SO BE IT.
"A WORLD WHERE SION
CAN DO NOTHING BUT BROOD
"IS BEST SWAPPED
FOR A WORLD
WHERE PEOPLE
CAN CLOSE THEIR EYES
"ON A LATE AFTERNOON AND NAP."
END QUOTE. I SEE.
SO THEN, THIS 'CAPTAIN MILK' IS
RYNER LUTE'S LYNCHPIN, IS SHE?
SHE'S WHAT KEEPS RYNER
FROM LEAVING ROLAND.
OR TO PUT IT ANOTHER WAY,
SHE'S THE SINGLE
THREAD THAT KEEPS
RYNER'S TIE TO HIS
MAJESTY FROM SNAPPING.
AND THAT IS THE KING'S WEAKNESS.
HIS DEEP-ROOTED
FEAR OF RYNER LUTE
LEAVING OF HIS OWN ACCORD.
HERO RELICS.
THROUGH THEM,
THE WORLD RYNER DESIRES
AND THE KING STRIVES
FOR CAN COME TO BE.
A WORLD WHERE PEOPLE
LIVE IN PERFECT HARMONY.
WHERE NO ONE DIES,
NO ONE KILLS, AND NO ONE
SUFFERS LIFE'S HARDSHIPS.
AN IDEAL KING.
THAT IS THE CHAIN THAT
BINDS HIS MAJESTY TO RYNER.
THAT SAME CHAIN WILL
STRANGLE HIS GRACE, HOWEVER.
HIS FANTASY OF AN IDEAL KING
ISN'T REAL.
CLINGING TO SUCH ILLUSIONS
BREAKS ONE'S WILL.
IT COULD EVEN BREAK
THE SPIRIT OF KINGS.
IN THAT CASE, RYNER,
IT SEEMS TO ME YOUR
REMOVAL IS NECESSARY.
- ( doors shut )
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: IRIS HAS COMPILED
EXTENSIVE REPORTS
DOCUMENTING OUR EXPLOITS.
I'VE A REALLY UNPLEASANT
FEELING ABOUT ALL THIS.
I'M TIRED OF BEING
BOSSED AROUND BY SION.
MAYBE IT'S ABOUT TIME
I HIT THE ROAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT, THIS SUCKS.