WAIT! WHAT IN THE HELL
IS GOING ON?
- ( man grunting )
( screams )
- ( lightning crackling )
- Rigwalz: THEY'VE BEEN
CROPPING UP IN RUNA TERRITORY,
IN A FOREST JUST SHY
OF ROLAND'S BORDER.
- THERE'S NO
OTHER EXPLANATION?
- NO, SIR. SEVERAL OF THE
SURVIVORS REPORTED IT FIRSTHAND.
- THE GALL OF IT.
RESORTING TO THE WORST KIND
OF FORBIDDEN MAGIC.
- IF I MAY, SIR.
THE SPY IN OUR CUSTODY
MAY KNOW SOMETHING OF THIS.
- ( theme song playing )
- Lafra: PLEASE, RYNER,
YOU HAVE TO SAVE THEM.
- Ryner: I'M DONE RUNNING.
SERIOUSLY?
- MAYBE HE DECIDED TO
CALL IT A DAY FOR ONCE.
- OH, GIVE ME A BREAK!
WILD HORSES COULDN'T DRAG HIM
AWAY FROM THAT STUPID DESK.
AS LONG AS THERE'S WORK, "BREAK"
ISN'T PART OF HIS VOCABULARY.
I'LL BET YOU ANYTHING HE'S
PULLING AN ALL-NIGHTER
AND TOO WRAPPED UP TO
NOTICE WE'RE BACK.
- WELL, THAT IS HIS STYLE.
- HEY! KING WORKS-A-LOT!
WE KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE!
OPEN THE HELL UP!
( in comical tone)
HELLO? YOUR MAJESTY?
HUH? WHAT THE...
YOU'VE GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
YOU TWO CERTAINLY
TROD HOME AT YOUR OWN PACE.
IT'S A GOOD THING FOR US
I'M PATIENT.
- WHAT THE HELL IS ALL THIS?
- THANKS TO THE ABSENCE
OF SOMEONE WHO SHALL
REMAIN NAMELESS,
A BACKLOG OF WORK HAS PILED UP.
- DON'T EVEN SAY IT!
- AS LONG AS THERE'S PAPERWORK
TO BE GOTTEN THROUGH,
SAY GOODNIGHT TO SLEEP.
AH, BUT DON'T FRET.
FERRIS WILL BE HELPING TO
PICK UP SOME OF THE SLACK.
- A-HO-HO!
VERY FUNNY, YOU...
SLAVE-DRIVER!
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
YOUR MAJESTY,
YOU'RE A FOOL TO THINK
I'D CARVE A HOLE
OUT OF MY DANGO-EATING ITINERARY
FOR GRUNT-WORK.
- THAT GOES DOUBLE FOR ME.
- ( door locks )
- Sion: GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- I HAD THAT KEY,
SPECIALLY CUSTOMIZED.
SO, THEN. LET'S ALL THREE OF US
PUT A DENT IN THE WORKLOAD.
- STAB HIM.
- UM.
THE GUARDS HAD ME SURRENDER MY
SWORD BEFORE WE CAME IN HERE.
- THERE ARE NO WORDS TO DESCRIBE
HOW BIG OF A BASTARD YOU ARE!
NONE!
- WELCOME BACK.
THAT IS TO SAY, I'M EXTREMELY
GRATEFUL YOU SAW FIT TO RETURN.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
IT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE,
BUT I AM.
- THAT'S ALL VERY WELL, BUT
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
KINDLY OPEN THE DOOR AND LET
ME CONTINUE WITH MY MISSION.
- WHAT?
- BALK ALL YOU WANT, LOWBROW.
MY DUTY IS OF VITAL IMPORTANCE.
THE DANGO SHOPS DEPEND ON ME.
- DON'T YOU EVEN TRY TO
WEASEL OUT OF THIS!
- HOW DARE YOU?
THE DANGO GOD ENTRUSTED ME
WITH THIS MISSION PERSONALLY
AND I INTEND TO SEE IT THROUGH!
- SO, RYNER,
YOU'VE REALLY
COME BACK FOR GOOD,
HAVEN'T YOU?
- HEY, SION.
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
ABOUT TO BE SICK OR SOMETHING.
- DO I? WELL
AREN'T YOU FLATTERING?
- ( boy crying )
- I KNOW THAT VOICE.
RYNER?
HEY, RYNER, IS THAT YOU?
HOLD TIGHT. JUST LET ME
GET MY BEARINGS!
YOUR MAJESTY?
BUT HOW CAN...
HOW CAN THAT POSSIBLY BE YOU?
- PLEASE KILL ME.
I DON'T DESERVE TO LIVE.
- ( gasps )
- Luke: THE SPELL FROUADE
PLACED ON HER HAS BEEN LIFTED.
WE CAN EXPECT HER
TO WAKE VERY SOON, I THINK.
- Lear: I'LL GO SEE
KAIWEL, THEN.
- Luke: NO NEED.
HE'S BEEN APPRISED.
AND HE'S JUST AS PREOCCUPIED
WITH RYNER LUTE AS WE ARE.
- HEY! TAKE A LOOK, GUYS!
THE CAPTAIN'S AWAKE!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
SHE'S IN THE PROCESS
OF RECOVERY!
USE YOUR INSIDE VOICE!
- HELLO. WHERE AM I?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Lach: HOW YOU
FEELING, CAPTAIN?
- LACH, PLEASE. AT LEAST BE WISE
ENOUGH TO TAKE YOUR OWN ADVICE.
- THIS IS MY INSIDE VOICE.
- WELL, GOOD MORNING.
SOMEONE DECIDED TO SLEEP IN
RATHER LATE TODAY, DIDN'T THEY?
- I DID?
BUT, I DON'T...
( gasps ) HE...
HE TOOK ME.
- Luke: THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
TRUST ME.
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
- WHAT YOU SHOULD BE
CONCERNED ABOUT IS FOOD.
I THINK THE OCCASION CALLS
FOR A SPECIAL MEAL, DON'T YOU?
- YEAH, I VOTE FOR CURRY.
- SHUT UP, IDIOT!
HE WASN'T ASKING US!
- Lear: HEY! THE CAPTAIN'S
STILL RECOVERING, REMEMBER.
- Luke: IN WHICH CASE
I RECOMMEND PORRIDGE.
- Lach: WE CAN MAKE
A BIG PRODUCTION OUT OF IT!
- Moe: WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WE DIDN'T GET A CHANCE TO
CELEBRATE HER BIRTHDAY, GENIUS.
THIS IS THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY.
- Luke: YOU'LL GET
NO ARGUMENT FROM ME.
- Lach: HELL YEAH!
- ( gasps )
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT. THEY'RE
HIDING SOMETHING FROM ME.
- Luke: THE SPELL FROAUDE PLACED
ON HER HAS BEEN LIFTED.
WE CAN EXPECT HER
TO WAKE VERY SOON, I THINK.
- Lear: I'LL GO SEE
KAIWEL, THEN.
- KAIWEL? AS IN MAJOR
GENERAL CALNE KAIWEL?
THAT'S ONE OF HIS MAJESTY'S
CLOSEST ADVISORS, ISN'T IT?
WHY IN THE WORLD WOULD
LEAR DROP A NAME LIKE THAT?
SURELY THERE'S NOT
SOME CONNECTION
BETWEEN THE ROYAL CABINET AND MY
BEING KIDNAPPED BY THAT CREEP.
I MEAN, WHAT CONNECTION
COULD THERE BE?
NOT THAT LUKE AND THE OTHERS
WOULD LET ME IN ON IT
IF THERE WERE.
I CAN TELL THAT MUCH.
SO HOW DO I GET TO
THE BOTTOM OF THIS?
( gasps ) FATHER!
IF ANYONE WOULD HAVE THE GOODS
ON HIS MAJESTY'S DEALINGS,
IT'D BE A NOBLE.
( screams )
( groans )
NO!
I'M SORRY!
PLEASE STOP!
YOU'RE HURTING ME, FATHER!
HELP ME, PLEASE!
( panting )
IT CAN'T BE.
WHAT'S HAPPENED?
MOM?
DAD?
( crying )
- Luke: I'M AFRAID THE DUKE
AND DUCHESS CALLAUD
HAVE PASSED AWAY, CAPTAIN.
AND, AS I'M SURE
YOU'VE SURMISED,
BOTH OF THEM WERE MURDERED.
- BUT WHY?
- YOU'RE SUCH A GENTLE,
KINDHEARTED SOUL, CAPTAIN.
THE THOUGHT LIKELY
NEVER CROSSED YOUR MIND.
NOBLES ROUTINELY BUY ORPHANS
AND HAVE THEM
TRAINED AS SOLDIERS
SO AS TO SPARE THEIR OWN FLESH
AND BLOOD THE HORRORS OF BATTLE.
IT NEVER OCCURS TO THEM
NOT TO WAGE BATTLES, OF COURSE.
- ( crying )
- THINK OF IT.
WHY GRIEVE FOR SUCH PARENTS?
- THEY...
THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN MONSTERS,
BUT THEY RAISED ME
AS THEIR OWN FOR A WHILE.
- TRULY, CAPTAIN,
YOU ARE TOO KIND.
- SO YOU KNEW. YOU KNEW
THAT THEY'D BEEN MURDERED,
AND YOU ALL KEPT IT A SECRET.
YOU KEPT IT A SECRET TO
KEEP FROM BREAKING MY HEART.
BUT NOW, I'M ASKING YOU TO BE
COMPLETELY HONEST WITH ME.
WHAT IS GOING ON? WHAT ROAD IS
THIS COUNTRY HEADED DOWN?
- Claugh: CRIMSON FINGERED
CLAUGH SPORTING AN ARM
AS BLACK AS MIDNIGHT.
KINDA RUINS THE NICKNAME, HUH?
- Noa: YOU REALLY MEAN TO
LEAVE THE HOSPITAL?
- BELIEVE ME, IT'S FOR THE BEST.
I'VE GOTTA GET USED
TO THIS THING.
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S A LOT
OF TRAINING OPTIONS HERE.
- THAT MAY BE,
BUT THE DOCTOR ADVISED YOU
TO GET PLENTY OF REST.
ARE YOU REALLY READY
FOR A TRAINING REGIMEN?
- AW C'MON, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
AND BESIDES,
I CAN NEVER BE THE GUY WHO JUST
SITS AROUND TAKING IT EASY.
- YOU'RE PLUNGING HEADLONG
INTO THE FRAY AGAIN, AREN'T YOU?
- YOU BETTER BELIEVE I WOULD
IF I HAD THE OPTION.
I HAVE TO PREPARE FIRST, THOUGH.
THAT'S THE STORY OF MY LIFE
FROM COVER TO COVER.
I AM A MAN OF ACTION.
- ( sighs )
- IS IT COLD?
- NO. NOT AT ALL.
IN FACT IT'S AS WARM AS IT WAS
THE DAY WE FIRST MET.
- ( clears throat )
GLAD I DECIDED AT THE LAST
MINUTE NOT TO BRING ESLINA.
SHE'S A BIT TOO YOUNG,
FOR THIS SCENE.
- ( both exclaim )
- HEY, THIS HAPPENS TO BE
A LADY YOU'RE ADDRESSING!
- WELL, I, UH...
WONDERFUL TALKING WITH YOU.
( clears throat )
- BYE.
SHE IS SO OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE,
IT ISN'T EVEN FUNNY.
- ( sighs ) SHUT YOUR
INSOLENT MOUTH.
SO, YOU'VE GOT NEWS, THEN?
- FOR THE TIME BEING
THE CALLAUD MURDERS
REMAIN AN ENIGMA.
DETAILS HAVE BEEN
VERY SLOW TO SURFACE.
THAT SAID, I DO HAVE
MY THEORIES.
I THINK NOBLES WHO OPPOSE
SION'S WAY OF DOING THINGS
ARE BEING PICKED OFF,
ONE BY ONE.
- I KNEW THE GUY. CALLAUD
WAS SOLID MILITARY BRASS.
TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
NOT FOR ALL THE WORLD WOULD
HE PLOT AGAINST HIS KING.
- WHEN I SAY "OPPOSED,"
I MEAN EVEN HONEST DISSENTERS.
- SO, NO ONE IS SAFE.
- NOT IF THEY HAVE
A BONE TO PICK WITH SION.
BEAR IN MIND, TOO, THEY WERE
LIKELY AT ODDS WITH HIM
BECAUSE THEY STUMBLED
UPON SOME SECRET.
- IS THIS FROUADE'S DOING?
- ACTUALLY, FROUADE
IS CLEAN SO FAR.
EVERYTHING WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO
UNCOVER EXONERATES HIM.
HE'S BEEN POKING AROUND, SURE,
BUT THAT'S IT.
- THE HELL'S GOING ON?
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT
SOMEONE'S ON THE MOVE.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS, WHO?
- Ryner: ( grunts ) STUPID SUN.
OH, MAN.
FERRIS OFFICIALLY SUCKS.
- ( grunting )
NO! NO MORE OF THIS!
I'M GETTING SOME DANGO
TO REPLENISH MY STRENGTH.
- WAY TO STAY THE COURSE
LIKE A TROOPER.
- I HATE TO SAY THIS,
BUT YOU'RE REPEATING YOURSELF.
- OF COURSE YOU REALIZE
THAT THE LONGER THIS KEEPS UP,
THE CLOSER I GET TO AN EARLY
GRAVE DUE TO LACK OF SLEEP.
- A SINGLE ALL-NIGHTER
ISN'T GOING TO KILL YOU.
- YOU DON'T FOOL ME
FOR A SECOND, SLAVE-DRIVER!
YOU'RE TRYING TO END ME,
AREN'T YOU?
- ( chuckles )
- IS THAT FUNNY TO YOU?
UH?
- ( sighs )
- ( scribbling )
- SERIOUSLY, HOW DO YOU
KEEP UP WITH THIS BY YOURSELF?
- MY WORK ETHIC, I SUPPOSE.
A BLESSING AND A CURSE, REALLY.
ESTABUL IS FAR FROM STABILIZED.
ON TOP OF THAT,
WE'VE GOT THE UPRISINGS
IN NELPHA, RUNA AND GASTARK
HANGING OVER US.
AND THAT'S NOT EVEN TOUCHING ON
THE MAGIC EYE BEARERS YOU MET.
- I MUST TRY TO SECURE THEM
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- THE PETTY PREJUDICES OF OUR
COUNTRYMEN NOTWITHSTANDING,
WE HAVE TO BRING
SUCH PEOPLE INTO THE FOLD.
NOT JUST FOR THEM,
BUT FOR ALL OUR SAKES.
- HOLD ON. YOU MEAN...
- WHAT I MEAN IS I'M DECLARING
YOU ESSENTIAL TO THE PURPOSE.
- DON'T YOU PREY
ON MY SYMPATHIES!
ESSENTIAL OR NOT,
NOBODY CAN GO ON LIKE THIS.
STOP AND SMELL THE ROSES
ONCE IN A WHILE.
IT'S QUITE POSSIBLE
TO DIE FROM OVERWORK.
- AND IF THAT WERE TO HAPPEN,
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT
SUCCEEDING ME AS KING?
- HUH?
NOW YOU'RE JUST
TOYING WITH ME.
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL I'M TOO LAZY.
- QUITE SO, BUT, I THINK
THAT RATHER MAKES YOU A SHOE-IN.
- ALLOW ME TO REPHRASE THAT.
NO WAY IN HELL
WOULD I WANT YOUR JOB.
IT'S TOO BIG A PAIN IN THE ASS.
- THAT IT IS.
I WOULDN'T ARGUE WITH YOU.
MAYBE I REALLY SHOULD
CONSIDER STEPPING DOWN.
- YOU SHOULD TOTALLY KISS
THIS WHOLE THING GOODBYE!
I COULD INTRODUCE YOU TO
THE PLEASURES OF NAPPING
WHENEVER YOU PLEASE!
- WELL, I HAVE TO CONFESS,
A NAP SOUNDS APPEALING.
PERHAPS ONE OF
THESE DAYS I CAN...
IF I JUST FIND THE TIME.
- Ryner: YOU, MY FRIEND,
PUSH YOURSELF WAY TOO HARD.
I'M NEVER GONNA WORK
AS HARD AS YOU DO,
BUT SOMEHOW YOU
NODDING OFF BEFORE ME
JUST DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT.
- SORRY. HOW LONG WAS I OUT?
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
- I DON'T KNOW.
COUPLE OF MINUTES, I'D SAY.
- SERIOUSLY?
- ( yawning ) I'M
CALLING IT A DAY.
THIS ALL-NIGHTER CRAP
IS FOR THE BIRDS.
- RYNER, HOLD ON.
- I'LL NEED AT LEAST
THREE-DAYS SLEEP
IF YOU EXPECT ME
TO DO THIS AGAIN.
SO BACK OFF.
- ( door closes )
- ( chuckles )
YOU'D DO THIS AGAIN?
- ( grunting )
I'M SORRY.
YOU MADE A MISTAKE
COMING BACK, RYNER.
A GRAVE MISTAKE INDEED.
- YOU MUST KILL HIM
WITHOUT DELAY.
- I MADE HIM A PROMISE,
TO CHANGE THINGS.
THIS LAND. THIS WORLD.
- YOU'RE UNABLE TO SEE
THE FOREST FOR THE TREES.
YOU ARE BEING NAIVE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- THE LONGER YOU WAIT
TO DO WHAT MUST BE DONE,
THE HARDER IT WILL BE.
- SILENCE! I WILL NOT FOLLOW
YOU DOWN THAT PATH.
HE IS MY FRIEND.
HE WILL LIVE.
- Miran: YOU'RE MAJESTY?
- Sion: WHAT IS IT?
- FORGIVE ME, SIR,
BUT DO YOU IN FACT INTEND TO LET
RYNER LUTE CONTINUE TO RUN FREE?
BECAUSE IF I MAY BE SO BOLD,
I WOULD'VE MUCH PREFERRED
LUKE STOKKART HAD DONE THE JOB
WITH WHICH HE WAS ENTRUSTED.
- HAD HE FOLLOWED IT THROUGH,
I MIGHT AS WELL HAVE KILLED
RYNER MYSELF.
- LIFE FEEDS ON LIFE,
YOUR MAJESTY.
AND ONE WHO RULES MUST BE
INURED TO THAT REALITY,
AS INDEED I IMAGINED YOU TO BE.
AFTER ALL, YOUR HIGHNESS,
YOU DISPLAYED NO SUCH
NIGGLING QUALMS OF CONSCIENCE
ON THE MATTER OF
PURGING YOUR DISSENTERS,
OR, TOO WHEN IT CAME TO
EMPLOYING MY SERVICES.
- DO YOU INTEND TO KILL HIM?
- YES, SIR.
ALLOWING HIM TO PERSIST,
WOULD PROVE DETRIMENTAL TO YOU.
HE IS A SYMBOL OF YOUR KINDNESS,
WHICH IS TO SAY, YOUR WEAKNESS.
HIS DEATH WOULD FULLY CONSUMMATE
YOUR RIGHT TO RULE US.
YOU WOULD BE A KING UNDISPUTED,
AND ALL WOULD RECOGNIZE IT.
THE GREAT SION ASTAL, FOR
WHOM NO SACRIFICE IS TOO COSTLY.
FOR WHOM NO CHILDISH IDEAL
OBSTRUCTS THE IRON FIST.
- I WON'T ALLOW IT.
SUPPOSE I SAID THAT?
- I WOULD HONOR YOUR WISH, BY
SUBMITTING TO YOUR PUNISHMENT.
- YOU WOULD KILL HIM
DESPITE MY ORDERS?
- IS THIS A TEST, YOUR MAJESTY?
IF SO, I HUMBLY
SUBMIT THAT DEEP DOWN
YOU WISH FOR NOTHING SO MUCH
AS THE DEATH OF RYNER LUTE.
- YOU WILL NOT TOUCH
ONE HAIR ON HIS HEAD.
- ( gasps )
NO, SIR! SAY WHAT YOU WILL, MY
DUTY TO THE THRONE DICTATES...
- I REPEAT. YOU WILL NOT TOUCH
A HAIR ON RYNER'S HEAD.
THE MATTER IS NOT
OPEN TO DEBATE.
- SIR, PLEASE.
- SILENCE.
- I DO NOT INTEND TO
STAND IDLY BY!
- SILENCE OR I'LL
HAVE YOU QUARTERED!
WE ARE WELL PAST THE POINT
WHERE TALK CAN SPARE YOU.
- ( door creaking )
- ( exclaims )
- YOU SAY I WISH
RYNER LUTE DEAD?
YOU UNDERSTAND NOTHING.
YOU DO NOT SEE THE WORLD
FOR WHAT IT IS.
THE CRUDE LITTLE MAP YOU'VE
ETCHED UPON IT IS A FANTASY.
- YOU'RE MAJESTY, I...
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU?
- VERY WELL.
I'LL SHOW YOU TRUTH.
DARKNESS AND LIGHT INTERTWINED.
YOU WILL SEE THE WORLD AS IT IS,
AND BEHOLD OUR TRUE ENEMY.
- ( chuckles )
( laughs )
- I FEEL LIKE DEATH WARMED OVER.
BUT IT'S NOT FAIR OF ME TO LET
SION DO ALL THE WORK ALONE.
( inhales deeply )
AND HERE I AM,
THE LAZY, CONTENTIOUS
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO LOATHE WORK
WITH A WHITE-HOT PASSION.
STILL...
IT'S WORTH IT TO SOLDIER ON.
- Lieral: RYNER.
- ( gasps )
WHAT THE HELL?
YOU CAN'T BE...
- TOO SLOW.
- ( Ryner groans )
- WELCOME BACK...
MY SON.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: AWESOME!
I'VE FINALLY MADE IT SOMEWHERE
THAT DOESN'T TOTALLY SUCK!
WAIT A SEC, WHERE AM I?
THIS LOOKS KINDA DANGEROUS.
NOT EXACTLY MY IDEA OF HEAVEN,
I GOTTA SAY. OH CRAP.
I'M REALLY IN
FOR IT NOW, AREN'T I?