- Keifer: AND IT CAME TO PASS
WHEN DESPITE HIS BITTER RESOLVE
THE BLACK HERO, WHO'D
TIRELESSLY PITTED HIMSELF
AGAINST THE WORLD'S
FILTH AND CORRUPTION
BUCKLED UNDER THE WEIGHT OF
HIS BURDEN, AND WAS SUBDUED.
- ( screams )
- Keifer:
BOUND INEXTRICABLY TO
THE DARKEST REGIONS
OF THE SOUTH,
SEALED THERE BY THE MAGIC OF
THE WORLD'S PROTECTOR GODDESS,
THE BLACK HERO LANGUISHED.
BUT A MONSTER NOT
UNLIKE HIMSELF
DWELLED IN THE FORGOTTEN
CORNERS OF THAT PRISON.
THE LONESOME DEVIL.
FOREVER ISOLATED FROM THE
SYMPATHY OF HIS FELLOW CREATURES
BY A POWER TOO
HIDEOUS TO FATHOM,
WANDERING THROUGH
A LIFE OF SOLITUDE AND REGRET.
- Sion: I WOULD BREAK
FREE OF THIS SEAL,
BUT LACK THE POWER TO DO SO.
I THROW MYSELF AT YOUR MERCY.
LET ME CONSUME
HALF OF YOUR BODY
THAT ITS STRENGTH
MAY RELEASE ME.
- Ryner: BECAUSE YOU ASK
AS ONE IN DIRE NEED,
I GIVE OF MYSELF FREELY.
I OFFER THIS BODY FOR
THE HONOR OF YOUR FRIENDSHIP.
THE FIRST I'VE EVER KNOWN.
- Keifer: PLEDGING HALF
OF HIS PHYSICAL FORM
TO THE BLACK HERO'S RELEASE,
THE DEMON KNOWN AS
ALL FORMULAS RENT ITSELF
INTO TWO DISTINCT ENTITIES
THE WEAVER OF ALL FORMULAS,
AND THE SOLVER OF ALL FORMULAS.
THE BLACK HERO GREEDILY DEVOURED
THE WEAVER AT ONCE,
AND ASSUMED THE INESTIMABLE
POWER CONTAINED THEREIN.
- ( theme song playing )
- Keifer: REINVIGORATED,
THE BLACK HERO RUTHLESSLY
GROUND AWAY AT THE WORLD
UNTIL IT WAS WORN DOWN
TO AN IRREDUCIBLE CORE.
AND THERE,
AT THE HEART OF THINGS,
DESPITE HIS NEWFOUND POWER,
HE DROWNED IN DESPAIR,
LONELINESS, PAIN,
ENDLESS NIGHT AND
THE WORST KIND OF HELL.
- Sion: I CAN'T BARE IT!
( screams )
HELP ME! I BEG OF YOU!
I WOULD DESTROY THE WORLD
TO SHED THIS AGONY.
I IMPLORE SOMEONE, ANYONE,
TO ASSUME THIS PAIN,
THIS UNYIELDING DARKNESS,
IN MY STEAD.
- Ryner: THEN I GIVE TO YOU
THE REMAINING HALF OF MY BODY.
THERE IS ROOM ENOUGH
HERE FOR NIGHT.
- Keifer: THE LONESOME DEVIL
HELD NO REGRET
FOR HIS RECKLESS VOW,
THOUGH THE COST WAS UNTHINKABLE.
BECAUSE IN HIS SACRIFICE,
IF ONLY FOR A MOMENT,
THE TINIEST SPARK OF SOMETHING
HE'D NEVER KNOWN FLICKERED.
TRUST.
MANY A WISE MAN MAINTAINS THAT
THE LONESOME DEVIL WAS A FOOL.
- ( exclaims )
- Keifer: IF THAT BE TRUE,
LITTLE HAS CHANGED.
- Claugh: IT'S NOT LIKE SION
TO BE OUT THIS LATE.
ESPECIALLY IF HE'S
GONE TO THE TROUBLE
OF DRAGGING THE TWO OF US IN.
- FIELD MARSHAL.
- WHAT IS IT, CALNE?
- I THINK I'VE GOT
A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
OF WHY HE CALLED US HERE.
JUST TAKE A LOOK
AT WHAT HE LEFT.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
ARE YOU REALLY CRYING?
- I AM NOT!
- OH YEAH? IT SURE
LOOKS THAT WAY.
- TRUST ME, IT'S THE RAIN.
- ( sighs )
SO, WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU INTEND
TO DO WITH ME NOW? SERIOUSLY.
WELL ALL RIGHT.
I FIGURED WE'D END UP LIKE
THIS ONE OF THESE DAYS.
SO IT'S NO BIG SURPRISE.
THAT'S KINDA HOW
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN, YOU KNOW?
WHEN THINGS GO WELL
I CAN'T LET 'EM BE.
I'M ALWAYS WAITING
FOR THE OTHER SHOE TO DROP.
IT GETS WORSE THE HAPPIER I GET.
BUT IT IS BACKED UP
BY EXPERIENCE.
SO, SION, OLD BUDDY...
YOU'RE, UH...
BENT ON KILLING ME, HUH?
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I HAVE TO.
- IT'S OKAY. I UNDERSTAND.
AT LEAST IT'S YOU, RIGHT?
I CAN IMAGINE WORSE
PEOPLE FOR THE JOB.
STILL, THOUGH,
I'VE GOTTA PASS.
BECAUSE I CARE
ABOUT YOU TOO MUCH
TO LET YOU GO THROUGH WITH IT.
I MEAN, C'MON.
IT'S A FOOL'S ERRAND ANYWAY.
STILL LOTS OF MONSTERS
LIKE ME OUT THERE.
THAT, AND I PROMISED THIS
TO SOMEONE ELSE.
I'VE ALREADY DECIDED
WHO GETS TO KILL ME.
- FERRIS?
- YEAH.
- I HAVE TO ADMIT, I'M JEALOUS.
BUT I HAVE NO ROOM TO COMPLAIN.
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH I HONORED
MY PROMISE TO YOU, NOW IS IT?
- YOU HAVE A POINT. EVEN SO,
I STILL CONSIDER YOU ONE OF
THE BEST FRIENDS I'VE EVER HAD.
- AND I, YOU.
- YOU STILL GONNA
GO THROUGH WITH IT?
- YES.
- YOUR MIND'S MADE UP THEN?
- IT IS.
- AND I CAN'T
PERSUADE YOU OTHERWISE?
- I'M AFRAID NOT, RYNER.
THIS ENDS TONIGHT. FOR GOOD.
- WELL I GOT NEWS FOR YOU,
SION. IT'S NOT OVER.
YOU CAN'T WIN AGAINST ME.
- ( rumbling )
- Sion: WE'LL SEE. NOW!
- ( groans )
WHAT I SEEK...
IS THUNDER! IZUCHI!
THE HELL IS THIS? NO! TELL ME
YOU DIDN'T RESORT TO THIS!
- SORRY.
I'VE DONE WHAT
NECESSITY REQUIRED OF ME.
- YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR DAMN MIND!
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THIS'LL DO OUR THE COUNTRY!
- DON'T PATRONIZE ME.
I'M PAINFULLY AWARE.
THESE DAYS, IT SEEMS
EXTREME MEASURES ARE CALLED FOR.
- BULLSHIT! YOU CARRIED OUT
EXPERIMENTS ON INNOCENT PEOPLE!
THERE'S NO EXCUSE!
YOU LET YOUR BURDEN
TURN YOU INTO A MONSTER!
YOU ARROGANT SON OF A BITCH!
WHY WOULDN'T YOU
LET US HELP YOU?
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
TAKE IT ALL ON YOURSELF!
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
BE A PART OF THIS!
WHY THE HELL COULDN'T YOU
LET ANY OF US IN?
GODDAMMIT, SION, YOU KNEW
WE WERE THERE FOR YOU!
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER! IZUCHI!
IZUCHI!
( yells )
( groans )
DAMN YOU, SION!
I REFUSE TO LET YOU DO THIS!
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH
SENSE IT MAKES TO YOU
IN THE STATE YOU'RE IN!
I DON'T CARE HOW HARD IT IS
FOR YOU TO SEE THE TRUTH!
HOW EASY IT IS FOR YOU TO CAVE
UNDER THE HOPELESSNESS!
IF YOU THINK I'M GOING
TO GIVE UP ON YOU,
YOU'RE IN FOR A RUDE AWAKENING!
- YOU'LL DIE.
BY MY HAND. TONIGHT.
- THE HELL I WILL.
- BY MY HAND...
- YOU WON'T KILL
YOUR BEST FRIEND!
SNAP THE HELL
OUT OF IT ALREADY.
SION!
- BY MY HAND. NO ONE ELSE'S.
- NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
I KNOW DAMN WELL YOU'RE CRYING,
YOU CAN'T BLAME IT ON THE RAIN.
I WON'T LET YOU DO THIS.
- RYNER...
I APPRECIATE IT.
BUT I'M DOING THIS FOR YOUR SAKE
FIRST AND FOREMOST, KNOW THAT.
REGARDLESS OF WHAT
BECOMES OF THE WORLD,
I HAVE TO SAVE YOU.
- ( grunting )
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
- IZUCHI!
- ( both yelling )
- ( whooshing )
- ( groans )
SION, PLEASE!
- THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE MISSED YOU,
MY DEAR, LONESOME DEVIL.
I'M IN YOUR DEBT FOR
WRENCHING ME FREE OF THE SEAL.
- SION!
( groans )
- THIS ISN'T YOU.
- THE TIME HAS COME, HASN'T IT?
I MUST CONSUME YOU. I MUST.
THE TIME HAS COME FOR YOU
TO WANDER FOR ETERNITY
THROUGH THE HELL
OF YOUR OWN MIND.
I MUST CONDEMN YOU TO THAT.
IF ONLY THERE WERE
ANOTHER WAY...
BUT COME NOW,
LET US FEAST.
THE WORLD AWAITS ITS SALVATION.
- I IMPLORE YOU TO STOP,
ANCIENT ONE.
THE TIME IS NOT YET RIPE
FOR WHAT YOU WOULD ACHIEVE.
- WHO ARE YOU? THE ALPHA?
NO, YOU CANNOT BE.
HINDER ME NOT, THEN.
I WOULD FEAST.
- I SAY AGAIN.
THE TIME IS NOT RIPE.
IF YOU COULD LOOK PAST
YOUR OWN DESIRE
SUCH WOULD BE PLAIN,
YE WEAVER OF ALL FORMULAS.
- INTERESTING. I DIDN'T
EXPECT YOU TO BREAK THROUGH.
I UNDERESTIMATED YOUR
EASE OF MOVEMENT ON THIS PLANE.
- PLEASE, PERSUADE HIM TO STOP.
PERSUADE HIM TO
RELEASE RYNER LUTE.
- I FEAR HIS HEART IS
RATHER SET ON HIS MEAL.
- PERHAPS. BUT IT IS
NOT YET THE HOUR.
HIS ROLE IS CRITICAL
AND IN HIS CURRENT STATE
THE WORLD WOULD BENEFIT NOTHING.
NO ONE'S SALVATION
WOULD BE SECURED.
NOT HIS. NOR YOURS.
NOR THE GIRL YOU
CARE SO MUCH FOR.
NO ONE.
- YOU HAVE A POINT.
SAGELY SPOKEN, MY LADY.
- THEN, YOU AGREE.
IT PLEASES ME TO KNOW
THAT YOU ARE STILL
POSSESSED OF SOME
SHRED OF REASON.
- MY REASON? IS IT REALLY YOUR
PLACE TO JUDGE SUCH A THING?
TRUTH BE TOLD, MY LADY,
IT WOULD PLEASE ME TO KNOW
THAT SOME SHRED REMAINED IN YOU.
THOUGH SION'S REASON IS HARDY,
IT DOESN'T STOOP TO BE
WHITTLED AWAY
BY SUCH HAPPENSTANCE.
THAT IS WHY I CHOOSE TO TARRY
BY HIS SIDE WHILE HE RULES.
THE ROAD RISES TO MEET HIM
AND HIS TREAD UPON IT IS TRUE.
( scoffs )
AND ALL ROADS LEAD TO HIS
BETRAYAL OF YOU, RYNER LUTE.
UNTHINKABLE MONSTER.
LONESOME DEVIL.
- ( gasps )
- BUT BY ALL MEANS,
UNTIL HIS PERFIDY CARVE ITSELF
IN STONE, PLAY THE ALLY,
DROWN HIS CONSCIENCE
IN THE LUKEWARM TIDE
OF YOUR IDEAS OF RIGHT.
REMAIN IGNORANT OF HIS PAIN,
AND SLEEP THE CHILDISH
IDLE OF THE NAIVE.
- Ryner: SION.
HEY. HEY, C'MON. WAKE UP.
I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME.
DON'T JUST SIT THERE
IN A DAZE. GET UP.
- WAIT, WHAT...
WHAT ON EARTH IS GOING ON?
- IT'S MORNING.
JUST SHAKE IT OFF ALREADY.
YOU'RE LUCKY I DIDN'T DUMP
COLD WATER ON YOU.
LEAVING ME TO SHOVEL
THROUGH ALL THIS CRAP
WHILE YOU GO SKIPPING
OFF TO DREAMLAND.
- UH, RIGHT.
HOW, UH, HOW LONG WAS I ASLEEP?
BE HONEST WITH ME.
- FOUR HOURS.
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
- NOPE.
- SO, THEN. IT WAS ALL
JUST A HORRIBLE NIGHTMARE.
- AH, IT WAS A BAD ONE, HUH?
- WELL, NOT THE WHOLE THING.
THERE WAS THIS...
NO, WAIT.
MAYBE THERE WASN'T.
- YOU DON'T EVEN
REMEMBER, DO YOU?
- I HAD A VIVID IMAGE
TILL A MOMENT AGO.
IT'S STARTING TO SLIP
AWAY FROM ME NOW,
BUT I DO REMEMBER THAT
IT WAS VERY UNPLEASANT.
- WELL THEN, I GUESS IT WAS
A GOOD THING I WOKE YOU UP
WHEN I DID, RIGHT?
- YES IT WAS. THANK YOU
VERY MUCH. YOU SAVED ME.
- YEAH, WELL.
IT DIDN'T SOUND ALL THAT BAD.
"OH WOW! JACKPOT! I'M
SURROUNDED BY BEAUTIFUL GIRLS
WHO'RE ITCHING TO
FULFILL MY EVERY WHIM!"
I FIGURED I'D LET YOU SLEEP.
WAKE ME UP FROM THE KINDA DREAM
I THOUGHT YOU WERE HAVING,
I'LL KICK YOUR BUTT.
- OH DEAR, MY SECRET
COMES OUT AT LAST.
- AH, DAMN IT!
DON'T GO ALONG WITH IT
WHEN I'M GIVING YOU GRIEF.
IT'S A HELLUVA LOT MORE FUN
WHEN YOU PUT UP A FIGHT.
- ( chuckles )
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PUT OUR NOSES
BACK TO THE GRINDSTONE?
- YOU AND YOUR WORK ETHIC.
ANYWAY, WHAT GRINDSTONE?
THE CRAP'S ALL BEEN SHOVELED
IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED.
- HUH?
- RYNER, YOU... YOU DIDN'T
DO THIS YOURSELF?
- I DID.
- SO YOU, YOU TOOK ON THE WHOLE
PILE WITHOUT TRYING TO WAKE ME?
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M NOT A SAINT.
I TRIED TO WAKE YOU UP AND YOU
WOULDN'T, SO, YOU KNOW...
- THANK YOU.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- NO, RYNER. THANK YOU.
- AW, GIVE IT A
REST ALREADY, HUH?
- SPEAKING OF, GO LIE
THE HELL DOWN!
- NO NEED FOR THAT ANYMORE.
LET'S GET A JUMP
ON THE NEXT BATCH.
- ( exclaims )
I HAVEN'T SLEPT
A FRIGGIN' WINK YET!
- ( laughs )
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
I KNEW THIS WASN'T REAL.
THE TIME HAS COME,
THERE'S NO DENYING IT.
I MUST SOLDIER ON, REGARDLESS.
THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT.
- ( breathing heavily )
DAMN YOU.
GET ON WITH IT.
END HIS LIFE RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
OR DOOM YOUR FRIEND
TO WALK THE EARTH FOR ETERNITY.
DO IT OR HE'LL
NEVER BE ABLE TO DIE.
WOULD YOU HAVE HIM WANDER
HIS OWN PERSONAL HELL FOREVER?
SPARE HIM!
SPARE HIM FROM THE DARKNESS!
FROM HIMSELF!
DAMN YOU!
I CAN'T BRING MYSELF TO!
GLOAT IN YOUR TRIUMPH
IF YOU WILL, BUT I CAN'T.
- SILENCE.
TRIUMPH BECOMES NEITHER
OF US IN THIS TRAGIC TURN.
- ( laughs ) OF COURSE
IT DOESN'T.
YOU AND I ARE THE SAME.
- WE ARE.
- I AM...
WE ARE SO LAMENTABLY WEAK.
- WE ARE, YET STILL
WE SOLDIER ON.
- BY BETRAYING OUR LOVED ONES?
BY SACRIFICING A FRIEND
ON THE PYRE OF OUR OWN LACK?
PLUNGING HIM INTO HELL
SO WE MAY INCH FORWARD?
- WE DO.
- IT'S UNCONSCIONABLE!
- IT IS.
- I CAN'T BEAR THIS.
- YOU CAN'T.
- AND YET, WE SOLDIER ON,
DESPITE MY INABILITY
TO KILL RYNER
OR AT THE VERY LEAST
GIVE HIM HIS FREEDOM.
- YOU ACTED ACCORDING
TO OUR NATURE.
- STOP PATRONIZING ME.
- STOP SHOULDERING THE BLAME.
THE CHOICE BEFORE YOU
WAS NO CHOICE...
- YOU KNOW NOTHING! NOTHING!
YOU RATIONALIZE OUR WEAKNESS!
- I WOULD DISAPPEAR
FROM THE WORLD.
- WOULD YOU?
- TAKE THIS BODY.
I GIVE THE REIGNS TO YOU.
I AM DONE WITH THIS STRUGGLE.
- VERY WELL.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
NEVER AGAIN NEED YOU
AGONIZE OVER A CHOICE
AS YOU DID THIS NIGHT.
INDEED, NEVER NEED YOU
AGONIZE OVER ANYTHING.
- FARE THEE WELL, DOUBT.
WE TWIST ABOUT INTERMINABLY,
BUT IN THE END WE
ALWAYS SOLDIER ON.
FAREWELL.
- ( groans )
- STAY BACK! TARRY HERE
UNDER PAIN OF EXECUTION!
- ( both scream )
- AFTER ALL THAT HE STILL
COULDN'T GO THROUGH WITH IT.
SO MUCH FOR THE COURAGE
OF HIS CONVICTIONS.
HEY! WHOEVER'S RUNNIN'
THIS JOINT
I GOT A COUPLE QUESTIONS
NEED ANSWERIN'.
HELLO?
- ( panting )
- OR, IF YOU'RE
LYING DOWN ON THE JOB,
I COULD JUST CHALLENGE
YOUR WORK ETHIC.
BECAUSE ON THAT SORE SUBJECT,
I LEARNED A THING OR
TWO FROM THE BEST.
I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT...
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
( exclaims )
- FERRIS?
- DO YOU REALIZE WHAT HELL
YOU'VE PUT ME THROUGH?
WHATEVER I MIGHT'VE DONE,
TRUST ME, I'M IN THE DARK...
- WAIT, WHAT THE?
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD.
( sniffling ) I WAS TOLD...
THEY ALL TOLD ME
THAT YOU WERE GONE.
THAT YOU WERE REALLY
AND TRULY DEAD. BUT I...
I NEVER BELIEVED IT. NEVER.
NOT EVEN... NOT EVEN WHEN
SION TOLD ME. I COULDN'T.
( crying )
- SO YOU SAW
THE OLD SLAVE-DRIVER.
- HE'S NOT HIMSELF ANYMORE.
AFTER HE TOLD ME YOU
WERE DEAD, HE JUST SMILED.
BUT THE LOOK IN HIS EYES...
IT WAS AS IF HE WANTED TO CRY.
I SCREAMED AT HIM.
I CALLED HIM A LIAR.
THEN HE SAID HE'D KILLED YOU.
AND STILL ALL HE
COULD DO WAS SMILE.
THEN HE TOLD ME TO LEAVE.
TO NEVER ASSOCIATE
WITH HIM AGAIN.
HE'S MARCHING THE ARMY
INTO IMPERIAL NELPHA.
- ( exclaims )
- HE LEADS THE CAMPAIGN
WITH SOLDIERS BORN OF
FORBIDDEN TECHNIQUES.
THE PEOPLE OF NELPHA ARE
ALL BEING SLAUGHTERED
LIKE LIVESTOCK.
AND THE CITIZENS HERE
ARE CHEERING IT ON
LIKE HE'S THEIR SAVIOR.
LIKE HE'S POISED
TO RULE THE WORLD
AND TRANSFORM IT INTO
THEIR PERSONAL SANCTUARY.
IT'S HIDEOUS.
THEY'VE ALL LOST THEIR MINDS.
THE NOBLES. SION. EVERYONE.
- IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
LOOK AT ME,
I'M MAKING YOU A PROMISE.
NONE OF THAT'S
YOUR PROBLEM ANYMORE.
- ( soldiers screaming )
- Man: THREE CHEERS
FOR THE HERO KING!
- DON'T LET HIM GET AWAY!
- LET'S GET THE HELL
OUT OF THE COUNTRY.
- YEAH, BUT THEN WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
WHATEVER'S DRIVING HIM
TO ACT LIKE THIS AND
FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO KNOCK SOME SENSE BACK
INTO THAT THICK SKULL OF HIS
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- Man 1: OVER THERE!
- Man 2: THAT'S HIM!
- HOLD IT!
- BEST OF LUCK TO YOU.
- LET'S MOVE!
- RIGHT!
- ( theme song playing )
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT, SION.
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING
YOU'VE PUT ME THROUGH,
I'M GRATEFUL.
BEFORE WE MET,
I WAS DEAD INSIDE.
SHUFFLING AIMLESSLY THROUGH
A KIND OF WAKING NIGHTMARE.
I WAS A MONSTER. I DIDN'T
DARE LET PEOPLE IN
OR ALLOW MYSELF TO
GET CLOSE TO THEM.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO
LET MYSELF LOVE THEM.
THERE WAS NO POINT GOING ON.
LIFE FOR ME WAS NO LIFE AT ALL.
BUT YOU SWOOPED IN AND
BROKE THROUGH THE BARRIERS.
YOU SAVED ME. AND FOR THAT,
EVEN THOUGH I PROBABLY
CAME OFF LOOKING ANYTHING BUT.
DEEP DOWN I WAS THANKFUL.
- WHAT I SEEK ARE
THE BURNING FIELDS! KURENAI!
- PINK TRESSES?
- YOU DON'T THINK?
- I DO.
- Ryner: I INTEND TO RETURN
THE FAVOR ONE DAY,
LIKE IT OR NOT.
SO... I MAY NOT HAVE THE
FIRST CLUE ABOUT THE KIND OF
EVIL CRAP YOU'VE GOTTEN
YOURSELF MIXED UP IN.
BUT I'M COMING FOR YOU ANYWAY.
I'M COMING TO SAVE YOU.
- ( chuckles )
SALLY...
FORTH!
- Ryner: I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
WHAT IT TAKES, EITHER.
OR HOW MUCH STRENGTH I'M GONNA
NEED TO FACE YOU AGAIN.
I'LL SUMMON EVERY OUNCE I'VE GOT
AND THEN SOME. FOR YOU.
SO MY ADVICE? BE READY
FOR THE DAY I FIND YOU.
'CAUSE YOU MIGHT THINK
YOU REGRET NOT FINISHING ME OFF
WHEN YOU HAD THE CHANCE,
BUT TRUST ME, NOT NEARLY
AS MUCH AS YOU'RE GOING TO.
AS ALONE AS YOU I KNOW
YOU WANT TO BE,
I REFUSE TO LET YOU BROOD.
I REFUSE TO LET YOU HEAP ALL
THE WORLD'S PROBLEMS ON YOURSELF
LIKE YOU'RE THE ONLY HUMAN
BEING WHO CAN HANDLE THEM.
I'M COMING FOR YOU, SION.
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO,
I'LL MAKE YOU SEE BEYOND
A SHADOW OF A DOUBT
THAT I'M THE BEST DAMN FRIEND
YOU'VE EVER HAD.
- ALL YOU HAVE TO DO,
IS WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
- Ryner: WE ALL HAVE TO
SOLDIER ON. IT'S WHAT WE DO.
AND MARK MY WORDS, SION...
I AM NEVER, EVER,
GIVING UP ON YOU.
PERIOD.
ALL RIGHT, THEN? SHALL WE?
- WE SHALL.
LEAD ON.