- ( Brophs laughs )
ASTAL THINKS HE'S LEADING
HIS MEN TO A SAFE GROUND.
BUT FIFTY MAGIC KNIGHTS
ARE WAITING THERE FOR THEM.
HE'S A TRUSTING FOOL.
HE THINKS HE CAN BARE
HIS FANGS AT A PRINCE
AND COME AWAY WITHOUT
A SCRATCH, DOES HE?
( groaning )
- YOU'RE A VERY, VERY SICK MAN!
DON'T YOU DARE LAUGH AT
MY SISTER WITH THAT BRUTE LOOK
ON YOUR FACE! JERK!
- THAT MEANS THE PRINCE...
BROTHER.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, SISTER?
( mumbling ) I CAN'T BREA--
- ALWAYS PROTECTING HER,
AREN'T YOU?
FERRIS, JOBS SHOULD BE
FINISHED THOROUGHLY.
TO LET SUCH A PARASITE LIVE
WOULD SULLY THE
ERIS FAMILY NAME,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- WHAT'S YOUR END GAME?
IS THE PRINCE BEHIND THIS?
IS IT TRUE
THAT SION IS ALSO A PRINCE?
- THE ERIS FAMILY SERVES
ONLY THE KING OF ROLAND.
THE TRUE KING.
- THE KING.
- WE MUST DISCERN
WHETHER YOUNG SION
WILL MAKE A SUITABLE RULER.
CAN HE, FOR INSTANCE,
SURVIVE A CONFRONTATION
WITH A TROOP OF
50 MAGIC KNIGHTS?
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- I COULD DO IT MYSELF, EASILY.
- SION ISN'T YOU.
- THAT IS TRUE.
HE'S DEFINITELY NOT ME,
BUT THERE ARE UNTOLD DEPTHS
TO THE MAN YET.
FROM THE MOMENT
YOU AND SION MET,
YOU HAVE BEEN
SAVING HIS LIFE, SISTER.
DON'T YOU FIND THAT FASCINATING?
- NOT PARTICULARLY, NO.
- ( theme song playing)
- Sion: ALL HANDS SHOULD BE
SETTING UP CAMP.
WATER IS OUR FIRST PRIORITY.
EVERYONE ELSE,
TAKE CARE OF THE TENTS.
- I'LL TAKE WATER DUTY.
- Student: MAKE IT QUICK,
WOULD YA?
- HEY, YOU WANNA GET OFF YOUR
ASS AND LEND A HAND HERE?
- HUH? NO,
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A PAIN.
- HEY, KIEFER!
WOULD YOU TALK TO YOUR BUDDY
RYNER HERE, HE'S USELESS.
- OH, MY STOMACH, AH.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
I WASN'T LISTENING.
- ( chuckles ) WE NEED YOU.
THERE'S A LAZY BUM OVER THERE
WHO SAYS HE'S NOT GONNA LIFT
A FINGER TO HELP US SET UP CAMP.
- YOU KNOW RYNER WILL ONLY
LISTEN TO YOU,
WILL YOU TALK
TO HIM FOR US?
- ( grunting )
- TALK, YOU. TELL US
WHAT THE HELL YOU DID TO KIEFER.
- NOT A THING.
- WELL, SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT
HERSELF TODAY SO EXPLAIN THAT.
- COME ON, GUYS, WISE UP!
I MEAN, WE'RE ABOUT TO
FIGHT IN A WAR!
WHEN YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN
TO THE PERSON YOU LOVE,
OF COURSE YOU GET ANXIOUS.
DID KIEFER SAY ANYTHING UNUSUAL
TO YOU THIS MORNING
BEFORE WE HEADED OUT?
- AND THERE'S YOU.
YOU'RE THE PERSON
I'M MOST AFRAID FOR.
- NICE!
- ( exclaims ) WHAT'S NICE?
- WELL, I'M OFF
TO FETCH SOME WATER NOW!
- AND FAHLE AND I ARE GONNA
HEAD INTO THE WOODS
TO FIND SOME FIREWOOD.
- WHAT ABOUT THE TENTS?
- YOU TAKE CARE OF THAT
WHILE WE'RE GONE, OKAY?
- UH, SO! NICE WEATHER
WE'RE HAVING TODAY.
- GOOD LUCK, RYNER.
YOU'LL NEED IT.
- WHATEVER. I'M JUST GONNA LAY
HERE AND TAKE A GOOD LONG NAP.
- RYNER.
- HMM?
- WOULD YOU RUN AWAY WITH ME?
IF I LEFT NOW?
WE... WE COULD JUST
RUN OFF TOGETHER.
FORGET ABOUT SION
AND STICK WITH ME INSTEAD.
- WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU, KIEFER?
- I JUST... I CARE ABOUT YOU.
I THINK I'VE ALWAYS
CARED ABOUT YOU.
EVEN THOUGH I KNEW
IT WAS HOPELESS,
I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
BUT YOU DON'T FEEL
THE SAME WAY, DO YOU?
- ( laughs ) OH!
YOU'RE JUST PULLING MY LEG!
YOU REALLY HAD ME GOING
FOR A SECOND THERE.
- YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS PRETTY RIDICULOUS
FOR ME TO THINK
THAT WE COULD
EVER HAVE ANYTHING.
- HEY, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
- I JUST COULDN'T FACE IT.
THE THOUGHT OF
YOU DYING OUT HERE LIKE THAT...
I'M SO SORRY,
I WANTED TO PROTECT YOU, RYNER.
BUT NOW I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO BEAR THE SPIRIT BEAST
OF LIGHT WHICH SLEEPS
WITHIN THE ATMOSPHERE!
GOODBYE, RYNER.
- TAHILE?
- ( students clamoring )
- MIGHT AS WELL NOT EVEN BOTHER
RUNNING, ROLAND SCUM!
- THINK YOU CAN ESCAPE
THE MAGIC KNIGHTS?
- WHAT'S HAPPENING? ROLL!
- AN ENEMY RAID BY ESTABUL, SIR!
KNIGHTS IN RED ARMOR
ARE ATTACKING THE CAMP.
THEY SEEM TO BE COMING AT US
FROM EVERY ANG--
- THEY'RE WEARING RED ARMOR.
THE MAGIC KNIGHTS OF ESTABUL!
ALL SOLDIERS RETREAT!
TAKE COVER IN THE WOODS.
FALL BACK AND REGROUP!
- Ryner: SION!
- THIS EVERYONE?
- YEAH. THEY GOT TAHILE.
HE WAS JUST ON HIS WAY
TO FETCH WATER FOR THE CAMP.
HE WAS SO SURE IF WE STUCK
WITH YOU WE WERE SAFE,
HE WASN'T CAREFUL.
- DAMN. AND KIEFER?
- NOT SURE ABOUT HER.
- I THINK IT WOULD BE BEST
IF WE SPLIT UP.
TONY, YOU AND FAHLE GO ON AHEAD.
WE'LL DO OUR BEST
TO HOLD THEM OFF HERE.
- Fahle: SION!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT US. NOW GO!
THERE MAY STILL BE SURVIVORS,
INCLUDING KIEFER.
- OH, AND YOU'RE GOING TO
SAVE THEM ALL, IS THAT IT?
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
- SO IT WOULD SEEM.
DID YOU SEE THEM?
- NO
- GO ON! LET'S SEE HOW FAST
YOU CAN RUN, YOU LITTLE BRATS!
- YEAH, IT'S NO FUN IF YOU JUST
STAND THERE AND WAIT FOR IT.
- READY? I OFFER UP
THIS CONTRACT
TO BEAR THE SPIRIT BEAST
OF LIGHT WHICH SLEEPS
WITHIN THE ATMOSPHERE!
- HE'S USING MAGIC TO GO FASTER!
I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO BEAR THE SPIRIT BEAST
OF LIGHT WHICH SLEEPS
WITHIN THE ATMOSPHERE!
ARE YOU OKAY?
- YES.
THAT MAGIC, HOW DID YOU DO IT?
- YOU KNOW HOW I DID IT.
YOU ALSO KNOW I DIDN'T
WANT TO USE IT, THOUGH.
DAMN IT!
- I WAS RIGHT, WASN'T I?
- YOU! HOW IS IT
THAT YOU KNOW OUR ESTABUL MAGIC?
- UNLESS YOU'RE--
- YES! OF COURSE!
HE'S AN ALPHA STIGMA!
- THE EYES OF DESTRUCTION!
HE HAS THEM!
- NO! I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO UNLEASH THE MAG--
- STOP! WE CAN'T USE
ANY MAGIC, FOOL!
- I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO UNLEASH THE MAGIC BEAST
THAT DANCES THROUGH THE SKY!
- ( both scream )
- YOU BASTARD!
IF YOU'D USED THAT POWER SOONER
NOBODY ELSE WOULD'VE HAD
TO DIE TODAY!
THERE WERE ONLY THREE
HERE THIS TIME,
THAT'S WHY WE'RE ALIVE.
I HAVEN'T USED THAT POWER
IN SEVEN YEARS.
I CAN'T CONTROL IT.
- WHAT AN INTERESTING SHOW
YOU PUT ON FOR US.
RARE TO SEE A MONSTER LIKE THIS
IN ACTION.
THAT'S RIGHT, BOY,
COWER BEFORE ME,
SO I CAN WATCH WHILE YOU SUFFER.
YOU ARE THE ALPHA STIGMA, RIGHT?
SHOW ME ONE OF YOUR TRICKS.
OR DON'T YOU GET IT YET?
THESE ARE THE ONLY TWO LEFT.
WE KILLED THE REST.
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
- THEY'RE ALL DEAD?
- NO FIGHT IN YOU AFTER HEARING
THAT? WHERE'S YOUR SPIRIT?
HEY!
- ( groans )
- ( screaming ) No! No!
- Ryner: STOP. PLEASE. STOP!
- Ryner's inner voice:
DEATH IS ALL AROUND YOU.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER, DOES IT?
- YOU'RE WRONG.
- AM I?
- YOU'RE WRONG!
- THE WORLD IS YOURS TO TAKE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS OPEN UP.
RELEASE IT AND KILL.
- ( screaming )
- UNTIL EVERYTHING DISAPPEARS
BEFORE YOUR EYES.
- ( Reyner screams )
( laughs menacingly )
- WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
IS HE ASLEEP?
- WEAKLING. YOUR MOLECULES
WILL SCATTER LIKE SAND.
- HE'S GONE. WHAT DID YOU DO?
- MONSTER. DEVIL. GOD. HERO.
CALL ME WHAT YOU WILL.
( laughs )
- MONSTER! I'LL FINISH YOU!
I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO UNLEASH THE SPIRIT
WHICH ENVELOPS THE AIR!
- ANALYZE EXISTENCE.
AND RELEASE.
- HE'S A GOD. NO! PLEASE!
- FIRST COMES DESTRUCTION.
I CREATE NOTHING.
FORGIVE NOTHING. SAVE NOTHING.
I JUST ERASE. COMPLETELY.
- Knight: MONST--
- SHATTER. COLLAPSE.
BREAK. AND DISAPPEAR.
I FEEL IT.
MY POWER.
THE CONTRACT IS DIFFERENT.
ERASE EVERYTHING.
- ( grunts) NO, RYNER.
PLEASE DON'T.
- Sion: STOP THIS.
- YOU'RE DANGEROUS.
YOU HAVE TO DIE.
MY EYES! THEY'RE CLOSING!
- PLEASE.
- NO.
DON'T CLOSE...
- CLOSE THEM!
- YOU ARE POWERLESS.
( groans )
- ( Kiefer sobs )
- RYNER! HEY!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
RYNER!
- Ryner: NOT AGAIN.
- ( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
- Sion: REINFORCEMENTS?
- Ryner: WHY?
- ( Kiefer continues crying )
- ( people cheering )
- ( Reyner groans )
- Militant: ALL RIGHT!
- ( scoffs ) Had enough,
monster?
- WISHING YOU HAD BEEN SMART
AND STAYED SHUT AWAY
IN THAT ACADEMY
LIKE YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO DO?
- IS KIEFER ALIVE?
THAT'S ALL I REALLY WANNA KNOW.
- SHE'S A PRISONER HERE,
JUST LIKE YOU.
- AND WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
SHE'D EVER COME BACK?
YEARS AGO HER OLDER SISTER WAS
KILLED IN AN INTELLIGENCE RAID.
THE OTHER TWO WERE REEDUCATED
TO ENSURE LOYALTY TO ROLAND.
- WE DECIDED TO KEEP HER
YOUNGER SISTER TO MAKE SURE
SHE NEVER FORGOT HER TRAINING.
- OKAY, WAIT A SECOND, WOULDN'T
IT JUST BE EASIER TO SAY
YOU TOOK HER YOUNGER SISTER
HOSTAGE OR SOMETHING?
- SHE'S JUST AS FOOLISH AS YOU.
WE KILLED THE SISTER AGES AGO.
AND WHAT DID WE GET OUT OF HER?
NOTHING. THE ASTAL BRAT LIVES,
AFTER ALL THAT.
- OH, OKAY, SO HE WAS
YOUR TARGET ALL ALONG.
- AND DO YOU KNOW THE KIND OF
PEOPLE WE'RE IN TROUBLE WITH,
HAVING FAILED
TO ELIMINATE THAT TARGET?
- IS THAT WHY
YOU'VE GOT ME IN HERE?
SO YOU'D HAVE SOMEONE WHINE
AND MOAN TO?
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH, MONSTER.
- ( Ryner groans )
THAT ONE ACTUALLY
HURT A LITTLE BIT.
- ARE YOU MOCKING ME,
DO YOU DARE?
- YOU'RE THE ONE
DOING THE MOCKING HERE.
NOT THAT I'M NOT USED TO IT,
OF COURSE, I AM.
BUT STILL, I THINK I'VE HAD
ABOUT ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD
AND PUT ME IN MY CELL
BEFORE I DROP DEAD OF MOCKERY?
- IF YOU COME QUIETLY
AND DO NOT ATTEMPT TO ESCAPE,
THE KING IS WILLING TO GRANT YOU
ONE REQUEST IN RETURN.
- SURE IS TEMPTING TO ASK THAT
YOU STOP TORTURING ME.
WAIT. HANG ON.
- ( gate opens )
- KIEFER.
IF YOU KEEP TAKING AFTERNOON
NAPS, YOUR GRADES'LL DROP.
- WAIT, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
RYNER, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- UH, IT'S KINDA HARD
TO EXPLAIN. THIS PLACE S--
- IF YOU SAY THIS PLACE SUCKS,
I SWEAR I'M GOING TO PUNCH YOU.
- I WON'T SAY IT!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HIT ME, OKAY?
I JUST GOT THE BLEEDING TO STOP.
- YEAH, WHY ARE YOU
SO BANGED UP?
- FORGET ABOUT THAT FOR NOW.
THERE'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO
TELL YOU, AND IT ISN'T GOOD.
YOUR LITTLE SISTER
ISN'T REALLY A HOSTAGE.
KIEFER, THEY TOOK HER LIFE
A LONG TIME AGO.
- HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT?
I SEE! YOU'RE ANOTHER PAWN!
YOU'RE ONE OF THEM, TOO, AREN'T
YOU? THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON!
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT?
HOW DARE YOU COME HERE AND
TELL ME MY SISTER IS DEAD?
YOU THINK I WANT TO HEAR
THAT FROM YOU?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN?
HAVE YOU BEEN LAUGHING
ALL THIS TIME?
LIKE WHEN I TOLD YOU
THAT I CARED ABOUT YOU.
YOU MUST HAVE THOUGHT
I WAS SUCH A FOOL!
( cries ) THERE WAS ALWAYS
A POSSIBILITY SHE WASN'T ALIVE.
I KNEW THAT.
BUT WHAT COULD I DO?
I COULDN'T BE SURE SO I...
- WHY DO YOU THINK WE HAVE WARS?
I CERTAINLY DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
I'VE NEVER CARED WHO OWNS
THE LAND OR HAS ALL THE POWER.
YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT I DO CARE ABOUT,
HOW SOON DO I GET TO
TAKE MY NEXT NAP, THAT'S IT.
TONY, TAHILE AND FAHLE LAID DOWN
THEIR LIVES FOR NOTHING.
- WHY ARE YOU SAYING THIS?
- THE PEOPLE WHO START
WARS ARE THE ONES
WHO WANT SOMETHING FROM IT.
AND THE PEOPLE WHO SUFFER
ARE THE ONES THEY CON
INTO FIGHTING FOR THEM.
SO THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY OUT.
UNLIKE SION,
I'VE NEVER HAD ANY REAL
INTEREST IN TRYING TO CHANGE
THE WAY THINGS ARE DONE
IN THIS COUNTRY.
I JUST WANT A QUIET PLACE
TO SLEEP THE DAY AWAY,
SOMEWHERE WHERE I
CAN LIVE MY LIFE
WITHOUT HURTING
ANYBODY ELSE.
MY HEAD! KIEFER.
WHAT KIND OF NONSENSE
HAVE I BEEN SPOUTING?
- Guard: ALMOST READY IN HERE?
- OH, RIGHT! I ALMOST FORGOT.
KIEFER, COME HERE A SECOND
- WHY?
- JUST WATCH YOUR HEAD, OKAY?
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR RELEASE
AND FOR MY IMPRISONMENT.
- WHAT?
- ALL RIGHT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE
THAT THE TERMS OF YOUR REQUEST
HAVE BEEN MET?
- YEP. PERFECTLY. THANKS.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
- WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
- Guard: MY ORDERS.
I AM TO ENSURE THE RELEASE
OF KIEFER KNOLLES IN RETURN
FOR THE VOLUNTARY IMPRISONMENT
OF RYNER LUTE.
AND I HAVE TO SAY, MAN,
YOU MUST BE SOME KINDA BADASS
TO MAKE DIRECT DEALS
WITH THE MILITARY.
- NOT REALLY. NO. I WISH.
- WHY WOULD YOU AGREE
TO SOMETHING LIKE THIS
AFTER WHAT I DID?
I BETRAYED EVERYONE
IN OUR REGIMENT.
THEY'RE ALL DEAD NOW
BECAUSE OF ME!
- PEOPLE DON'T KILL PEOPLE,
REALLY, MONSTERS DO.
MONSTERS LIKE WAR, HUNGRY
NOBLES, AND GREEDY KINGDOMS.
AND MONSTERS LIKE... LIKE ME.
NOT YOU, KIEFER.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IN HERE, I CAN RULE ON HIGH
AS KING OF THE AFTERNOON NAPS.
AND YOU CAN BE FREE.
- YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I WAS WRONG ABOUT
WHY I FELL FOR YOU, RYNER.
I THOUGHT IT WAS BECAUSE
YOU WERE SO LAZY,
THAT I DIDN'T HAVE TO TRY.
I COULD JUST BE MYSELF.
BUT I WAS WRONG.
IT WAS BECAUSE YOU'RE KIND.
AND STRONG. SO STRONG.
YOU'RE NO MONSTER.
I PROMISE YOU.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU THINK.
YOU SAVED ME AND I'LL--
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU.
SOMEDAY I'LL FIND A WAY TO--
I'M READY.
- Guard: COMING OUT.
- ( gates closing )
- I'M GLAD THAT'S DONE.
I THOUGHT
SHE WOULD SUFFOCATE ME.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU'RE HURT.
- YEAH. ONLY A LITTLE.
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING,
VOLUNTEERING TO BE
IMPRISONED INDEFINITELY?
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT WAS
FOR ME TO GET IN TO SEE YOU?
- YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE
BOTHERED, YOU KNOW.
THERE'S ACTUALLY NOT MUCH
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
STAYING IN A PRISON CELL
AND GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
WHAT'S THIS?
- TONIGHT AFTER DARK, A HORSE
WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
IN THE NORTHERN WOODS.
- THAT WOULD MAKE YOU A SUSPECT,
IF I WERE TO TRY AND ESCAPE.
- NO ONE'S BOLD ENOUGH
TO INCARCERATE A WAR HERO
IN THIS POLITICAL CLIMATE.
- THIS KIND OF STUNT
COULD DO AWAY
WITH THAT 'HERO'
TITLE FOR GOOD.
- I'VE DONE OKAY
FOR MYSELF SO FAR.
- THAT'S PRETTY BIG
TALK, THOUGH.
I MEAN, FOR SOMEONE
PEOPLE KEEP TRYING TO KILL.
- PLEASE. RYNER.
THINK ABOUT THIS.
IT MAYBE THE ONLY CHANCE
WE HAVE.
I CAN'T GUARANTEE THAT
I'LL BE ABLE TO BRIBE MY WAY IN
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
MY FRIENDS ARE DEAD.
WE'RE AT WAR AGAIN.
AND I'M NO CLOSER TO BEING KING.
I'VE FAILED ON SO MANY LEVELS
UP TO THIS POINT.
RYNER.
- ESCAPING'S A PAIN IN THE ASS.
BESIDES, WHO KNOWS WHAT WOULD
HAPPEN TO EITHER OF US
IF WE ACTUALLY SUCCEEDED.
- BUT THINK... THINK ABOUT
WHAT THIS WOULD MEAN.
IT WOULD MEAN I GET ALL
THE AFTERNOON NAPS I WANT.
- WHAT DO NAPS ACCOMPLISH?
- I'LL GET BACK TO YOU,
AFTER I GET A LITTLE SLEEP.
- RYNER!
- Guard: TIME'S UP.
ARE YOU READY TO GO, SIR?
- WELL, I'VE GOTTA GET BACK
TO BEING LOCKED UP NOW.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
A ROOF AND THREE MEALS A DAY
ISN'T SUCH A RAW DEAL.
GOOD LUCK, SION.
- YES, YOU, TOO, FRIEND.
THIS IS IT.
I'VE LOST EVERYTHING.
BUT I'LL NEVER LOSE
MY WAY AGAIN.
I PROMISE YOU THAT, RYNER.
- IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME,
ISN'T IT?
WAR NEVER CHANGES.
IT ALWAYS SUCKS.
WHY WOULD ANYONE EVER CHOOSE
TO BE A PART OF ONE?
I DON'T THINK I'LL EVER BE ABLE
TO UNDERSTAND THOSE PEOPLE.
- Guard: LIGHTS OUT!
- GOTTA SAY, THIS WAS
A FULL DAY, ALL TOLD.
GOOD BET TOMORROW
WON'T BE, THOUGH.
OH, WELL,
SO I'VE GOT SOME FREE TIME.
ALL THE FREE TIME
I COULD EVER ASK FOR.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: YOU KNOW WHAT SUCKS?
WORKING ALL DAY, STRUGGLING.
I FIGURED IF I JUST SLEPT,
NOTHING COULD GO WRONG.
AND I WAS OKAY WITH THAT.
BUT IT COULDN'T LAST.