- Ferris: IS THAT IT?
IT DOES MAKE SENSE.
IT'S ISOLATED WHICH WOULD
ALLOW FOR A VARIETY
OF NEFARIOUS ACTIVITIES.
- YES, I SUPPOSE.
- ( groans )
- KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN, PLEASE.
LEST AN ARROW REMOVES IT
FROM YOUR BODY.
- YEAH, GOOD CALL. THIS IS BAD.
MAGIC KNIGHTS OF RUNA.
( gasps )
- ( theme song playing )
- THE KING HAS ISSUED AN EDICT
PROCLAIMING THAT HE SHALL PAY
TRIBUTE TO THE NOBILITY
BY GRANTING THEM PROMOTIONS.
BUT, FRIENDS, THAT'S NOT ALL.
LET ME ASSURE YOU,
THE BENEVOLENCE OF HIS MAJESTY
DOES NOT END WITH THE NOBLES.
LORD ASTAL INTENDS
TO UTILIZE THE SKILLS
OF EVERY ABLE-BODIED CITIZEN
BY GRANTING US POSTS.
- ( cheering )
- JUST WHEN I THOUGHT WE
STOOD ON THE VERGE
OF BRINGING HIM TO HEEL,
THE MAN PULLS AN
EGREGIOUS STUNT LIKE THIS!
- HE, A STAIN ON OUR
NATION'S HONOR,
MOCKS US WITH HIS INSOLENCE!
- THE KING'S REALLY
PULLING OUT ALL THE STOPS.
- I KNOW, FROM
REAR ADMIRAL TO FIELD MARSHAL,
LOOKS LIKE CLAUGH'S MOVING UP
IN THIS WORLD, ISN'T HE?
- WHAT IS THE MEANING Of
MAKING ME FIELD MARSHAL?
- ARE YOU UNSATISFIED
WITH THIS?
YOU'RE AWARE THE ONLY POSITION
HIGHER IS HIGH MARSHAL?
- DON'T MAKE THIS ABOUT
SOMETHING IT'S NOT.
THE PROMOTIONS THEMSELVES
AREN'T THE ISSUE.
IT'S THE POLITICAL
RAMIFICATIONS BEHIND THE EDICT.
- FORGIVE US IF WE SEEM
UNGRATEFUL, YOUR GRACE.
HOWEVER, BEING YOUR LOYAL
AND TRUE SUBJECTS,
WE FEEL IT OUR SWORN DUTY
TO WARN YOU THAT
THIS ACTION IS ILL-ADVISED.
- IF MISPERCEIVED AS
PROVOCATION BY YOUR ENEMIES,
YOU RUN THE RISK OF
STOKING FURTHER IRE
IN THOSE WHO
WOULD SUPPLANT YOU.
YOU WILL PLAY
RIGHT INTO THEIR HATRED, SIRE.
- WELL, I'M AT A LOSS.
I OFFER YOU A PROMOTION,
AND YOU COMPLAIN.
IS YOUR AMBITION SO SMALL?
- I RESENT THAT
IMPLICATION, MY LORD.
WE TRADE NOT OUR LOYALTY
FOR THE PROMISE OF RANK
BUT RATHER STAND BY YOUR SIDE
BECAUSE YOU INSPIRE US.
WE STAND BY YOU
BECAUSE WE WISH TO AID YOU
IN BRINGING TO FRUITION
YOUR VISION FOR ROLAND'S FUTURE.
- BUT OF COURSE, LORD GNUBUL.
AND WHAT IF I WERE TO
TELL YOU THIS EDICT
PLAYS AN INTEGRAL ROLE
IN MY VISION FOR THE FUTURE?
- WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO ACCEPT IT THEN?
- WELL, I...
- I'M ASSUMING YOU ALL
HAVE HEARD
OF THE NATION OF
GASTARK, HAVE YOU NOT?
- YES, I'VE A VAGUE IDEA OF IT.
IT'S A SMALL COUNTRY
ON THE NORTHERN END
OF THE CONTINENT, ISN'T IT?
- Sion: CORRECT.
I TRUST, THEN, THAT YOU KNOW
OF THE NATION OF STOHL?
- OF COURSE, YOUR MAJESTY.
IT'S THE MIGHTIEST AND
MOST PROMINENT KINGDOM
ON THE MENORIS CONTINENT.
- Sion: WITH AN EVER-GROWING
POPULATION,
STOHL'S MILITARY MIGHT IS
ROUGHLY FIVE TIMES OUR OWN.
YET, ACCORDING TO A RECENT
INTELLIGENCE DISPATCH,
OVER TWO THIRDS OF THEIR
TERRITORY IS CURRENTLY
BEING OCCUPIED BY GASTARK.
- WHAT?
- Noa: UNBELIEVABLE!
HOW COULD THE MIGHTY FORCES
OF STOHL FALL SO EASILY?
- STOHL IS ONLY THE BEGINNING.
OTHERS HAVE FALLEN AND BECOME
SUBJECT TO THEM AS WELL.
THE TRUE EXTENT OF
THE INVASION IS UNKNOWN.
IT'S RATHER FAR AWAY, AFTER ALL.
- Gnubul: INDEED IT IS.
FROM A GEOGRAPHIC STANDPOINT,
GASTARK POSES NO THREAT TO US.
A FULL-SCALE INVASION OF ROLAND
WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE.
- YES. GASTARK
MAY NOT COME TO US.
BUT THE FALLOUT WILL.
FEELING PRESSURE FROM GASTARK,
NATIONS WILL BE COMPELLED
TO INCREASE THEIR MILITARY MIGHT
AND THE FIGHTING COULD VERY WELL
END UP ON OUR DOORSTEP.
WE'RE NOT IMMUNE.
TIME'S OF THE ESSENCE, FRIENDS.
THE DAYS OF CIVIL STRIFE
AND INFIGHTING
CAN NO LONGER PREVAIL.
THAT SAID, FROAUDE HAS
TENDERED A PLAN OF ACTION.
HE PROPOSES TO SET A TRAP
FOR THE NOBLES WHO OPPOSE ME,
AND PURGE THEM ALL
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
- PURGE THEM ALL, HUH? WOMEN,
CHILDREN, AND NOBLES, TOO?
MY KING, I BEG OF YOU,
IN ALL HUMILITY,
DO NOT CONSIDER THIS PROPOSAL!
- I'M SORRY, CLAUGH.
I BELIEVE THIS IS THE PATH
ROLAND MUST TAKE.
THIS IS A TIME FOR UNITY,
NOT FOR DIVISION.
WITH THAT SAID,
I AM THE SOVEREIGN KING
OF EVERY CREATURE
THAT DWELLS
WITHIN OUR BORDERS.
EVEN MY ENEMIES, WHO WOULD
SUPPLANT ME AND SEE ME DEAD,
ARE ROLAND'S CHILDREN.
THEY ARE THE CITIZENS
OF THIS GREAT NATION.
AS SUCH, THEY TOO
DESERVE MY PROTECTION.
I WISH TO SAVE THEIR LIVES,
EVEN IF JUST A FEW OF THEM.
THIS IS MY DREAM!
TO UNIFY THIS LAND,
WITHOUT BLOODSHED!
SO YOU SEE, THIS IS WHY
I'M CARRYING OUT
SUCH AN EXTREME MEASURE.
ANY NOBLE WISHING TO
PLEDGE HIS LOYALTY TO ME
SHALL BE A FRIEND TO THE CROWN
AND THE CROWN TO HIM.
TOGETHER WE SHALL WORK
TO FORGE THE BONDS OF UNITY
THAT WILL USHER ROLAND
INTO THE FUTURE.
BUT SHOULD THEY CHOOSE
THE PATH OF OPPOSITION...
THEY CHOOSE THE WAY TO DEATH.
REMEMBER, FRIENDS,
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
THIS COUNTRY CANNOT
FALL TO RUIN.
I WON'T ALLOW IT.
WHO AMONG YOU WILL PLEDGE
TO STAND BY MY SIDE?
- FOR THE GLORY OF ROLAND,
I AM AT YOUR SERVICE,
YOUR MAJESTY.
- All: FOR THE GLORY
OF ROLAND,
I AM AT YOUR SERVICE,
YOUR MAJESTY.
- QUELL THE NOBLES
WITH HONEYED WORDS.
WHEN THEIR GUARD'S DOWN,
PURGE THEM IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
I EXPECTED THAT
YOU WOULD ULTIMATELY
ACCEPT MY PROPOSITION,
BUT YOUR BENEVOLENCE
WAS QUITE SURPRISING.
YOU WISH TO SAVE THEIR LIVES,
EVEN IF ONLY A HANDFUL?
ISN'T THAT NICE?
YOUR HEART'S PURE,
BUT YOUR MIND, NAIVE.
SURELY YOU KNOW
HOW THIS WILL END.
OR, PERHAPS YOU'VE
CONVINCED YOURSELF
THAT YOUR ENEMIES
WILL EMBRACE YOU
AND REJOICE
IN YOUR VISION OF UNITY.
BUT, YOUR MAJESTY,
THE PATH IS FRAUGHT
WITH PERILS BEYOND NUMBER.
IT WILL LEAD TO FAR MORE
BLOODSHED THAN MY WAY.
BUT, YOU'RE NOT
A STUPID MAN, ARE YOU?
YOU WORRY BECAUSE
YOU KNOW WHAT'S COMING.
AND BECAUSE YOU ARE
PLAGUED WITH WORRY,
I MUST WORK TO
LIGHTEN YOUR BURDEN,
EVEN IF ONLY A LITTLE BIT.
SO, FOR THE GLORY OF ROLAND
AND YOUR MAJESTY,
I AM AT YOUR SERVICE.
- LOOKS LIKE
MAJOR MILLER WOKE UP
ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF THE BED AGAIN.
- HMM...
I GUESS HE'S UPSET
BECAUSE WE FAILED OUR MISSION.
- DON'T BEAT YOURSELF
UP, CAPTAIN.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
WE CAN HARDLY BE BLAMED
FOR HOW IT TURNED OUT.
OUR OPPONENT WAS
FAR TOO POWERFUL FOR US.
I STILL FIND IT HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT HIS MAGIC WAS MORE
POWERFUL THAN YOURS, CAPTAIN.
- Moe: YEAH, HIS STRENGTH
WAS BEYOND COMPARE.
HE EVEN CALLED FORTH
A RED DRAGON.
- ( roars )
- YOU'RE RIGHT, THAT WAS
TERRIFYING, WASN'T IT?
I WONDER WHAT'S
GOING ON OUT THERE.
- IT'S PROBABLY SOME SORT OF
TOURIST ATTRACTION BY NOW.
- Moe: I BET THEY'RE MAKING
A FORTUNE
PEDDLING DRAGON SOUVENIRS.
- OH PLEASE, WHAT IDIOT WOULD
BUY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- ( clears throat )
- LUKE, WHAT IF WE GET
PULLED OFF OF THE MISSION,
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
HOW WILL WE GO ON?
- LET'S NOT WORRY
ABOUT THAT YET.
I'M JUST CONCERNED
ABOUT THE FACT
THAT WHEN WE'RE
FACING YOUR TABOO-BREAKER,
EVERY ONE OF US SEEMS
TO BE OUT OF OUR ELEMENT.
- NO WE'RE NOT!
YOU MARK MY WORDS,
I WILL SAVE RYNER!
I WILL SAVE HIM
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
- ( Luke shushing )
- ( all laugh nervously )
- I SEE YOU'RE AS
SPIRITED AS EVER, CAPTAIN.
A POSITIVE QUALITY.
- OH, YES SIR.
A POSITIVE SPIRIT
BEGETS A POSITIVE OUTCOME!
- APPARENTLY, NOT ALWAYS.
ACCORDING TO YOUR REPORT,
THIS TABOO-BREAKER
WAS QUITE THE HANDFUL.
- SIR, THIS MISSION
SHOULD BE A CINCH!
- BUT CAPTAIN, WE CAN'T.
WE'RE NO MATCH FOR HIS SKILLS.
WE SHOULD WITHDRAW OURSELVES
FROM THIS MISSION.
- I AM NOT WITHDRAWING
MYSELF FROM ANYTHING,
AND NEITHER ARE ANY OF YOU.
I JUST WASN'T
SERIOUS ENOUGH LAST TIME.
ONCE I GET SERIOUS
I CAN TAKE CARE OF IT!
AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT!
- OF COURSE, CAPTAIN MILK,
WHATEVER YOU SAY, BUT...
I, I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
- Miller: WELL, WITH
A VOTE OF CONFIDENCE
THAT STRONG FROM LUKE,
I'M SURE YOU'LL DO FINE.
- UH, SIR, I DON'T THINK
YOU UNDERSTAND.
- IT'S SETTLED.
CAPTAIN, I WILL CONTINUE
TO ENTRUST YOUR SQUADRON
WITH THE MISSION TO PURSUE
THESE TABOO-BREAKERS.
- SIR, I WILL GIVE YOU
EVERYTHING I'VE GOT!
SEE? I TOLD YOU
WE WOULDN'T GET THE BOOT!
- IN YOUR OPINION,
THIS TABOO-BREAKER
IS A PROBLEM THEN. YES?
- YES SIR. RYNER LUTE IS
DEFINITELY GOING TO BE AN ISSUE.
MORE SO THAN I EVER
IMAGINED, IN FACT.
BUT MORE THAN THAT,
IT LOOKS LIKE SION IS FINALLY
GOING TO MAKE A MOVE.
- YES, IT DOES APPEAR
THAT IS THE CASE.
- I SUPPOSE OUR COUNTRY
CAN'T MOVE ON
UNTIL THE CORRUPT NOBILITY
IS DRIVEN FROM IT.
THEY MUST BE PURGED
OR WE ALL FACE RUIN.
- COME LUKE, SURELY THE
DEPTH OF YOUR HATRED
FOR THE NOBILITY HASN'T GROWN?
- I'M SORRY...
IT'S JUST WHEN I THINK OF
ALL THE INJUSTICES
CAPTAIN MILK
ENDURED AT THEIR HANDS...
- SHE WAS TAKEN IN FROM
AN ORPHANAGE, WASN'T SHE?
PEOPLE SAY THE CALLAUDS
SOUGHT TO PUT THEIR
MILITARY EXPERTISE ON DISPLAY.
AND SO THEY FORCED
EXTENSIVE TRAINING
ON THEIR OWN,
CAPTAIN MILK INCLUDED.
- Luke: YES. I DON'T BELIEVE
SHE'S EVER KNOWN TRUE HAPPINESS.
NOT UNTIL NOW, THAT IS.
THIS IS HER FIRST TASTE OF JOY.
- RIGHT NOW, WE MUST
NOT ALLOW MILK
TO REMAIN IN
THIS COUNTRY, LUKE.
- I UNDERSTAND.
TURMOIL IS UPON US, AND I WILL
DO EVERYTHING IN MY POWER
TO SHIELD AND
PROTECT HER FROM IT.
- HEY, WHO'S DOING
THE COOKING TODAY?
- EH, LET'S JUST LET MOE DO IT.
- NO FAIR!
I ALWAYS DO IT!
- Lach: WELL, THAT'S 'CAUSE
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOWS HOW.
- RYNER.
WHEREVER YOU ARE, MARK MY WORDS.
I'M COMING TO SAVE YOU, OKAY?
- ( Arua crying )
- Kalti: ARE YOU GOING
TO FIGHT BACK,
OR ARE YOU GOING
TO LIE THERE,
YOU LITTLE DEMON?
- I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
SUCH A SMART IDEA
TO PROVOKE THE THING.
WHAT IF WE MAKE IT ANGRY?
- THAT'S THE POINT OF
THESE EXPERIMENTS,
TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS, RIGHT?
- YOU LEAVE US NO CHOICE.
- ( Arua screams )
- AW, THE LITTLE WRETCH
IS SQUIRMING.
DOES IT HURT?
THEN BEG FOR YOUR LIFE.
ASK SAINT CHEZO KALTI FOR MERCY.
BEG HIM TO PUT YOU
OUT OF YOUR MISERY,
YOU LITTLE BEAST!
- ( Arua screams )
- ( men grunting )
- OH, HOW VERY DULL.
HURRY UP AND DO SOMETHING!
- HOW LONG CAN HE ENDURE THIS?
CALM DOWN.
EVEN IF WE TRIED, WE WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO SAVE HIM NOW.
REMEMBER, THEY'RE MAGIC KNIGHTS.
WE NEED TO FORMULATE
A PLAN FIRST.
- APPARENTLY YOUR
SURVIVAL INSTINCTS
AREN'T ENOUGH
TO SPUR YOU ON.
- NO, PLEASE. MOMMY.
( Arua groans )
- ( men laughing )
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( Arua crying )
PLEASE, MOMMY. WAKE UP!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
- RYNER!
- MOMMY, NO!
- YOUR MOTHER BROUGHT
EVIL INTO THIS WORLD,
AND FOR THAT,
SHE PAID WITH HER LIFE.
LOGIC DICTATES YOUR FATHER HAS
COMMITTED THE SAME EXACT SIN!
- ARUA.
- DADDY! THEY KILLED HER!
THEY MURDERED HER
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
- DON'T SAY THAT, ARUA. IT'S
NOT YOU. THIS ISN'T YOUR FAULT.
IT'S THEM.
THE ONLY REASON SHE'S DEAD
IS BECAUSE OF THEM.
MY SON, DON'T BLAME
YOURSELF FOR THIS!
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
DON'T GIVE THEM WHAT THEY WANT!
- NO, DADDY!
- DON'T DARE BLAME YOURSELF
FOR MY DEATH EITHER, SON.
YOU LIVE. YOU HAVE TO GO ON.
- OH, WE'LL LET THE BRAT
LIVE ALL RIGHT.
AT LEAST UNTIL WE BREAK HIM
AND HE'S SERVED HIS PURPOSE!
- Soldier: SIR!
WE'RE UNDER ATTACK!
- I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT,
TO BEAR THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS WITHIN THE EARTH!
- RUN HIM DOWN!
- ( men groaning )
- Ferris: THROW DOWN
YOUR WEAPONS AT ONCE!
FAIR WARNING THOUGH.
THE MONSTER YOU ARE
FACING IS A WILD BEAST
THAT HAS BEEN KNOWN TO ATTACK
MEN AND WOMEN INDISCRIMINATELY!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU FOOLS?
HURRY UP AND STOP HIM!
- ( men grunting )
- I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT,
TO UNLEASH THE BEAST
THAT DANCES THROUGH THE SKIES!
- I IMPLORE THE GODS ABOVE
TO ENDOW THY SERVANTS
WITH THE DEMON-SCORCHING LIGHT!
- ( explosion )
- GET OUTTA MY WAY!
- ( grunting )
- CALM DOWN, YOU FOOL!
I CAN TAKE IT FROM HERE!
- ( both grunting )
- Kalti: AN ALPHA STIGMA?
DID YOU CONJURE HIM FORTH,
DEVIL CHILD?
IS THIS YOUR DOING?
- WE DON'T FEAR YOU. HOLY RUNA'S
MAGIC CANNOT BE STOLEN
BY ONE WHOSE HEATHEN WAYS
SEVER HIM FROM HEAVEN.
I IMPLORE THE GODS ABOVE
TO ENDOW THY SERVANT
WITH THE DEMON-SCORCHING LIGHT!
- I IMPLORE THE GODS ABOVE,
TO BESTOW THY SERVANT
WITH THE DEMON-SCORCHING LIGHT!
- ( explosion )
- YOU EVIL MONSTER!
CURSE YOU, DEMON!
- HEY! YOU! HOW 'BOUT
A LITTLE HELP OVER HERE, HUH?
GET UP AND FIGHT, WE CAN'T
SAVE YOUR SON BY OURSELVES!
COME ON! FIRST, TAKE OUT
THOSE STUPID NOBLES!
THEN UNTIE YOUR SON
AND THE TWO OF YOU
GET THE HELL OUT
OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
YOU'D SAVE SOMEONE
FROM A DIFFERENT LAND?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS FOR US?
- DAD! DADDY, YOU'RE OKAY?
- YES, MY BOY.
I'M COMING! DON'T WORRY!
- I KNEW YOU WOULD.
- SON, I WON'T LET THEM
HURT YOU ANYMORE. I PROMISE.
- WITH THE
DEMON-SCORCHING LIGHT!
I CAN DO THIS.
YES, I CAN.
- ( Ferris grunting )
- TOGETHER, WE CAN DO THIS!
YES. WHEN I'M
WITH HER, I CAN.
- I'LL SAVE YOU,
MY SON. I WILL...
NO MATTER WHAT.
- ( crunching )
- ARU...
- YOU SEE THAT?
DIVINE RETRIBUTION FOR A PERSON
WHO SOUGHT TO RELEASE
EVIL INTO THIS WORLD.
- ( crying )
( laughing maniacally )
- IT'S HAPPENING.
- Ferris: RYNER, GO.
- ( continues laughing )
( continues laughing )
- ARUA. YOU MUST BE TIRED.
- ( Arua grunts )
- REST NOW. HAVE PEACE.
- LET'S GO. NOW, RYNER.
- STOP THERE! THAT BOY
IS OUR RESEARCH SUBJECT!
TAKE HIM AND YOU'LL BE
CONDEMNED AS HIS ACCOMPLICE
AND STRUCK DOWN
BY THE WRATH OF HEAVEN!
- OH YEAH? AND YOU'RE THE ONE
TO CAST THAT JUDGMENT, HUH?
YOU, A MERCHANT
OF UNCHECKED CRUELTY,
DOLE OUT THE WILL OF THE GODS?
YOU THINK WE'LL RECEIVE
DIVINE RETRIBUTION
BECAUSE OF THESE EYES?
- RYNER!
THEY'LL HAVE CALLED
FOR REINFORCEMENTS, LET'S GO!
- ( screams )
DAMN IT, DAMN IT, DAMN IT!
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE?
DIVINE RETRIBUTION? SERIOUSLY?
IF THE GODS DETEST US,
WHY THE HELL DID THEY
ALLOW US TO BE BORN?
IF THERE'S ANYONE
UP THERE, TELL ME!
WHY DID YOU MAKE
SOMEONE LIKE ME?
TO TOY WITH ME
FOR YOUR AMUSEMENT?
WHAT, IS THIS A GAME TO YOU?
IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT.
GUESS WHAT?
WE'RE NOT TOYS.
AND THIS LIFE'S NOT A GAME.
WE'RE LIVING THINGS.
WE ARE ALIVE, TOO.
WE DIDN'T CHOOSE
TO BE BORN THIS WAY.
WE DIDN'T CHOOSE TO BE
BORN DEMONS. WHY WOULD WE?
WHY WOULD WE?
WHO WOULD CHOOSE
TO BE CURSED WITH THESE EYES?
OR WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE IT IS OUR FAULT?
IF THERE'S REALLY
SOMEONE UP THERE
WATCHING OVER
THE PEOPLE OF THIS LAND...
PLEASE, TELL ME,
TELL ME WHY I'M HERE.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: AS FAR AS COUNTRIES GO,
ROLAND IS A REAL PAIN.
IF YOU ASK ME, SION WORKS
WAY TOO HARD FOR IT.
FORGET ABOUT THE NOBILITY.
JUST KICK BACK FOR
A LITTLE WHILE
AND TAKE A
HOLIDAY OR SOMETHING.
SERIOUSLY, GEEZ.