- I HAVE DONE AS YOUR
MAJESTY HAS ASKED ME.
THE REBEL IS SUBDUED.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( groaning )
( snoring )
( exclaims )
( chuckling )
YOU KNOW, FERRIS, THIS IS
THE FOURTH STRAIGHT DAY
I'VE BEEN SLOGGING THROUGH
THIS CRAP WITHOUT A BREAK.
I'D SAY IT'S A MIRACLE
SOME MISSTEP BROUGHT ON
BY LACK OF SLEEP HASN'T
LITERALLY BURIED ME ALIVE
UNDER AN AVALANCHE
OF FORM LETTERS,
IF YOU CATCH MY DRIFT...
- RYNER! RYNER! DON'T YOU
DARE FALL ASLEEP ON ME!
- SORRY, I'M JUST TOO TIRED TO
GO ON. REMEMBER ME FONDLY.
- NO, RYNER!
FIGHT IT, DAMN YOU!
THE TWO OF US HAD A DEAL!
WE... WE WERE GOING
TO GET MARRIED.
UH, I DON'T THINK
I REMEMBER THAT PART.
AH, BUT WHAT THE HELL.
IT WAS A LOVELY DREAM.
I'LL DIE A HAPPY MAN.
- NO! OPEN YOUR EYES!
YOU'RE NOT LEAVING ME TO
HANDLE THIS WORKLOAD ALONE...
- I HATE TO BE BEARER
OF BAD NEWS,
BUT THERE'S A
DISCREPANCY IN THE...
- FOR THE LOVE
OF ALL THAT'S SACRED,
JUST LOOK AT WHAT YOU'VE
WROUGHT! RYNER IS DEAD!
- THE CAUSE OF DEATH
REMAINS A MYSTERY,
BUT OVERWORK IS THOUGHT TO HAVE
PLAYED A SIGNIFICANT ROLE.
- STOP HORSING AROUND
FOR TWO SECONDS
AND LISTEN TO WHAT
I HAVE TO SAY.
- THERE'S AN EXTREMELY...
- NO, NO, NO, NO!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO HEAR WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING WHEN I'M DEAD?
WHATEVER IT IS,
GIVE IT TO SOMEONE ELSE!
- SORRY.
- YOU'VE GOT A HEART OF STONE.
- HERE'S THE LAY OF THE LAND.
IF THESE DOCUMENTS AREN'T GONE
THROUGH WITH A FINE TOOTH COMB
WITHIN THE NEXT WEEK,
A BIRTHDAY SOIREE OF TRAGIC
PROPORTIONS WILL LIKELY ENSUE.
- A BIRTHDAY WHAT? FOR WHO?
- WHO DO YOU THINK?
- YOU HAVE A BIRTHDAY?
- Miran: "OPEN ENROLLMENT
ESSAY CONTEST.
"TOPIC, CRIME AND PUNISHMENT.
"EXPLORE IN 500 WORDS OR LESS
THE MORAL ISSUES
"SURROUNDING ROLAND'S
TRADITIONAL PUNITIVE METHODS
"AND THE MANNER IN WHICH THESE
ISSUES MAY LEAD
"TO BOTH A GREATER UNDERSTANDING
OF THE CRIMINAL ELEMENT
AND A REDUCTION IN CRIME."
INTRIGUING.
HOWEVER, THAT BEING SAID,
I QUESTION SUCH A CONTEST'S
SUITABILITY AS THE KEYSTONE
OF HIS MAJESTY'S
BIRTHDAY REVELS.
THAT SAID, THIS YEAR
THE ANNIVERSARY
OF OUR KING'S NATIVITY WILL
BE RESPLENDENT!
( laughing )
- ( grunting )
EIGHT HUNDRED FORTY THREE,
NO! DON'T YOU DO IT!
DON'T YOU GIVE
THE HELL OUT ON ME!
I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU YET,
YOU BASTARD!
- OH, LOOK AT YOURSELF.
YOU'RE TRYING TOO HARD.
TRY WORKING THE MUSCLE
BETWEEN YOUR EARS.
- I CAN STILL KICK YOUR BUTT,
PRETTY BOY!
- HOW ABOUT I JUST GO
TELL LADY NOA
HOW HARD YOU'RE
PUSHING YOURSELF?
- DO IT AND YOU'RE A DEAD MAN!
THAT'S A PROMISE!
- WELL, WELL, LOOKS LIKE
I FOUND THE MAGIC WORD.
SOME INFLUENCE HER
LADYSHIP'S NAME HAS ON YOU.
- ( scoffs ) WELL,
TWO CAN PLAY AT THIS GAME.
HOW ABOUT I GO
AND CHAT WITH ESLINA?
SHE'D GET A KICK
OUT OF LADY PEARL,
OR FOR THAT MATTER
THE WIDOW FAZIA.
- ( exclaiming ) NOW SEE HERE!
NOTHING UNTOWARD HAPPENED IN
EITHER OF THOSE CIRCUMSTANCES!
- ( chuckling )
NOTHING UNTOWARD, HUH?
- DAMN RIGHT NOTHING!
- WELL, WELL,
I SEE THAT BOTH YOUR MINDS ARE
POSITIVELY SWIMMING
IN VISIONS OF THE SEASON.
I'M A BIT ENVIOUS, ACTUALLY.
- GREAT! IT'S MR. JOY HIMSELF.
- HEY, NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME
TO PICK A FIGHT!
- IT'S NOT MY INTENTION
TO RANKLE YOU.
ON THE CONTRARY, YOU HAVE
MY COMPLIMENTS, GENTLEMEN.
YOU'VE FILTERED OUT ALL
EXTRANEOUS CONTENT
FROM YOUR HEADS AND
IN THE PROCESS,
REDUCED YOURSELVES
TO FINE INSTRUMENTS.
TO WHICH END I MAY HAVE
FOUND THE PERFECT USE.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING TO KILL THE BASTARD.
- YOU'LL HEAR
NO ARGUMENT FROM ME!
- OH, DEAR.
- Sion: RYNER, I'M BEGGING YOU!
- GET DOWN ON YOUR KNEES
FOR ALL I CARE!
YOU'VE BEEN WORKING ME
TO THE BONE SINCE...
UH! I DON'T EVEN
REMEMBER HOW LONG!
YOU NEED TO GET SOME SLEEP,
MISTER! OH, AND TRUST ME,
WE HAVE WAYS OF
MAKING YOU FALL ASLEEP!
- NO, NO, WAIT.
- EITHER THIS OR SLEEP FOREVER!
- HMM.
- ( all grunting )
- NAP TIME. THEY CAN
KISS MY BUTT
IF THEY THINK I'M
STICKING AROUND
ANOTHER SECOND
FOR THAT B.S.
- HELLO, RYNER. WE'VE REALLY GOT
TO STOP MEETING LIKE THIS.
- IT'S JUST THAT HE TAKES THINGS
SO FREAKING SERIOUSLY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN ANY OTHER HUMAN
BEING WOULD BE HAPPY
TO CELEBRATE THEIR
BIRTHDAY, RIGHT?
- UH, YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- EVERYONE WANTS TO
THROW HIM A BIG PARTY,
HE JUST DOESN'T LIKE..
WAIT. HOLY CRAP!
I... UH, MAYBE, KINDA TOTALLY
DITCHED YOUR BIRTHDAY PARTY.
- YEAH, BUT AT LEAST
YOU REMEMBERED THAT YOU DID!
- YEAH, WELL, STILL SORRY
ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I DITCHED IT MYSELF.
I MEAN, A BUNCH OF
CRAZY STUFF HAPPENED
LEADING UP TO THAT NIGHT
AND I COULDN'T GO.
- AH.
- IT REALLY MEANS A LOT TO ME
THAT YOU REMEMBERED, THOUGH.
THAT'S A LOT MORE
THAN I WOULD'VE DONE.
( giggling )
( gasping )
OH, MY, LOOK AT THE TIME!
SORRY. I'VE GOT TO
GET SOME WORK DONE,
SO I'D BETTER BE HEADING BACK.
- OKAY.
- I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
CATCH UP ON YOUR SLEEP.
IF YOU LET FERRIS START
KEEPING YOU UP LATE NOW,
YOU CAN KISS YOUR PRECIOUS
AFTERNOON NAPS GOODBYE SOON.
- WAIT, WHAT THE HELL?
AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
- Luke: IS THERE ANYONE SWEETER?
- ( Ryner exclaims )
- DESPITE HAVING HER OWN
BIRTHDAY CELEBRATION
RELEGATED TO THE DUST BIN,
SHE SOLDIERS ON GALLANTLY.
- Lear: A CERTAIN
TABOO-BREAKER WE ALL KNOW
WHO SHALL
REMAIN NAMELESS.
- ISN'T WORTHY.
- YOU'RE JUST AS RESPONSIBLE
FOR LETTING HER BIRTHDAY
FALL THROUGH THE CRACKS AS I AM!
- WE'RE AWARE OF THAT!
WHICH IS PRECISELY WHY
WE'VE ALL BEEN AGONIZING
OVER OUR OPTIONS WITH REGARD
TO PROPER ATONEMENT.
- ATONEMENT, HUH?
- A MEANS FOR ADDRESSING
AN IMBALANCE!
- YEAH, ADDRESSING AN IMBALANCE!
- OH, RIGHT.
SION'S BIRTHDAY.
- IT ALMOST SLIPPED MY MIND.
I GUESS WE CAN'T AFFORD FOR IT
TO BE AS DULL AND LIFELESS
AS IT WAS LAST YEAR.
- DAMN STRAIGHT WE CAN'T.
OF COURSE IT'D BE EASIER IF SION
DIDN'T DESPISE OPULENCE.
- WE MUST BANISH ALL THOUGHTS
OF THIS CELEBRATION
RESEMBLING IN ANY WAY
THE TEDIUM OF LAST YEAR.
FOR THE SAKE OF THIS
KINGDOM'S FUTURE
I WOULD EMPLOY THE TWO OF YOU
TOWARD A VERY SPECIFIC PURPOSE.
- WELL, PUT IT THAT WAY AND
YOU CAN CERTAINLY COUNT ON US,
MR. RAIN CLOUD.
IN FACT, WE'RE ALREADY
TWO STEPS AHEAD OF YOU!
ALL RIGHT!
TIME TO RALLY THE TROOPS!
- BY WHICH I ASSUME
YOU MEAN THE WOMEN FOLK?
- YOU AND ME ARE ON THE
SAME PAGE, PRETTY BOY.
SEE, THIS IS WHY STORM CROW
OVER THERE NEEDS US.
- LET THERE... NO, NO.
SHOW SOME RESTRAINT.
- NOA WILL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- YOU THINK IT'S ALL RIGHT
IF I INVITE ESLINA?
- A DEPLORABLE IDEA
ANY WAY YOU SLICE IT.
INDEED, CRIME AND PUNISHMENT.
- I'M THINKING A BIG STAGE IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE PALACE PLAZA.
- Eslina: OOH AND SOME STALLS!
- THE KEY INGREDIENT HERE
IS PANACHE.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE
THE END-ALL, BE-ALL.
WHAT KIND OF STUFF DO
THEY DO IN ESTABUL?
- WELL, LET ME THINK.
IT IS TRADITION FOR US
TO DISPLAY FIREWORKS
AT ANY LARGE FESTIVAL.
-FIREWORKS, HUH?
- THEY'RE LIKE GIANT
BLOOMS OF COLORED FLAME
THAT LIGHT UP THE
WHOLE NIGHT SKY!
- IS THAT A FACT?
- I'VE HAD A CHANCE
TO SEE A FEW,
BUT NEVER THE REALLY GRAND ONES.
OH, WOW. I'D GIVE ANYTHING T
TO WITNESS THOSE FOR MYSELF.
- SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
- YEAH, IT SURE DOES.
THEY'RE JUST THE AMOUNT
OF FLAIR WE NEED
TO PULL THIS THING
OFF WITH STYLE.
- PERFECT, THEN! LET'S MAKE
FIREWORKS THE MAIN ATTRACTION.
- REALLY?
- THERE'S A CAVEAT.
FIREWORKS DO TEND TO CALL FOR
A FAIR AMOUNT OF PREPARATION,
ESPECIALLY FOR A KING.
- A TRULY IMPRESSIVE DISPLAY
CAN TAKE UP TO SIX MONTHS.
- SIX MONTHS!
- THE TIME FRAME WE'VE GOT
TO WORK WITH ISN'T SUFFICIENT.
AT LEAST NOT FOR A DISPLAY
OF THIS SIZE AND AS YOU SAY,
WE DO WANT PANACHE.
- SO I SUPPOSE FIREWORKS
ARE OFF THE TABLE, THEN.
- NO. I THINK I GOT
A WAY AROUND THIS.
- AND THAT WOULD BE?
- TRUST ME.
IT'S ALL ABOUT WHO YOU
RUB SHOULDERS WITH.
- COME NOW, AN ATTITUDE
OF REPOSE IS DISRESPECTFUL
IN THE FACE OF SUCH ARTISTRY.
- SORRY, BUT THIS IS THE BEST
I CAN GIVE IT.
I'VE GOT TOO MANY THINGS RUNNING
AROUND IN MY HEAD RIGHT NOW.
- AH! DOUBTLESS SOME POOR SOUL
YOU DEFLOWERED AGES AGO
IS HOUNDING YOU FOR ALIMONY.
OR MAYBE THE WOMAN WHOSE RICHES
YOU'VE SHAMELESSLY PILFERED
TO PAY HER OFF IS
SUDDENLY WISE TO THE RUSE.
SO YOU'RE TRYING TO IMAGINE
WHAT IT'S LIKE
BEING LEFT FOR DEAD IN A DITCH.
IS THAT ABOUT THE LONG
AND SHORT OF IT?
- SURE, FINE.
- ALL SUCH WORRIES SHOULD BE
PUSHED TO THE BACKGROUND
RIGHT NOW SO YOU CAN
FOCUS ON EATING DANGO.
- GOT IT.
- GO ON.
- WELL, I'M NO EXPERT,
BUT I'VE EATEN THIS STUFF
IN JUST ABOUT EVERY
REGION WE'VE BEEN
AND THE WYNNIT VARIETY
IS BY FAR MY FAVORITE.
- YOU THINK SO?
- IS THIS A NEW RECIPE, THOUGH?
IT'S KIND OF DIFFERENT,
BUT IT'S GOOD.
- HMM.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- NOTHING.
- THE RECIPE'S SCORED HIGH MARKS
WITH YOUR PARTNER, MISS FERRIS.
I TOLD YOU IT WOULD, DIDN'T I?
- UH, THAT'S ENOUGH.
- WHAT YOU'RE EATING, YOUNG MAN,
IS A BRAND NEW CONCOCTION MISS
FERRIS CAME UP WITH.
- YOU INVENTED THIS FLAVOR
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- I'VE GOT SOME
SERIOUS COMPETITION
WHEN SHE FINALLY OPENS UP HER
OWN DANGO SHOP.
- WAIT, WHEN SHE WHAT?
OF COURSE.
WHY DIDN'T I SEE IT BEFORE?
NO ONE'S TAKES DANGO MORE
SERIOUSLY THAN YOU.
- BECAUSE UNLIKE
SOME PEOPLE I KNOW,
I'M FULLY AWARE OF HOW IMPORTANT
IT IS TO PAY MY RESPECTS
TO THE GREAT DANGO GOD!
- YEAH, ABOUT THAT...
DANGO GOD?
- HE IS THE ARBITER
OF ALL THINGS EXQUISITE.
THOSE WHO IGNORE HIM TURN THEIR
BACKS ON THE WHOLE WORLD.
- AND THEY DO SO AT THEIR PERIL!
- OKAY.
- Claugh: HEY, HEY!
IF IT ISN'T HE WHO NAPS.
- YEAH. PLEASE FORGIVE
OUR LITTLE INTRUSION.
WE'VE COME HERE
TO COMMANDEER YOUR SERVICES.
- Claugh: ON YOUR FEET!
- ( loud thumping )
- Ryner: WHAT THE HELL?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING! GET
YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
- WE CAN DO THIS THE HARD WAY
OR THE EASY WAY.
I CAN'T GET ON MY FEET
IF YOU'RE DRAGGING ME!
- SO THE SORRY LETCH'S
CALAMITOUS MISDEEDS
FINALLY CATCH UP WITH HIM.
- ( chattering indistinctly )
- NICE TO HAVE KNOWN YOU,
PERVERT.
- Sion: CAN'T WE GO FASTER?
- NO, SIR!
IT'S ALREADY TOO DANGEROUS!
- DAMN IT. THE PREPARATIONS
SHOULD BE IN PLACE BY NOW.
- ( chuckling ) THE JIG IS UP.
NO ESCAPE FOR YOU.
AT LAST, THE MOMENT
I'VE BEEN DREAMING OF.
THE REDHEADED WALL OF
MEAT THAT'S HAD ME
IN VIRTUAL SHACKLES FOR DAYS
IS JUST AS BAD AS YOU ARE!
AND YOU...
WHAT THE HELL GIVES
YOU THE RIGHT TO RUN
YOUR HAPPY ASS OUT OF TOWN
- WHILE I'M TREATED
LIKE A FREAKING SLAVE!
- KNOCK IT OFF!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
ARE YOU MICE OR ARE YOU MEN?
- ( all chuckling )
- ( all yelling )
- Sion: WHAT IS THE
MEANING OF THIS?
- THAT'S RIGHT, MEN! AWAY!
- COME ON! COME ON!
LET'S GO! THIS WAY!
- I HAVE WORK TO DO!
PUT ME DOWN THIS INSTANT...
- BYE! HAVE FUN.
- ♪ FOR HE'S A JOLLY-GOOD FELLOW
FOR HE'S A JOLLY-GOOD FELLOW ♪
- ( people cheering )
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU,
YOUR MAJESTY!
- I CAN SEE HIM!
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SION!
- YOUR MAJESTY!
- SIR. WE'RE ALL WAITING
ON YOU, YOUR MAJESTY.
I KNOW IT'S SHORT NOTICE, BUT
COULD YOU IGNITE THE FIREWORKS?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- WE PREPARED THEM
ESPECIALLY FOR YOU.
- BUT THAT'S ABSURDLY
EXTRAVAGANT. THE BUDGET WON'T...
- COME ON! JUST HAVE A LOOK.
- MAY ALL YOUR WISHES
COME TRUE, MY KING!
- I LOVE YOU, YOUR MAJESTY!
- SEEMS EVERYONE IN THE KINGDOM
IS READY TO CELEBRATE THIS DAY
BUT YOU, SIR.
- SURELY IT WOULD BE GOOD FORM
TO REPAY THE HONOR.
- I SUPPOSE YOU'RE
RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
- TRAIN YOUR EYES ON THE
MOUNTAIN RANGE IN FRONT OF US.
FIRE AN IZUCHI IN THE DIRECTION
OF THAT TINY FLECK OF LIGHT
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
- THAT I CAN DO.
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER.
IZUCHI!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THAT'S SO COOL!
- WOW!
- All: AND HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO OUR VERY FAVORITE CAPTAIN!
- SERIOUSLY, YOU GUYS?
- FEAST YOUR EYES
ON THIS LITTLE WISH.
- Milk: "HAPPY BIRTHDAY"
- I'M SPEECHLESS. YOU...
- AHEM...
- All: YOUR ATTENTION
PLEASE, CAPTAIN.
- NOW, ARE WE READY, GENTLEMEN?
FIVE!
- FOUR!
- THREE!
- TWO!
- AND ONE!
- ( giggling )
- ( people chattering )
- HEY, JUST WHERE
DOES HE THINK HE'S GOING?
- RIGHT. NO MORE WINE,
I PROMISE.
- YOU'RE LEAVING?
- OH! HELLO, YOUR MAJESTY.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
- PREPARE THE CARRIAGE, PLEASE.
I THINK I'D LIKE TO TAKE IT OUT.
- YES, SIR. I'LL CALL
FOR A COACHMAN AT ONCE.
- OH, I'LL DRIVE MYSELF.
- SIR?
- I'VE SOMEONE TO PICK UP.
WELL, THAT IS... SOMEONE TO
WHOM I OWE A GREAT DEBT.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- AND OF COURSE,
IT STARTS POURING.
OKAY, THEN,
TIME TO HEAD BACK, I THINK.
THANKS.
YOU'RE A REAL LIFE-SAVER.
- IT IS I WHO SHOULD
BE THANKING YOU.
- HUH? FOR WHAT?
- YOU ARE THE ONE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE FIREWORKS THIS EVENING,
ARE YOU NOT?
- OH, THAT. WELL, YEAH.
- THE ROAD'S A BIT TREACHEROUS.
DO YOU MIND IF WE STOP OFF
SOMEWHERE FOR A WHILE?
- JUST TO BE SAFE?
- YOU'RE DRIVING. DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- VERY WELL, THEN.
- HUH. CONVENIENT, HUH?
THIS PLACE BRINGS BACK
A LOT OF MEMORIES, DOESN'T IT?
- I SHOULD HOPE SO. IT'S WHERE
I FIRST MADE MY OFFER TO YOU...
- RYNER?
- HUH?
- WHEN I SAID THANK YOU
FOR TONIGHT, I DID MEAN IT.
- YEAH, WELL, I GUESS EVEN I
CAN BE NICE SOMETIMES.
BUT JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I'M TOTALLY TAKING A NAP
WHEN WE GET BACK.
- DON'T START COUNTING SHEEP
JUST YET, MY FRIEND.
THERE'S STILL WORK TO BE DONE.
- OH, COME ON, GIVE IT A REST.
YOU REALLY ARE GOING TO HAVE
MY DEATH ON YOUR CONSCIENCE
IF THIS KEEPS UP.
- I SUPPOSE WORKING FOR
TEN DAYS WITHOUT A BREAK
DOESN'T COME EASILY TO YOU.
- YEAH, ABOUT THAT,
IT'D HAVE BEEN NICE IF
YOU'D RECOGNIZED THAT
A COUPLE OF DAYS INTO IT
OR ON THE FIRST DAY.
- MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE HEAD BACK,
GET OURSELVES SOME SLEEP?
- HELL, YES!
BEST PLAN YOU'VE EVER HAD.
- YOU'LL BE AT THE INN?
I'LL SEND A CARRIAGE FOR YOU
SO WE CAN PICK UP
WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
- NICE TRY.
- WILL THREE HOURS DO THE TRICK?
- WHAT? I'M SLEEP DEPRIVED HERE!
I'M GOING TO NEED A LOT MORE
THAN THREE FREAKING HOURS!
- HOW MANY HOURS
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO WAIT?
- HOW ABOUT THREE HUNDRED?
- FUNNY, BUT AFRAID NOT. HOW
ABOUT I SEND FOR YOU IN FOUR?
- THAT'S NOT EVEN FAIR!
I'M NOT THE ONLY PERSON YOU
SHOULD BE THINKING ABOUT HERE.
YOU PROBABLY HAVEN'T HAD PROPER
SLEEP IN GOD KNOWS HOW LONG.
- IT'S THE NATURE OF THE
BEAST AND THE PRICE I PAY
FOR WANTING TO CHANGE THE WORLD.
WE STILL NEED BETTER EDUCATION,
AND HEALTH REFORM,
AND LOWER TAXES.
OUR TECHNOLOGICAL
INFRASTRUCTURE IS FRAUGHT.
THAT'S JUST THE START, SO...
- SERIOUSLY, HOW LONG ARE YOU
GOING TO RUN YOURSELF
INTO THE GROUND OVER THIS CRAP?
UH, LISTEN, SION...
I DON'T MEAN TO
COMPLAIN SO MUCH.
BACK IN THE DAY
WHEN YOU FIRST MADE THAT OFFER
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
OUT OF YOUR MIND.
I STILL DO, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
THE FACT THAT YOU WANTED
TO CHANGE THINGS,
IT MEANT A LOT TO ME EVEN THEN.
FEW PEOPLE CARE ENOUGH
TO BE WILLING TO HELP
THEIR FELLOW MEN
RISE ABOVE IT ALL.
YOUR DREAM WASN'T AN EMPTY ONE.
THIS COUNTRY'S CHANGED.
YOU'VE CHANGED IT.
WE LIVE IN A WORLD NOW WHERE
PEOPLE CAN JUST CLOSE THEIR EYES
ON A LATE AFTERNOON AND NAP.
- BUT IT IS AN EMPTY DREAM.
HOW MANY GOOD PEOPLE
HAVE DIED TO MAKE IT HAPPEN?
HOW MANY MORE WILL HAVE TO?
HOW MANY WILL SURVIVE
LONG ENOUGH TO SEE IT?
HOW MANY FRIENDS
MUST I SACRIFICE
TO THE WORST OF THIS WORLD
BEFORE IT CHANGES?
- NOW YOU'RE BROODING.
SURE IT'S A HARD ROAD,
BUT THIS COUNTRY WOULDN'T
HAVE TAKEN THE FIRST STEP
WITHOUT YOU.
PLEASE, LOOK AT WHAT
YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED.
I KNOW YOU WORK HARD
BECAUSE YOU FEEL GUILTY,
AND IT KILLS ME TO SEE IT.
BUT YOU CAN'T CHANGE THINGS
BY PUNISHING YOURSELF.
AND WHATEVER YOU THINK,
THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
YOU CAN AFFORD TO TAKE IT
EASY ONCE IN A WHILE.
THE WORLD WILL WAIT.
THERE'S NO POINT IN
SECOND-GUESSING YOURSELF
IF ALL IT DOES IS
PARALYZE YOU, RIGHT?
TAKE MY WORD FOR IT.
AND BESIDES,
YOU'VE GOT HELP, YOU KNOW.
THAT INTENSE REDHEADED BRUTE,
THE GUYS IN THE TABOO
BREAKER SQUADRON,
HELL, EVEN FERRIS AND I
ARE ON BOARD...
AND LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOUR MAJESTY,
THAT'S KIND OF THE POINT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BEAR THIS ALL
BY YOURSELF. YOU'VE GOT US NOW.
- DO I?
- OF COURSE.
- IF ONLY...
IF ONLY THAT WERE TRUE.
I CAN THINK OF NOTHING
I WOULD WANT MORE.
BUT THE WORLD
HASN'T CHANGED. AT ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
- ( yelling )
- IZUCHI!
- ( both yelling )
- Ryner: SON OF A BITCH!
WHY DO THINGS ALWAYS
GO TO SHIT
JUST WHEN THEY'RE STARTING
TO GET BETTER?
YOU KNOW WHAT, SION?
I DON'T CARE!
COME AT ME WITH ALL YOU'VE GOT!
I TOLD YOU I WOULDN'T
GIVE UP, AND I WON'T!
NO MATTER HOW MUCH THIS TOTALLY,
COMPLETELY, TRAGICALLY SUCKS!