- HE'S LATE.
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO COMFORTABLY SPLIT
SEVEN BACKPACKS WORTH OF
DANGO BETWEEN US.
EXTREMELY.
RISE AND SHINE.
YOU'VE SLEPT ENOUGH TO FILL YOUR
QUOTA FOR THE YEAR.
- ( theme song playing )
- HEY, LUKE.
THIS IS REALLY BAD.
THE CAPTAIN'S GONE,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S HASN'T BEEN IN HER ROOM
SINCE YESTERDAY!
- THAT'S NOT LIKE HER.
SHE WOULDN'T HAVE GONE
WITHOUT LEAVE.
- OF COURSE SHE WOULDN'T.
THAT'S NOT THE CAPTAIN'S STYLE,
WE ALL KNOW THAT!
- YES. YES WE DO.
- ( inaudible )
- SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- TELL US YOU'VE GOT
SOME KIND OF PLAN.
- CALM DOWN. IN ALL LIKELIHOOD
THE CAPTAIN IS SIMPLY...
- ARE YOU ABOUT TO SPECULATE,
OR DO YOU ACTUALLY
KNOW WHERE SHE IS?
- SHE MIGHT BE IN THE
COMPANY OF RYNER LUTE.
- ( all gasping )
- Eslina: STAY WHERE
YOU ARE, PLEASE!
ONE JUST DOESN'T BARGE INTO
HIS MAJESTY'S QUARTERS,
SWORD IN HAND...
- WELL, HELLO THERE.
- I'M SO SORRY, SIR.
I REALLY TRIED TO STOP HER.
- IT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S SOMETHING LIKE AN
OLD FRIEND OF MINE.
- BUT, SIR, SURELY
YOU DON'T INTEND...
- ( clattering )
- OH, MY.
- THIS ISN'T OUT
OF THE ORDINARY.
THANK YOU, ESLINA.
IT'S FINE FOR YOU TO GO.
- VERY WELL, YOUR MAJESTY.
- SO, TO WHAT DO I OWE
THIS LITTLE TANTRUM?
- AS OF THIS MORNING,
RYNER'S GONE.
- WHAT?
I SEE. IS IT SAFE TO ASSUME
THE PROSPECT OF DESERTION
HELD MORE PROMISE
THAN THE IDEA OF
SHEPHERDING ME TO ESTABUL?
- YOU PLANNED TO ABSCOND
TOGETHER TO SPITE ME,
- BUT RYNER DIDN'T SHOW?
- YES.
- SO A GRAND TOUR OF
THE REGION'S DANGO
DIDN'T APPEAL TO HIM EITHER.
WAS HIS BEHAVIOR AT ALL
ODD YESTERDAY?
- NO. HE DID HAVE A
HEART-TO-HEART WITH MY BROTHER,
THOUGH. APPARENTLY.
- DID HE?
- I HAD A WORD WITH LUCILE
MYSELF BEFORE COMING HERE.
I THOUGHT RYNER MIGHT BE
SKULKING AROUND THE
MANOR GROUNDS, SO...
- AND? WHAT DID THEY
SAY TO EACH OTHER?
- HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW.
LUCILE WASN'T EXACTLY
AN OPEN BOOK.
- ( grunts ) DAMN IT, LUCILE.
WHAT WENT ON BETWEEN
THE TWO OF YOU?
AND JUST LIKE THAT, HE'S GONE?
- HE PROMISED...
HE PROMISED ME
HE WOULD CARRY THE PACKS.
HE GAVE ME HIS SOLEMN VOW.
- Calne: MAJESTY.
HEY, WHERE'VE YOU BEEN
SECRETING THIS DAZZLING NUMBER?
INTRODUCE US AND I WON'T
BETRAY YOUR HIDING PLACE.
OW! WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- YOU HAD AFFAIRS OF STATE
TO DISCUSS WITH HIS MAJESTY,
DID YOU NOT?
- UH, YES I DID IN FACT.
FIELD MARSHAL KLOM
SENDS THIS REPORT
FROM THE WILDERNESS OF ESTABUL.
- DOES HE?
AN ESPECIALLY
POWERFUL ALPHA STIGMA
HAS APPEARED IN THEIR MIDST.
HE HASN'T SEEN IT HIMSELF,
BUT THE TRAIL IS HOT.
CLAUGH HAS MARSHALED
TROOPS FROM BOTH SIDES
OF THE COMMON BORDER
TO TRY AND ALLAY THE THREAT.
- YOU DON'T THINK IT
COULD BE RYNER?
- THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
THE REPORT WAS WRITTEN
BEFORE HE DISAPPEARED.
- A POINT OF ORDER,
YOUR MAJESTY,
AN ALPHA STIGMA WOULD NOT
BE A WALK IN THE PARK,
EVEN FOR CLAUGH.
- I'LL DEPART FOR
ESTABUL IMMEDIATELY
AND OFFER WHAT HELP I CAN.
THAT WILL ENFORCE
THE NEW RULE
THAT ALPHA STIGMAS ARE TO BE
DETAINED, NOT SLAUGHTERED.
- DETAINED?
- OPPORTUNITIES TO STUDY AN
ALPHA STIGMA UP CLOSE
DO NOT GROW ON TREES.
AND AS FOR RYNER, I CHARGE
THE HUNT AND SEIZURE TO YOU.
EMPLOY THESE TWO AS YOU SEE FIT.
- DOES HE GENUINELY
BEAR AN ALPHA STIGMA?
- THERE'S NO MISTAKING IT.
HE'S REARED HIS HEAD
SPORADICALLY IN THIS
REGION FOR YEARS,
PREYING ON OUR CITIZENS.
DARK TRESSES.
SWATHED IN BLACK.
EYES LIKE PITCH
GILDED WITH VERMILLION
IN THE DREADED PATTERN.
HE'S NOT A TYPICAL
BEARER, EITHER.
THIS ONE ENGORGES ITSELF
ON HUMAN FLESH.
NEVER IMAGINED MYSELF HUNTING
THE CREATURE DOWN IN CLOSE RANKS
ALONGSIDE THE PHILANDERER
WHO STOLE OUR POOR
PRINCESS'S HEART.
LET'S HOPE ACCOUNTS OF
YOUR BATTLE PROWESS
PROVE AS SUCCESSFUL.
- "DARK TRESSES,
SWATHED IN ALL BLACK.
"EYES LIKE PITCH
GILDED WITH VERMILLION
IN THE DREADED PATTERN."
- ( groaning )
- MY, AREN'T YOU A
TASTY LOOKING MORSEL.
- THIS SHOULD PROVE INTERESTING.
- GRENSLADE. CAPITAL
OF THE GASTARK EMPIRE.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE SUCH
A TRANQUIL TOWN
HOSTS A PEOPLE CAPABLE OF
SACKING A NATION LIKE STOHL.
AND THE FOLKLORE
PECULIAR TO THIS PLACE!
STORIES OF RAVENOUS CREATURES
WHO DEVOUR HUMAN BEINGS WHOLE.
DESCENDANTS OF ANCIENT HEROES
WHO SOW CHAOS AND DESTRUCTION
LIKE PLAGUE RATS.
IF THE TALES WE PASS ON FROM
GENERATION TO GENERATION
ARE A TRUE INDICATION OF
OUR HOMELAND'S CHARACTER,
THIS REALM IS A
STRANGE ONE INDEED.
BUT AT LEAST I'VE FOUND
WHAT I CAME HERE FOR.
A PLACE THAT ABOUNDS IN A VERY
PARTICULAR TYPE OF MYTHIC FIGURE
THE SO-CALLED PEOPLE
OF THE MAGIC EYE,
EACH ONE BEARING
A DISTINCT SYMBOL,
DEPENDING ON THE
NATURE OF THEIR POWER.
THERE'S EBRA CRYPT,
WHICH SIGNIFIES THE ABILITY
TO PEER INTO THE
DREAMS OF ANOTHER.
IINO DUOE, WHICH IS SAID
TO FEAST ON HUMAN LIFE.
AND OF COURSE PROPER
ALPHA STIGMAS, ABLE TO ANALYZE,
COMPREHEND AND
DUPLICATE INSTANTLY
WHATEVER MAGIC THEY ENCOUNTER.
THERE'S ALSO THE TORCH
CURSE AND THE WILL HAME,
BOTH VERY POWERFUL.
AS THE RECORD STANDS NOW,
A TOTAL OF FIVE TYPES OF MAGIC
EYE HAVE BEEN CONFIRMED.
AT BIRTH, ALPHA STIGMA
BEARERS APPEAR NO DIFFERENT
FROM ORDINARY HUMAN CHILDREN.
IN SHORT ORDER, THOUGH,
IT BECOMES CLEAR
THAT THEY POSSESS A STARTLING
KNACK FOR DISCERNING TRUTH
FROM FALSEHOOD.
EVEN AS INFANTS.
THE DEEPER ARCHITECTURE OF
REALITY LAYS ITSELF BARE
BEFORE THEIR GAZE
WHEN ALL OTHERS SEE ONLY
THE SURFACE OF THINGS,
MAGIC COMES NATURALLY TO THEM,
BUT WITH THIS GIFT
COMES A PRICE.
CERTAIN TRIGGERS SEND THEM
SPIRALING OUT OF CONTROL.
IN THE THROES OF MADNESS,
THEY YEARN TO ERASE TRUTH,
TO DESTROY REALITY.
ONCE THEY'VE REACHED THAT POINT,
AN ALPHA STIGMA IS FOREVER
LOST TO REASON.
AND YET...
RYNER CAME BACK FROM THE ABYSS.
WHAT CAN THAT POSSIBLY MEAN?
DOES RYNER NOT BEAR AN
ALPHA STIGMA AFTER ALL?
IF SO, THEN...
A GODDESS? A DARK, BROKEN HERO
OF OLD AND A SOLITARY DEMON?
- Lefahl: KNEE-DEEP IN STUDIOUS
CONTEMPLATION, I SEE.
( chuckling )
- I DIDN'T NOTICE YOU COME IN.
- AN URGENT SIGN THAT YOU'RE IN
NEED OF A BREAK. GOOD TIMING.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO
MAKE MYSELF A POT OF TEA.
WOULD YOU CARE FOR SOME?
- YOU CAME TO MAKE YOURSELF TEA?
- ARE YOU SURPRISED?
IT'S MY COUNTRY.
- I'M FREE TO TAKE REFRESHMENT
WHERE I PLEASE.
- OF COURSE, BUT...
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS CHANCE.
AT LAST I'LL SHARE A POT
WITH KIEFER KNOLLS.
WHAT'S IN A NAME?
EVEN WHEN IT BELONGS TO THE
WOMAN YOU'VE FALLEN FOR...
- SO YOU'VE DONE
A LITTLE HOMEWORK.
- NOT AS MUCH AS I COULD HAVE.
- DOES IT MAKE A DIFFERENCE
TO A MAN OF YOUR STATURE,
KNOWING THE NAME OF
A PEON LIKE ME?
- WELL FOR ONE,
IT'S AN EFFECTIVE PREAMBLE
TO BEDDING YOU.
MY MEN WERE POISED TO UNEARTH
QUITE A BIT MORE ABOUT YOU,
BUT I CALLED THEM OFF.
WOULDN'T WANT TO LEECH THE SPORT
OUT OF THE CHASE, NOW WOULD I?
I MUCH PREFER YOU AND I
BE ON THE LEVEL.
- OH, PLEASE. YOU CAN'T
EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
YOU'RE THAT MUCH OF A ROMANTIC?
FOR ALL YOU KNOW,
I COULD BE ENGAGED IN ESPIONAGE.
- I LIKE TO THINK I'M AN
EXCELLENT JUDGE OF CHARACTER.
BESIDES, I'M SURE OUR MUTUAL
DISTASTE FOR WARFARE
GOES SOME WAY TOWARDS
BRIDLING YOUR CONSCIENCE.
- Kiefer: SHOULD I REJOICE IN
WAR WHEN ALL IT BRINGS IS DEATH,
DESTRUCTION AND PAIN!
- Lefahl: BLOODSHED, TEARS
AND MISERY, I ABHOR.
I'M CONFIDENT WHATEVER
KNOWLEDGE YOU GLEAN
FROM THIS COUNTRY'S LITERATURE
WILL BE PUT TO GOOD USE.
TO WHICH ENDS, TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF ME TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT.
MY HOMELAND IS YOURS TO ROAM.
JUST DON'T BE
RELUCTANT TO ANSWER
WHEN I CALL IN A
FAVOR DOWN THE ROAD.
- THAT'S VERY GENEROUS OF YOU,
BUT DON'T GET AHEAD OF YOURSELF.
BEFORE ANYTHING ELSE, WE SHOULD
AT LEAST SHARE A POT OF TEA.
- WHY, INDEED WE SHOULD.
- IT'S CLOSE BY.
- THAT'S HIM. I'M CERTAIN.
- YOUR EXCELLENCY,
LOOK OVER THERE!
- IT'S HIM.
SO, TODAY'S THE DAY. FINALLY.
- DID HE JUST...
-I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
HE CONSUMED A HUMAN BODY!
- EVERYONE KEEP YOUR CALM!
HOLD RANKS AT ANY COST!
GET IN FORMATION AND
PREPARE TO CAST!
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS. KILL
THE SON OF A BITCH! KILL HIM!
- ( all gasp )
- HUMAN BEINGS ARE SO
EXQUISITELY FRAGILE.
IF ONLY I'D LEFT ROOM
FOR DESSERT.
AH, WELL. I'LL SHOW
MYSELF OUT, THANK YOU.
- SNAP TO! KEEP HITTING HIM
WITH ALL YOU'VE GOT!
- ( screaming )
- I'D LOVE TO PLAY,
BUT I'M SEARCHING FOR SOMEONE.
SO NO OFFENSE, BUT I REALLY
DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
- EXCELLENCY!
- DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
THE MAN NEEDS BACKUP!
- ( grunting )
- ( screaming )
- FOR A MERE HUMAN
YOU'RE REMARKABLY FAST.
GOOD. I LIKE A DISH
WITH SOME KICK.
WAIT...
UNBELIEVABLE.
SOMEONE'S GROWN UP TO BE
A CHOICE CUT OF MEAT,
HAVEN'T THEY?
SO YOU DO REMEMBER, THEN.
THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
PREPARE TO LAMENT NOT KILLING
ME THE FIRST TIME WE MET,
YOU BASTARD!
( screaming )
( grunting )
- I THINK HE CAN WIN THIS!
- THAT ALPHA STIGMA DIDN'T SEE
THIS COMING. IF HE HAD A CLUE
WHAT WAS GOOD FOR HIM,
HE'D JUST TURN TAIL AND RUN.
- IT MUST BE SAID,
YOU'RE QUITE GOOD.
- HUMAN, HOWEVER...
- Bayouz: I OFFER UP A CONTRACT
TO UNLEASH THE BEAST
OF LIGHT THAT DANCES...
- THIS ONE IS FOR MY FRIENDS!
- THROUGH THE SKIES!
- MY. A BOLD MOVE.
I CONSUME POWER
AND LET IT SPRING!
( laughing maniacally )
- ( gasps )
- ( gasping )
- EXCELLENCY!
- WHAT THE HELL HAS HE DONE
TO THE FIELD MARSHAL!
- CRIMSON FINGERED CLAUGH'S
BEEN BESTED BY AN ALPHA STIGMA!
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
STAND FIRM, ALL OF YOU!
- JUST HOLD ON.
I'M DOING WHAT I CAN.
SIR? SIR?
- Tiir: WORDS CANNOT BEGIN TO
DESCRIBE HOW PLEASED I AM NOW
TO HAVE LEFT YOU ALIVE
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
AH, TO BE BRIMMING
WITH SUCH POWER!
WITH WHAT YOU'VE GIVEN ME
I COULD KILL EVERY MAN HERE.
INDEED I JUST MIGHT!
- ( all groaning )
- STOP TRYING TO PUSH
YOURSELF, EXCELLENCY.
WE HAVE TO RETREAT AND
GET YOU LOOKED AFTER.
- DON'T CODDLE ME!
I'M IN NO SHAPE TO RUN!
- LISTEN TO REASON...
- I'M GIVING YOU AN ORDER.
STEP OFF AND LET ME DO WHAT I
CAN TO DRIVE THIS MONSTER BACK.
IT'LL BUY YOU AND THE TROOPS
SOME TIME TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS...
- YOU GOT A PROBLEM DOING
WHAT YOU'RE TOLD?
DON'T THINK I WON'T CUT YOU DOWN
FOR DISOBEYING A DIRECT ORDER.
- SIR.
- WHEN YOU GET BACK HOME, GIVE
MY REGARDS TO SION AND NOA...
( grunting )
THE HELL?
- WHY DO YOU IMAGINE THE
PRINCESS WOULD GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT REGARDS SENT HER
BY A FIELD MARSHAL?
- VERY FUNNY.
ARROGANT SON OF A...
- PUT ME THE HELL DOWN.
- LOOK!
- PROTECT HIS EXCELLENCY!
- CLEAR A PATH SO FIELD MARSHAL
KLOM CAN RETREAT TO SAFETY!
- BLINDSIDED IDIOTS. EVERY
ONE OF THEM TO THE LAST MAN.
- MUST DO YOU PROUD.
TAKES A SPECIAL KIND OF IDIOT
TO BE A ROLAND SOLDIER.
I'M ONLY BAILING YOU OUT BECAUSE
I CAN'T STAND TO SEE YOU PEOPLE
STUMBLE ALL OVER EACH OTHER.
STAND YOUR GROUND, MEN!
SAVE THESE POOR DIMWITTED
BASTARDS FROM THEMSELVES.
ASSUME LARGE-SCALE
CASTING FORMATION!
- WHAT KIND OF STRATEGY IS THAT?
YOU RISK CATCHING YOUR OWN
TROOPS IN THE CROSSFIRE.
- YOUR PAL IN BLACK WILL
ABSORB THE SHOCK
BEFORE THERE'S ANY
COLLATERAL DAMAGE.
SHOULD BUY US A FEW SECONDS.
- FALL BACK!
- DAMN IT ALL.
DAMN IT TO HELL.
- CAPTAIN MILK.
LUKE BAKED YOU A CAKE
TO DIE FOR, CAPTAIN.
YOU'VE GOT NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE MISSING.
- I'M STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE WORRIED.
COME ON OUT, MILK!
- RYNER LUTE CHECKED OUT
OF HIS INN THIS MORNING
AND HASN'T BEEN SEEN SINCE.
CAPTAIN MILK WAS THE
LAST PERSON TO SPEAK WITH HIM.
THE EDICT...
I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK IT MIGHT
HAVE BEEN CLUMSY OF ME
TO ATTEMPT TO
ORCHESTRATE MATTERS
SO THAT HE'D BE SURE TO SEE IT.
I'M WELL AWARE OF YOUR PRESENCE.
COME, STEP INTO THE LIGHT.
THERE, THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
NOW WHAT CAN I DO FOR
YOU FINE GENTLEMEN?
- YOU SHOULD KNOW WE HAVE
MILK CALLAUD IN CUSTODY.
- AH. AND?
- WE'D APPRECIATE YOUR COMING
WITH US QUIETLY, LUKE STOKKART.
- WHAT IF I WERE TO REFUSE?
- ( chuckles ) YOUR YOUNG
CAPTAIN WON'T SURVIVE THE NIGHT.
- YES, OF COURSE.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THE CHANCE RYNER LUTE TOOK HER
WITH HIM WAS FAIRLY SLIM.
THIS MAKES MORE SENSE.
THE CAPTAIN DISAPPEARED,
NOT OF HER OWN VOLITION,
BUT BECAUSE YOU ABDUCTED HER.
- STOP BABBLING TO YOURSELF LIKE
A MADMAN. JUST DO AS WE SAY!
WHAT THE HELL?
- ( thudding )
- THAT'S RIGHT. YOU'RE MOORED
TO THE SPOT CARE OF MY MAGIC,
SO TRY NOT TO MOVE.
UNLESS OF COURSE YOU'RE
THE TYPE OF FECKLESS,
THICK-SKULLED ROGUE
WHO'D WELCOME OBLIVION.
IF IT'S ALL THE SAME
TO YOU, THOUGH,
I'D RATHER NOT BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE HORRIFIC DEATH
OF A FELLOW COUNTRYMAN.
- YOU HAVE NO CLUE
WHERE I'M FROM!
- YOUR MANNERISMS
BETRAY YOUR RANK.
YOU AND YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS
HAIL FROM THE ROLAND MILITARY.
WHICH MEANS THE
PERSON RESPONSIBLE
FOR YOUR CURRENT EMPLOYMENT
AND THE ABDUCTION
OF MILK CALLAUD,
NOT TO MENTION THE ATTEMPTED
ABDUCTION OF YOURS TRULY,
CAN BE NONE OTHER THAN
COLONEL MIRAN FROAUDE.
- IMPRESSIVE.
I CAN SEE YOU'RE CERTAINLY A
MAN WHO'S DONE HIS RESEARCH.
- MY DEEPEST APOLOGIES.
I DIDN'T KNOW...
( grunting )
- DO I HAVE THE PLEASURE
OF ADDRESSING THE SUBJECT
OF THAT RESEARCH?
- INDEED YOU DO.
IT'S AN HONOR TO MEET YOU.
I'VE DONE A FAIR SHARE OF
DIGGING ON YOU AS WELL.
TO REMAIN UNDEFEATED IN
UPWARDS OF TWENTY BATTLES
IS A RARE ACCOMPLISHMENT.
PARTICULARLY WHEN ONE
STOPS TO CONSIDER
THAT EACH OF THOSE
LITTLE SKIRMISHES
SAW YOU STAGGERINGLY
OUTNUMBERED.
- YOU HAVE DONE A
FAIR AMOUNT OF DIGGING.
ESPECIALLY WHEN ONE CONSIDERS
THAT IN MOST OF THOSE BATTLES
MY NAME WAS WITHHELD.
MY UTMOST APOLOGIES
FOR CONDESCENDING
TO PIT YOU AGAINST MEN WELL
BENEATH YOUR CALIBER.
- TELL ME WHERE YOU'RE
HOLDING CAPTAIN MILK.
- BEFORE WE DELVE INTO THAT,
PERMIT ME TO ASK A FAVOR
OF SOME IMPORT.
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO PERSONALLY
ELIMINATE RYNER LUTE
AS PER THE LATELY
PENNED ROYAL EDICT.
- I MUST RESPECTFULLY DECLINE.
I DON'T SEE WHY HE WOULD
BE ANY OF YOUR CONCERN.
- LET THERE BE DARKNESS!
WHAT IS THIS?
- STRUGGLE THE LEAST BIT
AND YOUR FINGERS,
PROBABLY YOUR ARMS,
WILL GO FLYING.
- THAT'S RIGHT. I PROMISED
TO CARRY THE DANGO, DIDN'T I?
POOR FERRIS.
SHE'S GONNA BE PISSED.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: CRAP. I SCRAMBLED TO
GET OUT OF TOWN SO FAST
I DIDN'T POCKET ENOUGH SCRATCH.
NOW HERE I AM A DAY
INTO MY ESCAPE
AND ALREADY FUNDS ARE LOW.
UGH! THIS SUCKS!
WHY DO WE EVEN NEED MONEY?
EH, NEVER MIND.
WHAT I NEED RIGHT NOW MORE
THAN ANYTHING IS FREE,
A FRIGGIN' NAP.