- ''I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,''
THE MAN AVOWED.
THE AUTHOR'S USE OF THE
WORD "LOVE" ELUDES ME.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN
IN THIS CONTEXT?
- MUST LOVE HAVE A CONTEXT
WITHIN WHICH TO THRIVE?
THE CONCEPT IS TRICKY. IT POINTS
TO A THING BEYOND WORDS.
SUCH ARE MY FEELINGS
FOR MY SISTER.
- I DON'T FOLLOW YOU.
ARE YOU SUGGESTING THAT YOU
FEEL FOR ME SOMETHING AKIN
TO WHAT IS WRITTEN HERE?
- ABSOLUTELY.
AS DOES OUR MOTHER,
AS DOES OUR FATHER
AND OF COURSE, LITTLE IRIS.
- IS TRAINING A BURDEN?
- UH-UH.
- THEN YOU IMPRESS ME
BEYOND WORDS.
- I TAKE IT YOU'RE BEING
COMPLIMENTARY?
- I PREFER TO SAY THAT
I'M BEING AFFECTIONATE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( gasps )
- ALAS MY DAUGHTER IS A
PERENNIAL DISAPPOINTMENT TO ME.
THE UNINTERRUPTED BLOODLINE
OF GREAT WARRIORS
CULMINATES IN HER,
AND SHE CANNOT HOLD A SWORD
AGAINST THE SIMPLEST BLOW.
- I WILL STAND FAST, MOTHER.
( grunting )
- YOU SULLY OUR NAME. TO THINK
IT WAS MY WOMB THAT BORE YOU.
YOUR EFFIGY WILL COME
TO SIGNIFY THE FAILURE
OF A ONCE GREAT HOUSE.
- THERE IS HOPE. SHE MAY WELL
BE USELESS AS A WARRIOR,
BUT THERE IS SOMETHING TO
BE SAID FOR HER BLOOD.
IT MAY HONOR THE GENIUSES OF
THIS FAMILY IN LESS OBVIOUS WAYS
THAN IN SERVICE TO THE SWORD.
- NO, FATHER, PLEASE DON'T.
- SHE COULD YET BE A VESSEL FOR
THOSE GREATER THAN HERSELF.
INDEED, EVEN SO PITIFUL A CHILD
MIGHT HONOR THE SEED
THAT BORE HER BY
BEARING IT IN TURN.
- I FEAR I DON'T UNDERSTAND
YOUR MEANING, MOTHER.
- NO, I DON'T IMAGINE
THAT YOU DO.
YOU FAIL ME IN EVERY
SENSE OF THE WORD.
BUT IF YOU MUST BE A FAILURE,
BE ONE WORTHY OF US.
- ( gasping )
( whimpering )
PLEASE, I BEG OF YOU, NO.
- ( loud thud )
- HELL SPAWN.
- MY SISTER IS NOT AN OBJECT
WITH WHICH YOU MAY SATISFY
YOUR SICKENING WHIMS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I SEE.
THEN MY SON, TOO, IS A FAILURE.
HOUSE ERIS WILL NOT SUFFER
A DE-GENERATIVE REJECT
LIKE YOU TO LIVE.
( groaning )
- I BEG TO DIFFER, FATHER.
PERHAPS IT IS YOU THE HOUSE
WILL NOT SUFFER TO LIVE.
- HOW COULD YOU
HAVE DONE THIS?
- THE GLORIES OF REBIRTH
FOLLOW THE LEES OF DESTRUCTION.
SUCH IS THE CYCLE.
DESTRUCTION, REBIRTH.
- YOU'RE USING THE TECHNIQUE.
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY...
- ( thudding )
- ( gasps )
- COME. SLOUGH OFF THE MANTEL OF
FEAR. THE TRAGEDY IS AT AN END.
FROM THIS MOMENT ON, I WILL BE
THE ONE TO PROTECT YOU.
AGAIN SHE SETS OUT. THE BOY
MUST REALLY BE SOMETHING.
- ( snoring )
- Ferris: THIS IS NO
TIME FOR SLEEP!
WE'VE AN EMERGENCY ON OUR HANDS.
- YOU HAVE TWO SECONDS
TO GET READY.
- HUH?
- A-ONE, A-TWO... ALRIGHT
THEN, GET ON YOUR FEET.
- Ryner: WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
EVEN DOING HERE THIS EARLY?
- AVERTING POTENTIAL
CATASTROPHE.
WHILE WE'VE BEEN
GALLIVANTING LANDS AWAY,
- THE DELICATE ECOLOGY OF DANGO
HERE AT HOME HAS ALTERED!
AN EMBARRASSMENT OF NEW
DANGO STALLS HAVE DESCENDED
ON ROLAND LIKE AN AVALANCHE.
FLAVORS UNKNOWN AND
COMBINATIONS UNTRIED AWAIT.
TELL ME YOUR HEART
DOESN'T BURST INTO SONG!
- IT WILL AFTER A FEW MORE
MINUTES OF SHUT-EYE.
- RYNER, YOU STILL WANT ME
TO BRING YOU SOME...
( gasps ) WHAT IS THIS?
NO, I REFUSE TO ACCEPT IT.
- WAKE UP, HANDSOME.
- C'MON SWEETIE. LET ME KEEP
SLEEPING AND DREAMING OF YOU.
- YOU FILTHY PHILANDERER!
- WHATEVER YOU'RE THINKING
RIGHT NOW, THIS IS NOT.
- I TRIED SO VERY HARD
TO RESIST AT FIRST,
BUT HIS MASTERY OF THE
SEDUCTIVE ARTS IS PEERLESS.
- HEY, YOUR SENSE OF HUMOR ISN'T
HELPING THE SITUATION AT ALL!
- WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
- I'M OFF. HAVE FUN, NOW.
- Milk: IZUCHI!
- Ryner: NO, NO, NO, NO...
- ( explosion )
- AH, SUCH LOVELY WEATHER
FOR DANGO, TOO.
- Milk: NO! LYING, STUPID,
BEASTLY MAN!
- ( Ryner screaming )
- I SEE YOU'VE TAKEN A SHINE TO
THE SLEEPING ACCOMMODATIONS.
- MY NAPS DON'T GET INTERRUPTED
BY DANGO-OBSESSED
PSYCHO-VIXENS HERE.
OR MY BED SET ON FIRE
BY LIGHTNING BOLT
WIELDING STALKERS.
- MY CONSCIENCE GIVES
ME NO END OF NOISE
FOR WHAT I'M ABOUT
TO ASK OF YOU.
- THEN DON'T ASK.
- I WOULD LIKE YOU AND
FERRIS TO ACCOMPANY ME
ON MY TRIP TO ESTABUL.
- SORRY, CAN'T HEAR YOU.
YOU'LL HAVE TO SPEAK UP, OR
BETTER YET, JUST LEAVE.
- IT'S AN IMPORTANT MISSION.
I NEED AN ESCORT.
I'M NOT SAFE OUTSIDE OF ROLAND.
- YOU CAN HAVE YOUR
PICK OF BODYGUARDS,
WHAT THE HELL'D YOU
NEED THE TWO OF US FOR?
- WELL, I, I FEEL YOU
BOTH ARE THE ONLY ONES
I CAN TRUST WITH MY SAFETY.
- WHAT?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO ACCEPT
MY REQUEST IF YOU DON'T WISH.
JUST BEAR IN MIND, AS KING,
I DON'T HAVE TO GO
EASY ON YOU EITHER.
THERE ARE MUCH HARDER JOBS
THAN SERVING AS MY GUARD.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I DON'T BELIEVE YOUR NERVE,
THAT WAS TOTALLY A THREAT!
- OH, SOMETHING ELSE.
I BRING NEWS REGARDING THE
PRECOCIOUS ALPHA STIGMA CHILD
YOU BROUGHT BACK.
HE'S BEEN PLACED WITH
HOUSE ERIS FOR NOW.
- HOUSE ERIS? YOU MEAN ARUA'S
BEEN PUT UP WITH FERRIS' FAMILY?
- YES, THEIR CLAN IS WHAT'S
COMMONLY REFERRED TO
AS A FAMILY OF THE SWORD.
SO THE BOY SHALL BE
WELL-PROTECTED.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
- YOU COULD PAY HIM A VISIT
OR I COULD ASSIGN YOU A JOB.
- BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT,
COME TO THINK OF IT
I DO HAVE BUSINESS WITH ARUA.
LET'S REVISIT THIS ANOTHER TIME.
- BEST RETURN TO WORK
BEFORE SLEEP BECKONS.
- ( yawning )
SO MUCH FOR GETTING BACK HOME
AND CATCHING UP ON MY
AFTERNOON NAPS.
- Miller: IT TOOK SOME
DIGGING TO FIND IT,
BUT I BELIEVE THIS IS WHAT
YOU WERE LOOKING FOR.
- I APPRECIATE YOUR HELP.
WE'RE ALL IN YOUR DEBT.
- IT'S A MUCH MORE VALUABLE
BOOK THAN I FIRST THOUGHT.
ONLY A HANDFUL
OF COPIES STILL EXIST,
SCATTERED ACROSS THE
ENTIRE CONTINENT.
- WELL, I'M NOT AT ALL SURPRISED
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
I HAVE EVERY HOPE
IT'LL BE A VITAL RESOURCE...
- FIND SOMETHING USEFUL
AT FIRST BLUSH?
- OH, NO, NOTHING SO
SERENDIPITOUS AS THAT, I FEAR.
IT'S JUST, ONE GETS
ENGROSSED BY THE DATA.
I'LL HAVE TO COMB THIS BOOK
IN FINE DETAIL.
- "BEARERS OF THE ALPHA STIGMA
INEVITABLY LOSE CONTROL.
"AND LOSING CONTROL,
THEY PERISH, INEVITABLY.
"POUR FAR AND WIDE
THOUGH A SEEKER MAY,
"NO HISTORIC EXCEPTION
TO THIS WILL BE FOUND."
THAT CAN'T BE ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
RYNER DEFINITELY LOST CONTROL
ON THE FIELDS OF ESTABUL.
BUT HE SURVIVED.
THERE'S NOTHING NEW HERE.
GASTARK IS SUPPOSED TO BE
RICH IN FOLKLORE
SURROUNDING THE SO-CALLED
PEOPLE OF THE MAGIC EYE, THOUGH.
MAYBE IT'S TIME.
- WHOA.
WELL, OKAY.
THAT IS IMPRESSIVE.
- THE HEARTIEST OF WELCOMES
TO YOU, MASTER LUTE, SIR.
YOU DO US HONOR BY YOUR VISIT.
YOUNG MASTER ARUA AND
YOUNG LADY KUKU AWAIT YOU.
- Ryner: SO, UH, THE TWO OF 'EM
HAVE TAKEN TO THIS PLACE?
- Kroselli: OH, YES,
QUITE SO, SIR.
THOUGH THEY'VE BEEN BOUNCING
ON THEIR HEELS ALL MORNING
AT THE PROSPECT OF YOUR
COMING HERE, IT MUST BE SAID.
- WHAT'S THAT THING?
- THE DOJO, SIR.
IT FUNCTIONS THESE DAYS
PRIMARILY AS THE DOMICILE
OF HIS LORDSHIP LUCILE,
THE FAMILY'S STANDING PATRIARCH.
- SO THAT'S WHERE FERRIS'
OLD MAN LIVES?
- NO, SIR. LUCILE IS HER
LADYSHIP'S ELDER BROTHER.
- WHAT ABOUT THEIR, UH...
- A TRAGEDY, I'M AFRAID.
- I SEE...
IF I CAN BE FRANK WITH YOU,
I BET THEIR DEATHS
WERE A BREATH OF FRESH
AIR AROUND HERE.
NO WARRIOR AS SKILLED AS FERRIS
COULD'VE HAD AN EASY CHILDHOOD.
SHE SUFFERED A LOT OF ABUSE
TO GET WHERE SHE IS.
SORRY TO ASK, BUT HOW OLD
WAS SHE WHEN THEY FINALLY DIED?
- THE PRIOR PATRIARCH MET
HIS END ALONG WITH HIS WIFE
AT THE CUSP OF HER LADYSHIP'S
FOURTEENTH BIRTHDAY.
- SCARRED FOR FOURTEEN YEARS.
- THAT'S A HELL OF A LONG TIME.
- QUITE SO, SIR.
BUT, IF I MAY VENTURE
A SMALL RAY OF HOPE,
SHE IS NOW SURROUNDED
BY FINE PEOPLE
LIKE YOURSELF AND HIS MAJESTY.
- Iris: STAND ASIDE!
- ( groans )
- LOOK OUT, KROSELLI!
YOU MUSTN'T LET THE WICKED
BEAST NEAR YOU.
THE SLIGHTEST BRUSH WITH
HIS KIND CAN SADDLE
EVEN THE MOST VIRTUOUS
PEOPLE WITH CHILD!
- ( groaning ) OW.
- MR. RYNER!
- LOOK SHARP, GANG!
WE'VE GOT OURSELVES
A WICKED BEAST TO CATCH.
- I'LL COVER HIS LEFT WHILE
ARUA FLANKS HIS RIGHT!
- YOU GOT IT, IRIS!
- LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY'S
BEEN TOTALLY TAMED BY...
( groaning )
- BIG SISTER FERRIS!
- YOU'VE SOME NERVE CAUSING
A RUCKUS ON THESE GROUNDS.
- JUST SO WE'RE
CLEAR, I'M NOT NOW,
NOR HAVE I EVER BEEN YOUR
PERSONAL SANDBAG.
- WOW THIS DANGO STUFF
REALLY IS GOOD.
- I'VE NEVER TASTED
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
CAN'T POSSIBLY BE FULL.
- NOT ONE OF THEM IS
BLAND, PRECISELY,
BUT THEY LACK ANY SUBTLETY.
PERHAPS MY PALATE IS
OVERWHELMED BY QUANTITY?
DIFFICULT TO SAY AT PRESENT.
I SUSPECT THE FINER OVERTONES
OF EACH INDIVIDUAL VARIETY...
- Kroselli: IT FUNCTIONS
PRIMARILY AS THE DOMICILE
OF HIS LORDSHIP LUCILE,
THE FAMILY'S STANDING PATRIARCH.
- ( whimpering )
( gasping )
( screaming )
- Arua: MR. RYNER?
IS SOMETHING WRONG? YOU
LOOK LIKE YOU'VE SEEN A GHOST.
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
I'VE GOT A TINY LITTLE
FAVOR TO ASK YOU.
MIND USING YOUR ALPHA STIGMA
TO TAKE A QUICK LOOK
INSIDE THAT DOJO?
- SURE, NO PROBLEM.
IS THIS THE FIRST PART OF
MY NEXT TRAINING LESSON?
- YOU COULD CALL IT THAT,
I SUPPOSE.
IF THINGS START GETTING
DODGY THOUGH,
I WANT YOU TO CLOSE
YOUR EYES TIGHT.
- UNDERSTAND?
- YEAH, I GOT IT.
OKAY, NOW WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO DO?
- WAIT, YOU MEAN YOU DON'T,
LIKE, SEE ANYTHING?
- WELL, I CAN SEE
INSIDE THE DOJO.
- RIGHT. VERY GOOD, THEN,
CLASS IS DISMISSED.
- ( snoring )
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
HE ACTUALLY WANTS US
TO ESCORT HIM ALL THE
WAY TO FRIGGIN' ESTABUL.
- SO, WHAT YOU'RE ESSENTIALLY
TELLING ME IS THAT
YET AGAIN WE'RE BEING
WORKED TO THE BONE
BY OUR TYRANNICAL,
SLAVE-DRIVER OF A KING?
WHY AM I NOT THE LEAST BIT
SURPRISED BY THIS?
I SAY WE RESUME OUR SEARCH
FOR HERO RELICS INSTEAD.
- YEAH, THAT'D REALLY GET
HIS GOAT, WOULDN'T IT?
WHEN WERE YOU THINKIN'
WE SHOULD PUSH OFF?
- TOMORROW MORNING. I'M
ASSIGNING THE WYNITT DANGO SHOP
AS OUR SECRET RENDEZVOUS POINT.
- AH. GOTTA STOCK UP
FOR THE JOURNEY, RIGHT.
- WE CAN COMFORTABLY SPLIT
SEVEN BACKPACKS BETWEEN US.
- SEVEN BACKPACKS'
WORTH OF DANGO?
- Kroselli: IF I MAY VENTURE
A SMALL RAY OF HOPE,
SHE IS NOW SURROUNDED
BY FINE PEOPLE
LIKE YOURSELF AND HIS MAJESTY.
- OR HOW ABOUT
I GO YOU ONE BETTER?
I'LL CARRY ALL SEVEN
DANGO-PACKS BY MY LONESOME.
- REALLY? DARE I HOPE.
YOU'VE FINALLY COME
TO APPRECIATE
THE EXQUISITE ART OF DANGO.
METHINKS THIS CALLS FOR
FOURTEEN BACKPACKS!
- THIS IS WHAT I GET
FOR TRYING TO BE NICE.
FERRIS AND THE KIDS
ARE BOUND TO BE OFF
SKIPPING THROUGH
DREAMLAND BY NOW.
TIME FOR ME TO FIND OUT
WHOSE WATCH THEY'RE UNDER.
HELLO THERE. YOU MUST BE
FERRIS' BIG BROTHER, AM I RIGHT?
- LUCILE ERIS AT YOUR SERVICE. I
PRESUME THEN YOU ARE RYNER LUTE?
MY SISTER APPEARS TO GET ON
EXTRAORDINARILY WELL WITH YOU.
I'VE BEEN HOPING FOR A CHANCE
TO CONFER WITH YOU IN PRIVATE.
WELL DONE.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN FLINCH.
I'D SAY YOUR POWERS ARE,
FOR ALL INTENTS AND PURPOSES,
ON PAR WITH FERRIS.
- NICE OF YOU TO SAY,
BUT I'VE GOTTA DISAGREE.
IF SHE EVER GETS SERIOUS,
I'M A DEAD MAN.
- EVEN SO, IT PUTS ME AT EASE
TO SEE HER PARTNERED WITH YOU.
YOU'LL BOTH BE CONDUCTING
HIS MAJESTY TO ESTABUL, CORRECT?
IS IT FOOLISH OF ME
TO HAVE FAITH
IN YOUR ABILITY TO PROTECT HIM?
- TRUST ME, WE'VE
HANDLED A LOT WORSE.
THE THING IS, THOUGH,
ISN'T PROTECTING HIM YOUR FORTE?
KINDA FUNNY SION WOULD
ASK FERRIS AND ME
TO BE HIS BODYGUARDS.
I MEAN, HE'S GOT YOU.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU'RE
ONLY ABLE TO DO YOUR THING
FROM HOME BASE, SO TO SPEAK.
I DON'T MEAN TO PRY,
BUT IS THERE SOMETHING
KEEPING YOU HERE?
LIKE, MAYBE...
SOME SORT OF A BINDING-CURSE?
- WHAT, PRAY TELL, WOULD
SUCH A THING LOOK LIKE
IF ONE WERE TO
BRUSH UP AGAINST IT?
SUCH AN IMAGINATION YOU HAVE.
- YOU CAN CHALK THIS UP
TO IMAGINATION,
BUT I CAN SEE IT WITH MY
OWN EYES, OR RATHER I CAN'T.
YOUR PRESENCE DOESN'T EVEN CAST
A SHADOW ON MY ALPHA STIGMA.
SO JUST WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU, EXACTLY?
- APART FROM FERRIS'
OLDER BROTHER,
NO ONE OF ANY CONSEQUENCE.
- DON'T PLAY GAMES WITH ME,
DAMMIT, FERRIS IS A HUMAN BEING.
THERE'S NO WAY THE TWO
OF YOU ARE RELATED.
( gasps )
WAIT... I JUST...
I WANTED TO KNOW...
- WHAT A KIND THING FOR YOU
TO INTIMATE ABOUT HER.
THAT SHE ISN'T THE MONSTER
HER ELDER BROTHER IS, I MEAN.
FERRIS IS INDEED HUMAN.
QUITE UNLIKE YOU OR I.
TO THAT END, I'D LIKE YOU
TO KEEP THIS IN MIND.
TO BE BLUNT,
I WILL TOLERATE ABSOLUTELY NO
ENCROACHMENT UPON MY SISTER.
YOUR BLOOD WILL NEVER
MINGLE WITH HERS.
HARBOR AMOROUS FANTASIES
AT YOUR PERIL.
- YOU THINK I'VE GOT
DESIGNS ON HER?
- COME NOW.
I'M ONLY BEING CAUTIOUS.
YOU'VE A TALENT FOR
IMPROBABLE DREAMS, AFTER ALL.
DREAMS FOR A WORLD WITHOUT WAR.
WHAT BASTION CAN YOU HOPE
TO ERECT AGAINST BLOODSHED,
WITH YOUR HANDS DYED IN
THE BLOOD OF INNOCENTS?
SUCH HANDS ARE USEFUL
FOR ONE THING ONLY.
PARADOXICAL THOUGH IT MAY SOUND,
THAT IS WHY I AM PLEASED THAT
YOU AND MY SISTER ARE PAIRED.
YOU DAREN'T TOUCH HER,
YOU DAREN'T TOUCH ANYONE.
NOT WHEN YOU FIND
LIFE ITSELF REPUGNANT.
DESPAIR NOT, RYNER LUTE.
- ( screaming )
- THIS ENCOUNTER DOES NOT
MAKE US ENEMIES.
GO WITH MY BLESSING AND
LOOK AFTER MY BELOVED SISTER.
- Milk: AH-HA! THERE YOU ARE!
WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE YOU
UP TO SO LATE IN THE EVENING?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOUR COLOR'S NOT GOOD.
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
I'LL BE FINE.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING
UP SO LATE?
- UH, WELL... I KIND OF... UM...
HERE! THE SQUAD'S HOLDING
A LITTLE BIRTHDAY GET-TOGETHER
FOR ME TOMORROW.
IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
I'D REALLY LIKE YOU TO BE THERE.
- WELL, I UH...
- TOMORROW MORNING I'VE
ASSIGNED THE WYNITT DANGO SHOP
AS OUR SECRET RENDEZVOUS POINT.
- LUKE'S DOING ALL THE
COOKING HIMSELF,
WHICH MEANS THE FOOD WILL BE
SOMETHING YOU DON'T WANNA MISS,
BELIEVE ME.
HE'S SO SWEET, HE MADE ALL THE
INVITATIONS COMPLETELY BY HAND.
- SO YOU'RE GONNA COME?
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
- WELL, I DON'T. AT LEAST
NOT MY REAL ONE ANYWAY.
SEE THE GUYS... I MEAN THE SQUAD
THOUGHT TOMORROW WAS PERFECT.
BECAUSE IT'S THE ANNIVERSARY
OF WHEN THE SQUAD WAS FORMED.
SO IT'S KIND OF BETTER
THAN MY REAL ONE!
AND IF YOU WERE THERE,
IT'D BE PERFECTION ITSELF.
- CAN'T REALLY BACK OUTTA THIS.
I GUESS HOLDING OFF FOR
ONE DAY WON'T BE TOO BAD.
I CAN APPEASE FERRIS BY
HELPING HER PLAN SION'S DEMISE.
THAT'S ALWAYS GOOD
FOR BUYING US A LITTLE TIME.
- I'M SO SORRY, CAPTAIN,
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
IF A TABOO BREAKER OF
HIS TYPE LOSES CONTROL,
IT WOULD MEAN THE END OF HIM.
AND I CAN'T BEAR TO SEE YOU
SUFFER THAT LOSS.
FORGIVE ME. THIS WAS THE ONLY
THING I COULD THINK OF
TO AVOID A TRAGEDY.
- ( chuckles excitedly )
I GAVE HIM THE INVITATION.
AND IF HE COMES TOMORROW,
IT WILL OFFICIALLY BE THE
BEST BIRTHDAY EVER.
- "IF THE ALPHA STIGMA BEARER,
RYNER LUTE, LOSES CONTROL,
"OR SHOWS SIGNS
OF LOSING CONTROL,
"OR BEHAVES IN A
MANNER CONSISTENT
WITH AN ACT OF TREASON
"AGAINST ROLAND WHILE
TRAVELING ABROAD,
"HE IS TO BE EXECUTED.
"SIGNED AND SEALED BY
HIS ROYAL HIGHNESS, SION ASTAL."
- Lucile: COME NOW.
I'M ONLY BEING CAUTIOUS.
YOU'VE A TALENT FOR
IMPROBABLE DREAMS, AFTER ALL.
- I GET IT NOW.
I SHOULD'VE SEEN IT.
I'D DO THE SAME THING
IN HIS PLACE.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: I'VE KNOWN THIS FOR
AS LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER.
SO LONG AS I'M AROUND,
THINGS WILL ALWAYS GO TO SHIT.
BUT HEY, I GUESS
THAT'S LIFE, RIGHT?
TELL YOU WHAT, WHY DON'T YOU
PEOPLE LEAVE ME THE HELL ALONE?