- Iris: THE ONLY THING MORE
TERRIBLE THAN A WICKED BEAST,
IS ONE WHO'S MADE OFF
WITH YOUR BIG SISTER
LIKE A THIEF IN THE NIGHT.
OH, HOW AWFUL IT MUST BE
HAVING TO EAT STRANGE DANGO
IN FOREIGN LANDS.
NOT KNOWING THE FLAVOR
UNTIL YOU BITE INTO IT.
BLEH! STILL, MAYBE SHE STUMBLED
ON SOME AMAZING NEW TASTE
THAT WILL CHANGE THE WAY
SHE LOOKS AT THE WORLD.
THIS IS SO THE LAST THING
I WANT TO DO
BUT HIS MAJESTY DID ENTRUST ME
WITH A SPECIAL RESPONSIBILITY.
( chuckles )
ALL DONE.
RISE AND SHINE, SIR.
- WHY ARE YOU SITTING
AT MY DESK, IRIS?
BECAUSE I WROTE A REPORT.
I CALL IT "THE PRINCESS
AND THE WICKED BEAST."
- ( theme song playing )
- Iris: THE WICKED BEAST
TOOK ONE LOOK AT THE THRONE
AND WENT SLACK-JAWED.
- Sion: TO BE EXPECTED.
TO BID YOU A FAIR WELCOME
IN THE COURTLY MANOR, HI.
- THE FOUL CREATURE HAD NO IDEA
WHO'D BECOME KING
WHILE HE WAS BUSY NAPPING
HIS LIFE AWAY IN A PRISON CELL.
- I DON'T SUPPOSE SO.
- IF YOU ASK ME,
EVERYONE IN THIS STORY WOULD
HAVE BEEN BETTER OFF,
IF YOU'D JUST KEPT HIM LOCKED
AWAY FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE.
- WELL, LET'S JUST SAY
SOMETHING TOLD ME IT WAS PRUDENT
TO GIVE HIM A SECOND CHANCE.
- YEAH, BUT WHAT IF HE'D
ALREADY BLOWN THE SECOND CHANCE
SOMEONE ELSE GAVE HIM
AND THAT'S WHY HE WAS TOSSED
IN THE CLINK TO START WITH?
- RYNER'S SITUATION
WAS RATHER UNIQUE.
- ( grunts ) YOUR MAJESTY'S GOT
A SOFT SPOT FOR PERVIES
THAT KNOW HOW TO MASH
A FEW PRETTY WORDS TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHY YOU FORGAVE HIM.
- ( chuckles ) NOT EXACTLY.
BUT WHEN THE WORDS,
THEY "MASH" TOGETHER
CAN POTENTIALLY
CHANGE THE WORLD,
THAT'S ANOTHER
MATTER ALTOGETHER.
- RYNER? CHANGE THE WORLD?
( chuckles )
- WHAT HE WROTE MAY HAVE
THE POWER TO STEER US ALL CLEAR
OF A VERY BAD END.
ITS CENTRAL IDEA SEEMED TO ME
TO POSSESS WHAT SOME
PEOPLE CALL VISION.
- VISION? WAIT A SEC. WE LOOK AT
WORDS, NOT THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
ER, ADULTS MAKE
NO SENSE SOMETIMES.
- OW.
- GOOD AFTERNOON, YOUR MAJESTY.
- TAKE CARE OF YOUR CHARGE.
- LET GO OF ME!
- QUIT STRUGGLING, PERVERT.
- STOP CALLING ME THAT!
- AND SO THE WICKED BEAST
WAS SENT ON A MISSION,
WITH THE BEAUTIFUL,
VIRTUOUS PRINCESS IN TOW.
BY A ROYAL DECREE, THEY WERE
ORDERED TO UNCOVER HERO RELICS
AND BRING THEM HOME
TO THE KING.
- I DIDN'T ORDER THEM.
I ASKED THEM AS A FRIEND.
- THE FIRST RELIC
THEY UNCOVERED,
MYSTERIOUSLY GREW
A HUNDRED TIMES
IT'S ORIGINAL SIZE IN A FLASH.
- Ryner: IT'S POINTLESS,
I DON'T SEE A THING!
- Iris: THE SECOND ONE,
HE GOT IMPATIENT WITH
AND THREW TO THE GROUND,
UNLEASHING A NASTY SURPRISE.
- THINGS DON'T ALWAYS WORK OUT
QUITE AS YOU EXPECT THEM TO.
- WAIT, HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN WEARING THAT?
- OH. I PICKED IT UP
IN THE RUINS.
- Iris: HE STOLE A LOVELY
PIECE OF JEWELRY
THE PRINCESS HAD EVERY
RIGHT TO WEAR,
AND BEING THE EPITOME OF EVIL,
HE TURNED IT INTO A WEAPON
THAT MADE THE GROUND UNDER
THEIR FEET TREMBLE FOR MILES.
NO, NOT EVEN MOUNTAINS
ARE SAFE FROM WICKED BEASTS.
LAND SURVEYORS AND MAPMAKERS
WHO'D SPENT THEIR WHOLE LIVES
CHARTING THE REGION,
SHUFFLED LISTLESSLY BACK TO
THEIR DRAWING BOARDS IN DEFEAT.
- Sion: PERHAPS, THE
CARTOGRAPHY GUILD
SAW IT AS A BLESSING
IN DISGUISE.
I DOUBT, OF COURSE, THE MOUNTAIN
SHARED THEIR ENTHUSIASM.
- Ryner: ( gasps )
SOMEONE'S STILL KICKING.
NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU GO ON AHEAD, FERRIS.
I'LL CATCH UP TO YOU AS SOON
AS I'M DONE HERE.
- ALWAYS KEEP IN MIND
THAT HIS EVIL KNOWS NO BOUNDS.
IT'S IMPORTANT ENOUGH TO SAY
ALOUD AT LEAST TWO TIMES.
YOUR MAJESTY, FOR YOUR OWN GOOD,
REPEAT AFTER ME.
BEING FRIENDLY WITH
THE WICKED BEAST
WILL PUT A BABY IN
YOUR TUMMY! GO!
- BEING FRIENDLY
WITH THE WICKED BEAST
WILL PUT A BABY IN YOUR TUMMY.
- ( snoring )
- IN HIS HALF-HEARTED SEARCH
FOR HERO RELICS,
THE WICKED BEAST RUMMAGED
THROUGH THE LIBRARIES
OF NEIGHBORING KINGDOMS.
- STUPID LITTLE...
- ( groans )
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- Iris: OF COURSE, PRESENTED
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR WICKEDNESS, THE BEAST
MADE NO BONES ABOUT
TRYING TO STEAL AN INNOCENT
LITTLE GIRL'S FAVORITE BOOK.
FORTUNATELY, THE
PRINCESS WAS THERE
TO MAKE SURE JUSTICE PREVAILED,
AND GAVE THE BEAST
A STERN LESSON.
- ( grunts )
- Sion: HMM. PERHAPS,
YOU MEAN LESION.
- ALWAYS BEWARE OF
THE CHARMING BEAST,
HE HAS MANY TRICKS WITH WHICH
TO LURE THE UNSUSPECTING.
- ( groans) I'M GOING
TO KILL YOU.
( yawns )
- HELLO, OLD FRIEND.
I HAVE MISSED YOU TERRIBLY.
- Iris: THEIR TRAVEL FUNDS
WERE WAY TOO MUCH
FOR SUCH A SIMPLE MISSION.
SO TO MAKE UP THE DIFFERENCE,
HIS MAJESTY PUT THEM
ON A SECOND JOB.
- Sion: WELL, WE COULDN'T
JUST LET THEM VACATION
AT THE CROWN'S EXPENSE,
NOW COULD WE?
- Iris: RUMOR HAD IT
THAT SHADOWY ASSASSINS
WOULD SEE HIS MAJESTY'S
JOURNEY TO NELPHA
AS A CHANCE TO STRIKE HIM DOWN.
THE WICKED BEAST DID A
LOT MORE COMPLAINING
THAN GUARDING, THOUGH.
- Ryner: I'M EXHAUSTED.
AND FOR THE RECORD, THIS SUCKS.
REMIND ME WHY WE LET SION
TALK US INTO THIS FARCE?
- Iris: TO WHICH
THE PRINCESS REPLIED...
- WELL, IT'S EITHER BE HIS
TEMPORARY BODY GUARDS,
OR THE WYNNIT DANGO SHOP
WILL BE DECIMATED.
- SO, UH, I TAKE THAT TO MEAN
YOU'RE NOT WORRIED FOR HIM.
- Iris: SENSITIVE TO
THE BUSINESS STRATEGIES
OF REGIONALLY AFFILIATED
MARKET SHARE COMPETITORS,
THE PRINCESS SAW HER
OWN KINGDOM'S CHANCE
TO SITUATE ITSELF WITH A BROADER
ECONOMIC CONTEXT.
- WELL, I WOULDN'T NECESSARILY
CALL THE DANGO INDUSTRY BROAD,
BUT IT WAS CERTAINLY
UNDER THREAT.
- TO GUARANTEE THAT THE BEAST
STAYED ON HIS BEST BEHAVIOR,
WHILE WANDERING ABROAD
WITH SUCH A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN,
HIS MAJESTY APPOINTED AN ELITE
FORCE TO KEEP TABS ON HIM.
- AND WHEN THOUGHTS OF SLAYING
YOUR FORMER BRETHREN AIL YOU,
MAY THOUGHTS OF JUSTICE
SPUR YOU ON.
KNOW THIS, THE ETERNAL
THANKS OF YOUR KING
GOES WITH YOU ON YOUR QUEST.
- AND WE, YOUR SQUIRES,
ARE GRATEFUL FOR IT.
MY LORD, I GLADLY ACCEPT,
WHATEVER MAY BEFALL US.
I GAVE UP ONCE. I TURNED
MY BACK ON THE IDEA OF HOPE.
I SOUGHT TO CLOSE MY EYES
TO THE TROUBLES OF THE WORLD
AND SLEEP IN APATHY.
BUT THEN...
A GOOD FRIEND OF MINE
FROM CHILDHOOD,
GAVE ME THE STRENGTH
TO CARRY ON WITH MY LIFE.
SO, YOU SEE, I OWE HIM.
FOR GIVING ME THE COURAGE
I NEEDED TO VENTURE FORWARD.
I SWEAR IT. I GLADLY ACCEPT THE
MISSION WITH PRIDE, MY LIEGE.
- Iris: NEVER ONE TO MISS OUT
ON DOING WHATEVER HE PLEASED,
THE WICKED BEAST EVEN STIRRED
UP TROUBLE IN A TOMB.
HORSING AROUND CARELESSLY
WITH SHARP OBJECTS,
TRYING TO PLAY THE SYMPATHY CARD
BY GETTING BURNT TO A CRISP.
- Sion: SURELY THERE ARE BETTER
WAYS TO ELICIT SYMPATHY
THAN BY ROASTING ONE'S SELF.
- ( gasps ) RYNER!
- Ryner: WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
YOU ENJOYED THAT.
- Iris: THE PRINCESS WAS ALERT
TO THE TOMB'S DANGERS AT ONCE,
AND DID HER BEST TO WARN
THE STUPID CREATURE.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- BEHIND YOU.
- Iris: SADLY, THE CUR WAS
AS DUMB AS HE WAS DERANGED,
SHOUTING TO HIS
WOULD-BE RESCUER.
- YOU ARE SO DEAD WHEN
I FIND A WAY OUT OF THIS.
- Iris: SO MUCH FOR GRATITUDE.
- NOT COOL, I COULD'VE BEEN...
- OH, ANGRY BUTTERFLIES.
- Ryner: WHO ARE YOU?
- I... ( gasps )
( screams )
- Sion: I'VE GOT
A TRIVIA QUESTION FOR YOU.
- Iris: UH... OH, DARN.
UM...
( Iris replies )
- Sion: CLOSE, BUT NOT QUITE.
- AND YOU ARE NONE OTHER THAN
OUR QUARRY, A TABOO BREAKER.
- ( Iris speaking )
- Sion: GETTING COLDER.
( Iris speaking )
- Sion: ONLY IF RYNER
WERE CAPTAIN.
- HUH?
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
FERRIS. BUT I'M STARVING.
- HMM. YOU KNOW, DANGO
WOULD BE THE PERFECT ANTIDOTE
TO THE AIR IN THIS PLACE.
- DON'T THINK
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT SADISTIC TROLLOP HAS
FIENDISHLY ENSNARED YOU
BY HER WILES. IT'S OBVIOUS.
- BELIEVE IN YOURSELF,
YOU CAN BREAK FREE OF HER.
I'LL WHISK YOU AWAY TO SAFETY.
- I SEE, THIS LITTLE FIREBRAND
WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO BE ONE
OF YOUR MANY VICTIMS,
NOW WOULD SHE? SOMEONE YOU TOOK
ADVANTAGE OF AND LEFT FOR DEAD?
- ENOUGH WITH THE PERV THING!
- HEY, WAIT, I HAVEN'T BEEN
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF.
- OH, SO SHE GAVE HERSELF
TO YOU WILLINGLY, MY MISTAKE.
- Both: NOTHING HAPPENED!
- THE TRUTH BECAME
ALL TOO PLAIN.
THE ELITE FORCE WAS LED BY ONE
OF THE BEAST'S EARLY VICTIMS,
WHO HE'D LEFT TO ROT.
THE PRINCESS
WORRIED THE BEAST
WOULD SOON SET HIS SIGHTS ON
HER OWN VIRTUE.
- TRUE TO HIS NATURE, I SUPPOSE.
THE MAN DOES LIKE TO
CAST HIS NETS WIDE.
- NOT LONG AFTER, A LETTER
TO HIS MAJESTY ARRIVED
FROM THE WICKED BEAST,
CLAIMING HE AND THE PRINCESS'
SEARCH FOR HERO RELICS
HAD BEEN RUDELY INTERRUPTED
BY A PAIR OF PINK-HAIRED BADDIES
FROM SOME DISTANT LAND
BENT ON STOPPING THEM
IN THEIR TRACKS.
I RECALL THAT LITTLE
MISSIVE ALL TOO WELL.
SADLY NOT A WORD OF IT
COULD BE VERIFIED.
- BE PREPARED. THE TREASURE
WE SEEK IS RIGHT HERE.
IF THEY OVERRUN US, BE READY
TO TAKE TO YOUR HEELS AND FLEE.
GO!
OH, NO. THIS CAN'T BE.
THERE'S NO TREASURE IN HERE,
IT'S JUST JUNK.
- WHAT? NO WAY.
- FESS UP! WHERE DID YOU HIDE
THE TREASURE, YOU ROGUE?
- THERE WAS NOTHING HERE
FOR US TO HIDE, MISSY.
- HOLD ON.
- WHAT ARE THE TWO
OF YOU DOING HERE?
- TRYING TO CATCH A GLIMPSE OF
THE RUMORED DRAGON, OF COURSE.
SO, WHAT DO YOU TWO
THINK IS GOING ON HERE?
- HEY, YOUR GUESS
IS AS GOOD AS MINE.
IT'S WEIRD THERE BEING NO
TELLTALE SIGNS OF BLOOD,
BUT... FERRIS?
- PERHAPS YOU TWO HAVE
YOUR OWN THEORY
AS TO THE NATURE OF THIS BEAST?
- SO YOU'RE OUT TO FIND
HERO RELICS AS WELL.
- THERE IS SO MUCH
YOU DON'T KNOW.
HERE, LET ME BEGIN
BY ILLUSTRATING
HOW THE RELIC YOU
ABANDONED IS USED.
- ( exclaiming in pain )
- WHAT I SEEK
IS THUNDER. IZUCHI!
- OH, PLEASE.
- DON'T TELL ME THAT'S
ANOTHER RELIC HE'S USING.
- SO SORRY.
IN ADDITION TO THE AILECRONO
SCYTHE KUU SO DEFTLY WIELDS,
AND OF COURSE, THE
DOLUELI SWORDSCALE,
WE HAVE THE ELEMIO COMB.
FOR A GRAND TOTAL OF THREE.
- WE MUST RETREAT. THE ODDS IN
THIS FIGHT ARE NOT IN OUR FAVOR.
MOVE IT, RYNER!
- ALL RIGHT FINE. RUN!
- RUN IF YOU MUST.
YOU WON'T GET FAR.
RESONATE!
- ( moans in pain )
- COME ON.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU... HEY.
- Alpha Stigma: WHY DENY IT?
YOU WANT EVERYTHING TO JUST
CRUMBLE AND DISAPPEAR.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO HIM?
- DON'T BE CUTE. I CAN'T VERY
WELL STEAL THE ALPHA STIGMA
WITHOUT FIRST ROUSING IT.
- ROUSING WHAT?
- YOU MEAN YOU REALLY
HAVE NO IDEA.
OF ALL TABOOS, THE ALPHA
STIGMA IS THE MOST HATED.
ONCE AWAKENED
IT KNOWS NO RESTRAINT.
IT ANNIHILATES INDISCRIMINATELY.
HENCE IT'S BEARERS
ARE MALIGNED AS DEMONS.
- Alpha Stigma: YOU KNOW
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- ( Ryner groaning )
YOU, YOU...
YOU'VE GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE, FERRIS!
RUN AS FAR AWAY
AS YOU CAN.
DON'T LOOK BACK, I CAN'T...
- WHAT IS THIS?
- ( grunts )
GET OUT OF HERE.
I CAN'T CONTROL MYSELF!
I'M A MONSTER.
I'LL... KILL...
I'LL KILL YOU.
- Alpha Stigma: SO WHAT?
PEOPLE DIE EVERYDAY.
WHAT DIFFERENCE
WILL ONE POSSIBLY MAKE?
- ( screams ) SHUT UP!
- JUST ACCEPT IT.
THE WORLD IS YOUR PLAYGROUND.
LET LOOSE. HAVE A FEW LAUGHS.
- ( screams )
- ( laughing )
- AND, THE FINAL TETHER
HAS SNAPPED.
THE ALPHA STIGMA IS AWAKE.
I'VE FREED HIM TO RAIN DOWN
CATASTROPHE LIKE A GOD.
- ( laughing )
- HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED ANYTHING?
I TOLD YOU, THE COMB
NULLIFIES YOUR STRENGTH.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN TRYING TO RESIST US.
- ANALYZE EXISTENCE AND
RELEASE. BE GONE, WORM.
- WHAT IN THE HELL? ( screams )
- BURN IT.
OH, MY...
WHAT ON EARTH IS HE?
AN ORDINARY ALPHA STIMGA BEARER
DOESN'T HAVE THIS KIND OF POWER.
- YOU REALLY THINK
YOUR KIND OF MAGIC
IS GOING TO GET
THE BETTER OF ME?
THE ELEMIO COMB MIGHT AS WELL
BE A CONJURER'S PROP.
LITTLE WORMS, CRAWLING IN DIRT.
( laughs )
WRITHE IN A FLASH AND BE GONE.
LET ALL RETURN TO NOTHING.
- THE LAST THING YOU'RE CAPABLE
OF DOING IS HURTING ME, RYNER.
DO YOU HEAR ME IN THERE,
MR. "RUN AWAY"?
I DO NOT PARTAKE OF DANGO,
DRINK TEA, OR CAVORT
WITH THE LIKES
OF HOMICIDAL DEMIGODS.
YOU'RE NOT WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
LED TO BELIEVE YOU ARE.
OPEN YOUR EARS
AND LISTEN TO ME!
-Ryner: NO.
- Alpha Stigma: ALL OF YOU...
- Ryner: SHUT THE HELL UP.
EVERYTHING GOES BACK TO NOTHING.
YOUR TIME IS DONE.
- RYNER!
- ( screams )
- FERRIS, I'M SORRY.
YOU HAVE TO CLOSE MY EYES.
I CAN'T DO IT.
- RYNER, STOP.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN.
YOU ARE NOT A MONSTER.
RYNER, YOU ARE NOT A MONSTER!
- ( screams )
- Iris: DESPITE THE PRINCESS'
BRAVE EFFORTS
TO KEEP THE WICKED BEAST
UNDER CONTROL,
HER HOPELESSLY DEPRAVED
COMPANION SOON SLIPPED BACK
INTO HIS VILE WAYS
AND PLUCKED A YOUNG BOY FROM THE
WARMTH AND SECURITY OF HIS HOME.
- IZUCHI!
- Iris: EVEN WORSE, HE
BRAINWASHED AND CRUELLY TWISTED
THE INNOCENT CHILD
INTO A WEAPON OF WAR.
THE PRINCESS WAS STRONGLY
AGAINST THIS, HOWEVER,
AND REFUSED TO LET THINGS STAND.
- MEDDLING WITH THE VERY
STRUCTURE OF YOUR SPELLS...
- KUKU, WAKE UP!
- ARUA.
- Iris: THE PRINCESS
FREED THE POOR BOY
FROM THE WICKED BEAST'S CLUTCHES
AND DELIVERED HIM SAFE
AND SOUND TO THE CARE
OF HIS MAJESTY'S ELITE FORCE.
KINDNESS AND BRAVERY
WON THE DAY!
- ( laughs )
- WHAT I SEEK
IS THUNDER, IZUCHI!
- WHOA! HEY, CUT IT OUT!
- Luke: PLEASE, CAPTAIN MILK,
CALM YOURSELF!
GET IT TOGETHER, CAPTAIN!
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, FUNBOY!
- WHERE THE HELL
IS THIS COMING FROM, HUH?
FERRIS?
- INDEED, THE DANGO PREPARED
AT THE WYNNIT HOUSE
ARE ON A DIFFERENT LEVEL.
- WHOA, WHERE DID YOU
GET THOSE FROM?
- WELL, I BOUGHT
THEM, OBVIOUSLY.
WE ARE WITHIN ROLAND'S
BORDERS, AFTER ALL.
- WHAT?
- IT'S HOUSE ERIS,
A TERRITORY OF MY
FAMILY POSITIONED
ALONG THE COASTAL REGION.
- ALL RIGHT! HOW ABOUT WE
DESTROY THE ROOT OF EVIL
THAT PUT US THROUGH THIS TORMENT
AND BE DONE WITH IT, HUH?
- YES, ON THE DAWN OF HIS
DEFEAT, LIKE A SUN RISING,
I SHALL TAKE HIS PLACE.
AND I SHALL MAKE ROLAND
INTO THE DANGO EMPIRE.
- Iris: WHEN THE SIMPLE LITTLE
MISSION GIVEN TO HIM BY THE KING
AT LAST PROVED
TOO MUCH TO HANDLE,
THE STUPID, VILE, LAZY,
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING, WICKED BEAST
WAS FORCED TO CRAWL
BACK HOME EMPTY HANDED.
- THANK YOU, IRIS.
THAT REPORT WAS AS DELIGHTFUL
AS IT WAS INFORMATIVE.
I WONDER HOW FAR
THE WICKED BEAST
HAS COME ITEMIZING
THEIR EXPENSES.
- ( sighs )
- OKAY, SO... WHAT THE HELL?
THAT WAS... AND THEN THIS.
BUT THEN THOSE... HOLD ON.
WHOA, WHOA. WHAT?
REALLY? OH, NO, NO.
YOU ARE KIDDING ME?
SON OF A...
THAT'S INSANE!
NO ONE CAN EAT THAT MUCH DANGO.
DOES SHE HAVE MORE THAN
ONE FREAKING STOMACH?
SHE'S BLOWN THROUGH
MOST OF OUR BUDGET!
IT'S LIKE SHE'S THE
DANGO- CHOWING EQUIVALENT
OF THE ELEMIO COMB.
- HOW DARE YOU TALK
ABOUT MY SISTER LIKE THAT?
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- STOP HITTING ME.
- HUH. YOU SEEM TO HAVE RACKED
UP QUITE A LOT OF FOOD EXPENSES.
OH, UH. AND THE COST
OF REPAIRING THAT CHAIR
WILL COME OUT OF YOUR WAGES.
- WHAT? HEY! THAT'S SO UNFAIR.
FERRIS, THOUGH... AND I...
BUT THE CHAIR WASN'T EVEN...
- IRIS ATTACK!
- WHAT'S LEFT OF YOUR
TAKE-HOME PAY IS DIMINISHING.
- YEAH, WELL,
YOUR CHANCES OF ME NOT KICKING
YOUR ASS ARE DIMINISHING.
- ( laughs )
NO ONE DEFEATS IRIS.
GO ON, SIR. SAY IT.
- YOU'VE DONE WELL.
THERE'S NO DOUBT IN MY MIND,
YOUR SISTER WILL BE PROUD.
- ( laughs excitedly )
- BE SURE TO MENTION
HOW HARD I WAS ON THE BEAST.
SHE'LL BE PROUD OF THAT
MOST OF ALL!
- OH, NO.
- I'D BEEN SO PREOCCUPIED
WITH OUR MISSION,
I DIDN'T CONSUME ENOUGH DANGO.
I HAVEN'T MANAGED TO PUT AWAY
EVEN HALF MY NORMAL AMOUNT.
THAT EXPLAINS WHY I'VE HAD
SO LITTLE ENERGY.
WHAT A FOOL I'VE BEEN.
WELL, THE FAMINE ENDS NOW.
THEY SAY INDULGING
IN DANGO JUST BEFORE BED
IS A SURE FIRE WAY TO LOOSE
ONE'S GIRLISH FIGURE.
BUT SURELY HAVING TO DEAL
WITH IDIOTS ALL DAY
EXEMPTS ME FROM
HAVING TO ABSTAIN.
( moans )
I HAVEN'T PARTAKEN IN THE WYNITT
TEA HOUSE VARIETY IN SO LONG.
OH, YES. NOW, I AM TRULY
IN MY ELEMENT.
- ( cries with joy )
- ( theme song playing )