[KIKKOU]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
[SENGO]
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
[SENGO]
It's so hot! Better strip!
All these steamy clothes,
constricting all around me!
Oh, are you hungry?
These dumplings are
wrapped up tight, too!
[KIKKOU, SENGO] This is the tale
of the legendary sword warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
[JIROUTACHI humming]
Brother dear, are you going out?
[TAROUTACHI] It's a lovely day,
so I thought I might
take a walk.
In that case, could
you swing by the store
and nab a few things
for me while you're at it?
[TAROUTACHI]
Of course.
[JIROUTACHI]
Peachy!
Here's a shopping list, then.
[crash]
[JIROUTACHI]
Ah... Not again!
Are you all right?
I'm perfectly fine.
We always have to
keep our heads down.
The world's too small for us.
Yes.
It's the cruel fate
of those who are tall.
Please, forgive me.
[gasps]
It's too far for me to reach.
[TAROUTACHI]
Ow!
[GOTOU] Looking for
something, Taroutachi?
[TAROUTACHI]
A shopping list.
It fell under here.
Ah. Let me handle it for you.
[GOTOU]
Here.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
You kidding? That was nothing!
And while I'm at it,
might as well get this dirt
off your face.
[TAROUTACHI]
Oh. Thank you.
[GOTOU]
See ya!
[CHICKS cheeping]
[TAROUTACHI]
Uh-oh.
[cheeping continues]
How terribly rude of me.
[CHICKS cheep]
[TAROUTACHI]
A bit tight in here, isn't it?
[IMANOTSURUGI]
Taroutachi! Hey!
[TAROUTACHI]
Yes?
Oh, dear.
[laughing]
Guess you're just too
big for shopping, huh?
Happens to me, too.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault for yelling
your name like that.
[TAROUTACHI]
Not at all.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm embarrassed
that it came to this.
[FUDOU]
Whoa, buddy.
Why is this so big?
That one belongs to Taroutachi.
Okay. Here we go!
[KASEN] Fudou, are you sure you
don't need help with that?
[chuckles] Nah. Easy peasy--
[FUDOU yells]
Are you hurt?
[FUDOU]
I am so useless!
[JIROUTACHI]
Hey, you're back!
[FUDOU]
Sorry, Taroutachi.
I got mud all over your futon
and your sleeping clothes.
Borrow mine until
tomorrow, okay?
[TAROUTACHI]
Insufficient.
[JIROUTACHI inhales]
Not a good look.
[GROUP chattering]
[TAROUTACHI]
I really am very sorry.
Why, 'cause of my clothes?
[TAROUTACHI] Your pajamas simply
could not contain my enormity.
If I didn't want 'em
to get stretched,
I shoulda thought about that
before I ruined yours.
Be gentle.
He's quite sensitive
about his size.
I didn't know.
When I was a blade,
I was far too large to be
wielded by any human.
So instead, I was
dedicated to the gods.
For a sword, never seeing combat
is a fate worse than death.
It's as if I never existed.
Why was I made like this?
My body is just a curse.
[NIHONGOU laughs]
Are you kidding?
The bigger you are,
the more booze you can drink!
What else do you need?
Drink up, buddy!
Celebrate your size! C'mon!
Yeah!
I mean, drinking aside,
I wouldn't trade my height
for anything in the world.
Same.
After all, what if our
friends are in danger
and we have to protect them?
In that case, the bigger
we are the better,
if you ask me.
You've all been too kind.
Perhaps you're right.
[KOGARASUMARU]
Today's expedition has been
quite auspicious,
I must say.
[GOTOU]
So, we're done?
Did you find something cool?
[AIZEN]
Ah, persimmons!
Those look good!
My brothers would love them.
I have to get some.
Good idea, I bet Kuniyuki
would like one too.
Nice catch, Sayo.
But now what?
[sighs]
[KOGARASUMARU]
Worry not.
Let Father take care of this.
[KOGARASUMARU]
Goodness.
That is quite tall.
[GROUP sighs]
[GOTOU]
Don't give up!
We can just make a ladder!
[SAYO]
We're still too short!
I'm so happy.
[GROUP]
Wow!
Must be nice being tall, huh?
We would never've reached that.
Thank you so much.
I shouldn't complain so much.
It all works out.
[HOTARUMARU] I can't believe
we all got one; this is perfect.
[IMANOTSURUGI]
Hey, welcome back!
Look, we made stilts!
Now the short swords
don't have to be so short!
[IWATOOSHI laughs]
When short people
rule the world,
remember that I helped you.
[GOTOU]
Let me try!
[HOTARUMARU]
Looks fun.
[IMANOTSURUGI]
Here, use mine.
[GOTOU]
Thanks.
You tall guys get such
a nice view from up here.
I'm jealous!
This is all I
dreamed it would be!
Just wait and see!
One day, I'm gonna
be this big, too!
Whoa, whoa... ah!
[GOTOU laughs]
[AIZEN]
Hey, me next!
I wanna be tall!
[HOTARUMARU]
Here, Sayo, I'll help you up.
[SAYO]
Oh, thanks.
[KOGARASUMARU]
Let father try as well.
[ALL laughing]
[KASHUU whines]
It's so hot.
How are you supposed
to get anything done
on a day like this?
Lovely weather we're
having today, isn't it?
Indeed.
And simply perfect for tea.
What the heck?
It's sweltering out here
and you two are
drinking hot tea?
Warm tea on a warm day
has a certain elegance to it,
if you ask me.
[KOGITSUNEMARU]
Ooh!
I think it's even
hotter in here.
Hey! The room's all full!
Nice! I think we might
have enough to play!
What're you talking about?
[MUTSUNOKAMI] I got a way
for us to spar and stay cool.
Come with me! It'll be fun!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
All right!
Now let's split into teams
and get this battle underway.
What kind of battle, exactly?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
A brand-new kind!
And one that doesn't use swords.
Today, we'll be fighting...
with these here!
You've lost it.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] No, look! I dug
these out of the master's stuff!
[gun cocks]
That's cold!
What kind of weapon
is that thing?
[MUTSUNOKAMI laughs]
A gun that shoots
water instead of bullets.
That sounds like a blast!
I'm in!
Hand me a gun
and I'm ready to go!
I'll pass.
It's not really my style.
That's no fun!
Can't use your precious sword
so you give up right away?
You're just afraid
you might lose, huh?
What did you say?
Well, damn.
I'm not afraid of anything,
and I'm not gonna lose, either.
So let's do this thing!
That's better!
Now, if you're game,
draw one of these
to decide your team!
It's on!
There is no way we're
losing this thing.
If you think you can
beat me in a gunfight,
you're crazy.
[HORIKAWA]
I guess we're enemies now, Kane.
Never thought this would happen.
[KANESADA] Sorry if you get
wrecked, but I'm going all out.
And you'd better do the same!
You bet I will.
You can't defeat
a true masterpiece.
Trust me.
This is no duel,
it's all-out war!
[NAGASONE]
Feelings. Family.
These sort of things have
no meaning on the battlefield.
Sorry, but you're done!
[YAMANBAGIRI] You won't
get one drop on my cloak.
Hey, wait, how do you
decide the winner?
If you get sprayed with water
even a little, then you're out.
We fight till one
team loses everyone.
Battle begins in five minutes.
Are you ready?
'Cause there's no turning back!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[NAGASONE] The other team
is tough; this won't be easy.
[YAMANBAGIRI] In that case,
we'll have to outsmart them.
Kashuu, do you have a
plan that might help us?
But of course.
The key to victory lies
in taking your opponent
by surprise.
An ambush?
Secret weapons.
No way they'll see this coming.
It's a bit crude, I must admit,
but this would appear
to be a showdown
where anything goes.
Now you're finally getting it!
[KASHUU]
And thus, in sweltering heat,
a battle without honor
and humanity began.
[URASHIMA]
Hachisuka, over there!
Yamanbagiri.
All right.
Let's move in and surround
him before he notices us.
We've been had!
[HACHISUKA yells]
[URASHIMA]
Hachisuka! No...
Forget about me.
Save yourself.
You're my brother.
I can't just leave you to die!
It's too late.
I'm already dead.
Hachisuka, no!
Who could do such a thing?
It can't be!
You were finally getting
along and now this?
I told you, family
has no meaning here.
[KASHUU] This'll be easier
than I thought.
Sorry, but you're in
the real world now, kid.
You adapt, or you get
gunned down like a chump.
[HACHISUKA]
Ch-Cheater--
"Cheater"? Really?
There are no rules anymore.
Look out! Above you!
[KASHUU]
What?!
Water balloons?
Sucks to be on the
receiving end, I know,
but like you said,
there are no rules!
Here I go!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Take that!
[KASHUU]
I hate it! Stop it!
I'll cover you guys!
But we gotta go!
Get up!
We don't have much time!
I hear you!
How did it come to this?
Don't get cocky.
No matter what weapon you use,
I'll win this.
Oh, will you?
Why don't we test
that right now?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
They're a lot more resourceful
than I thought they'd be.
We're teaming up and the
master didn't even have to
order us this time. Wow.
We drew lots for the teams.
What am I supposed to say?
Hey. What's gotten into you?
[KANESADA]
Can't hide from me!
[KANESADA] You too scared to
fight face-to-face or what?
Urashima?
[NAGASONE gasps]
[URASHIMA]
Nagasone.
Please, don't make
me pull this trigger.
[NAGASONE]
Shoot me.
Take your revenge.
I've already lost one brother
today. Isn't that enough?
[NAGASONE]
Shoot!
[URASHIMA gasps]
[NAGASONE] I was prepared for
this the moment I picked up
my gun.
I knew the stakes.
This isn't some game.
What're you even saying?
You're scaring me!
[NAGASONE]
Listen up!
This is a battle with
your pride on the line.
So fight!
This isn't such a bad way to go.
I have no regrets.
[water squirting]
[URASHIMA]
Nagasone!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
You may be a copy,
but at least this time
I know you're not a fake!
Careful there! Ha!
Sorry, it looks like the
gods are on my side today.
I've got enough left
for one good shot.
[YAMANBAGIRI]
Is that so?
Then tell me,
where are your gods now?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
What?!
[yelling]
[YAMANBAGIRI]
It's fine to trust yourself,
but don't underestimate
your enemy.
[MUTSUNOKAMI grunts]
[KASHUU] Okay, we've got you,
me and Horikawa.
The other side is down to
Kanesada and Urashima.
I think we're in
the home stretch.
[URASHIMA] I wouldn't be
so sure if I were you.
He's hardcore. Whoa.
This isn't the Urashima
you know and love.
It's a man who just lost
two of his brothers.
His heart and soul have
been tempered like steel.
His conviction forged anew
in the flames of battle!
[URASHIMA]
Hachisuka. Nagasone.
[KANESADA] Some warriors
are crippled by sorrow,
but those who overcome it
become stronger than ever!
Line up!
I'm sending you all
straight to hell!
[yelling]
Damn it!
[YAMANBAGIRI]
He's too fast! I can't hit him!
Not my cloak. No...
There's only one thing to do.
Tactical retreat!
[URASHIMA]
Get back here!
[rustling]
[KANESADA]
So there you are.
[HORIKAWA] Let's settle
this, once and for all.
Say goodbye!
[KANESADA] How do you expect
to beat me if all you do
is run away?
Fine! How's this?
[HORIKAWA] I knew he'd
give me a good fight!
[KANESADA]
Now this is fun!
Crap, where'd he go?
[KANESADA]
They've got a sniper! But who?
[UGUISUMARU]
Ow!
[KANESADA]
Gotcha!
Uguisumaru?
What were you doing
hanging out up in a tree?
[UGUISUMARU]
What else?
I was watching Ookanehira
from a safe distance.
[rustling]
[HORIKAWA]
Prepare yourself, Kane!
[KANESADA]
I'm getting dizzy!
Heh!
[UGUISUMARU]
What did I do wrong?
I'm sorry, I didn't see you--
[KANESADA]
This is a battlefield, remember.
Wow, Kane.
You really are the best,
aren't you?
[HASEBE]
What the heck? Come back!
[URASHIMA] Just let me
spray you already! Jeez!
[HASEBE] Whatever you're
doing, stop it immediately!
Akashi!
Hey, there.
Did ya need something?
Wait, what are you doing?
No mercy!
[URASHIMA]
Hey, stop!
Kashuu!
You're the last one
left, y'know!
Are you kidding me?
I thought Horikawa had this!
What d'you think?
Should we make even more stilts?
For everyone, huh?
Whoa! Kashuu?
[KASHUU]
Later! I'm busy!
[GOTOU]
Huh?
[KANESADA]
Over there!
[URASHIMA]
Hey! Where'd he go?
This doesn't make sense!
[KASHUU]
Try looking up.
Now say goodbye!
[KANESADA, URASHIMA yell]
[KANESADA]
Man!
And I thought we had
that one for sure!
[URASHIMA] You were
outnumbered and everything!
[KASHUU]
I've been here the longest,
so I know a trick or two.
[KANESADA]
Come to think of it,
you were pulling tricks
on us that whole match.
My favorite was
the fake Yamanbagiri!
I would've fallen
for that one, too!
You don't have to humor me.
Tricks or not, congrats on
the big comeback, Kashuu.
[clapping]
I wish Yasusada
had been there to see!
He'd love this!
[URASHIMA laughs]
Now. I present to you
this invisible certificate.
Celebrating your excellence
in water pistol trickery
and balloon dodging
under pressure.
Truly admirable work.
I'm sure it'll look
perfect on your wall.
Ha-ha!
I'm so proud.
[GROUP laughing]
[KASHUU]
I'm finally done.
[KASHUU] We might have
to have a water gun duel
when you get back, Yasusada.