[SAYO]
The year is 2205 AD.
[SOUZA]
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
[KOUSETSU]
Born from the heart of swords,
[GROUP] we travel through time
to intercept and eliminate them.
Hi, Master.
We brought some flowers for you.
We started a flowerbed
together out in the field.
I hope that this lavender
will put you at ease.
[GROUP] This is the tale of
the legendary sword warriors,
and the Hanamaru days they
spent in a certain citadel.
[URASHIMA grunts]
[HRA SOLDIER 7B growls]
Just try to hold on!
[NIHONGOU]
Stay back!
[HRA SOLDIERS growl]
[MONOYOSHI yelling]
You ready?
Yeah!
[HRA SOLDIER 7B growls]
--[MONOYOSHI] Let's go!
--[KASHUU] No mercy!
[HACHISUKA]
Monoyoshi.
You really saved us back there.
Awesome work!
[NAGASONE chuckles] And on
your first mission, no less!
I'm just glad you're safe!
[KASHUU]
Nice job.
Oh, yeah, same.
Quite the concidence.
If that boulder hadn't fallen,
we'd be dead.
[MONOYOSHI]
Yes, good fortune indeed.
Better get going.
I still haven't given Monoyoshi
a proper tour of the Citadel.
[NIHONGOU] Even after a mission,
our proud tour guide
never abandons his duty, huh?
What can I say?
Anyway, are you ready?
Of course.
Y'know... I think
he's cheered up a bit.
Hey. Do ya have a sec?
Introducing Monoyoshi Sadamune.
He just returned from a
stellar first mission, right?
I got lucky, that's all.
I'm Uguisumaru, hello.
I'm Hirano Toushiro.
Here, let me make some tea.
Great! We haven't had
the chance to sit down yet.
I can help out, if you'd like.
[HIRANO]
Thanks.
Here. Hope it's good.
You're so thoughtful!
Thank you, but this
is nothing, really.
Oh, my.
Three tea stalks standing up.
Even just one would
mean good luck.
I admit, this is a first for me.
[KASHUU gasps]
So many!
It's like a magic trick.
I wonder what will happen next.
[KASHUU]
Kasen! You here?
Kashuu?
A-ha!
And you're Monoyoshi?
Uh-huh.
I guess word travels fast here.
Laundry, huh?
I could lend you
a hand, if you'd like.
If you could take
down the dry sheets,
that would be great.
Of course.
Where do they go?
Right in the basket.
[MONOYOSHI, KASHUU gasp]
[yells]
[KASEN]
Come back!
We'd better help.
On it.
[KASEN]
They'll be soiled! Soiled!
Have mercy, please!
That worked out rather nicely!
[MONOYOSHI chuckles]
Good fortune, indeed.
[KASEN] Ah. That was quite
remarkable, wasn't it?
[KASHUU]
Yeah, funny, huh?
[MORTAR 7A]
Mortar!
[OTEGINE yells]
Wait! I'm not a pestle!
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Hey, Kashuu!
Shokudaikiri.
What's up?
I'm cooking dinner,
but we ran out of soy sauce.
Do you think you could get
some from the store for me?
I'm not busy. No problem.
And I'd love to see the store.
[OTEGINE grunts]
[MORTAR 7A]
Mortar. Mortar. Mortar. Mortar.
[OTEGINE]
What do you want?!
Now this I can handle!
[GROUP laughing]
[NIHONGOU]
Yeah!
So yummy!
When it comes to stabbing
things, nobody's better than me.
Thanks for your help!
Better hurry.
Yeah.
Ah. It's crowded today.
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)]
Oh, my!
Is that a new
Sword Warrior I see?
It's nice to meet you.
I was once a lucky sword
of the Tokugawa Clan.
My name is Monoyoshi Sadamune.
That's cool, we both
came from the same place!
[MONOYOSHI]
I don't believe we've met.
I'm Houchou Toushirou.
My name means "kitchen
knife," by the way,
because that's what my
blade was shaped like.
My master was Tokugawa
Ieyasu back in the day.
So yeah, neat, huh?
Hey. Atsushi, can I
pull a string candy?
[ATSUSHI]
Yeah, go for it.
You two don't know each other?
Well, The Tokugawa Clan
had a pretty huge collection
of swords, so I didn't come
in contact with everybody.
[HOUCHOU]
Ahh...
Oh, lucky!
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)]
You pulled a big one!
Good fortune!
Yes, indeed.
Aw, nice! I gotta try too!
[ATSUSHI yells]
I did it!
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)]
Congratulations on your victory.
Amazing.
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)]
Let's see how we do.
[ATSUSHI]
Whoa!
Wow! We sure cleaned up!
I've never seen so much candy!
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)]
I can't wait to show it off.
Everyone's going to be jealous.
We'll have to share.
You sure weren't
kidding when you said
you were a "lucky sword."
You don't seem too
surprised, though.
Is life always
like this for you?
[ATSUSHI]
Hey, what's going on?
Hi there, Kashuu.
Are you planting something?
We're looking for
four-leaf clovers, actually.
Is there any reason why?
[AKITA] Hakata's trading stocks,
so he needs good luck.
[KASHUU]
Again?
What for? I thought we made
all the money we needed.
Well, the thing is...
[MIDARE]
That's a big grin you've got!
Did something happen?
Kasen invited me for tea,
and it was so lovely.
I hope you enjoy.
[ICHIGO] A mysterious lustre
like the twinkle of stars.
A faraway universe
is beckoning to me!
[KASEN]
I see you are a man of taste.
Perhaps you would
like another cup?
I can scarcely explain it,
but something about
that ethereal teacup
simply captivated me.
I wish I had one of my own.
[HONEBAMI]
Like this one, right?
[GOKOTAI]
Let's buy it!
[NAMAZUO]
Yeah, about that.
It's not exactly in our budget.
[MIDARE]
Guess it's not happening, then.
[HAKATA]
We'll make it happen.
Because stock trading is magic.
[GOKOTAI] It's not much, but if
we can't help with the stocks,
we can at least do this for him.
[KASHUU chuckles]
I see.
Thing is, we haven't
found one yet.
[MONOYOSHI]
Is this what you're looking for?
Ah! Yeah, that's it!
[GOKOTAI]
I found one, too!
[MAEDA]
You're right!
How did we miss these before?
[AKITA] Look! There's
a whole bunch of them! Ah!
Like they came out of nowhere.
[AKITA] If this won't bring him
good luck, nothing will!
Wow, and they're
all four-leaf clovers?
[GROUP]
Uh-huh!
Thanks, Monoyoshi.
I thought we'd be here all day!
You're really lucky, huh?
I didn't do anything
special, really.
Well, tell me how it turns out!
[GROUP]
Okay.
[HAKATA] This is the most
intense battle of my life,
but I refuse to quit!
[MIDARE]
Well, okay. Don't die on us.
[HOUCHOU]
Hey, Hakata!
[laughs]
Houchou?
Hope you like free candy!
We brought tons!
Whoa, just what I needed!
Thanks, you guys!
And also... Here, show him.
[GOKOTAI] We made you a crown of
four leaf clovers for good luck.
Whoa! There's so many!
No way!
And, you can have
this weird thing, too.
[HAKATA]
Uh...! Is it alive?
[NAMAZUO]
Looks creepy!
[MIDARE]
E-Ew, gross!
[HONEBAMI]
What is it?
Hey, that's not
for tigers to eat!
Anyway...
It's a caterpillar fungus.
Oh, wow.
I'm surprised you know that!
Only 'cause I saw it in that
reference book you gave me
a while back.
It's a medicinal herb,
and rather costly!
Oh! "Costly!"
All right, nothing can
stop me now!
When I'm done, we'll buy a whole
mountain of teacups!
[AKITA]
We're counting on you, Hakata!
[YAGEN] Don't eat all
that fungus at once!
Okay.
I got all the assets I need.
Now it's time for me
to get to work.
[ATSUSHI]
Good luck!
Ichi's counting on you!
It's up to you now!
[HAKATA]
Let the stock showdown commence!
Here we go!
[ALL]
Whoa!
Hakata! Hakata! Hakata!
[MONOYOSHI]
Looks like they're having fun.
[KASHUU]
Yeah.
--[ALL] Hakata! Hakata! Hakata!
--Oh, wow!
Look, it's going up!
It's going way up!
[OOKURIKARA]
Kashuu.
Hasebe needs you now.
[KASHUU]
Oh, yeah? Okay, then.
[chanting continues]
What happened?
It's like all my good luck
just walked away!
[MIDARE]
The stock keeps dropping!
[ATSUSHI]
Louder, everyone!
[KASHUU]
Oh, hey.
I forgot to ask, where
is Hasebe, anyway?
[OOKURIKARA]
In the kitchen.
[KASHUU]
'Kay, thanks.
[HAKATA]
Uh-oh! It's going crazy!
No, stop it!
What in the world
is going on here?
Thanks for coming to help.
No problem.
Yeah! Now it's up!
Getting ready to sell...
Aw yeah, more money, more money!
[ALL]
Ah... whoa!
Whoa!
[HAKATA whining]
I blew it.
[MIDARE]
Is he dead?
This is our fault, too,
we shouldn't have dumped
all the hard work on Hakata.
Well, we can't fix
the money problem,
but we can try to cheer him up!
What d'you say, guys? You in?
Yeah, of course!
Great idea.
But what does he like?
[GROUP]
Hmm...
Let's ask around, I'm sure
someone knows more
about his history.
[HASEBE]
Depressed, huh?
I see.
[YAGEN] You were with the
Kuroda Clan at the same time
as him, right?
Is there anything from back then
that might help cheer him up?
--[rustling]
--[NIHONGOU] That's easy!
Have a Gion Yamakasa!
Do you think we could?
[MAEDA]
Wait.
What is a Yamakasa?
It's a festival held every
year in Hakata's hometown.
It's named after these giant
floats that people pile onto
and parade around town.
It is the right season,
but I wonder if we have
the resources.
Well, it doesn't
have to be perfect.
As long as it cheers
him up, we're good.
You're right!
But still, we'll need a float.
[NIHONGOU]
Ha, then make one!
It's okay.
Right, Hasebe?
Fine, fine.
I'll ask the master
and see what they think.
--[YAGEN, MAEDA] Thank you.
--[GOKOTAI] Thank you very much.
[NIHONGOU]
We're on top of this.
Long as there's a float,
we got all the festival
we need, right?
One look at this and
Hakata will be right back
to his old self.
This is coming together fast!
Uh-huh!
We gotta get these stalls
in working order
before Hakata finds out!
This is gonna be a blast!
So, hey.
What are we building?
Hmm... Gotta be a food stall.
What else?
I bet you're the
most awesome chef
in the whole world, Mitsu!
I don't think I'd go
that far, but thank you.
I'll give it my best!
You're making the banner?
You've decided what
you want it to say?
[KOUSETSU]
If it pleases you, yes.
I think that's perfect.
It's even worse than before.
[HAKATA whining]
Hey, Hakata, how 'bout
a little change of pace?
I can't, the stock might
go up while I'm not here.
[MIDARE]
Just come with me for a sec.
[HAKATA]
You guys...
It's a Yamakasa!
So, what d'you say, kid?
Does it pass the test?
Can't believe they're going
to carry that thing around.
I can't wait to see.
They did this every year, huh?
Sounds like your
hometown was fun.
Would it be okay if I
worked on it with you?
[NIHONGOU] Like I could
say no to that face!
[HAKATA gasps]
I'm coming in.
[gasps] Scared me.
Here. From the Master.
So tell me how cute I look!
[ALL chattering]
Thanks for all this, Hasebe.
Don't mention it. Of course.
I'm just worried it might rain.
Y'think we're ready or what?
Yeah!
[rain dripping]
[HAKATA] My luck is
really in the pits, huh?
Eh, it's not so bad,
we just gotta wait
until the rain lets up.
It won't be long at all.
Have patience.
Don't lose heart yet.
[MONOYOSHI]
Hey, we're back.
Oh, went on an expedition?
Uh-huh.
We already heard the big news.
So we're having
a festival today?
It's raining.
We can't.
Looks like it's clearing
up if you ask me.
[HAKATA]
It's a miracle!
You really are good luck.
I've been watching this
happen all day long.
When my master
took me into battle,
he would win, without a doubt.
I was like a good luck
charm for the clan.
Yeah, I see what you mean.
I hope I can bring
good luck here, too.
[GROUP] Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
[chanting continues]
[HAKATA]
This was the best day ever!
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Another udon is ready!
Coming!
Satisfaction guaranteed!
[NIKKARI]
Why, thank you.
Hey, Kara! Pretty tasty, huh?
[OOKURIKARA]
Yeah.
[HASEBE humming]
Cold noodles make
for the perfect texture.
All done! Enjoy!
Can you get that one for me?
Easy!
Whoa, wait, hey,
that's not how you play!
Gah!
Whoa, they're so pretty!
We have some
candied apples as well.
[HOUCHOU]
Sweet!
We should have a
festival every day!
My brother's the best.
So cool.
Ka, ka, ka!
We might as well do
the Star Festival
while we're at it, right?
We'll hang our wishes
on these here!
[AKITA]
I want to write a wish!
I've heard that in the past,
people didn't write
wishes on these papers,
but rather, wrote what they
wanted to improve upon
in the coming year.
So like a personal goal,
that kinda thing?
Oh, easy! I want to
get better at dancing!
I want to make more effective
medicine, and fertilizer too!
I want to be brave
and tough and cool!
I want to make the best
tea in the whole Citadel.
Huh. I'm already cute and
strong, so this is kinda tough.
[KASHUU]
I'll bend the rules a little.
I know that you can't hear me,
but we're all having fun
here without you again.
Come back soon, Yasusada.
That should do it.
[YASUSADA]
They're really blowing up now!
[HAKATA] I'm pretty sure there
was a fan in here somewhere.
Found it!
With my name, too.
Okay, I better hurry
back to the festival!
Huh? Huh?! Huh?!
[HAKATA]
It's really blowing up now!
[KASHUU]
Huh?
What the heck?
Wow!
My wish came true and I'm
a fabulous dancer already!
[KASHUU gasps]
And I've become the
perfect dancing machine!
[MAEDA] This Festival's
getting wild and crazy!
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)] I guess
I'll have to break out my
producer chair once again!
All right, if my brothers
are singing, I'm singing too!
[KASHUU]
Huh? What the--?
How? Why?
What a nightmare.