[HIGEKIRI]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
[HIZAMARU]
Born from the heart of swords...
[HIZAMARU, HIGEKIRI] ...we
travel through time to intercept
and eliminate them.
Master, we're back.
Me and, uh, you know...
It's Hizamaru! Jeez!
Right.
We brought you a souvenir.
Enjoy. See you!
[HIGEKIRI, HIZAMARU] This is
the tale of the legendary
sword warriors,
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
Here goes.
Excuse me!
General, listen.
I have a request to make.
[URASHIMA sighs]
[KOGARASUMARU]
That's an awfully heavy sigh.
[HIZAMARU]
Is something bothering you?
We've got new Sword
Warriors showing up
every month now.
Since it's getting
kind of crowded,
I suggested that Nagasone
move into the room
I share with Hachisuka.
But then, last night...
[NAGASONE groans]
I'm thirsty.
[HACHISUKA yells]
Oh, sorry.
[HACHISUKA growls]
Even for a fake,
this is a new low!
Huh, what?
[HACHISUKA] I only resigned
myself to sharing this room
with you because
Urashima asked nicely!
I said I was sorry.
[NAGASONE growls]
You could've at least
tried walking around us,
you clumsy oaf!
And where are you going?
I'm not finished
chewing you out!
I don't know.
Maybe I was too optimistic
thinking they might
finally get along.
Well, siblings fight and
compete with each other
all the time--there's
nothing wrong with that.
Reminds me of our
former masters.
Eventually, Yoritomo wanted
his brother Yoshitsune dead.
At least it hasn't
come to that yet.
But it doesn't matter if our
old masters hated each other.
We still get along just fine.
--Me and...
--It's Hizamaru.
Me and the other guy don't
let history get in the way
of our friendship.
Glad you agree.
Brotherly love can
be a wonderful thing,
but for some siblings,
the closer they are,
the more they're
inclined to fight.
Maybe so, but there
has to be some way
they can get along.
[KOGARASUMARU chuckles]
Take heart.
For no matter how you
quarrel amongst yourselves,
your father will always
love each and every
one of you unconditionally.
Uh...! Oh, oops.
You go ahead and take it.
Don't be ridiculous--
there's an easy solution.
Sharing is caring, as they say.
Wouldn't you agree, Miza...
It's Hizamaru, okay?
That's it!
[HRA SOLDIERS growling]
[URASHIMA]
I got this! Stand back!
You're really on fire today!
This time, I gotta be MVP!
I have a plan that's gonna
bring my brothers together!
Guess what?!
This sword here just
won today's MVP award!
Nice work, buddy!
I would expect no less!
[URASHIMA]
So, in honor of my achievement,
could I ask you two a favor?
Say the word!
Whatever you want, you got it!
All I need you to do
is make dinner for me.
Easy, 'kay?
You mean together?
We're on it pal.
You're not in charge!
What's the big deal, man?
If that's what our little
brother wants from us,
then I think we can
play nice, can't we?
I suppose I can't
very well say no now.
Thanks, guys!
I'm sure it'll be great!
I was asking around
the citadel to find some help,
but Kasen and Shokudaikiri
are both out on missions.
A fake like you might need help,
but for a treasure like me,
cooking is a simple matter.
Okay. So what're we gonna make?
A feast of culinary
perfection, of course!
Our little brother
deserves nothing less
than a modern masterpiece!
I'll do it!
Alone.
♪ A fake like you lacks
the skill it takes ♪
♪ for dishes so precise ♪
♪ Make yourself useful with
something, well, simple. ♪
♪ Like rice! ♪
All right, fine then.
♪ Now for the stew
every vegetable ♪
♪ should be cut with
beauty and finesse ♪
♪ This thing is strange,
doesn't handle like a sword, ♪
♪ I must confess! ♪
♪ My, that is a shape
rather uncommon... ♪
♪ Cherry blossoms ♪
♪ You're too unrefined
to understand such art! ♪
♪ Seasoning time!
So sublime... ♪
♪ One can never have
too much spice in life! ♪
[NAGASONE] ♪ That might
be too much soy sauce,
♪ don't you think? ♪
♪ Your sense of taste
clearly stinks! ♪
♪ Tempura oil must be
heated with efficiency ♪
♪ Got to work fast if
perfection is to be achieved ♪
♪ I'm not so sure, you
might want to be careful ♪
♪ Seems like a dangerous plan. ♪
♪ Don't you know that
I am a very dextrous man? ♪
♪ I know exactly
how to multitask ♪
♪ See, unlike you, ♪
♪ I am not a fake
and therefore grand! ♪
Next up is egg custard!
♪ Throw in some shrimp
with some veggies ♪
♪ and some eggs and some broth ♪
♪ I've gotta say that to me
that looks like way too much. ♪
♪ Then I guess... I care
too much... For Urashima ♪
♪ He deserves the best,
so I give him my all! ♪
♪ But I guess you just
don't care enough. ♪
[HACHISUKA]
Ow!
I do not need your help!
♪ Stay out of the way,
you'll only ruin things. ♪
♪ Every detail
must be just right. ♪
♪ When our dear
brother arrives! ♪
♪ He's our MVP! ♪
♪ Thus he deserves
a first-rate party! ♪
That's why we're doing
a whole grilled sea bream!
♪ Did you gut it or
remove the scales? ♪
♪ Doesn't look like it to me. ♪
♪ So uncultured! Uninspired! ♪
♪ My way's better;
it's more refined. ♪
Now for the tempura!
♪ You'll splash the oil,  ♪
♪ so be careful not to
get yourself burned ♪
Shush. know what I'm doing.
♪ I thought by now you
would have learned ♪
♪ Just looking out ♪
♪ Didn't seem to me like
you were prepared ♪
♪ Hey, I don't
need your opinion ♪
♪ You're just full of hot air! ♪
[BOTH yelling]
[dishes clatter[
Laugh at me if you must.
I certainly deserve it.
I couldn't even
prepare a single dish.
We're in this
together, remember?
Besides, I'm pretty rotten
at cooking, myself.
What are we going
to tell Urashima?
There is something
I used to make
when I first came here.
It's a dish my former
master used to like.
If you wanna help me,
we could try making
it right now.
♪ First you take egg whites
and mix them about ♪
♪ Whisk 'em until
they make peaks ♪
♪ How much longer
must I whisk? ♪
♪ Keep it up until they're
frothy throughout ♪
♪ That is the texture you seek ♪
♪ It's the only way
to do it right ♪
Once the peaks have formed,
♪ Add the yolks and
whisk a little more! ♪
♪ How could it be
such a dish ♪
♪ Can turn into
something delicious? ♪
♪ Oh, don't you worry  ♪
♪ Now we pour
the eggs over broth ♪
♪ But we gotta make sure
it's nice and hot ♪
♪ Then finish with some
lovely parsley on top ♪
♪ Fluffy eggs!
Fluffy fluffy eggs! ♪
[URASHIMA]
Wow!
Amazing!
Jeez, you guys have
been holding out on me!
He likes it.
[URASHIMA]
You should have some too.
There's plenty.
Besides, we're a family.
We should all have
dinner together, right?
You won't hear me complain.
Yes. Let's eat.
I made some food, too.
Rather, I salvaged your
mess after I got back.
[GROUP]
Whoa!
Wow, something
smells good in here!
[TSURUMARU] Urashima, whatever
you're eating looks incredible.
It is! But I won't share!
'Cause it's a special present
my brothers made
just for me!
You can't beat family, can ya?
I'm glad you guys all get along.
[URASHIMA laughs]
Hey, fake.
[NAGASONE]
Hm?
Thank you for your help.
[NAGASONE]
Wasn't a big deal, really.
Since yours was damaged
today, you should take this.
[NAGASONE]
Sure.
[HACHISUKA]
However!
This doesn't mean
that I accept you. Hmph.
A fake is still a fake.
[NAGASONE chuckles]
Night.
[ATSUSHI]
I'm back, you guys!
Welcome back!
We're glad you made it!
--Welcome back!
--We're glad you made it!
Did you train hard
out there, Atsushi?
You bet I did!
Check it out!
This is the next evolution!
[NAMAZUO]
Whoa!
That's so cool!
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)]
You're like a real samurai!
When you guys see me in battle,
it is gonna blow your mind!
What kinda training did
you do to get so strong?
I learned military tactics at
Lord Kuroda's place in Chikuzen.
I got tougher, sure,
but I also got smarter and
learned how to lead a team!
I think the master's doing
great running this place,
but if they ever
need a vacation,
I'm pretty sure I could step up!
I can't wait to see you fight!
Can you spar with me?
[ATSUSHI]
Sure!
I'll meet you in the training
hall after I give my report
to the master.
[KANESADA, KASHUU grunt]
Hey, did your training wrap up?
Yeah! I just got back!
Looks to me like you're
ready to train some more!
Nice!
Show us what you
learned out there!
I'm not holding back,
so good luck!
Should I attack you first?
Or do you want me
to fend you off?
Either works for me!
Okay, here I go!
[BOTH grunting]
[MIDARE grunts]
[MIDARE yells]
That's one heck of a change.
He's serious business now!
Look at those moves!
Okay, you got me.
[ATSUSHI laughs]
How about we go again?
Impressive!
I second that.
--[KASHUU] Hey.
--[ATSUSHI] Uh, what?
Got anything left?
How 'bout ya try me? C'mon!
Any time.
[KASHUU] I've been training
day in and day out.
He's strong, but I won't lose.
[KASHUU grunts]
Not enough!
It's over!
Wide open!
[KASHUU grunts]
Holy crap, I really
pulled that off!
You okay?
[KASHUU]
Huh?
Uh, yeah.
I gotta get in on this.
[ATSUSHI]
Keep it coming!
[grunting]
Hold on.
Hey, Kunihiro!
You gotta fight
him next, it's fun!
Yeah. One sec.
I am one of the Five
Great Swords of Japan,
Oodenta Mitsuyo.
And I'm Sohayanotsurugi.
One of Sakanoue's famous
swords, or a copy, at least.
Hey, bro!
Nice how we showed up
at the same time, huh?
Yeah.
[SOHAYANOTSURUGI]
Uh... What's up?
You're a copy, like me?
Yep. I sure am!
[chuckles]
Okay, got it!
I'm sorry to make you
do this on your first day.
No sweat off my back.
Take 'em to the storehouse
you said, right?
If you would.
I have a feeling you're
going to do just fine here.
Hey!
When you're done,
I could use some help, too.
I'll be back in one sec,
pal, then I'm all yours.
[AIZEN]
'Preciate it.
[SOHAYANOTSURUGI]
Right. Don't move an inch!
[JIROUTACHI]
You've gotta slow down, Fudou.
Getting drunk isn't a race.
Also, I'm sick of
pouring this giant bottle
into your silly little cup.
No prob, I'll handle it for you.
If I can copy a famous sword,
I can copy you too!
Just kidding.
[JIROUTACHI]
Oh, you are too much!
[YAMANBAGIRI] He just got here
and he's smiling and laughing
with everyone already.
Even though we're both copies,
he's nothing like me.
[SOHAYANOTSURUGI]
You can come out.
I may be a copy, but I can
still sense your presence.
You've been following me around
ever since I got here, right?
You don't have to lay
low anymore, it's cool.
If you got something to say,
then I'd be happy to listen.
I don't understand.
How is it you're
always so happy?
Is it really that weird, bro?
I dunno.
You haven't been
here all that long,
but you made friends as
soon as you showed up.
I can't even imagine doing that.
What I'm saying is,
if we're both copies,
why are you so
different than me?
[SOHAYANOTSURUGI] If you think
being a copy doesn't bug me,
you're wrong.
But it's not like I can
do anything about it.
So why suffer?
We can't help the way
that we're born, right?
But we can change
the way we live.
What's that supposed to mean?
Every story has to have
some kind of beginning,
and that goes for us, as well,
but we get to
decide how it ends.
It's the story of your
life, so make it count.
There's something out
there only you can do.
You just gotta find it.
That's funny, I guess Kashuu's
not coming today.
[HORIKAWA]
Kashuu!
The food's ready.
Come and eat with us.
I'm not hungry.
[HORIKAWA]
What's wrong?
I hate seeing you like this.
Listen, I know I'm not exactly a
replacement for Yamatonokami,
but I'm good at
helping out, I think.
You know...
I haven't been dispatched
one time since January.
Since the Sunomata mission.
But even so, I've been
training every day.
Improving, I thought.
Till Atsushi came back and
beat me in a matter of seconds.
Then challenge him to a
rematch. It was just once!
Kashuu, you're amazing, too!
Otherwise, the master wouldn't
have so much faith in you!
You're the only one
they trust to take care
of the new recruits.
It has nothing to do with trust!
I only have that job 'cause
I've been here the longest!
[HORIKAWA]
C'mon, it's not like that!
A sword is made to do
battle, don't you think?
So if I'm denied the
chance to do that,
I'm not worth anything, am I?
This place doesn't
need me anymore.
The master doesn't need me!
You know that's not true!
[HORIKAWA grunts]
I'm sorry.
Wait! Kashuu, come back!
Something that only I can do?
But what?
Sorry.
Kashuu, stop!
Did you two get
in a fight, or what?
Not exactly.
[YAMANBAGIRI]
So that's it.
I wanted to help him,
but I made things worse.
Cheering people up
isn't really my thing.
At all.
But this time, there's
something only I can tell him.
[KASHUU chuckles]
Sulking in my room
and running away.
Not cute. Not cute at all.
What am I supposed to do now?
Come back and tell
me already, Yasusada.
[YAMANBAGIRI]
Here. You dropped this.
[KASHUU]
Yamanbagiri.
Right, thanks.
You're not being excluded
because you're too weak.
You're excluded because
you're too strong.
Uh, what're you saying?
I heard it straight
from the master's mouth
right after they put you in
charge of the new recruits.
I was the attendant that day.
They said,
"It's not just that Kashuu has
been at the citadel the longest,
he's also been dispatched
more than anyone else here.
That's why I'm having
him take a little break.
To give everyone else
a chance to catch up."
Only I'm not the
strongest at all.
I just lost a match to Atsushi.
[YAMANBAGIRI] Strength on the
battlefield is about more than
just swordsmanship.
You also need the
power to keep your cool
in combat and bring
your team together,
with leadership.
Yeah?
So the master put me in charge
because I'm a good
leader, or what?
It's more because you of all
of us possess a good heart.
A lot of the new
recruits are nervous
when they first manifest,
so the master thought
if they had someone
like you to guide them,
they'd feel better.
I see.
That's a relief.
I thought that the master
didn't like me anymore.
You probably don't wanna
hear this from me,
since I'm a copy and all.
But, uh...
I think you're doing a good job.
It's something only you can do.
Thank you.
And thank you for
cheering me up, too.
By the way,
I noticed you're not hiding
underneath your hood for once.
What happened?
[YAMANBAGIRI]
Nothing!
[KASHUU] Your cloak is dirty,
but your skin is spotless!
I'm jealous!
[YAMANBAGIRI]
I'm never showing my face again!
[KASHUU laughs]
[MIKAZUKI] Lovely moon
tonight, don't you think?
[KASHUU]
Hey, Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI] I seem to recall a
similar scene from last year.
You, me and Yamatonokami,
I believe.
Oh, yeah.
I sure wish he'd hurry back.
I don't know what
he's doing out there.
[MIKAZUKI] Since we haven't
heard a word from the master,
I'm sure he's doing well,
wherever he is.
Did you work through
whatever trouble
you were having earlier today?
You noticed, huh?
Ugh! I'm so embarrassed
I could die!
It may trouble you now,
but soon it will become
a fond memory.
As usual, that's something
an old man would say.
I am an old man.
Kashuu.
You've grown kind.
[KASHUU chuckles]
What do you mean?
I've always been like this.
[MIKAZUKI]
Oh, have you? [laughs]
Splendid. Simply splendid.