[UGUISUMARU]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
Perhaps you'd like some tea?
Or a small snack?
This is the tale of the
legendary sword warriors,
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
Where am I?
It can't be...!
Osaka Castle?
[HONEBAMI]
Ichi. Everyone.
[HONEBAMI gasps, grunts]
Ichi!
Come back!
[gasps]
[groans] Good news.
I got that manure for you.
You don't want it?
Huh? Ah-ha!
Is that a new recruit
I spy at the table?
It is a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
I'm one of the Five
Great Swords of Japan.
Juzumaru Tsunetsugu.
[YAMABUSHI]
Ka ka ka ka ka!
I am Yamabushi Kunihiro,
famous for my roaring muscles.
Oh, are you copying sutras?
How pious of you, my new friend!
[JUZUMARU]
Are you a Buddhist as well?
[YAMABUSHI] Yes, though I walk
a different path than yours.
There are many
roads to enlightenment.
Indeed, that is true.
I wish to greet
hardship with a smile,
and laugh away every challenge.
I train day and night
to achieve that end.
[JUZUMARU]
That's quite fascinating.
For today's training regimen,
I thought I might seclude
myself in the mountains a bit.
Is that so?
I'd be honored if you'd
allow me to join you.
Ka ka ka!
The honor is mine!
That sounds lovely.
Might I tag along, too?
Of course!
For the road to enlightenment
and the road to friendship
are surely side by side!
[KASHUU]
Uh...?
Why am I here too?
You're responsible
for the new recruits,
so I thought you'd like
to oversee our little trip.
Okay, then what is
Doudanuki doing here?
[DOUDANUKI]
What?
You're doing bodybuilding,
right?
That's my scene.
Ka ka ka!
Your muscles will be thankful,
because our final
destination happens to be
the top of that mountain.
[KASHUU]
You're joking, right?
We're not climbing that.
[KASHUU groans]
Okay, fine! I guess we are!
Kashuu, that's not
the way we're going.
This is the path of the Buddha!
Why?!
Onward!
To enlightenment!
And even bigger muscles!
Why?
Why am I here?!
The weather's
warming up a bit, isn't it?
And so soon, too!
Yes, indeed.
It's the perfect season
for a cup of tea.
[HASEBE]
You two.
Have you seen
Yamabushi anywhere?
I have a job that could
really use some muscle.
He said he'll be training
in the mountains today.
Is he doing this to avoid me?
He took other Sword
Warriors with him, too.
[HIRANO]
"Ka ka ka ka!
Let the training commence!"
He said, with Juzumaru
and Doudanuki
lining up right behind him.
Nikkari and Kashuu were
there too for some reason.
They all went off
with Yamabushi, huh?
Is something the matter?
The thing is I joined
Yamabushi for training
once before and
it was hardly ideal,
to say the least.
In fact, it was a state
of utter madness.
Quite frankly, I fear
that someone might die!
This is my fault for not
offering them some tea.
Kashuu will work things out.
Well, probably.
[KASHUU] So, uh, we're just
going straight up?
[YAMABUSHI grunts]
Follow my lead, guys!
Onward! Ka ka ka!
[JUZUMARU]
Ha!
You cheater.
If they can climb
this thing, so can I!
[grunts]
[DOUDANUKI] I'll carry
the weights with my teeth!
But why?!
This is a mess.
My shoes aren't
exactly fit for climbing.
I have an extra pair
of tabi that you could use.
Tabi?
They have grips on the bottom,
so they're better
than your sandals.
I'll take what I can get.
[NIKKARI chuckles]
There are two to choose from.
These regular, boring tabi.
--[KASHUU] Uh...
--[NIKKARI] Or if you're daring,
these shiny golden tabi.
I'm certain that you'll
make the right choice.
Ugh. Let's go.
[KASHUU grunts]
That was an absolute nightmare.
[NIKKARI]
Nice work.
[KASHUU]
Huh?
How did you climb so fast?
[NIKKARI chuckles]
I took the easy way up
while no one was looking.
What? Cheater!
[YAMABUSHI] Now, we enter
the next phase of our training!
[KASHUU] Meditating under
a waterfall? Seriously?
[JUZUMARU]
Rather picturesque, isn't it?
I can't. I don't have
anything to wear.
[NIKKARI]
Never fear.
[NIKKARI chuckles]
[NIKKARI]
There are two to choose from.
This regular, boring robe.
Or if you're daring,
this shiny, golden robe.
I'm certain you'll make--
--[DOUDANUKI] Let's do it!
--[KASHUU] Why not?
[YAMABUSHI] Who wants to
try the waterfall first?
[JUZUMARU]
Please, allow me.
Then I offer to you a warning.
Ready yourself, for
my waterfall training
will be unlike anything
you have experienced before.
I face it with courage.
[YAMABUSHI]
That you must, my friend.
Nam myouhou renge kyou.
Nam myouhou renge kyou,
nam myo-ho...
[YAMABUSHI]
Let's roll!
My muscles roar with power!
Haja kenshou!
No surprise. He is legendary.
An excellent performance,
I must say!
That very nearly
caught me off guard.
[YAMABUSHI]
You're next, Kashuu!
Come forward!
If you are able to
overcome this trial,
then without a doubt,
you will acquire the strength
to laugh away any challenge!
I can't turn back now.
Fine! I'll do it!
[KASHUU] The strength to
laugh away any challenge.
[YAMABUSHI yells]
[KASHUU]
No weakness. No fear.
No way, bye!
[KASHUU sneezes]
I'm so cold.
[NIKKARI]
I warmed this up for you.
[KASHUU]
Yeah. I'll pass.
[NIKKARI]
Hm?
An empty stomach can prove
to be a deadly adversary!
Let us vanquish
this beast with food!
[JUZUMARU] I've never seen
such a fierce training regimen.
Ka ka ka!
It's another path
to enlightenment!
New feelings, new experiences
from a new perspective
on a road you've
never walked before!
Indeed.
I feel as if a gate inside
me has opened up.
I dunno about all
that spiritual stuff,
but we are weapons, right?
It's our job to be strong,
so we gotta keep
challenging ourselves
any way we can.
[KASHUU]
To be strong. Huh.
[NIKKARI chuckles]
Here. Have a bit
of rice porridge.
[JUZUMARU]
Yamabushi.
I hope that you'll allow
me to train with you
next time as well.
Of course!
[KASHUU chuckling]
[YAMABUSHI] Now that our
hunger has been satiated,
let's race back to
the citadel, full speed!
Training isn't over
'til your body gives out!
That's true devotion.
[NIKKARI]
You know how to entertain!
That's it. I'm done.
I'm training by myself
from now on!
Whoa, you've got big
bags under your eyeballs!
Do I?
What, did you sneak
out or something?
You rolled on top of me and
then wouldn't stop snoring.
That's all.
Oh, oops, sorry!
Can't really blame me,
though huh?
Our room's getting
really packed.
I'm heading off now.
Oh. Then let me go with you!
Honebami, don't take too long!
[HONEBAMI]
Right.
Are you okay?
There is a mission that requires
your immediate attention.
This citadel is facing a crisis.
We're out of money!
[HASEBE] I have only my
own negligence to blame
for this travesty!
Master, forgive
your foolish servant!
We've been doing whatever
we can to get by,
but with all the new recruits,
things are getting pretty tight.
[OTEGINE] That New Year's
party didn't help, I'm sure.
In the basement of Osaka Castle,
there might be treasure
left by the Toyotomi Clan.
All their gold was lost,
therefore we can bring it
here without altering history.
There's no tax and no bank fees?
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)] The lost
riches of the Toyotomi Clan
are like a legend!
I bet it's a massive haul!
It's a real-life treasure hunt!
Sounds like fun!
Guess we know Osaka Castle
better than anyone
else, don't we?
I remember a bit.
Now that I think about it,
I burned up when
the castle caught fire,
so my memory's a little hazy.
Same with you, right?
Uh-huh.
All I can remember
anymore are flames.
Consuming me as the
castle fell to pieces.
Have faith in the Master.
If they chose you for this
mission, then you can do it.
The captain will
be Ichigo Hitofuri.
You will depart immediately.
So exciting! A treasure hunt!
I forgot something.
Be right back.
[NAMAZUO]
Honebami, wait!
[HAKATA]
I can almost smell the gold.
All set, everybody ready to go?
You bet I am!
No, we can't leave!
Wait for Honebami!
[HONEBAMI]
I'm too late.
I think I remember
where they went, though.
Here?
[HONEBAMI]
Ichi? Hey, guys?
It can't be...
[HONEBAMI]
Ichi.
Everyone.
[HAKATA] What's taking
Honebami so long? C'mon!
[ICHIGO]
He should be here any second.
[NAMAZUO]
Ichi.
Is something the matter?
[NAMAZUO] This is where
we all burned, isn't it?
[ICHIGO]
Yes.
For what it's worth.
[NAMAZUO] Instead of
just taking the treasure,
what if we were able
to save the castle?
[ICHIGO]
We can't.
Then we'd be no
different than the enemy.
No regrets.
This is history.
Yeah, I know that.
And I'm happy
with our new master.
I wasn't serious or anything.
Honebami's taking too long.
I'm worried.
[NAKIGITSUNE (FOX)] The
equipment probably just goofed
up and he's stuck
at the citadel.
I hope so.
[NAMAZUO sighs]
Let me handle it.
One sec. I'll go back and
check on him real quick.
[NAMAZUO]
Honebami?
[NAMAZUO panting]
Honebami!
Brother?
You worried me!
I'm sorry!
It's my fault for being
so hung up on that gold!
Are you okay?
[HONEBAMI]
I'm fine.
I found you collapsed
in front of Osaka Castle.
[HONEBAMI]
I see. I messed up.
No, everyone's just
glad you're safe!
Let him rest.
I think we should
call it a day now.
I was the leader,
so I'll report to the master.
[ALL]
Okay!
Just take it easy.
We'll talk tomorrow.
I'll fix this.
Where'd he go?
[NAMAZUO]
I knew it.
Honebami!
[GROUP]
[HONEBAMI]
You followed me. Why?
That's not the issue!
What the heck're you doing?
I'm here because
I want to save you.
To stop you from burning.
We're supposed to protect
history! Why would you--
[HONEBAMI]
I'm just moving the swords.
When the fire has died down,
I'll move them right back.
Don't worry,
it shouldn't alter the past.
Losing your memories is painful.
I've felt it myself.
But I can save you
from that suffering.
It's not worth it!
[NAMAZUO]
I understand.
During our last mission,
I thought the same thing.
Then I realized. I'm happy
with how things are now.
We're who we are because
we lost our memories.
[NAMAZUO]
We're finally all together,
and we have so much fun
at the citadel every day.
So what does it matter
if I don't remember
what happened in the past?
If I got those memories back,
then I probably wouldn't be
the same person I am now.
And besides, instead
of getting hung up
on the memories we lost,
we should appreciate the
ones we're making, right?
So don't worry.
We've got each other now.
I think we'll be just fine.
You mean that?
I told you before, didn't I?
We'll make good memories
and forget the bad ones!
We're all done here.
Let's go home now.
We shouldn't make
the master worry.
Let's put all this behind us.
We'll do fine.
We've got each other.
I'm sorry.
--You're right.
--[thunder crashes]
[GROUP gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
The Kebiishi!
They must have sensed
that we were going
to alter history and
came to erase us
from the flow of time.
Yeah, but we didn't do anything!
Be that as it may, I doubt that
they would listen to reason.
Even this raging fire
couldn't tear us apart.
We're going home together
and you can't stop us!
[ICHIGO]
Get ready!
No touching, go away!
Yagen, go for it!
[YAGEN yells]
It's not enough.
[NAMAZUO grunts]
You're too slow!
[HRA SOLDIER 2A growls]
[NAMAZUO sighs]
[HONEBAMI grunting]
Prepare yourself.
[ICHIGO yells]
--[HRA SOLDIER 2D growls]
--[MIDARE, ATSUSHI yelp]
Oh, no! You okay?
You jerk. I'm gonna make
you pay for that one.
[HRA SOLDIER 2D roars]
That's my family, you know.
I won't let you harm them!
[HONEBAMI]
Ichi!
As long as one of us
is left standing,
we won't give up!
[HRA SOLDIER 2D roars]
This is my finishing blow.
None shall survive!
[HONEBAMI yells]
[MIDARE]
That was amazing!
Thank you.
Quite the close call!
We survived; that's the
only thing that matters.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[KASHUU sighs]
I am so worn out!
That took forever!
And you got us lost!
[YAMABUSHI]
Ka ka ka!
All part of the training,
my friend!
You don't need to train
while we're taking a bath, too!
[NIKKARI chuckles]
I'll scrub you clean.
Their hardcore workouts
don't really seem
like your style.
Yeah, well.
I'll probably get called for
dispatch all the time now.
Oh, by the way.
What was Hasebe
yelling about earlier?
Something happen?
Uh, this and that.
Nothing too crazy!
It was scary, but we pulled
through together, right?
I think our days
of time traveling
without the Master's
permission have come to an end.
I wouldn't say that
breaking the rules
was a good thing,
but I'm grateful to share
another memory with my brothers.
[NAMAZUO]
It's a shooting star!
[KASHUU]
Where?
Everybody, make a wish okay?
I wish for a bunch of
cute new clothes to wear!
I wish I could eat
meat 'til I blow up!
I wish I could make a miracle
drug that actually works.
[NAMAZUO, HONEBAMI] I wish for a
bright future with my brothers.