Please tell me we didn't
lose someone out there!
It isn't that dire just yet.
But according to the master,
the strength of Ookurikara's
team is dwindling quickly.
[SHISHIOU]
What went wrong?
[KASHUU]
Yeah, that's such a strong team.
I know.
It's confounding me as well.
If it's that bad, why can't
the master call them back?
It's a delicate
situation, I'm afraid.
They're locked in
combat right now,
protecting Date Munemura.
[HASEBE]
If we pull them back now,
then history will
doubtlessly be changed.
[SHISHIOU]
So we do nothing?
Just wait for the enemy
to destroy them?
[NAGASONE]
They're performing their duty.
We have to have faith.
[KANESADA]
Damn it!
There has to be a way to help!
We can send backup, can't we?
I wish, but there's only
one transportation device,
and we can't send
in another team.
[MIKAZUKI] We have the
original device, don't we?
It was sealed away back
when we remodeled,
but it should still work.
[KOGITSUNEMARU]
Then what are we waiting for?
Start it up before
it's too late!
[SHISHIOU]
I'll go!
Stop it!
There's no precedent for this.
It could cause a
complete disaster!
What do you mean?
We are dealing with a
disaster already, aren't we?
I don't care about the risk.
We have to do all
we can to save them!
I understand.
Allow me to consult the master.
[KONNOSUKE] A second dispatch
has been approved.
However, only three
swords are to be sent in
at this time.
The destination is
the fourteenth of August,
year 1747, at Edo Castle.
And this will be the team.
Tantou, Aizen Kunitoshi!
I'll blow 'em away!
[HASEBE]
Tantou, Atsushi Toushiro!
Leave this to me.
And the caption of this mission:
Uchigatana, Kashuu Kiyomitsu!
No problem.
[HASEBE] You should
be honored, by the way.
The master said you are
the only one they could trust
with this mission.
Well, I'm popular
after all, right?
And don't worry.
I'll bring them home.
Remember, we've never tried
two time-jumps concurrently.
You may be pulled back
here suddenly, so act fast.
Sure. We'll make it quick.
[HASEBE]
Kashuu, Atsushi, Aizen.
Make it home safe.
You hear me?
We'll be right here
waiting for you.
Okay. Time to go!
--[SAYO grunts]
--[TAIKOGANE grunts]
[KASEN grunts]
[MUNEMURA]
Who are you?
We're strangers, and yet you're
risking your life to protect me.
My mission is more than
just protecting you.
There is a legacy
that binds us all.
One that stretches
through history.
You speak riddles.
Never mind all that.
The point is that we cannot
and will not submit.
Take heed.
A thousand deaths would
be too kind for those
who would oppose us!
Accept your
punishment gracefully.
[OOKURIKARA grunts]
[KASEN gasps]
And now we're even.
No complaints from me.
[TSURUMARU grunts]
They sent more.
And the flying ones, too.
Why did it have to be them?
Aw, man. I'm wrecked.
This might be my
grand finale, you guys.
[AIZEN yells]
Stop floating around
and die already!
[ATSUSHI]
Heh.
[KASHUU grunting]
--Kashuu.
--Aizen!
Atsushi!
[KASEN]
How did you get here?
We'll explain once
we're home safe.
Let us handle the fighting.
You get these people
away from the castle.
You sure?
[KASHUU]
We're Sword Warriors, aren't we?
It's our duty to
protect history.
Of course...
I'd like to protect my
friends too, while I'm at it.
Take this.
And good luck.
Thanks.
The enemy is brutal.
You think they're okay?
They didn't come here to lose.
Have faith.
[KASHUU grunts]
[AIZEN, ATSUSHI grunt]
Seems that's the last of them.
It was a nice workout,
I will say.
Wait. There's more.
I see a shadow. It's up
there on the roof, look.
What the heck is that?
Another new monster?
They're stubborn. It figures.
[HRA BEAST 12A growling]
Should've known they wouldn't've
let us escape that easy.
[AIZEN grunts]
--[KASHUU grunts]
--[ATSUSHI grunting]
[ATSUSHI]
These things are a pain!
We need a full team
for this fight!
[KASHUU]
No, we just need one more!
[YASUSADA yelling]
[KASHUU]
Yasusada?!
[YASUSADA]
Ow...
Kiyomitsu?
Where are we? I'm lost.
[YASUSADA yells]
What the heck are those things?
I dunno.
Doesn't really matter, does it?
[YASUSADA growls]
[YASUSADA]
Yeah, you're right.
'Cause no matter what they are,
they're about to die!
[YASUSADA yells]
You ready?
Here we go!
[HRA BEAST 12A growls]
You've gotten pretty strong.
Yeah, I know it.
And you're not so bad, yourself.
[HRA BEAST 12B growls]
[AIZEN]
You're done!
Do it!
[ATSUSHI yells]
[HRA BEAST 12C growls]
[AIZEN yelling]
[KASHUU]
Just one left!
[GROUP gasps]
[KASHUU grunting]
I got this!
[HRA BEAST 12D growls]
--Careful!
--Get up, quick!
[YASUSADA]
Heh.
[HRA BEAST 12D growls]
Those who gaze upon
my naked skin must die!
Come on! It's time
for our dance of death!
[KASHUU]
I think that wraps it up.
[ATSUSHI] They're finally
out of reinforcements.
[AIZEN sighs]
Good! I'm beat!
Welcome back, Yasusada.
It's been a while,
don't'cha think?
[KASHUU]
Yeah, no kidding.
Where in the world have
you been all this time?
Oh, here and there--
it's a long story.
That's okay, you can
take your time with it
once we get back home.
I want to hear every detail!
If you're this strong,
it must be epic!
Let's get going, then.
I can't wait.
I'm ready!
Um...
I think I lost my device.
You what?!
Well, I'm sure it's
around here somewhere.
Hey! I found it!
But, uh...
Looks pretty busted.
It won't work.
[AIZEN, ATSUSHI, KASHUU]
What?!
Huh? Wait! I didn't start this!
We had a limited time after all.
We can't just leave!
What now?
It's okay!
I'll be right behind you,
I promise!
But how?
I'll come home.
No matter what!
[swishing noise]
[KASHUU grunts]
[KASHUU]
It's glowing.
Yasusada!
Kiyomitsu!
I'm so surprised you
showed up out of nowhere!
I don't really know
how I got here,
so I'm pretty surprised, myself.
Whatever.
The point is,
you're back. For real.
And happy to be here.
I'm sorry I kept you
waiting so long.
[YASUSADA]
Four months?!
I didn't know I kept
you waiting that long!
[KASHUU]
Yep.
[YASUSADA]
That's weird.
I got my transportation
device working
right after you left Edo.
[KASHUU] Your device
was in pretty bad shape.
It probably malfunctioned.
[YASUSADA]
Good point.
So, you gonna tell
me about your trip?
You were gone a whole year.
Like where did you go?
Different places
and different times,
though I didn't think it
would take quite so long.
Of course, I didn't want
to interfere with history,
so I could only stay
in each time period
for a few days.
Then I would jump
forward a couple of years
and repeat.
I wanted to see Souji's life,
but I wanted to witness
his final moments as well.
That's why?
It was painful
to watch him suffer,
but when I thought
about everyone
that was waiting
back at the citadel,
it gave me strength.
As time went on,
Kondo, Hijikata,
and Souji all passed away.
The Shinsengumi itself
died, as well.
But I continued onward
into the next era.
Then the next era.
And the era beyond that,
and on and on.
Then to modern day?
Yeah.
I saw the age of swords end,
the country fall into war,
and the country at peace again.
It made me dizzy
seeing how quickly
the world changed.
It was like stepping
into a whole new country
over and over again.
Wow.
And yet, no matter
how many decades passed,
and no matter what changed,
the tale of Souji
and the Shinsengumi
continued to be
passed down every time.
And that made me
realize something.
History really is worth
protecting, no matter what!
And I'm so proud to be here
with you fighting for it!
I'm sure that's not exactly
a big revelation for you.
But now, after I've
seen it all in person,
I finally get it.
I'm ready to give this fight
of ours everything I've got!
Good for you, then.
You've grown stronger.
Just like you promised me.
[YASUSADA]
Mm-hmm.
It's time to work hard.
I owe it to the master
and to everyone else
since I've been
away for so long.
Oh, hey.
How did you randomly
show up at Edo Castle?
Uh, yeah, funny story.
Huh? What the--?
I'm back home.
[HASEBE sighs]
Finished cleaning
the master's room?
Yes.
They have proven
to be quite the handful.
[KASHUU] You gotten
used to your body yet?
I still suffer some
lingering awkwardness,
but being locomotive
really does have
some nice perks.
I admit, humans
have it pretty good.
It is kinda convenient
to go wherever you want.
[glass breaks]
Hasebe!
I broke another plate!
I'm so sorry!
[HASEBE]
What did plates ever do to you?
[KASHUU]
Are you hurt?
Oh, no, I'm doing fine.
Dinner, on the other hand...
We've suffered
enough of this mess.
Listen, from now on
I'll take care
of the master's
daily necessities.
Hey! I didn't agree to that!
[HASEBE]
Come now, Kashuu,
you've told me that you
don't like getting dirty.
[KASHUU]
And what's your point?
[HASEBE] You might get food
on yourself in the kitchen.
So leave it to me.
It's fine.
Hasebe's cooking does always
turn out the best, anyway.
[sighs]
I'll be happy when the
master summons more of us.
There's too much work!
It feels so lonely with
all this empty space.
I sure wish Iwatooshi was here.
Iwatooshi?
He's Musashibou
Benkei's giant spear.
He and I protected Lord
Yoshitsune way back in the day.
Is there someone like that
you'd like to have here?
There is.
Another sword that was
used by the Shinsengumi
would be really nice.
[IMANOTSURUGI]
Oh, I guess so, huh?
It'd be even better if they
were one of Okita Souji's
swords like me.
We'd have a lot to
talk about, in that case.
[IMANOTSURUGI] Let's hope your
wish come true soon, then!
[KASHUU]
Yours too.
I wanna go back to my time.
To where all my friends
are waiting for me.
Back to Kiyomitsu.
Did it hear me?
It's glowing!
Then, before I knew it,
I was at Edo Castle with you.
You think the tree sent you?
[YASUSADA]
It's done crazy things before.
Anyway, that's my story.
Now I want to hear about
what you've been up to.
Well, a lot, really.
We have a ton of new
recruits for one, and...
Sorry.
When we fought,
I noticed that you were
much stronger than before.
Is that any surprise?
You think I'd let
you overshadow me?
Let's get stronger.
This time as a team.
If you insist.
I'll leave you in the dust
if you're not careful, though.
[BOTH laugh]
[YASUSADA]
How do you like this?
[KASHUU]
Just fine, thank you!
It feels heavy.
Your sword, I mean.
I've been training my butt off.
Frankly, I'm surprised I
haven't crushed you already.
--[YASUSADA yells]
--[KASHUU yells]
[YASUSADA]
Let's spar again.
Tomorrow, too.
And every day.
I'll be ready any time.
You didn't decorate the room
much; is something wrong?
[KASHUU] We just moved
in a little while back.
We can decorate
it together, then!
Come on!
How long're you gonna keep
everyone waiting out there?
Hold on a sec.
It's been a long time, okay?
I'm nervous!
[KASHUU]
Take this.
[YASUSADA]
Huh? Wow, you fixed it!
I think I improved it.
I had a lot of spare time
while you were gone.
[YASUSADA laughs]
Thanks for waiting!
Yamatonokami!
[GOKOTAI]
It's so good to see you!
Good to be back.
We're glad you're home.
And I trust you found
what you were looking for?
[YASUSADA]
Yeah.
[KASHUU] I was once the
beloved sword of Okita Souji,
and the first to
manifest at the citadel.
I hope that I can
keep growing stronger,
to protect my friends,
and to protect our home.
But even someone as
talented and popular as me
has room to grow.
So...
[YASUSADA, KASHUU]
Thanks for being patient.
Ah!
Seems the cherry blossoms
are waving at you!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Man, we got a real crowd!
I'll take a test picture first.
Smile! And smile big!
Let's see.
That turned out pretty good.
Let's do one more, 'kay?
[KONNOSUKE]
Wait for us!
The whole gang is here!
Please excuse our tardiness!
The master insisted on
speaking with all the new
Sword Warriors that have
manifested this past year!
Okay, this is the real deal!
Everybody ready to smile?
[ALL]
Ready!
One for the history books!
[AKITA, ATSUSHI chuckle]
[YASUSADA] I don't know,
this seems a little too cutesy.
[KASHUU]
Well, I think it suits you.
And what's wrong with cutesy?
If you say so.
Well, the master
likes cute things.
Don't you want to be popular?
[YASUSADA]
Eh...
Nope, it's way too flashy.
[KASHUU] And here I thought
we were competing.
[YASUSADA, KASHUU] This
was the tale of the legendary
sword warriors,
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.