[TAIKOGANE]
The year is 2205 AD.
[OOKURIKARA] The History
Retrograde Army seeks to control
the world by altering its past.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Born from the heart of swords,
[GROUP] we travel through time
to intercept and eliminate them.
Hello, Master.
I brought you some
zunda mochi to snack on.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Aw, c'mon,
there's enough to share!
[GROUP] This is the tale of
the legendary sword warriors,
and the Hanamaru days they
spent in a certain citadel.
[TONBOKIRI]
Oh. Hello there, Kikkou,
are you here on business
with the master?
Oh, no, I just thought I
might stop by for a little chat.
Hi! My name is Kikkou Sadamune.
I was once passed down
through the Tokugawa clan.
And I'm most famous
for the tortoiseshell crest
engraved on the tang
of my blade.
And you are?
[chuckles]
My name is Sengo Muramasa.
Or perhaps you know
me by my other name,
"the Demon Sword."
[chuckles]
But if you really want
to get to know me,
I should strip!
Not here!
You keep giving people
the wrong idea!
I don't care.
Let people think what they like.
I think I'll pass, thank you.
I believe whatever is hidden
under someone's clothes
should remain a secret.
That's a real shame.
[HASEBE]
I'll be on my way.
You here again?
The master has
important work to do.
I will not have
you pestering them.
Then I'll just sit quietly
and watch, that's all!
No, I am not leaving
you alone with them.
Oh, hello, you must
be the new recruit.
My name is Sengo Muramasa.
We don't share a name,
but we were forged
by the same man.
We're both a part
of the Muramasa Family.
I'm Heshikiri Hasebe.
I serve as attendant
to the master.
[SENGO] Oh? And what does
that entail, pray tell?
Sometimes I clean their room
and tidy up
clutter on the floor.
Sometimes I help them
finish their paperwork.
I also relay their orders
to everyone here.
And in my free time,
I devote myself
to personal projects
aimed at making the
master's daily life easier.
[KIKKOU]
Why hello there, Master.
Do you mind if I pop in?
Hey, stop that!
I said that they
have work to do!
Either remove yourself
or I'll do it for you!
[KIKKOU]
Excuse me.
[TONBOKIRI]
Hey, Sengo.
Not that you would,
but try not to do anything
that might trouble the master.
But of course.
Tonbokiri, let's go.
We've been assigned a mission.
No problem.
If you have any other questions,
Kashuu will take care of you.
Have fun out there.
[HASEBE] Kashuu, this may be
a lengthy expedition for us.
Oh. Really?
[HASEBE] I'm leaving the citadel
in your hands while I'm gone.
You got it. Have a nice trip.
[KIKKOU]
Might I make a suggestion?
Allow me to be the master's
attendant while he's gone.
Don't startle me.
[SENGO]
Not so fast.
I'd like to nominate myself
for the position as well.
It's nothing but
busy work, really.
If I were to obtain
such a coveted position
so soon after coming
to the citadel,
why, that would make me
a legend, don't you think?
No. Other than Hasebe,
I don't think anyone
here actually cares.
Surely I am fated to do this.
Your reasons are selfish.
I, on the other hand,
am motivated only
by my desire to aid
my beloved master
in any way I can.
Therefore, I am the
only suitable choice.
You know what this means.
A contest!
Kashuu, you will decide
which of us is more fit
to perform the job!
[KASHUU]
Fine.
The master's wellbeing should
begin with the proper care
of their environment.
So our first challenge
will be cleaning.
Clean body, clean mind,
and clean abode.
Now the job must be done
quickly but thoroughly.
And whoever cleans to the
end of the porch first wins.
It's the Super Speed
Scrubbing Showdown!
Challenge accepted.
By the way, what is this?
[KIKKOU]
Mr. Spick-and-Span the Second!
Apparently, it allows you
to clean and polish
at the same time.
Ho ho!
A modern convenience!
All right.
In that case, we might
as well be generous
in its application!
Stop it! You only need a bit!
I am ready when you are.
This should be fun.
[WIPERS cheer]
[KASHUU] Good.
Looks like the coast is clear.
Ready... Go!
Now eat my literal dust.
Oh, no!
[yells]
I'll clean your
side when I'm done!
I have blundered.
[KIKKOU yells]
Not over!
You said it!
[BOTH grunting]
[JIROUTACHI] You won't believe
what Nihongou did next!
Are you okay?
[yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[TAROUTACHI]
Coming through.
[yelling]
[TAROUTACHI]
Excuse me.
[JIROUTACHI]
Someone stop me!
[yelling]
[crash]
Well, that was
certainly unexpected.
[KASHUU]
Okay. What's next?
A warrior must have endurance,
and they must be prepared
to fight in any situation,
even if they find themselves
completely nude.
I have combined these two
concepts into what I call:
The Steamy Stamina Showdown!
[KASHUU sighs]
I see.
[door opens]
[KIKKOU]
Sorry I'm late.
You're wearing clothes!
Do you mock me, sir?
[KIKKOU] Forgive me,
but I'm simply not fond
of exposing myself.
This robe surely gives me
no advantage, you see.
So I'm sure you
won't object, right?
I suppose it's fine, I guess.
For in the end, my nudity
will surely prevail.
[KASHUU sighs]
[KASHUU groans]
[KASHUU gasps]
Everyone has a secret
or two worth hiding,
so let's keep this one
between us, shall we?
Yeah, okay.
I can't take this heat.
See you when you're done.
You're a worthy adversary,
but this inferno will melt your
resolution soon enough.
On the contrary,
I'm enjoying the pain.
[SENGO laughing]
I heard a weird noise
in here. You okay?
[BOTH groaning]
[KASHUU] Nobody's suffering
from heat stroke, right?
[KIKKOU] I'm fine.
Sorry for the trouble.
[SENGO]
That was perfectly refreshing.
What shall we do for
our next showdown?
What? You're still at this?
[TSURUMARU]
Now that is a surprise!
What's going on
in here, you guys?
I'm doing magic tricks.
I've been practicing
for a while now.
Yeah, and he's really good!
He can read minds
and everything!
He pulled all sorts of stuff
right out of thin air!
I've been watching
him like a hawk
and I can't tell how
he makes it work.
I still have an escape
trick to show you guys.
I can't move my hands, so cover
them with a towel for me.
Okay, is that good?
Uh-huh!
You better watch carefully!
Voilà!
Whoa!
You tied that improperly!
True bondage must
be done tightly!
Oh. I see.
Why don't we make
this our next competition?
We each choose
someone here to tie up,
and whoever's knots
get untied last
will be declared the winner.
And what's the
relevance of that?
Ingenious.
After all, an intruder might
breach the citadel's defenses
and assault the master.
In that event, sub-par rope
work would simply not suffice.
Indeed, the intruder
must be bound properly.
So let us begin the Snared-Up
Security String Showdown!
[SENGO] This will be
our final competition.
Winner takes all.
[KIKKOU]
I couldn't ask for more.
I'm finished!
[SENGO]
As am I.
Behold the beauty of bondage!
Let's go!
Goodness.
It seems I'm all tied up!
[IWATOOSHI laughing]
So, may I escape now?
Yes. If you think you can!
It's another surprise!
How did you pull that one off?
I'm afraid that's a secret.
I'm sorry.
I don't know any fancy
escape tricks like Nikkari,
but I'll try.
[grunting]
That was cool, Iwatooshi!
[IWATOOSHI laughs]
Maybe I'll do it
again sometime!
Seems you chose
your volunteers poorly.
Well, it looks like
we have another tie.
In that case...
I challenge you to a duel!
As you wish!
We'll settle this quick!
I'm back.
[KASHUU]
Welcome home.
So, did I miss anything big?
[KASHUU]
Same old same old.
Very well.
What are two doing?
If you have time for horseplay,
then you have time to train.
Anyway, I need to
report to the master,
so goodbye.
[KIKKOU] I fought valiantly
to prove myself,
but it was all for naught.
You've been a worthy rival.
I had fun today.
Yes. As did I.
We can settle this another time.
And I'll be ready for it.
[IWATOOSHI]
Let's tie everyone up next time.
[chattering]
What freaks.
Uguisumaru, what is that there?
Are you writing a book?
In a way...
A diary, really.
Why does it have Ookanehira's
name on it, though?
I'm confused.
I wanted to keep a journal
like all of your brothers do,
but I'm not exciting.
So I aimed for a more
engaging subject.
[HIRANO]
Now that I think about it,
Ookanehira is a
complete mystery to me.
I've only spoken
to him once or twice.
If you don't mind,
would you share
some of your
observations with me
so I can get to know
him a little better?
Heh. But of course.
[UGUISUMARU] For starters,
despite his casual appearance,
he's actually quite
serious about work.
Field duty, huh?
No prob.
I can handle the monotony.
Why are you drinking tea?
There's work here to be done,
you buncha bums!
Don't stress out,
we're doing just fine.
We wake up early,
so we finished all our chores.
Right?
Yeah. And I was careful.
I didn't spook the horses
with my power this time.
Bragging about your power, huh?
You're one of the Five Great
Swords of Japan, I know.
But if Ikeda Teramasa
had discovered me sooner,
then I'd be every bit
as famous as you.
Why do you get
so hung up on that?
I don't think cleaning
the barn has anything to do
with being a Great Sword.
It's only a title, Ookanehira.
You're just fine how you are.
Shut up!
You don't understand my
feelings and you never will!
[JUZUMARU]
Hello.
Are you my partner
for field duty today?
Let's do our best, shall we?
Yes, of course.
I will work hard.
[JUZUMARU] We'll be
planting daikon radishes.
So he yells at us,
but he's all polite to him.
[laughs]
[JUZUMARU] Create a shallow
depression in the ground,
like so.
Then place four or
five seeds inside.
Cover them with dirt
when you're finished,
then do it again.
Thanks. Got it.
[JUZUMARU]
Then I shall take my leave
to the other side
of the field.
This side is
your responsibility,
so please fill it with
seeds all the way to the end.
Okay, easy!
Make a depression
in the ground, huh?
Then four or five seeds.
Cover them with
dirt when I'm finished,
then do it again.
Keep going till
the end of the field.
Make a shallow
depression in the ground.
Add four or five seeds.
Make a shallow
depression in the ground.
Add four or five seeds.
Make a shallow
depression in the ground.
Add four or five seeds.
Make a shallow
depression in the ground.
Add four or five seeds.
Make a shallow
depression in the ground.
Add four or five seeds.
Make a shallow
depression in the ground.
[HIRANO]
I see.
Sounds like he's
a really serious guy.
Indeed.
Serious to a fault,
you might even say,
since he's a bit stubborn.
[HIRANO giggles]
Oh, by the way.
You went to the beach with
him a while back, didn't you?
I did.
And that's in here too.
[GROUP]
One and two and one and two
and one and two and one and two!
[whistle blows]
Point goes to the Black Team!
[UGUISUMARU]
Even though it was just a game,
he fought as if his
pride was on the line.
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Looking good, looking good!
Nice one, Mitsu.
I would expect nothing less.
No, I owe it all
to your teamwork.
One more point, huh?
We got this in the bag.
Damn it!
I should've had that one.
It's all my fault!
[HIZAMARU]
Don't blame yourself.
It was a good play.
Exactly.
After all, even my little
brother, um... uh...
It's Hizamaru.
Even he missed it.
It'll be fine.
Let's just focus
on the next one.
If we fail, it'll be our last!
Our lives are on the line here;
we have to fight like it!
Please, lend me your strength!
We're representing
the Minamoto Clan.
If we don't answer his call,
we'll look bad.
You're right.
Come on.
Let's show them
what we're made of!
[whistle blows]
I'm gonna finish 'em off!
[TSURUMARU grunts]
Don't worry, I got it!
And go, Ookanehira!
[OOKANEHIRA]
Ready!
Our comeback starts now!
A comeback?
Is that so?
[TAIKOGANE]
Ooh, nice.
You're next! Now go!
Yeah! I'm on it!
Brace yourself!
I call this baby the
Trinity Assault Strike!
What the--?
Somebody!
[OOKANEHIRA]
Leave it to me!
[HIZAMARU]
There's no time!
I won't lose! Watch!
[HIGEKIRI, HIZAMARU]
Ookanehira!
Forget about me!
Just get the ball!
I say we show 'em a
special move of our own!
I was thinking the same thing!
[HIZAMARU, HIGEKIRI]
Flying Double-Sword Attack!
[TAIKOGANE grunts]
[whistle blows]
[ICHIGO]
Point goes to the White Team!
Nice save!
I thought we were finished
for sure back there!
I see they don't call you the
Yokozuna of Sword Warriors
for nothing!
That's only a
sample of my strength!
[HIRANO] If nothing else,
Ookanehira sure is
a hard worker, isn't he?
That's true.
Although sometimes
that work is misguided
and he struggles to no avail.
That, or he ends
up hurting himself.
I see.
Now that you mention it,
when he came back from
his mission the other day,
I noticed that he
was injured pretty badly.
He was.
But each wound he bore
was proof of his bravery.
[HASEBE] Your destination
is the Genroku Era.
The captain this time
is you, Ookanehira.
Come and get me!
[HRA SOLDIER 8B growls]
[OOKANEHIRA]
I'll finish him!
I noticed you're
short of breath.
I can take over
if you need a rest.
My strength is equal to
the Great Sword Doujigiri!
I won't falter!
[HRA SOLDIER 8C growls]
Now what?
[UGUISUMARU]
Kebiishi?
--[KEBIISHI 8A growls]
--[HRA SOLDIERS growl]
[HRA SOLDIER 8D growls]
[HRA SOLDIER 8E growls]
[OOKANEHIRA grunts]
They're fighting the enemy,
too, that's good, right?
Well, for now.
But there's too many--
we need to withdraw.
Very well.
Everyone, retreat!
[OOKANEHIRA]
Shinano!
It's too late to
stop the transfer--
you have to save him yourself!
[SHINANO grunts]
Are you okay?
[OOKANEHIRA grunts]
I'll be fine.
A captain won't rest until
all of his men are safe.
[OOKANEHIRA]
Looks like I'm sticking around.
Not your lucky day.
[HRA SOLDIER 8D growls]
[OOKANEHIRA laughing]
Watch close. 'Cause this...
...is the last thing you'll see!
That's amazing.
He won the battle,
then brought Shinano
back here with him?
Indeed.
It sounds like
he was a real hero,
so why is this the
first I've heard of it?
He said,
"If I had been stronger,
the rest of the team
wouldn't have been
forced to retreat,
and I wouldn't have
been injured so badly.
So speak nothing
of this, please."
I honored his request
until now, at least.
But he should be proud, and you
can keep a secret, can't you?
Sure!
I won't tell a single soul
how brave he was.
Well, I'm sure
he'll be heroic again.
I don't doubt it one bit.
That guy really
is something else.
[OOKANEHIRA]
What guy?
[HIRANO]
Hey, Ookanehira!
How are your injuries?
Feeling better?
It was barely a scratch.
I'm tougher than that.
But seriously, what were
you two talking about?
Looked like you were having fun.
It's a secret.
Well, fair enough.
[UGUISUMARU]
Since you're here,
would you like to have
some tea with us?
[HIRANO] We have some
snacks to go with it.
[OOKANEHIRA]
Sounds great.