[ALISHA sighs]
[ALISHA] This world...
It's falling apart.
[ALISHA]
Sunrise?
[ALISHA gasps]
That's a hero brandishing
the sacred blade.
It's a mural of the Shepard!
[gasps]
[NORMIN hums, giggles]
[ALISHA]
I think this is what it depicts.
Yes. It's the Legend
of the Shepard.
The Capital of Seraphim
was a sacred place.
It stood higher than
the highest peaks,
magnificent and unassailable.
Its gates remained
tightly closed,
opening only for those
whose task it was
to lead the world of man.
And a time came when
the Shephard arrived
on the Earth,
accompanied by Seraphim
and wielding their might.
The Shepherd then cleansed
the world of darkness.
and brought salvation.
[ALISHA sighs]
Nothing but a legend.
It's too late for this world.
[whines]
Ah...
[screams]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[NORMIN growls]
[yells]
[screams]
[ALISHA screams]
[yelling]
[ALISHA]
More of them.
[ALISHA grunting]
[screams]
[yelping, screaming]
[gasps, pants]
[gasps]
Is that the floor?
[ALISHA yelps]
[ALISHA]
What is this place?
Could it be another
ruin of Asgard?
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
This looks like...
I think it is.
The symbol of the Shephard.
Where the symbol...
How does the legend go?
[rumbling]
[gasps]
The symbol will guide the way,
and the path will open.
Is the legend actually true?
[SOREY pants]
[SOREY]
Look at that!
I was hoping I'd find
something good out here!
[MIKLEO]
Sorey!
Hey, Mikleo!
[MIKLEO]
What are you thinking,
wandering off on your own again?
Sometimes I think you forget
that you're just
a regular human.
Fall from here,
and that's it for you.
[laughs nervously]
Still...
I can see why you risked it.
Pretty amazing, huh?
Yeah, it is!
[MIKLEO]
Anyway,
we may not have known
about those ruins,
but you can be sure
the elders did.
[SOREY]
I guess you're probably right.
I wonder...
They know we love
exploring ruins,
and they didn't tell
us about that one.
Is there a reason?
Huh?
[MIKLEO]
Hm? What are you doing?
[SOREY]
Nice! I found it.
[sighs]
What? I don't see
anything but stone.
You don't yet,
but check this out.
[MIKLEO]
I get it now.
One of Gramps' illusions, huh?
That's a nice catch Sorey.
Ha, ha!
So... What now?
We head right down and
check it out, obviously!
[GRAMPS]
No.
[BOTH gasp]
[SOREY]
Gramps?
Why aren't we allowed in there?
Because the area is sealed off,
and it's not your
place to question why.
You boys are not to
approach it for any reason.
Do not even think
about exploring it.
Understood?
I wonder why that ruin's
off-limits to us.
Gramps was so serious about it.
Come here and look at this.
The chapter of arrival.
"Long ago, in the
age of the gods.
the world was
shrouded in darkness.
but dark fled when
the Seraphim came.
bringing light back
into the world.
The Seraphim did not
all abide in one place.
Rather, they spread
throughout the world,
that they could support
all its inhabitants.
Some choose to reside
in the Capital of Seraphim.
And you're thinking
the ruins we saw today
are that same Capital.
Interesting theory,
I'll give you that.
Look.
[MIKLEO] According to this,
the humans who lived
within the Capital of Seraphim
began to worship the Seraphim,
and those men who had the talent
were allowed to speak to them.
Humans and Seraphim, together?
[SOREY] That's right,
living in the same place.
The people prayed to the
Seraphim, and in return,
the Seraphim blessed them.
Can you imagine what living in
that era would've been like?
Two worlds uniting--
humans and Seraphim actually
bonding together and
talking to each other.
[MIKLEO] Hm. Certainly
sounds different.
[MIKLEO]
The Celestial Record .
You put a lot of faith
in that book, don't you?
Of course.
Anyway, it's got
tons of descriptions
of what certain places
used to look like.
Based on what it says,
I think the ruins we found
are the Capital of Seraphim!
[MIKLEO]
So you're going to explore them?
[SOREY]
Aren't you coming with me?
Of course.
But there is something
we ought to keep in mind.
I noticed it when
we were out there.
Did you catch it?
The ruins are outside
Gramps' area of protection.
Guess they are, aren't they?
[MIKLEO]
Even so,
I still wanna see them.
Are you sure?
Gramps'll be really mad
if he finds out.
[MIKLEO] Don't tell me you've
changed your mind about going.
No way, and I'm
gonna find something
cool in there before you do.
So it's a race, then.
Yeah!
[ALISHA panting]
[panting, whimpering]
[ALISHA screams]
[ALISHA panting, whimpering]
[SOREY grunts]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[laughs]
I knew I was right!
[SOREY] A hero lifting up
the sacred blade!
An image of the
Shepherd, for sure.
Yeah!
[SOREY]
What's this glove doing here?
It's the Mark of the Shepherd.
[SOREY gasps]
[SOREY] Hey, what're you
doin'? That's my find.
I guess this means
you win. Well done then.
How many wins is
that for me now?
[MIKLEO]
I don't recall.
[laughs]
[gasps]
[SOREY] This lightning
came out of nowhere.
It's not natural.
[ALISHA panting]
[screams]
Master Zenrus.
Thank you, Kyme. But I am aware.
There has been a disturbance.
Some fool's causing
trouble outside my area.
Yes.
How would you like to proceed?
[GRAMPS] What do you know
of Sorey and Mikleo?
Have they returned yet?
[KYME]
No, sir.
[GRAMPS exhales]
[GRAMPS]
Such reckless young men.
It's natural to be curious
about secrets of the past,
but I wish they would
be more careful.
Go, Kyme.
I will remain here for now.
[KYME]
Yes, sir.
[ALISHA panting]
[ALISHA]
Am I in some kind of temple?
It's a dead end.
[gasps]
[ALISHA yelps]
[ALISHA screams]
They better not
come into my area
of protection,
because if they do,
they will feel my wrath.
Am I imagining it,
or does it seem like
these ruins are
calling the lightning?
[yelps]
[MIKLEO]
Sorey?!
[SOREY pants, laughs]
[sighs]
Let's get outta here.
[grunts]
[yelps]
[gasps]
[MIKLEO, SOREY scream]
[SOREY yelping]
Surging currents!
Twin Flow!
Huh? Are you--?
Wait, no, Mikleo!
--[MIKLEO] Sorey!
--[SOREY] Ow.
[MIKLEO]
That could've been bad.
[MIKLEO] The ruins even
extend underground.
[SOREY] I guess it was
lucky we fell down here.
[MIKLEO]
Yeah, real lucky.
Let's start trying to find
a way out of here, okay?
[SOREY]
Good call.
[SOREY] Wow, that would
be a long way to fall.
I've had enough falling
for one day, thank you.
Think of all the
cool things we saw.
It's totally worth it.
Yeah. I guess it was.
[SOREY]
Someone's over there!
[MIKLEO]
What, down here?
I can't believe it.
[SOREY]
That's... a human girl.
[MIKLEO]
A human? How did she get here?
Let's find a way down.
Remember what Gramps said.
You know you're supposed
to stay away from humans.
[SOREY]
I can't leave her!
What if she's still alive?
She could be injured.
[MIKLEO] All right, fine.
I'll help you if I can.
[SOREY]
Thank you!
[MIKLEO]
But how do we get across?
Huh?
[grunts]
You're not gonna...
Yup! And so are you!
[SOREY]
Let's go!
[MIKLEO yelps]
[MIKLEO]
What good did that do?
We still have to cross
that gap somehow.
Won't be a problem.
Take a look.
[MIKLEO]
Right, I see it now.
You know, you are
surprisingly good
at finding these things.
[gasps, laughs]
[MIKLEO]
Well...
The girl?
Oh, right.
[SOREY]
How do you think this was made?
[MIKLEO]
Not with human technology.
That would've been impossible.
Then wouldn't that
mean that the bridge
is at least as old as
the Era of Mythology?
[MIKLEO]
I don't know.
I don't think this
is a good idea.
Sorey!
Hello? Are you okay?
I think...
[sighs]
[ALISHA]
What happened?
All that lightning...
And then...
[gasps]
She's alive. And not too hurt.
Can you stand?
Thanks for helping me.
I must've hit my
head when I fell.
You are?
My name is Sorey.
Nice to meet you!
Sorey...
Tell me.
Sorey, are you a Shepherd?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Mikleo. I'm going
to try talking to her.
Do you think I'm ready?
A cleanly appearance
is essential.
Did you bathe today?
I did.
And your hair?
Washed it.
Your teeth?
Brushed 'em!
Handkerchief?
Got it!
The weather today?
Lovely!
All right. I think you're ready.
[SOREY]
No, I can't.
It's too scary! I don't
know where to start.
Mikleo, I need you to
tell me everything you know
about talking to girls.
Gramps did give me
a few pointers for that.
As the guy, you've
gotta keep it cool.
So...
Show me an example.
Okay.
I'll be playing the girl.
Right.
Oh, my.
It's warm today, isn't it?
I ignore.
What's your favorite food?
Mine's salad!
I ignore.
And how exactly is this
supposed to help me
get close to her?
Don't ask me, okay?
Gramps just said this is the
right way to deal with humans!
Next week, "Elysia."
Look forward to it!
Sorey. You've got some time.
Make sure you practice.
Okay...