I knew you'd show up
right when I needed you.
Of course I did. I know
you're helpless without me.
Admit it, you're a wreck
when I'm not around.
Don't be silly.
You've gotten stronger. Good.
Found yourself a
hardworking Shepherd, huh?
Purifying the water
supply is important.
Ultimately, it's going to be
the key to rebuilding Marlind.
I'm surprised water boy
was so willing to tag along.
Of course, those two
are practically inseparable.
The air feels worse
the deeper we go.
[MIKLEO]
This is the place.
[SOREY]
Yeah. Let's get started.
Well? How's it feel?
Good enough to me.
If you're ready,
let's release it.
We call upon you now.
O great water,
mother to us all,
grant us the power
of purification.
[EDNA yelps]
[BOTH sigh]
[SOREY] This is starting to feel
like a never-ending chore.
There's always more
water to be purified.
[MIKLEO] No one ever said
being Shepherd would be fun.
[SOREY] Heh. Yeah,
you're right about that.
All right, how long
have we been
trudging around
these sewers for?
Three days.
Good thing you're
a seraph of water
or it would be a lot
longer than that.
If I was doing this job alone,
it would've taken more than
a month to get this far.
[MIKLEO]
Ha. Flattery?
That's not like you.
Feeling okay?
[SOREY]
Heh. You're right, I'll stop.
Well, let's get going.
[LAILAH] You are growing into
a wonderful Shepherd, Sorey.
Your diligence and dedication
are the sign of a good leader.
Isn't that right, Edna?
Eh, wouldn't go that far.
Sorey, a leader?
That isn't what I'd call him.
Well, what then?
[VILLAGER A]
Sir Shepherd!
[VILLAGERS cattering]
[EDNA sighs]
I'm exhausted.
How are you tired when
you didn't do anything?
I spent most of the day in
your company. That's real work.
You're such a brat!
That's quite enough, little boy.
Now, you two, try not
to bicker so much.
Alisha found us a place
to relax, so let's enjoy it.
[SOREY] What about you, Rohan?
How're you doing?
Much better than
I've been in some time.
For which I have you to thank.
[SOREY sighs]
[SOREY]
I'm glad to hear it.
I failed in my sacred duty.
As a Seraph, I should've
protected Marlind
from the chaos.
[ROHAN]
Instead, I allowed myself
to be consumed by malevolence.
You must not blame yourself.
The world is unsettled.
Every Seraph faces corruption.
And it's worse for
those near humans.
[SOREY]
Can you tell us more
about how the city
became consumed?
What fed the malevolence?
I only wish I could tell you.
But I'm afraid I don't
remember that much.
I do believe it started
as something small though.
Someone borrowing a book maybe,
without asking for permission?
That sort of thing.
I know what you're sayin'.
I've seen it before.
Whole villages up and vanish.
Small ones, it's
true, but still.
And it always seems to start
out as such a small thing.
Then suddenly, boom!
Darkness is everywhere!
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
a Normin Seraph was among us.
[ATAKK]
Well howdy!
I remember now that
Normin Seraphim
used to live
throughout the city.
We worked together to
maintain harmony here.
It has been a long time,
but I still can't believe
I'd forgotten that.
Those were the good old days
with a Seraph for each city
and a Normin for each village.
We may not be much
in terms of size,
but we sure got the numbers!
Seraphim and Normin sort
of balance each other.
That's fascinating.
[ATAKK]
There used to be so many of us,
all working for the same thing,
but now we're scattered
all over the world.
[ALISHA] Sorey. I brought
you something to eat.
[SOREY]
Thank you.
If you don't mind me
eating with you,
I could use the company.
Of course.
Once again, thank you.
The water seems
much cleaner now.
That's the key,
according to Lailah.
When rainwater filters
through trees and soil,
it absorbs the
land's malevolence,
thus becoming toxic.
It may take a year
to truly purify.
I see.
It must be very difficult
to keep all the elements
balanced and in harmony.
I humbly thank you, Seraphim.
You have my deepest gratitude.
The citizens know what you did.
They welcome you with open arms.
I'm sure they would be happy
to live alongside you,
as we all did long ago.
I pray you will continue
to lend us your aid.
How goes the city's repairs?
It's too early to know
if we can restore it
to its former glory,
but I do think there's
reason to hope.
And to me, hope can make
all the difference.
If there's anything else
I can help with, just ask.
[ALISHA] Are you sure?
You look a bit tired.
[SOREY] Well, you look like you
could use a break yourself.
At the very least,
he is a hard worker.
I'd say the same goes
for Princess Alisha.
That is one of Sorey's
finest qualities. Although...
[EDNA]
Although?
[LAILAH] Nothing.
Sorry, I'm just babbling.
It burns!
All right then.
We're beginning to
receive supplies
for the reconstruction
of the city,
and there's a lot of
organizing we need to do.
Do you think you could
help us out with that?
Sure.
Here.
Okay, that should
be the last one.
[sighs]
[ALISHA] We are distributing
emergency provisions evenly
amongst all the city's people.
There is to be no hoarding
and no stealing.
Any who do so will be
severely punished.
All right, let's get to work.
Alisha really doesn't
get tired, does she?
You know, the princess
could delegate
instead of doing
all this herself.
Well, that's just the kind
of person that Alisha is.
Oh, you know her well, do you?
Don't make it sound weird.
Huh?
She looks familiar.
[ROSE]
Hey, think you can help us?
We're the Sparrowfeathers,
come from Ladylake.
We've got a wagon packed full
of food and supplies
for the people of Marlind.
Can you tell us
where to put it all?
[ALISHA]
You're a welcome sight.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I was talking
to a Hyland princess!
Out here, I'm just
another knight.
I have heard good things
about the Sparrowfeathers.
I've heard some things about
you too, Princess Alisha.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
[SOREY]
Hello again!
Hey there! Long time no see.
Oh, Sorey, you two
know each other?
Yeah, we met at Ladylake.
This is, uh...
The name's Rose.
And it looks like you are
the Lord Shepherd now.
When we parted ways,
you agreed you owe me one.
Do you remember?
Uhh...
[ROSE] How are you going
to settle our debt?
You have moved up a lot
in the world, after all.
Well, being the Shepherd isn't
exactly a paying gig, you know.
Hey, if you're not good for it,
I completely understand.
Fortunately, you have friends!
Oh, unclench. I'm just kidding!
[SOREY sighs]
So the wagon. We've got
a lotta food here.
Where would you like it?
Right, just over there, please.
[ROSE]
Got it.
[MALTRAN]
Alisha!
[ALISHA] What is it, Master?
Is something wrong?
[MALTRAN]
Shiller has a report for you.
Go ahead. It sounds urgent.
Yes, but, Master.
[ALISHA] He can hear whatever
it is that you have to say.
This is Sorey, the Shepherd.
I'm a personal rider
to the princess.
My name is Shiller.
Your Highness, Chancellor
Bartlow has ordered our troops
to march to Glaivend Basin.
Are you certain about this?
Glaivend Basin acts
as the buffer zone
between Hyland and Rolance.
When we left on our journey,
I sent Shiller and others
to be my eyes and ears,
but I didn't think Bartlow
would go this far.
[SHILLER] Rumor has it that
the high-ranking officers
have been told to
prepare for war.
All-out war?
First, he chased you out,
and then Bartlow got exactly
what he wanted all along.
That snake. Why is
he striking now?
[MALTRAN] He had a convenient
excuse to send you away,
and Hyland's resources
likely need replenishing.
A good motive.
What better way to resupply
than by raiding the enemy.
I wonder what will happen
after he takes all he can get.
[SHILLER]
The second wave of troops
is leaving Ladylake as we speak.
We can never make it.
I must. I'll stop them somehow.
Don't be reckless.
[SOREY]
I'm going with you.
[LAILAH]
I advise against that.
[SOREY]
Lailah! I don't understand!
You were the one who said
I had to travel around
and see things for myself!
[LAILAH] Sorey, you don't know
what it's like for a human
to be truly consumed
by malevolence!
Things are different
on a battlefield!
I feel it too.
There's a hellion.
It's different.
Yeah, it is.
That's because, this is... It's
malevolence born of a human.
It's heavy. Intangible,
but oppressive.
[SOREY]
In here.
[thud]
It's a human? That thing?
Yes, or it was.
To a normal person he would
still appear human.
You should be able
to see it too, Sorey.
Look closely, and you'll
see his original human form.
He looks scared.
Now use your power.
Purify him, Shepherd.
[VOICES screaming]
Are you okay?
Quick! You can't let
that hellion escape!
[SOREY] I won't let him
spread more malevolence!
You all right? Can you stand?
It was so much harder than
anything I've done before.
I didn't know it
could be like that.
Yes. Purifying a human
is quite different.
In order to do so,
the Shepherd accepts the
malevolence into himself.
[EDNA]
You are the only one
who can internalize
malevolence that way.
Even the Seraphim can do
nothing to ease your burden.
As the Shepherd,
you stand alone.
[MIKLEO]
Sorey.
This... isn't over.
[SOLDIER A]
We need more horses!
[SOLDIER B]
Round up as many as you can!
[ALISHA]
Is the rescue squad ready?
We're awaiting confirmation.
Medical team?
Yes, soon.
Make it sooner.
Yes, Your Highness.
My squad is waiting
for me to join them.
They're stationed here.
Are they carrying any
additional supplies?
Hiding it from Chancellor
Bartlow wasn't very easy,
but we managed.
Thank you, Shiller.
This is the only way to get
to Glaivend from Ladylake.
There is no other route
for them to follow.
To decrease our travel time,
we'll cut through
these mountains here.
[SOLDIER D]
I have a report, ma'am.
How is it going?
[SOLDIER D] We were able
to acquire 13 more horses.
Good.
I want to take every soldier.
Keep looking.
[SOLDIER D]
Yes, ma'am!
I wish there was another way.
We were just
starting to rebuild,
but I need to take a
sizable force with me.
We have no time to spare.
I want us ready to
march by morning.
Let's get back to work.
[ALISHA]
Master!
Yes, Alisha?
What is that?
Ah.
A spear given to me by a
citizen grateful for our aid.
It's quite a spectacular weapon,
don't you think?
It'll help me protect
you on the battlefield.
Thank you, Master.
We'll speak more soon, but
for now, I must keep working.
[MALTRAN]
Yes.
[MIKLEO]
Why are we here?
[EDNA]
A cemetery at dusk?
Searching for ghosts
or something?
Does the scary
cemetery frighten you?
I can hold your
hand if you want.
Tough talk from a little boy.
Let's see... Mikleo-boy.
Or maybe we could call
you "Mibo" for short.
How 'bout neither?
Mibo has a nice ring to it.
[MIKLEO]
Uh...
Please, Sorey,
tell us why you've
brought us to this place.
The hellion from before.
This is the grave of the
person he murdered.
[SOREY] I, Sorey the Shepard,
purify this sorrowful spirit,
that he may know rest.
[SOREY] It all started out
as a simple argument.
Then one of them
picked up a weapon
and the other tried
to defend himself.
In the end, the second man
emerged as the victor
and his attacker lay dead.
They both had their reasons
and neither one of them
set out this morning
hoping they would
end another's life.
But still...
That's strange. Where have
all the guards gone?
I don't have much time,
so can we make this quick?
[SOREY]
Sorrow doesn't discriminate.
It doesn't matter
who started it.
who's responsible.
When a loved one dies,
there is always grief.
[SOREY]
In time, grief becomes hatred,
which seeps into the land.
[LAILAH]
It's true.
You're beginning to understand
the root of malevolence.
[MASKED FIGURE] Not so much
as a hint of fear.
Impressive. You're no ordinary
princess, are you?
I only wish that I could
be an ordinary princess,
but I have seen far too much.
We are in an age of calamity.
Can we just skip past the tests?
[MASKED FIGURE]
You can't blame me, can you?
I like to know what
I'm up against.
Stop wasting time and fight.
There are things
that I need to do.
[MASKED FIGURE] And what
exactly are these "things"?
I have a war to stop.
[MASKED FIGURE]
And you think you can do that?
[ALISHA] If something needs
to be done, I do it.
[MASKED FIGURE]
Is that so?
Let's say your men are
toe-to-toe with the enemy,
you would want them to put away
their arms and stand down?
Those are the orders
you would give?
If necessary.
[MASKED FIGURE]
So it's true.
You want Hyland to fight
only on the defensive.
[ALISHA]
Yes.
[MASKED FIGURE]
You realize that people will die
as a result of your decision.
And that first death?
That's all it takes.
[MASKED FIGURE]
I won't allow you to sacrifice
the people of Hyland
for your ideals.
So that's the reason
you're after me, is it?
[MASKED FIGURE] The Scattered
Bones have a purpose.
One death is all it
takes to breed hatred.
So we will do what
we must to stop it.
[ALISHA] All right, but what
if I promise you this?
I will die first!
[MASKED FIGURE] You aren't
bluffing. You really mean that.
Yes, I do.
Stop there.
You assaulted a
princess of the realm.
Do you truly expect
to walk away?
There will be consequences.
[MASKED FIGURE] Oh? Do you plan
to capture us all and hang us?
You will follow me
into the battlefield,
and there, witness my
actions for yourself.
You'll see more clearly
without the mask!
My troops need supplies
and I have a feeling that you
can provide them for us.
If you're willing.
[MASKED FIGURE]
I knew you were brave,
but I admit you're more
intelligent than I had realized.
All right, Princess,
I accept your request on behalf
of the Sparrowfeathers.
[ALISHA]
One more thing.
If I die on the battlefield...
Yes. Then what?
...let there be no retaliation.
Everything must be forgiven,
and that also includes my death.
There shall be no revenge sought
in the name of Alisha Diphda.
I want you to make that known.
[ROSE]
Very well.
If you should die,
Alisha Diphda,
then I vow that I will make
your wishes known to all.
Good.
Now see to your people.
Prepare them.
We leave for Glaivend
Basin in the morning.
[LAILAH] You still intend
to go to the battlefield,
knowing you will have
to purify humans?
[SOREY]
That is why I must go.
I am the Shepherd.
For ten gald, I've got a lotion
that'll make your
skin silky-smooth!
Silky-smooth? I'll take it!
And a great freckle-removing
cream for only 100 gald!
Is that all? I'll take it!
Special weight-loss water,
only a thousand gald a bottle.
Weight-loss water? I'll take it!
Stop this, Your Highness.
You really shouldn't
be so trusting.
[ALISHA] But why not, Rose?
You're so trustworthy!
Ugh! I can't take this anymore!
One hundred gald for all of it!
Such a discount?
I can't possibly accept it.
I would feel bad.
Eh, it's okay!
I got it all for free.
Well, if you're sure.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
No...
Gah! I give! Just take
it already, will you?
A present for me?
So now it's suddenly okay?
Thank you, Rose.
Next time. "The War."
I have to say, you've got
some serious haggling skills.