[AIGUILLE] That one?
Let's put it over here.
[SOREY grunts]
[ROSE]
Good morning.
[SOREY]
Morning!
I've just gotta make
sure that these goods
get on their way,
then we'll have breakfast!
Sure.
[SOREY]
Your days start early, huh?
[ROSE]
Life of a merchant.
We have to be up
before the market opens.
Well, time to eat.
Don't know about you,
but I'm starving. Dig in!
[ROSE]
Did you sleep well?
Yeah.
Hey, Sorey, are those
Seraphim folks
still hanging around somewhere?
They're sitting on that bench,
but I can call them
over. Want me to?
No!
Hey, Rose, were you ever
able to get in touch
with that Glenn guy?
[ROSE]
No.
I'm starting to get
a little worried about him,
so I think I'll drop buy his
house today to check on things.
[SOREY]
Good idea.
[ROSE] Don't worry.
You're off the hook.
Uh...
I mean it.
You held up your end of
the bargain by coming here.
So we're even. You don't
owe me anymore.
Now, will you eat something?
It's quite a spread.
This is delicious!
Isn't it though?
That's why I insist on
the highest quality goods!
What's with her?
She clearly wants
nothing to do with us.
Because she didn't
want us over there?
Does it matter? It's not
like she could talk to us.
That's the problem.
We make her uneasy.
I'm guessing Rose
is the type of person
who doesn't like
what she can't see.
That describes most humans.
[laughs] Oh, look.
We have company.
[footsteps]
I hope you'll excuse
my behavior last night.
I was foolish. I came
here to apologize.
[ROSE]
This early in the morning?
[SERGEI]
Mm!
Well, thanks, but it's
really not a big deal.
Drinking does that to people.
You're not alone there.
But I'm the commander
of the Platinum Knights.
My actions should always
be beyond reproach.
You need to lighten up.
Oh, are those for me?
Did you come here to
confess your undying love?
U-Uh, of course not.
I heard women like flowers,
so I brought them
as a peace offering.
Aw, are you sure?
It's not a gift
to prove your love?
No! It's just a bouquet.
Calm down. I know.
You're just so fun
to tease, that's all.
Perhaps flowers
were not appropriate.
I brought something else, but I
don't know if it's any better.
[ROSE laughs] Thanks.
This, I like. It's perfect.
Have you had breakfast yet?
[SERGEI]
Uh, no, I haven't.
You can join us
if you want. Come on.
[SERGEI] Interesting,
you're travelling the world
with these "Seraphim,"
and our country
was your first destination?
[SOREY]
Mm-hm.
I know that Rolance has
a lot of dragon-related lore.
Seemed a good place to start.
All these things you speak of.
The Seraphim and the
hellions, malevolence...
It's hard to believe.
[SOREY] So, where are the rest
of the Platinum Knights?
[SERGEI] My men are responding
to an incident in town.
There was a death
last night, a Bishop.
[SOREY]
A bishop?
That sounds important.
Shouldn't you be there?
Someone must keep
an eye on the Shepherd,
so that's what I'm doing.
[SOREY]
Oh. Um...
No, not like that.
Of course, now I understand
that you didn't come
intending to bring
the war to Rolance.
Truly, I do.
I only wish to extend to you
the curtesies of our nation.
[SOREY]
All right, then.
[horse whinnies]
[SOLDIER 15A]
Sir Sergei!
[SERGEI]
What news?
An explosion near the cathedral.
[gasps] Explosion?
[SOLDIER 15A] We don't know
what caused it yet,
but the ground has collapsed
and water is coming out.
Right.
[MIKLEO]
Sorey.
[SOREY]
Sergei.
[SERGEI]
Hm?
It's possible malevolence
is the cause.
Malevolence.
Then I'll have to ask
you to accompany me.
Of course
I'm sorry, sir.
There's one more thing.
Tell me.
[SOLDIER 15A]
It's about the bishop's death.
Do we know what
illness killed him?
[SOLDIER 15A] No, and this
is still speculation, but...
Understood. Now, tell me.
[SOLDIER 15A] Last night,
it appears that somebody
may have attacked the cathedral.
According to the rumors,
the Blue Storm Knights
who were on guard duty
engaged in combat.
The outcome?
[SOLDIER 15A]
None of the knights were killed,
but five of them were
quite badly injured.
The only death was the bishop's.
Under mysterious circumstances.
As I said, we don't
know for certain, but...
Assassination?
[SOLDIER 15A]
It seems a likely explanation.
We'll have to investigate
further to be sure.
[SOLDIER 15B]
Good to see you, sir.
Your report?
[SOLDIER 15B] The water
has mostly settled down.
Do you feel it?
[SOREY] No doubt about it.
Malevolence, for sure.
[MIKLEO]
Yeah.
[SERGEI] Sheperd Sorey.
Anything to share?
To find out the cause,
I'll need a closer look.
I'm coming, too.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm Rose of the Sparrowfeathers.
May I come in?
Preparations for cremation
are progressing?
[SOLDIER 15C]
Yes, sir.
[GROODMAN]
Make them hurry.
There are certain
things that we don't
want the public to know about.
Lailah, can you
give us some light?
Of course.
[yelps] What is that?
It's the power of
the seraph of fire.
You wanna stay inside, Lailah?
Sure.
I think I'll come, too.
[SOREY]
Mikleo, you ready?
We're gonna head
further in. Follow me.
Uh. Sure. Right behind you.
[SOREY] The malevolence
isn't too bad yet.
Hey, Sorey, does it feel
like we're always underground?
Heh, I guess that's
part of being a Shepherd.
So basically you're
saying it's your fault.
[SOREY] I don't think
I would put it that way.
[MIKLEO]
Really? I would.
[SOREY laughs]
Well, that's just rude.
[GLENN'S WIFE] You came
all this way for nothing.
I'm sorry about that.
Don't be.
It's our fault for
dropping in unannounced.
My husband talks
about you a lot,
so it's nice to
finally meet you.
He says that you're a
very promising young lady.
Oh, really? How sweet.
Anyway, ma'am.
Would you mind me asking how
long Glenn has been gone?
Oh, no, please don't
call me "ma'am."
It makes me feel
about 20 years older.
But to answer your question,
he left three days ago
to make a delivery
to the cathedral.
The cathedral.
He was looking forward
to the delivery
because he'd made
an amazing shelf.
Glenn doesn't show excitement
like that very often.
[ROSE] Well, he is really
good at what he does.
So, after he didn't come back,
did you visit the
cathedral yourself?
Yes.
I did, but he'd
already gone home.
That's what the knights
there told me, anyway.
I-I'm worried because
I haven't heard
anything from him. I don't
know what I'm going to do.
The tea is getting cold.
I'll just brew us a fresh pot.
The malevolence gets stronger
the further we go.
Yeah. They're starting
to get noisy.
There are soon-to-be hellions
all over the place down here.
There's something
moving in the water!
Don't touch it, Sergei!
The creatures here
have already turned.
What do you think?
Yeah.
Let's go ahead and
perform the ritual here.
Stand back, okay?
We'll purify this area.
It won't take long.
Very well.
[SOREY]
Let's begin.
[MIKLEO]
Water, our mother, bring forth
the power of purification.
Purify.
Now.
[SOREY pants]
I'd say that's a job well done.
[SERGEI] So that's the
ritual of purification.
They're all gone.
The water creatures
and the insects.
Whatever you did
got rid of them.
[SOREY]
They're not gone, actually.
We didn't kill them, just
calmed them down a little bit.
I'm starting to
believe more and more
of what you've told me,
and if it is true,
then Lastonbell's tainted
with malevolence.
I wish I could give
you better news.
What's more,
I feel a strong malevolence
coming from up ahead.
[SERGEI]
The power of the Shepherd.
I wonder what else he can do.
Will he be the one
to save the world?
Will he bring an end
to this era of chaos?
Sorey, is there really
a seraph here with us?
Yes. Mikleo.
He's a seraph of the water
and my oldest friend.
Hello, Sergei.
[SOREY] I know you can't
hear it, but he says hello.
[SERGEI] Oh, I am pleased
to make your acquaintance,
master seraph.
Sorry, I guess I'm still
finding this all a bit strange.
[SOREY]
Don't worry about it.
[SERGEI] Thank you.
It's a lot to take in.
Hey, tell me something.
Is there some sort of
large building nearby,
like a cathedral or a castle?
[SERGEI]
There is.
If I'm remembering correctly,
this waterway should lead
straight to the cathedral.
Sounds a little too
much like Ladylake.
What do you mean by that?
It's sort of the equivalent of
sweeping things under the rug.
Things are hidden,
emotions buried underground.
So, the malevolence piles up.
[gasps]
[SERGEI]
It's gotten bigger.
We should go. Come on.
[SERGEI]
Right.
[gasps] Looks like a dead end.
This shouldn't be here.
[BLUE STORM KNIGHT 15A]
Halt!
This area is
strictly off-limits.
[BLUE STORM KNIGHT 15B]
Where's that fire coming from?
What do you mean
by "off-limits"?
Who's in command?
That's Sir Sergei,
of the Platinum Knights.
[SERGEI]
Are you Knights of Blue Storm?
[BLUE STORM KNIGHT 15A]
We are, sir!
[SERGEI] I need to get
through here. Open the gate.
[BLUE STORM KNIGHT 15A]
We can't do that.
You're going to refuse
knowing who I am?
Perhaps you should reconsider.
[BLUE STORM KNIGHT 15A]
You have my apologies,
but it's out of our hands.
Our leader has given explicit
orders to let no one pass.
What's Groodman up to?
Understood. I don't fault
you for doing your duty.
I won't ask again.
Shall we?
Yeah.
[SERGEI] I'm not sure how you
knew it, but you were right.
It seems there's something
under the cathedral
that someone wants
to keep hidden.
[AIGUILLE]
Rose. Rose!
You can't go running
off like this!
[AIGUILLE]
Stop!
What good do you
think this will do?
The whole area
around the cathedral
will be swarming with knights.
We need to stay away
from there right now.
I know that!
Don't lie to yourself.
You've realized by now
that Glenn is dead.
Murdered by the bishop
and his gang of thugs.
That kind of violence
was the reason
we took him out, remember?
How many lives do you think
we saved by killing him?
It's okay, Rose.
We did the right thing.
Did we?
[SERGEI]
As much as I hate to admit it,
Rolance is far from perfect.
We have our share of problems.
Officially, we are
an absolute monarchy
ruled by the imperial family.
But the church has become an
increasingly dominant force
in our political system.
The men back there,
they're Blue Storm Knights,
an arm of the church
that has gained
significant influence recently.
As you know, I lead
the Platinum Knights.
We report directly
to the imperial family.
Things are strained
between the knighthoods.
We no longer seem
to be working toward
the same goal, that became
more apparent at Glaivend Basin.
[SOREY] So it isn't just the
malevolence that's similar.
The political situation here
is a lot like Ladylake's.
Still, one thing worries me.
So far, no dragon has
appeared in Rolance.
Yeah, that's true.
But, it doesn't seem
that the malevolence
here in Rolance is
less than in Hyland.
There's something else
different. What is it?
Hey, Sergei.
How have things been in Rolance?
Anything weird like
natural disasters lately?
Natural disasters?
Not exactly--nothing
like the tornadoes
and floods I've heard about.
Although, in Pendrago, there's
been a near ceaseless rain.
It'll stop for a short time but
then start again right away.
[BOTH]
That's it.
Really? You think
that could be related?
[gasps]
Who are you?
[GROODMAN] Well, if it
isn't the esteemed leader
of the Platinum Knights.
I'm very curious to know what
you're doing here, Sir Sergei.
Care to enlighten me?
Hello, Groodman.
[AIGUILLE]
What are you saying?
This isn't like you.
I thought you swore, Rose,
to protect the people,
no matter your own sacrifice.
You said you could silence
your emotions to do this.
Stop, will you?
I know what I said.
Then what's gotten into you?
[DEZEL]
Need my help? Just say so.
[gasps]
If you seriously wanna
do this, then tell me.
Ask for my help.
I'll handle it for you.
You again.
Who are you talking to?
They deserve punishment.
People like them are disgusting.
They're nothing but frauds.
Trading on religion to
steal from the innocent.
They should be taught
a lesson, don't you think?
[ROSE] If I hadn't met Sorey,
I would never have believed it.
I always thought I had an
over-developed sixth sense,
but this is crazy.
He was right.
To think that the
Seraphim actually exist.
What's going on?
Rose, is something the matter?
[DEZEL] Like he said, what
you've been doing is right.
Whether you know it or not.
So, I'll help if you need it.
Maybe. Tell me who you are.
I'm Dezel.
[ROSE]
I'm Rose.
I know.
See ya.
Hey! Come back here!
That's odd.
Where are you going?
[GROODMAN]
Are you the Shepherd?
I guess appearances
can be deceiving.
Who's this guy?
He is the leader of
the Blue Storm Knights,
Sir Groodman.
I remember you mentioned
his name earlier.
Now, tell me.
What business do you have
beneath the cathedral?
Nothing that could
possibly concern you.
You realize I'm not going
to let you walk away.
[explosion, rumbling]
[SOREY]
Is that...
It's Rose!
[EDNA] If we're going
after her, we should hurry.
Are we?
Let's go.
[DEZEL grunts]
Okay, purification complete!
Purifying all that
malevolence is no easy task.
[LAILAH] Good work,
you two. I'm impressed!
This country's choc full
of sacred relics.
I'm surprised you haven't
gone spelunking yet.
We thought we'd
save the fun stuff
until the malevolence
was purified.
It must be rough,
having such a tedious hobby.
What do you like to
do for fun, Edna?
It's not really a hobby,
but I like combining words.
Like Mibo.
Any other?
Eaprin.
What's that?
The title of the next episode.
That doesn't make any sense.
And there's another thing
I don't get. Why "Mibo"?
Is that really just
short for "Mikleo Boy"?
Because that seems
a little ridiculous.
I don't know why you're
always so mean to me.
Edna, I'm really sorry.
I accept apologies
in the form of snacks.
and you'd better make
sure they're tasty.
[MIKLEO growls]
Okay, fine. You win.
Next week: "Each One's
Principles," or, if you prefer,
"Eaprin" for short.
"Mikleo is a gullible
dumbo." "Mibo" for short.
Ha, ha, she made a joke!