[KONAN gasping]
[yells]
Die!
[panting, grunting]
[grunting]
[SOREY]
Something's off.
He's become a hellion!
[yelling]
[grunts]
[SOREY]
Rose!
You need to get away from him!
[yells]
This is the end for you.
Whatever it costs,
you die tonight.
Rose, please!
You okay?
Where is he?
Gone. Probably dead.
[ROSE]
Then where's his body?
[SOREY]
In the lake somewhere.
[ROSE]
I have to go.
[SOREY] Rose, what are
you talking about?
I need to find him.
There's no way he survived that.
I need to see for myself.
[LAILAH]
Rose, you don't understand.
Becoming a hellion doesn't
make a somebody immortal.
The body can still die.
There is a numbness
that takes hold of them,
so they may not feel pain
the way other people do,
but their bodies
can still be wounded.
And I assure you,
his wounds were fatal.
[ROSE]
After all this time...
I was so close to
finally getting closure.
That's all this is? Closure?
Somebody like you
shouldn't be an assassin.
I don't like it.
You don't like it?
What's it to you?
If you don't like what
I am, leave me alone.
I can't leave you alone
after all that's happened.
[ROSE]
What do you want from me?
A promise I'll change
my evil ways?
What would be the point of that?
Do you know how many lives
I've already taken?
It's no small number.
I'm sure it's not.
Do you do this because you think
it's right to take a life?
[ROSE]
What?
Answer me, Rose.
[ROSE] Whether it's right
or not, somebody has to do it.
The world isn't a nice place.
It's full of people
who need killing.
That may be ugly, but it's true.
[pants]
I'm sorry, I should've noticed.
Let me find something
to keep you warm.
[pants]
[SOREY]
Here, take this.
You don't wanna catch cold.
All the disasters
across the world,
the chaos we face.
It's because humans have
turned their backs on Seraphim,
losing faith and
embracing violence.
At least, that's
what Gramps told me.
[ROSE]
Hmph. Yeah, sure, whatever.
I didn't believe him when
he first said it, either.
How could something like
this never-ending rain
be caused by what people feel?
It was unimaginable.
But I believe it now.
[SOREY]
Hard as it is to accept,
just because you
can't see something
doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
Surely you realize that?
You can't see Dezel's face,
but you can hear his voice.
Malevolence can seep into
anything, infecting it.
The earth, the water, the sky,
all forms of life. Us, too.
People and Seraphim
are no exception.
Like in Marlind,
the Seraph that was supposed
to protect the city
became the drake that
nearly destroyed it.
Well, I must be a giant
mess of malevolence then.
But you aren't, though.
I don't need you to comfort me.
I'm not just saying that.
You are far from
a hellion, Rose.
[SOREY] The thing is,
there's malevolence in everyone.
The amount may vary,
but all of us carry it.
Good and bad alike.
It took a while, but I can
finally see the truth.
So, enlighten me.
Our negative emotions,
like jealousy and hate--
they're dangerous, and they
can create malevolence.
But we can't
deny their existence.
That would be
denying our humanity.
Most people,
they live their lives
trying to hide
their inner darkness.
But you're different because
you face your darkness head-on.
You believe all you're
doing helps people.
So you fight.
It's all you can do.
It's never easy.
Where are we?
I lost track hours ago.
[LAILAH] The storm makes
everything out here
look the same. All one,
big, dreary landscape.
[EDNA]
And the weather is depressing.
The rain seems to be
getting stronger
the farther we travel.
I guess that means we're
getting closer to Pendrago?
Yeah, we're not far away.
Won't be much longer.
How do you know that?
[DEZEL]
Hmph.
Talk to us, Dezel.
Who is Rose to you?
What is it that you
actually want from her?
I can see it.
How she's completely
opened up to you
and become your vessel.
So, you have possessed her body.
I get the feeling she has
no idea about that, does she?
Which is just wrong.
[DEZEL] Have you ever
wanted something so badly
that you were willing
to sacrifice anything?
When you hunger for
something that desperately,
nothing can stand in your way.
I did what I needed to do,
and I'm not sorry for it.
So I sure hope
you weren't planning
to wait around for an apology.
An apology?
Tell me, how long have
you been using Rose's body
without her knowledge?
And how much of who she's
become is the result
of what you've done to her?
I've gotten my revenge.
Now I'll pick up
where Brad left off,
making the world a safer
place for the weak.
That's why I'm here.
Why Rose is here.
[gasps]
[DEZEL] Brad was the man
I vowed to follow and Rose
is his adopted daughter
and successor.
Her goals are mine,
and mine are hers.
You asked me what
I want with Rose.
What I want is to see
Brad's dreams realized.
Whatever it takes.
She's nothing to you?
Just a tool?
We're stopping? What's going on?
[PLATINUM KNIGHT 18A]
A moment please.
Is the Shepherd
traveling with you?
Why would you want to know that?
[SOREY] Is there something
I can help you with?
[PLATINUM KNIGHT 18A]
Are you the Shepherd?
[SOREY]
Mm-hm.
[PLATINUM KNIGHT 18A]
Please excuse me.
We're men of the
Platinum Knights.
Sir Sergei commanded
us to locate you
and provide you with an escort.
The Blue Storm Knights
have established
a checkpoint up ahead.
We can help you evade it.
Why should we trust you?
It's not as if you've
given us any reason to.
I assure you, we don't
intend you any harm.
Sir Sergei believes that
the battle at Glaivend Basin
was a terrible mistake.
He is thankful to the Shepherd
for putting a stop
to the fighting.
As his soldiers,
we share that gratitude.
[SOREY]
It's all right, Rose.
If you say so.
[PLATINUM KNIGHT 18A]
The Blue Storm Knights
are watching all of
the roads into Pendrago,
so we'll have to take
a different route.
Unfortunately, our only option
is to cut through the forest.
You're welcome to our
horses if you need them.
We'll look after your wagon
and see that it's
returned to you later.
All right, then. Thanks.
You, okay?
[ROSE]
Leave me alone.
[gasps]
[ROSE]
What's wrong?
[MIKLEO] The whole forest
is saturated with malevolence.
[LAILAH] The tainted rain
falls and the malevolence
seeps into the earth,
poisons the forest.
We have to do something.
[EDNA] If it spreads,
all of Rolance will be doomed.
[LAILAH] Just purifying
this area won't be enough.
[MIKLEO] She's right.
We should push forward.
Let's go.
[ROSE]
What's out there?
Dezel, what do you see?
[DEZEL] Malevolence.
Hellions by the thousands.
Pouring down with the rain,
oozing out of the earth,
swirling through the air.
[gasps]
[DEZEL]
That was malevolence.
To humans it feels
like an icy wind,
but it's something
a great deal darker.
There's so much
I can't perceive.
[ROSE] Like a whole other
world that's invisible.
Let's hurry.
We ride straight on through.
[ROSE] Sorey, do you
know what scares me?
The idea that
everything I've done
has been nothing more
than a waste of time.
I've spent my life
fighting for justice.
Or what I thought was justice.
The weak deserve
a place in this world,
even if it's only a small one.
So I kill the people who
would deny them that,
but is it working?
Sometimes I don't know.
Sometimes what I do
feels meaningless,
hollow, and empty.
[SOREY] I can't tell you
whether or not there's meaning
in the way you live your life.
But, Rose, there is one
thing I can tell you.
Killing is wrong,
no matter what the reason.
[SOREY] Still, regardless
of what you've done,
I don't hate you for it.
We really need to hurry.
The malevolence is
only getting worse.
I was wrong.
I thought I was
strong and righteous.
The truth is, I'm completely
powerless, aren't I?
You are a strong person, Rose.
Nobody can deny you that.
But the world is in chaos.
It needs less darkness
in it, not more,
and that requires a
different kind of power.
[gasps]
[ROSE]
I'm helpless.
I can't do anything
to heal this world.
So, there's my answer.
It was all a waste.
[screams]
[screaming]
I'll just take this, you won't
be needing it anymore.
Huh?
[gasps]
[SCAVENGER 18A]
Well, hello, there.
Aren't you pretty?
You look a little lost.
Why don't you come with me?
[yelps] Hey! Let go!
Leave me alone!
Please! Lemme go! Lemme go!
Let her go.
[SCAVENGER 18A]
Huh?
[SCAVENGER 18A groans]
[SCAVENGER 18A]
Dammit! Who the hell are you?
[BRAD]
The misery in this world
can take a lot from a person.
But don't let it
take your intellect.
Because that is
what truly separates
men from animals.
You know what. Let's get going.
I recognize these guys.
It's the Windriders!
[SCAVENGER 18A]
Wha...? Seriously?
[SCAVENGERS yelping]
You coming?
Yes.
Hey, Brad.
When I grow up, I wanna
be just like you.
You do, huh?
Are you sure about that?
[ROSE]
Yep.
I wanna help people and
make them happy, like you do.
That's not a bad goal.
But ya gotta remember this:
first and foremost,
we are friends of the weak.
You can't help them if
you're all talk and no action.
We have to start
somewhere and that means
putting immediate justice
over unreachable ideals.
Sure!
[SOREY grunts]
It sounds like dinner
for tonight is mabo curry.
How do you know that?
The evening wind whispers
its secrets to me.
That's totally awesome!
Maybe he just smelled it
like the rest of us.
That makes sense.
Don't listen to her.
It's not the smell.
It's the whisper of the wind.
The wind knows more
than you realize.
Like the fact that dessert
tonight is strawberry shortcake.
[LAILAH]
Hey, everybody.
I hope you're hungry!
Dinner's all ready.
Grab a plate.
It's mabo curry time.
Hey, Mibo, what's for dessert?
Some strawberry shortcake.
For real, he totally called it!
That's odd, Rose isn't here.
Huh? I thought she was
over with you guys.
She probably wants
to be alone right now.
Give her space
until she's ready.
Wow, that's very insightful.
The wind has more to talk about
than just the dinner menu.
Clearly.
It's whispering the title
of the next episode.
"Negotiation." Got it? Good.
So, what's it say about
breakfast tomorrow?
[DEZEL]
Who knows.
Tomorrow will bring
its own winds.
[BOTH]
Whoa. That's so profound.