[SOREY]
So how do you feel?
Do you think this
is going to work?
Well having been tainted before,
I am nervous, but I will try.
I promise I'll do my best
to protect Marlind.
If this young pup of a Shepherd
is trying to save the whole
world, it's the least I can do.
Think of it this way,
because you have
felt malevolence,
you know your own limits and
can guard against peril.
Or maybe you'll just make the
same mistakes all over again.
Hey.
And besides, with
a Normin on my side,
I can't possibly fail.
[ATAKK sighs]
Golly! It sounds like you're
really counting on me.
Guess I'll have to stay.
[EDNA] What happens
once can happen again.
Calamity is never very far away.
[MIKLEO]
Seriously? You're not helping!
[EDNA]
Just keeping him on his toes.
[horse whinies]
If you're ready, Sorey,
let's go.
[ALISHA] We're heading
for Glaivend Basin,
which is on the border
between Hyland and Rolance.
The army that Chancellor
Bartlow mobilized
must be using that area as
their base of operations
for the coming
invasion of Rolance.
It's possible they have mustered
as many as 21,000 soldiers,
and we can't expect Rolance's
army to be sitting idly by.
We must use the 1,200 men
we brought from Marlind
to come between them
and stop this war.
[MALTRAN] Let's not forget
that this is Bartlow
we're talking about.
He won't have sent
the whole army.
He'll be using at least
some of the troops
to guard the road to Ladylake.
You're probably right.
So there will be fewer
Hyland soldiers.
Let's assume it'll
be around 18,000.
Bartlow doesn't skimp when
it comes to protecting
his own hide, but even so,
you're still going to be
outnumbered 15-to-1.
I understand that, Master.
So it's a good thing that
I'm not riding to war.
Always the optimist, aren't you?
Believe what you will,
but the fact remains,
we may be fighting our
own before this is done.
No, they will understand.
I have faith in my people.
[IAN]
Your Highness!
Hello, Ian.
Hi. It's good to
see you, Highness.
Doing well?
Yeah, thanks.
How about you?
You look more like a girl than
the last time I saw you.
That was ten days ago.
[chuckle]
Be careful, Ian.
If your chest gets any bigger,
you won't be able to
fit in your armor.
You know,
I think I can actually feel it
getting tighter right now!
I was just joking.
Sure you were.
How long have you two
been friends, again?
Forever. We're like sisters.
We actually fell for
the same boy once.
His name was Robert,
and he was the second son of
the lord of a nearby town.
He had a very handsome face.
He was so sweet and thoughtful.
Ian.
Yes?
I don't know if now is really
the best time for this story.
Of course! I'm sorry!
I'm so glad recent events
haven't changed you,
Your Highness.
You're just as I remember:
As beautiful as a flower
and as noble as a stallion!
[ALISHA laughs]
I'm glad to see that you haven't
changed at all either, Ian!
Thank you, Highness.
By the way, I killed a
prickleboar on the way here.
It should make a nice
change from road rations.
Prickleboar? That's impressive.
You took it down in
one shot, I'm sure.
Of course I did!
Is that who I think it is?
The Shepherd.
[IAN]
Lord Shepherd!
It's a real honor.
Uh, is something wrong?
No, you just look different
than I expected from the rumors.
Rumors?
[IAN] They're saying
you slew the dragon
that appeared in Ladylake
with a single blow,
then roasted it and ate
it whole, bones and all!
[SOREY]
Uh.
[chuckles nervously]
I didn't know you were
a dragon-eater, Sorey.
Anyway, I was expecting you
to look a little on
the rougher side.
Lord Shepherd, if you don't
mind, can I touch your hand?
Okay, I guess.
Ahh!
I've been blessed!
I can feel the good fortune
coursing through me!
Lord Shepherd, I vow I will
never wash this hand!
My, she is an energetic one.
Why does that rider believe
that the Shepherd is some
kind of good luck charm?
[chuckles nervously]
[ALISHA] I'm glad that
you've returned safely, Ian.
Will you give us your
report now, please?
Yes.
As requested, I scouted
the force leaving Hyland
to determine their number.
And?
The chancellor is a coward.
He'd never risk leaving
himself unprotected.
I knew he wouldn't.
He sent 20,000.
What's wrong, Your Highness?
[ALISHA]
I was expecting 18,000.
If Bartlow is leaving only
a skeleton force behind,
I may have underestimated
his commitment to this war.
[AIGUILLE] Leader,
are you certain about this?
Should the Scattered Bones
truly be getting involved
in this conflict?
I made a promise.
I can't go back on my word.
Nothing to do now
but see it through.
Besides, this princess
has piqued my curiosity.
What's so fascinating about her?
Well, she wants to
prevent this war
and she's willing to
risk her life to do it.
Now I understand.
A noble sentiment, yes,
but a rather reckless
one, as well.
Sounds like a fool to me.
[ROSE]
She may well be one.
[LANDON] This mist offers
us the perfect chance
to conceal our troops.
A clear sign that the heavens
themselves want us to prevail.
Bartlow will be greatly pleased
with our victory.
When the second wave
of troops arrives,
we will launch a surprise
assault on Rolance.
If we strike quickly enough,
the fools won't even
see us coming.
[SOREY]
Alisha.
Where you off to?
Just getting some water.
[SOREY]
Ha. In the middle of the night?
I couldn't fall asleep.
Me either.
We're not far from
Glaivend Basin now.
Pretty soon I'll get my first
look at a battlefield.
Yes.
[SOREY] People killing each
other right out in the open...
I have a hard time imagining it.
I know what you mean.
I have seen battles before,
but they were much smaller.
Nothing anywhere
close to this scale.
I hope we get there in time.
If we arrive before
the war begins,
I'll do my best to help
you prevent it.
But, well, if it's
already started...
I'm sorry for putting
you in this position.
You're so kind.
Always looking out for me.
I'm always happy to help you.
Still, I have to remain neutral.
If there is war, I can't
side with Hyland.
Of course, I can't side
with Rolance, either.
As the Shepherd,
you can't choose sides.
I respect your role.
If the war hasn't started,
I'll prevent it somehow.
And if it has begun, I'll
find a way of stopping it.
That's my duty. I just wanted
you to know before we arrived.
Thank you.
I understand completely.
[MIKLEO]
Hey, Sorey.
[SOREY]
Hm?
[MIKLEO]
I was thinking.
We're about to get involved
in a war somewhere
we didn't know existed
a few months ago.
[SOREY] You mean, we're about
to go and stop a war.
[MIKLEO]
Of course. That's what I meant.
Stopping the war.
My point is, this
feels so unreal.
It wasn't long ago that we were
exploring ruins in Elysium.
[SOREY]
I'm surprised.
I mean, you're not
usually so sentimental.
[MIKLEO] After everything
that's happened,
don't you feel sentimental, too?
[SOREY]
Kinda.
[MIKLEO]
I thought so.
How do you think
Gramps is doing?
Gramps is always doing fine.
You're right. Stupid question.
[BOTH chuckle]
[MIKLEO]
You know what?
Once we've stopped the
war and this is all over...
...let's find some
ruins to explore.
[SOREY]
That sounds perfect!
Even the Shepherd deserves
a break sometimes, right?
Yeah, absolutely!
It's a promise.
Promise.
[LAILAH] I'm worried
about what's to come.
Sorey is about to be tested,
and it will not be easy.
But as the Shepherd, it's
a challenge he must face.
[EDNA]
Are you sure about this?
I thought you said it
was too soon for him.
[LAILAH] I was hoping he
would be more experienced.
Actually, I was hoping we
might avoid war altogether,
but that seems impossible now.
[EDNA] The humans go out of
their way to start these things.
I don't understand it.
I mean, really,
how stupid are they?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MESSENGER A]
General Landon!
Rolance has attacked
from our rear!
It's an ambush!
What should we do?
[LANDON]
An attack from behind?
That's our territory!
[SERGEI] What were you thinking
crossing the border?
It's a violation of the treaty!
I don't see the
problem, Lord Sergei.
After all, what matters
most in war is who wins.
But victory ought to be
achieved with honor.
Instead, we will be the villains
when this tale is told.
No, I doubt that.
We just have to win.
Then we can sit back and let the
politicians work their magic.
At any rate,
the feint is working.
We should mobilize
our main forces.
Where you going? Come back.
[SERGEI]
My men will not fight.
We didn't make it here in time.
I can feel the malevolence
all the way out here.
It will do no good
if we try to ride
between the armies
at this point.
All we'll do is get
ourselves killed.
What now, Alisha?
I'll have to speak
to General Landon,
ask him to stand down.
What if he doesn't
listen to you?
I'll give him no choice.
Sorey.
I'll leave you to it. Good luck.
[SOREY]
I'll do the best I can, Alisha.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[LIEUTENANT A]
Push through!
[MIKLEO]
This malevolence!
The hatred, the anger, the pain,
many hellions are born
in the carnage of war.
Let's end this. Come on.
Look out!
What are Rolance troops
doing across the border?
Alisha, you go around the side.
Yeah, we'll hold them here.
[ALISHA]
I can't leave.
Yes, you can.
Peace was your dream.
Now go make it a reality.
Right!
Rose, are you coming with me?
What did I tell you?
Yes, I'm in.
[ALISHA] I am Alisha Diphda.
Let me through!
General Landon!
I demand to speak
with General Landon.
[SOLDIER E] We're in the middle
of a battle! Can't this wait?
[LANDON]
Princess Alisha, here?
Don't be stupid.
What would a little girl like
her be doing on the front lines?
Looking for you, General.
[LANDON] Oh, Princess Alisha!
Hello. Welcome to our camp.
To what do we owe this honor?
[ALISHA] You will send an envoy
to the Rolance camp immediately
and petition for a truce.
That is a direct order.
[LANDON]
An order? Is that so?
Regrettably, I cannot obey.
What?
Seize the princess.
[ALISHA] You have no
right to detain me!
[LANDON]
Matter of fact, I do.
Lord Bartlow has given
me full authority
in matters regarding this war.
If she doesn't come willingly,
feel free to use force,
but try not to
injure her too badly.
Well, Highness. What's the plan?
[MIKLEO]
Sorey!
[LAILAH]
Are you all right?
All this malevolence.
This hate. Stop this.
[MIKLEO]Can you keep going?
Yeah!
Forgive me.
[LANDON]
What are you fools waiting for?
Don't just stand there,
capture her!
[ROSE]
You are her soldiers.
Would you assault
your own princess?
[LANDON] This has nothing to
do with you. Go now or die.
[SOREY, LAILAH]
Ready, Calamity Flare!
[SOLDIER E] We have friendlies
in the area of effect!
[LEADER A]
I don't care. Fire!
I can't believe all
of you together
can't take down two girls!
It's time for lethal force.
These guys are serious.
[ALISHA]
No, Rose!
[ROSE]
Why not?
I get that they're
your soldiers,
but your life is in danger.
This is a matter of
self-defense now.
If we don't kill them,
they'll kill us.
No, we can't do it.
We just can't.
Take them down!
[ROSE] This has gone too far.
It's time to fight for real.
What? No!
Move!
We cannot destroy ourselves!
I won't let it happen.
You're a stubborn
little fool, Princess.
--[thud]
--[ALISHA gasps]
[ROSE]
Alisha!
[SOREY]
Almost finished.
Let's go, Mikleo! Luzrov Rulay!
[SOREY, MIKLEO]
Arrow Squall!
[MIKLEO]
Sorey! We did it! We did it!
We purified them all!
It's over now.
Can you believe it?
We stopped the war!
[SOREY]
It can't be.
[MIKLEO]
Hey, wait!
[yelling]
No.
Good work, soldier!
[ROSE]
How could you?
Do you understand
what you've done?
I'll be okay.
It's not that bad.
Save your breath.
Soldier. You should
clean that blade.
You don't want it to rust.
[SOLDIER U screams]
[ROSE]
You bastards.
She's your princess, and
you're going to kill her?
[yells]
[ROSE]
Again?
What's happening to me?
I don't understand!
I've felt this before.
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
Seraphim!
What is that?
This place is toxic.
Worse than any
we've seen before.
And that malevolence.
There's something
different about it.
Is it possible?
[SOREY]
That's... a human hellion.
[MIKLEO]
There's no way.
[SOREY] Except, I can't
see the human form.
What does that mean?
[SOREY] So that's him:
The Lord of Calamity.
You know, Luzrov Rulay is
very difficult to pronounce.
Why don't you shorten
it to Zroe, instead?
Not happening.
Honestly, I almost bite
my tongue when I say it.
Sorey!
Imagine real quick we're in
the middle of an epic battle.
"Mikleo, let's armatize!
Luzrov Rure-- Ow!
I bit my tongue!"
Do you realize how completely
ridiculous I'd look?
Or maybe you could try adding
some syllables in, Rulalalay!
I totally love it!
What do you say, Mikleo?
No chance!
I know, how 'bout Shiv?
Shiv and Zroe? Those aren't even
anything like the original.
They're new names.
That's our time. Bye now!
See you all later!
Stop shortening things already!
Next time. "Lord of Calamity."
Why are you alll only
picking on my name anyhow?
It's our way of showing
how much we love you.
Sorey.
Rulalalay!
I knew it, you are
making fun of me!
[ALL]
Rulalalay!
Cut it out!