This is all from
the tornado last year?
How awful.
[BOLTA] We found a small
village not too far from here.
Yes, Princess.
The accommodations
would be basic,
but I'm sure they can provide
us shelter for the night.
No.
That won't be necessary.
At least, not on my account.
We'll find somewhere to camp.
[ALISHA] This is as good a place
as any to spend the night.
[gasps]
Find something, Princess?
I have.
This is ancient artwork.
[BOLTA] Do you think it could
be from Asgardian times?
[ALISHA]
Mm. It's possible.
[GANETTE]
What is this?
[BOLTA]
A Shepherd!
That's what it looks like.
If Clemm were here to see this,
she would be
absolutely ecstatic.
She's obsessed with
this stuff, you know.
She believes every
word that's written
in The Celestial Record .
I showed her the book,
so I understand her fascination.
I share it.
So, Princess, do you
agree with her
that what's written
in the book is true?
Do you believe in the Shepherds?
[ALISHA] All I know for certain
is that if Shepherds
do exist, I would
like to meet one.
Very much.
[CLEMM]
Attention please!
Those who wish to attempt
the Rite of the Warrior
during the Sacred Blade
Festival should apply
inside the temple.
[TAO]
Clemm!
The princess is looking for you.
Go, and I'll take
over for you here.
Thank you. I'll go right away.
[TAO] The Rite of the
warrior is approaching!
Is there anybody here
who wishes to attempt it?
[CLEMM]
How may I be of service?
[MALTRAN]
I understand you have an uncle.
And he's a doctor in Griel,
is that correct?
[CLEMM]
Yes. it is indeed, Master.
So, I believe Clemm is
who we want for this task.
What task?
We've had a report.
It comes from Professor
Drake, the astronomer.
He has recently
observed the appearance
of what he describes as
a strange cloud or mist.
According to the professor,
it seems to be unaffected by
wind or rain but remains still,
stubbornly hanging in the sky
regardless of the weather.
[MALTRAN] The location
is where you come in.
The cloud was
sighted over Griel.
I see why you called me.
[ALISHA]
Hyland has seen many unusual
weather phenomena in
the past few years,
and crops have been seriously
damaged as a result.
I want to know if this has had
any lasting negative effects
on the people there.
[CLEMM]
Yes, ma'am! I'll see to it.
[ALISHA]
Good, thank you.
[CLEMM]
I'll head out at once.
Your Highness, before I go.
Thank you so much
of giving me this copy
of The Celestial Record .
I consider it my most
treasured possession.
I'm glad I shared it with you.
That's what it's for.
[laughs]
[ALISHA]
Absolutely not!
These young people
came here to celebrate
the Sacred Blade Festival,
and you want to conscript them?
That would be a flagrant
abuse of power, Lord Matthia!
Please consider
carefully, Highness.
We cannot know for
certain what will happen,
but the sickness in
the town of Marlind
could very well
become an epidemic.
If it does, military
intervention may be required.
Perhaps, but deploying the army
and reinforcing its ranks
are two separate discussions.
I'm afraid they are not.
Where will we find the manpower
to send a security force
if we don't begin
looking at once?
You, Your Highness
should be using
your power and influence
to recruit patriots
in the royal family's name.
That is the duty
of your position.
[ALISHA]
I see now.
That's why you agreed to hold
the Festival in the first place.
To boost recruitment numbers.
I say this in the name
of the royal family.
The Sacred Blade Festival
shall not be used to wage war!
[ALISHA] The mist does
seem to be thickening.
But what could it mean?
[DRAKE] I can't say for sure.
But I don't like it.
I feel there's something
sinister about the mist.
And that feeling
only intensifies
as the cloud keeps growing.
Forgive my dramatics,
but it feels like a sign
that something terrible
is about to happen.
[ALISHA] Someone must go
to Griel to find Clemm
and learn what
she has discovered.
I'd be happy to, Princess.
[ALISHA]
Ganette.
How long has it been now
since Clemm left for Griel?
[GANETTE] I believe it was
about two weeks ago.
That's far too long.
[TAO]
Princess.
Yes? What is it?
[gasps]
[TAO]
We've been ambushed!
Hah!
[LUNARRE gasps]
[grunts]
[LUNARRE growls]
[gasps]
Tell me what you're doing here!
[ROSE]
That's enough. Retreat.
[LUNARRE]
Leader. I can still fight.
[ROSE] You're no match
for her. You've lost.
[LUNARRE laughs]
I'm impressed, Princess.
You're quite skilled.
[ROSE gasps]
[LUNARRE cackles]
--[gasps]
--[LUNARRE laughs]
[ROSE]
Why didn't you finish him?
You could have, and easily.
Is that your idea of justice,
or are you just soft?
[ALISHA]
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
[MALTRAN] You're saying
you want to go to Griel?
[ALISHA]
I'm worried about Clemm.
If you somebody
needs to check on her,
then I should be the one to go.
As her teacher, that
duty is surely mine.
[ALISHA]
No, Master.
I need you to stay here
and see to the preparations
for the Sacred Blade Festival.
It must go on.
Nothing can stand in the way.
Why are you so fixated
on the festival, anyway?
Even if someone appears who
is able to pull the blade out,
what do you think will happen?
[ALISHA] "The one who draws
the sacred blade,
protected by the
Lady of the Lake,
shall become the Shepherd."
I know it's only a legend...
But a hopeful one.
And I want to keep hope alive in
this land for as long as I can.
Surely you understand that.
[BOLTA]
How much do you wanna bet
Clemm just got carried away
exploring the ruins?
What are you talking about?
I guess you don't
get out very much.
Don't tease him.
There is an ancient
underground aqueduct in Griel
much like the ruins in Ladylake.
[TAO]
I had no idea.
[BOLTA] Clemm likes
to talk on and on about
how she would go
exploring down there
when she was a child.
[TAO] Well, if that's
what's keeping her,
she deserves a good scolding.
[ALISHA] I'll give her one,
that's for sure.
Once she's safe.
[ALISHA]
Masks on.
[ALISHA] This reminds me of
something Clemm said before.
She compared the green grapes
that grow in this
region to jewels.
[TAO] Something tells me
that we can forget about
bringing a gift back
for Lady Maltran.
[TAO]
Princess Alisha!
[GIRL 1A]
Hey, you! No stealing!
[TAO]
I-I'm sorry.
I think we've given
you the wrong idea.
[ALISHA]
Please forgive us.
I assure you, we had no
intention of stealing from you.
You sound like an outsider.
Where are you from?
[BOLTA]
How dare you!
Don't you know to
whom you're speaking?
[ALISHA]
Easy, now. That's enough.
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
Can you tell me something?
How long has that strange,
dark mist been in the sky?
[OLD MAN 1A] It's only
recently that it's become
very noticeable, but it's been
there for quite some time now.
We don't know
where it came from.
One day it was just there.
[ALISHA]
It just appeared out of nowhere?
[GIRL 1A]
You can have some if you want.
Here.
[ALISHA]
Thank you.
[GIRL 1A giggles]
[ALISHA] I think we should visit
the local guard station first.
Clemm must have stopped there.
[SOLDIER 1A]
When she got here,
she took a look around
the city and then--
[SOLDIER 1A coughs]
[ALISHA]
Are you all right?
[SOLDIER 1A]
Please excuse me.
[SOLDIER 1A coughing]
She had said that she
intended to make her way
toward the forest in the north.
To the north...
So she was heading
in the direction of the mist.
[SOLDIER 1A]
Yes, Your Highness.
Can you tell me
what the mist is?
No, I'm sorry.
Truth be told, we don't even
know how it came to be there.
It suddenly appeared one day
and just kept growing.
[coughs]
Of course, we sent some of
our men to search the area,
but they didn't find anything
that was out of place.
Tell me something.
What do you think about
the state of this town?
Truthfully.
[ALISHA]
This place is so spiritless.
Tao.
I want you to stay here.
Someone should continue
to investigate the town.
[TAO]
Understood. And you, Princess?
[ALISHA] I will head north.
Towards the forest.
[DRAKE grunts]
What's this?
[ALISHA gasps]
The mist. It's moving!
[ALISHA]
There's Clemm!
Princess Alisha?
[GANETTE]
Behind you, Clemm!
[BOLTA]
Look out!
[CLEMM gasps, screams]
[CLEMM]
Your Highness!
[ALISHA]
We have to get away from here!
[CLEMM] But Professor Drake
is still below!
[ALISHA]
Below?
[CLEMM]
Something about discovering
the nature of the Earth pulse.
[ALISHA]
What was he thinking?
[BOLTA, GANETTE]
Princess!
[DRAKE grunts]
There's something big
going on up above.
[gasps]
[ALISHA] If this keeps
going, the whole town
will be swallowed.
What can we do?
[CLEMM]
The professor has a theory.
He says the world is
connected by the Earth pulse.
It's like a pathway
that circulate
the forces of nature throughout
the world, creating balance.
But that balance is being lost.
In the past,
mankind did not live alone.
We dwelt in the company...
[DRAKE]
...of other beings
who have now become
invisible to us.
We doomed ourselves
through our own arrogance.
We forgot that we were meant
to share this world,
and for that, we are
now paying the price.
That is what I believe,
though I don't know
the whole truth of it.
My hope is that, by
studying the Earth pulse,
I might better understand
this world's secrets.
[DRAKE yelps]
[BOLTA yelps]
[BOLTA screams]
[GANETTE]
Bolta!
[GANETTE yelps]
[GANETTE screams]
[ALISHA]
Ganette!
Gone. They're both gone.
Let me get down.
We can't keep riding
double like this,
or it's going to
catch up with us!
[ALISHA]
Stay where you are.
Please, Princess!
[ALISHA]
I said no! We stay together.
That's final!
Ride on. I will open
the gate of chaos with you.
[ALISHA gasps]
[ALISHA] What's happening?
This is madness!
We have to get away!
[LUNARRE cackles]
[LUNARRE]
Interesting! Very interesting!
[ALISHA gasps]
[CLEMM, ALISHA
grunting, gasping]
[ALISHA]
Why are you here?
[LUNARRE cackling]
This one is going to make
a tasty main course.
[LUNARRE yelps]
[ALISHA] It's like I'm
trapped in a dream.
Or a nightmare.
[LUNARRE yells, laughs]
[ALISHA] What in the world
is going on? What is this?
[LUNARRE laughs]
[CLEMM, ALISHA scream]
[ALISHA]
Clemm?
No...
No!
Where are you?
Hello?
Please say something!
Please, Clemm!
I'm done with this.
[LUNARRE growls]
[ALISHA sobs]
Why?
Clemm...
Ganette...
Bolta...
[ALISHA sobs]
[ALISHA gasps]
Please help...
[gasps]
[ALISHA grunting]