We have until sunrise
to execute our plan.
If everything goes
the way it should,
Ladylake will be ours again.
We'll do this without
killing anyone. Understood?
[bell ringing]
[BARTLOW SOLDIER A]
She's here!
The princess is
inside the walls.
[SHILLER]
They'll have us surrounded soon.
Maybe not.
If I remember correctly,
there's a hidden
passage... right here.
Ian!
[IAN]
Yeah, I'm on it.
Shiller, watch your back!
[yells]
[IAN]
Got 'em!
Come on, we've got work to do.
[BARTLOW SOLDIER A]
Chancellor Bartlow.
[BARTLOW] I take it the
princess and her rebels
have breached the walls.
[BARTLOW SOLDIER A]
Yes, sir.
We've deployed our troops
throughout the city
as instructed.
Very well then.
Let's begin. Make ready
to light up the square.
[laughing]
[LUNARRE]
It's almost too much fun!
[laughs]
The stage is set, and
the players are ready.
Time to draw the curtain up.
I'm going to enjoy
this so very much!
[chuckles]
No use. We can't catch it!
[MIKLEO] The tornado seems
to be gaining momentum.
[LAILAH]
It's almost as if something
is pulling it toward Ladylake.
[EDNA]
Something's very wrong.
[LUNARRE grunts]
[LUNARRE]
There are too many.
She won't even be able
to approach the capitve.
Maybe I need to go and stir
things up a bit down there.
You haven't died
already, have you?
[LUNARRE laughs]
I thought you would
like to know
that your dear pupil Princess
Alisha is coming to rescue you.
What do you want? Who are you?
[LUNARRE]
Who am I, you ask?
Well, now there's an interesting
question. Let me think...
I am many things.
But for tonight, let's say
that I'm a supporter
of the sweet princess.
For the most part.
I admit I'm disappointed
that she's willing
to sacrifice her
soldiers to save you.
That's exactly the kind
of short-sightedness
her opponents accuse her of.
I've come to expect better of
her during our time together.
[MALTRAN]
Hmph.
If you think that, then
you're no supporter of hers.
Oh, yeah?
[MALTRAN] Anybody who really
knows Alisha and her methods
would realize
where she's headed.
She wouldn't enter this
city without a solid plan.
[LUNARRE grunts]
You really don't see it?
She's not coming for me.
[growls]
[LUNARRE yells]
You are her beloved teacher.
If she's not coming
to your rescue,
then what is she doing here?
Being a leader in
a kingdom like ours
comes with certain
responsibilities.
It means not acting
on personal emotion.
We owe that to our people.
With the world in
its current state,
we can't let selfish
desires drive us.
Alisha has always known that.
It wasn't something
I needed to teach her.
In her heart,
she is a true leader,
rightful Princess of Hyland.
[BARTLOW]
What is taking so long?
The outer wall isn't far.
She should've reached
the square by now.
[BARTLOW] Unless she has
a different destination.
Prepare my carriage!
[MIKLEO]
We've got no choice
but to continue
chasing the tornado.
Though, honestly, I have no idea
what to do when we catch it.
[EDNA]
I'm with Mibo on this one.
[SOREY]
It'll be okay.
[MIKLEO]
Huh?
[SOREY]
It has to be.
[MIKLEO] What are you thinking?
You have a way to stop it?
[SOREY]
Not stop, exactly.
We're going to purify
the malevolence
the tornado is carrying.
Like I've said before, we've
all got malevolence inside us.
Most of us spend
our lives fighting it,
trying to deny the darkness
and do what we believe is right.
The struggle may not always be
obvious, but it's always there.
Always.
[MIKLEO] And if someone
starts to lose that battle...
[SOREY] ...that's when the
hellions begin to appear.
Malevolence manifests
differently in everyone.
There's no telling how
much someone can handle
before they're consumed.
One person may burn out with
only a few small mistakes.
Other can endeavor,
try to fight against it.
[EDNA]
And as the Shepherd,
you can gauge the
size of malevolence.
[SOREY]
I can.
[MIKLEO]
And what about the tornado?
[SOREY]
I can see inside it.
I know what's hiding in there.
What's driving it.
[EDNA]
So?
[SOREY]
Dragons cannot be purified.
That's what you've all told me,
but if that's not true?
What if no dragon
has been purified
because there's never been
a Shepherd who could?
Just because it hasn't been done
doesn't mean that it can't be.
[LAILAH]
That is possible.
[MIKLEO]
It's a big risk.
Do you really think
you're ready for it?
[SOREY]
I won't know until I try,
but it's a risk I have to take.
[MIKLEO] Sorey, what happens
if you can't carry it all?
[SOREY]
Then... I'll probably die.
It'll be okay. I have
all of you beside me.
Let's go!
[ALISHA]
Hello, Father.
[KING]
Is that you, Alisha?
Yes.
It has been a long time.
[KING]
Indeed it has.
[ALISHA]
Father. No, King Hyland.
I've come here to
make a request.
I ask you to please hear me out.
The danger our kingdom
faces now is greater
than any we've known before.
Hyland is drowning.
Our land is overrun with anger,
jealousy, and hatred.
Those emotions are
what has given rise
to this era of
chaos and calamity.
Our people deserve
peace and stability.
We must put a stop to all the
fighting. It's the only way.
If we can realize that goal,
the chaos may finally end.
Come, Alisha, move closer.
It's been too long
since I've seen you.
[ALISHA]
Of course.
I didn't realize how much you've
come to resemble your mother.
What-What happened to you?
[ALISHA]
Father.
It can't be.
[door opens]
[BARTLOW]
There you are.
I hadn't expected you to come
after the King directly.
I should have, of course.
Taking out the enemy leader
first is a sound strategy.
I let the fact that he's your
father cloud my judgment.
I didn't think you
capable of such a thing.
Clearly I underestimated
your ruthlessness.
You were right the first time.
I'm not here to kill my father.
I just came to talk to him.
[BARTLOW] You came here
in the middle of the night
with a battalion because
you wanted to talk?
Nonsense.
[ALISHA]
Put the sword down, Chancellor.
I have no intention
of fighting you.
[BARTLOW]
Alisha Diphda.
You are guilty of treason
and the attempted assassination
of your father, the King.
It's time for you
to pay for your crimes.
Stop this!
Fairwell.
[thud]
[KING groaning]
Please forgive me, Alisha.
[ALISHA] Wake up, Father!
Don't leave me!
[BARTLOW]
You and I aren't finished yet.
Now, pick up your weapon.
Better you die on your feet.
[ALISHA] If we fought, I would
win, but I refuse to kill you.
Death won't be your punishment.
You'll spend your life
in a cell for regicide.
[BARTLOW]
Who will the people believe
when they hear of
the King's death?
The treasoness princess
or the trusted Chancellor,
who guided the kingdom
through this bloody war?
So you intend to
spread falsehoods
in a desperate attempt to
hold on to your power.
[BARTLOW] Why not? It's been
a good strategy so far.
All right, everyone.
You can come in now.
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
Your men heard everything.
[BARTLOW SOLDIER A]
How could you do this?
I don't understand. We thought
we were protecting our country.
We fought our own men because
you said it was the only way.
[BARTLOW]
Don't let her decieve you.
She's a traitor, arrest her!
[ALISHA]
Put the sword down. It's over.
Remember what you said, Alisha.
That my punishment wouldn't be
death, but a lifetime in a cell.
There's still a way for
me to win, after all.
[gasps]
God, we'll never survive that.
[ALL gasp]
[MALTRAN] Get out of here!
Retreat to the castle!
This is no ordinary storm.
Ladylake will be a pile
of rubble before long.
It grows stronger
the closer it gets.
[roars]
[gasps]
[SOREY] Alisha!
Alisha, can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
[SOREY]
I'm going to need your help.
I'm calling on you,
as my Squire.
[ALISHA]
Of course!
[SOREY]
We're coming in fast!
[ALISHA]
I'm on my way!
[SOREY]
Mikleo!
[MIKLEO]
Right!
[SOREY]
Luzrov Rulay!
Lailah, can Sorey really
purify the dragon?
Yes, I believe he can.
He's ready to meet
this challenge.
We'll see.
It's not impossible.
Just because it hasn't been done
doesn't mean it can't be.
And today, we're
going to prove that!
[SOREY]
Azure Assault
Let's give this everything
that we've got!
[SOREY]
You're up, Rose. You ready?
[ROSE]
Yeah. Let's do it.
Now.
[SOREY]
Hear me, malevolent one.
The Sheperd has come
to purify your soul!
[grunting]
[ROSE screaming]
Hold on tight
[SOREY]
Rose!
[ROSE]
Keep going.
I... can do this!
I wouldn't doubt it.
You never quit.
Of course I don't.
I'm the leader of the Scattered
Bones. I fight to win.
[DRAGON roars]
[ROSE screaming]
Here, let me help you.
[SOREY]
You made it!
Took ya long enough, but thanks.
Hurry. Send me some
of the malevolence now.
All right. Get ready!
We can do this. Hold tight!
Don't worry about us.
Yeah, just keep going!
[SOREY yells]
[yells]
Don't worry. They're okay.
Just unconscious.
It was a close call, but they
stood firm the whole time.
Got ya.
[ZAVEID] I can't believe
he purified a dragon.
He really did it.
[SOREY] You know what
this means, right?
Edna, we should be able to
purify your brother now.
[EDNA]
Look at you. You're a mess.
Thank you, Sorey.
[SYMONNE] If this is your
grand plan to save the world,
you'll be sorely disappointed.
[SOREY]
It's you.
Nomatter what tricks
you have up your sleeve,
you cannot stop my master.
His goal is to shroud the
entire world in malevolence,
and I promise you,
he will succeed.
The end isn't far away now.
I don't know why
I didn't see it,
but Alisha and Rose
are pretty similar.
They're both extremely
reliable and responsible.
What else is there?
They're both respected
by their subordinates.
Oh, I've got one. They're
both excellent fighters.
I have Master Maltran to thank.
She taught me everything
I know about fighting.
When she was a knight, she was
known as the Blue Valkyrie,
and everybody feared her.
[ROSE]
Hm.
It was my foster father
Brad who taught me
how to handle myself in a fight.
He was the leader
of the Windriders,
and people all
across the continent
knew how strong he was.
Oh?
However strong he was, I'm sure
Master Maltran is stronger.
No, Brad is!
Master Maltran is!
Nope, it's Brad!
No, it's Master Maltran!
No, Brad!
No, Master Maltran!
Hey, guys, we're, uh, kinda
runnin' out of time here.
[ALISHA, ROSE] All right!
Then look forward to next time.
"The ideal world."
That's another one.
They both hate to lose.