[MIKLEO]
All of these people are here
to pray for Alisha's recovery?
They must truly love her.
Really? She's not that cute.
Don't be mean.
[EDNA]
Just a joke.
[LAILAH] Alisha's subjects are
genuinely concerned for her.
That says a great deal
about her as a princess.
She's strong,
but will she recover?
[SOREY]
Of course she will.
[MIKLEO]
Sorey, you should be resting.
No. I definitely shouldn't.
I've been in bed
for five days now.
Any more rest and
I'm gonna go crazy.
What about Rose and Alisha?
How long have those two
been unconscious for?
It's been nine days.
I see.
The dragon, it really
took a toll on you.
Yeah.
It's like you're being
invaded by emotions
that don't belong to you.
Then they collide and explode.
Bang!
Kinda like fireworks
in your head.
After that, they just
need some time
to sort through the
leftover emotions
and let them settle
in the right places.
It'll be best if we wait and
let them wake up on their own.
All these people...
Alisha is truly loved.
Without being asked,
they gathered here
not to pray for an escape
from hardship for themselves,
but out of honest concern
for the well-being
of another person.
That's good. It gives me
hope for the future.
[gasps]
Good news. They're awake.
[ALISHA]
Good morning.
[ROSE groans]
[ROSE]
Back at ya.
[ALISHA, ROSE]
It wasn't a dream!
It really happened!
We're alive. We did it, Rose!
[IAN crying]
I'm so glad you're awake!
I don't know what we
would've done without you!
Please don't cry. I'm all right.
I know that I worried a lot
of people. I'm so sorry.
Don't be. We're just glad
to have you back with us.
[MALTRAN] This latest
tornado hit Ladylake hard.
There's a lot of
damage to be repaired.
Even so, the people are
still in good spirits.
That's thanks to you.
Your recovery has given them
a renewed sense of hope.
I wish you could've been
in the square to hear them
when news came
that you'd awoken.
It worked.
We purified the dragon like
we wanted, but at what cost?
The Squires took serious damage.
We can't expect to do that
over and over again.
I know what you're thinking,
but please don't worry about me.
[MIKLEO gasps]
[ROSE] I'm not going to pretend
what we did was easy.
It wasn't.
It may've been the most
difficult thing I've ever done,
but still... I did it.
It was a lot to ask of you.
When we started,
it felt like my heart
was being wrenched
out of my body.
I wasn't sure if I
could withstand it,
but then I thought of
all I've been through
and I realized I could.
Yeah, same goes for me.
We can do this.
Thank you. Both of you.
As different as we are,
I think it's clear we
make a pretty good team.
I help her to loosen
up a little bit
and she helps to
keep me in line.
Where's your shadow?
I didn't think Dezel
ever left your side
for more than a minutes.
If that's the best you can do,
I'm very disappointed.
Can't you be more original?
Let's have fun.
Here, I'll start.
[DEZEL]
Flashy, but weak.
Considering who your master is,
I would've expected you
to be stronger than this.
That's enough, Dezel!
Don't get involved.
When I'm done with her,
she'll tell us whatever we want.
[SYMONNE chuckles]
[SYMONNE]
What more do you need to know?
My Lord will do as he pleases,
and nobody can stop him.
That can't be true.
You will bear witness
to this calamity, Shepherd.
[SOREY]
What about you?
Could you stop him?
[SYMONNE] Even if I tried, the
Lord no longer has ears to hear.
He is calamity incarnate now,
an immovable force.
It will help if I show you.
[SYMONNE]
This is the northern land.
It is a harsh, barren place
where no humans live
and even the strongest of
beasts struggle to survive.
[SYMONNE] Every being
that carries malevolence
gathers to attend him.
They are drawn to
the power of my Lord.
[SYMONNE] Soon, this force of
grief and hate will overflow.
Malevolence will crash down
upon this world like the tide.
[yells]
[DEZEL]
Curse you.
[SYMONNE]
Painful, was it?
Just imagine how worse
the reality will be.
Do you now see what I mean
when I say the world is ending?
Perhaps you should try
to enjoy your final days.
I don't understand why
you're telling us this.
You serve the Lord of
Calamity. What do you want?
To see the world
destroyed like he does?
What do I want?
Guys. I'm sorry.
I guess it's time to pack
our bags for the north.
This place was
getting dull anyway.
[DEZEL] Yeah, guess I could
do with a trip up north.
[MIKLEO] You should know by now,
wherever you go, I go.
Thank you. Truly.
[LAILAH]
Sorey.
Before we go anywhere, there is
something I must give to you.
What is it?
You've accomplished
so much already,
faced every challenge
that we've encountered
head-on and unafraid.
And, Sorey, you did what no
other Shepherd has been able to.
With your Squires,
you purified a dragon.
On top of all that,
you're close to uncovering
the true nature of malevolence.
When you started this journey.
it was because you believed in
the certain words of a book.
The Celestial Record .
[LAILAH]
You know its verses well,
but you may be
surprised to learn
it was a Sheperd who wrote them.
Is that true?
Yes. I knew him.
The author of the book
was Shepherd Michael.
[gasps]
And there's more.
He wrote another volume.
Kept inside is all he learned
of the origin of malevolence.
I can't believe it!
Another Celestial Record ?
Amazing!
[SOREY]
Thank you.
[LAILAH] Inside this book are
the secrets Michael uncovered
about the world and how it
came to be the way it is.
[SOREY] "Chapter One:
The Beginning of Calamity."
This is it. What Emperor
Doran told us about.
[SOREY] Velvet Crowe. This is
where everything started.
The hatred in her heart
was the beginning of it all.
[SOREY]
The savior. Artorius Collbrande.
He sacrificed Velvet's
brother in a ritual
that would eliminate
all human emotion
and thus the malevolence
that it created.
[ROSE]
Hmm...
Hmm.
[ROSE]
Mh-hm...
Mm.... Mh-hm.
Ugh!
[SOREY]
It seems okay to me.
You're the Shepherd.
You need to dress appropriately.
People expect it of you.
Next!
[SOREY] Ugh. Pass.
It smells like moth balls.
Excuse me. Can I have a moment?
Sorry to bother you,
but we heard that you were
intending to head north.
Please let us come.
It can never hurt to have
an extra sword or two along.
What do you think?
[SOREY] It's fine with me, but
the decision is really yours.
If you're all right
with it, then I am too.
We appreciate this,
Sir Shepherd.
Our place is with the princess.
It is.
[SOREY]
Wait, does that mean...
...you're coming
with us, Alisha?
Of course I am.
I'm glad to hear it, but what
about rebuilding the city?
What will happen to Hyland
if the world is destroyed?
You're facing something big.
If I can help, then I will be
doing my duty as a princess
and my job as your Squire.
[SOREY]
Thank you.
Oh! Hey, Schiller.
Ask the Shepherd to shake
your hand. It's good luck!
[SOREY]
This again? Aw, come on!
[IAN] Mine, too! I think
my luck's worn off.
Here. Try this one.
Nice. Fits perfectly.
It looks great!
You think so?
[MIKLEO] All these
people are volunteering
to come north with us?
The line just keeps
getting longer.
Word got out that the Shepherd
was going on a journey,
and people started showing up.
Not totally sure what they're
hoping to get out of it, though.
I would like to
join the Shepherd
on his journey to
save the world.
I can fight. I'm considered
a master of the spear.
I'm not great with a sword
or a bow, but I'm a good cook.
[VOLUNTEER D] I'm happy to
carry out any task you give me.
[MALTRAN]
A lot has changed.
Not long ago, we were
so short on soldiers
that Bartlow wanted to use
the Sacred Blade Festival
as a recruiting fair.
[ALISHA] We aren't having
that problem now.
You have come so far.
I know it wasn't easy,
but you should be proud of
what you've done for Hyland.
That means a lot
coming from you.
But still, the real
battle has just begun.
Yes, it has.
You'll stay here?
Look after the city?
I'd rather come along and stand
beside you when you fight,
but if you're asking
me to stay behind,
then that's what I'll do.
After all, how could I say no
to the new leader of Hyland?
I appreciate it, Master.
[OFFICIAL A]
Your Highness, it's time.
I should go now.
[EDNA]
You're going to come too, right?
[ZAVEID] It sure is nice to
think that we might finally
be coming to the end
of this long road.
Yeah, and we might get there
more quickly with your help.
I'm sure Sorey would be more
than happy to have you.
[ZAVEID]
Heh.
And I guess I owe him one
after what happened
on the mountain.
[ALISHA] I wish we could've
taken every volunteer with us.
But not everybody can face
what we'll be up against.
So, I chose only
the most capable
to make up the squad
we're bringing.
[SOREY]
Good.
[ALISHA] However, I made
sure everyone understood
that staying behind didn't
mean they couldn't help.
They can do their part by
working to rebuild the city.
Exactly.
And I'll do everything I can
to make sure that
work isn't wasted.
[EGUILLE]
With all the food, clothing,
and weaponry we're supplying,
they've run up a pretty
sizable tab already.
Better be able to
pay for it all.
I wouldn't worry too much.
Our client's the entire
nation of Hyland,
they're good for it.
It's like the Scattered
Bones has become
a legitimate operation.
Kind of strange, ya know?
We're heading to
a dangerous place
to fight an unstoppable enemy
and yet everybody's
acting like this trip
is some sort of holiday.
Well, they're idiots.
Really. Bunch of morons.
Absolute fools.
We're actually
agreeing on something.
You're agreeing with me.
Get it straight, Mibo.
[BOY A]
Sir Shepherd!
[GIRL A]
Princess Alisha!
[ALL gasp]
[SOREY]
You know, Edna,
if we turned here
and head for Rayfalke,
we could find your brother
and purify him.
[EDNA] We could, but what good
is saving him if the world ends?
[SOREY]
Are you sure?
[EDNA] The Lord of
Calamity comes first.
Wait for me, Brother.
I'll be back.
I'll bring Sorey,
and he'll set you free.
[ATAKK]
Mikleo!
[ATAKK laughing]
How ya doin'?
[MIKLEO]
Atakk! What're you doing here?
Looking for you!
I heard what you were up to,
and I figured you could
use some help, so...
Hey, Lailah!
I brought some
reinforcements, too.
[NORMINS laughing]
[SOREY gasps]
[MIKLEO] Our very own army
of Normin Seraphim.
Oh, one more thing.
There are a buncha big,
burly guys on horseback
coming behind us.
I think they might be
chasing after you.
[MIKLEO]
Huh?
[SOREY]
It's Sergei!
Princess Alisha. The foe you
face threatens the entire world.
We would fight
beside you, if we may.
Absolutely.
Look at Dezel and Zaveid.
They sure seem to get
along well, don't they?
The way they're actin',
it's like they're old
buddies or somethin'.
[SOREY]
Same with those two. Ha.
[DEZEL]
Be honest.
This fight we're heading
toward... can we win it?
I don't know.
You'll do what needs to be done.
Even if it's impossible.
That's who you are, Sorey.
Funny, I thought you were
describing yourself.
Huh? Why would you say that?
[SOREY, MIKLEO laugh]
Look, the fight at
Glaivend Basin was tough,
but our enemy's only gotten
stronger since then.
There must be something
more we can do this time.
He isn't the only one
who's gotten stronger.
Yeah.
You've got two Squires, so find
a way to make use of us.
We could always try the armatus.
And that would be?
Don't even ask. Dezel,
you know it's impossible.
It would put too much strain
on the Squires and on us.
[DEZEL] Look, in case
you hadn't noticed,
the Squires want to fight.
So let them try.
Okay, does somebody
wanna clue us in, here?
[LAILAH] Armatization
is the ultimate form
of collaborative combat
among humans and Seraphim.
It is also the Shepherd's
greatest and final weapon.
Trying it with a Squire
is too dangerous.
Think, Dezel!
We risk the life of the
Seraph attempting to merge.
You think they're
still too green.
I can't deny that.
Still, if the Lord of Calamity
is trying to destroy
the entire world, it'd be
foolish not to go after him
with every weapon we've got.
[LAILAH]
Maybe so, but, Dezel...
[DEZEL]
I'll take care of Rose.
As for Alisha--
[LAILAH]
I'll do it.
[DEZEL]
It can't be you, Lailah.
If we lost you, the Shepherd
would lose his own powers.
We need someone else.
Someone who won't put too
heavy of a burden on the Squire.
Okay then, it's me. I'll do it.
You'll need a Sub Lord
agreement with Sorey.
[DEZEL]
Hmph.
I figured as much.
Hepshin Yulind!
Lukeim Yurlin!
[BOTH yell]
[ALL gasp]
[ALISHA]
How's this ever going to work?
I can't stand up,
let alone fight.
[grunts]
Much harder than I expected.
I can see why you were so
worried about us dying now.
[LAILAH] Armatization
is a kind of merging.
The Seraph's role is to
become a full-body weapon.
In turn, the Squire acts as the
platform to support that weapon.
If the fusion is incomplete,
both Seraph and
Squire will fall.
What a miserable showing.
At this rate, the little fools
won't even last long enough
to reach my Lord.
How cool! Looks like we
got everyone here today!
Yeah, and things are
getting a little crowded.
Hey, be nice. Stop pushing me.
I'm barely in the shot!
We should do something special!
Why don't we all sing
a song together?
Make me.
'Kay. Let's play
a word game instead.
Last letter of
the previous word.
All right, why don't we
start with Arrow Squall?
Lukeim Yurlin?
Next time we do this, somebody
better bring me snacks.
"S," huh? Sparrowfeathers!
Scattered Bones!
Soufflé!
I have the perfect "E"! Elysia!
Mm... Master Maltran!
Nu-- Nu-- Uh...
Ha! Next time: "Northern land."
Look forward to it!
Whew, I thought you
were gonna choke!
I didn't know you had
such a unique talent.
Well, if you're so good, you
can handle the rest from here.
Start with "R."
Uh. Rayfalke Spiritcrest.
For "T," Twin Flow.
For "W," Windriders!
Strawberry shortcake! Edna!
Armatization. Normin!
What'cha think?
[OTHERS]
Impressive!