[knocking]
[ROSE]
Yeah? What is it?
Good news.
We heard from one of our people.
We've got him. We've
located Prince Konan.
It's time for revenge.
Are you ready?
[WINDRIDERS murmuring]
Ta-da!
So, whatcha think?
Do I look like
a princess, or what?
[WINDRIDER 17A]
Are you really Rose?
[WINDRIDER 17B]
There's no way!
I gotta make sure
she's not an imposter.
No touching!
Oh, yeah, that's the
real Rose, all right.
[WINDRIDERS laugh]
Shut up, you jerks!
It's still hard
to believe our Rose
is going to be
marrying a prince.
It's Brad we're talkin' about.
Is there anything he can't do?
If we stick with him, there's
no tellin' how far we can go.
[WINDRIDER 17C]
Yeah!
[WINDRIDER 17D]
Hey boys, Brad's back!
There he is!
Well, it's about time!
[WINDRIDER 17C]
Brad!
[DRUNK WINDRIDER 17A]
How ya been?
[laughs] Check it out! Look.
You'll never believe it!
I'm a princess now!
[WINDRIDERS groaning]
[ROSE]
You look lost. Need something?
Yeah, actually.
I'm looking for Dezel.
Have any idea where
I can find him?
He was over there
just a second ago.
Not that I can see him
or anything like you can,
but I do sense when he's around.
What do you want?
I'm not so sure it's a good idea
to leave him on his own
after what happened.
The thing at the church?
I dunno, can you be sure they
didn't get what they deserved?
[SOREY]
What do you mean?
[ROSE]
Who knows.
[SOREY] Hey, I'm making
a trip to Pendrago.
Apparently, they have
non-stop rain there.
I wanna figure out why.
I thought that maybe
you'd come along.
[ROSE]
Oh, did you now?
I don't suppose that's
because if I came along,
then Dezel probably would, too?
[sighs]
Well, count me out.
I've got things to take care of.
So, how'd it go?
[SOREY] It's crazy how
fixated Dezel is on Rose.
I wonder what that's about.
I'd guess it probably
has something to do
with her adoptive father, Brad.
It seemed like Dezel
really cared about him.
Maybe there's more
to her than we know.
The Rose we've seen is the
head of the Sparrowfeathers,
a merchant traveling the world.
Always upbeat
and happy, carefree.
I always thought it was
a lot more like
irresponsibility.
Yeah, I guess you do
kinda have a point.
I shouldn't have said that!
[MIKLEO] The people here
really do seem to trust her.
That was a surprise.
So, that's the Rose we know.
But maybe Dezel knows
a different side of her.
Looks like they're leaving.
Yeah.
What do you say?
Keep to the plan?
I'll follow Rose.
[SOREY]
And I'll go with Groodman.
I did promise to travel
to Pendrago with him.
Thanks for this.
I'm always here for you.
Here we go.
Uh--
I figured you could
use some help with Dezel.
We can't have "poor Mibo"
getting hurt, can we?
You can stop staring at me now.
Thanks, Edna.
Any idea where the
Sparrowfeathers might be headed?
[MIKLEO] Well, the load's light,
so she's probably out to buy.
[EDNA] No, there's
more to it than that.
I can't put my finger on it,
but something's off here.
Yeah. I haven't
seen Dezel either.
[DEZEL]
Sorry. Were you looking for me?
[MIKLEO]
Yeah, actually.
[DEZEL] The Shepherd
didn't come with you?
We're worried about
Pendrago, too,
so that's where he's heading.
[DEZEL] "Too?" meaning
you have other worries.
The biggest being you.
That was some show
the other day.
We can't leave you
alone after that.
Me, huh?
You really don't get it, do you?
What do you mean by that?
[DEZEL]
You'll find out soon enough.
[SOREY]
So, you think war is inevitable?
Just another part
of being human.
It's natural for the
strong to rule the weak,
and war is how we
distinguish between the two.
Will you feel that
way if you lose?
I never lose,
so that's not an issue.
And is that why you have
Sergei under arrest?
'Cause you think he's weak?
No, it's not.
You don't understand.
Sergei, well...
He claims it's his duty
to protect the Shepherd himself.
Since his superior and mine
aren't on the best of terms,
it isn't a good idea
to have him here at all.
But I have a soft spot.
I could have ignored him,
but I brought him along instead.
She's here to meet someone.
I wonder who.
Let's go and find out.
Standing here won't
do us any good.
Time for you two to see
what's behind the facade.
The truth.
He's tucked away
in a remote castle.
It's perfect.
[ROSE] And you're
positive that it's him?
Yes, we're absolutely certain.
It's Prince Konan.
You ready?
[ROSE]
Yeah. I am.
Let's take him out.
What was that?
Tell us what Rose
is trying to do.
[DEZEL] She's trying
to fulfill her mission.
Not as Rose, leader of the
Sparrowfeathers, but as Rose,
leader of the Scattered Bones.
They're planning
an assassination.
Assassination?
She was still a child
when she learned to kill.
But she's a quick study.
She fought to defend the weak,
as a member of the Windriders,
the predecessor to
the Scattered Bones.
[DEZEL] When Rose kills,
it isn't a murder.
It's an execution based on
what Brad would want,
something she sees
as a necessary evil.
Between her work with
the Scattered Bones
and her success with
the Sparrowfeathers,
it's hard not to be impressed.
[ROSE] You ever think
we're going to hell
for the things we do?
[EGUILLE]
Sure, all the time.
Except then I think,
"The people we kill deserve it,
and they're gonna end up
in an even deeper hell
than we are, so it's all right."
I guess that's
one way to look at it.
[DEZEL] We're going after
a very special target.
The man who betrayed Brad,
who murdered him.
More than anybody else,
he must be killed.
[gasps]
"Immediate justice over
unreachable ideals."
That was the motto
that always drove Brad,
why he went after those
who preyed on the weak.
But then someone convinced him
his ideals could be reached.
That person was Prince Konan.
The Windriders
had become a force
great enough to influence
an entire continent.
The prince asked them
to assist him in a war.
He lured them in,
promising, in return,
a swift end to the war.
And that wasn't all.
As a guarantee,
he pledged to marry Rose.
[MIKLEO]
Well? What happened?
It was a great victory,
but one achieved at
the cost of many lives.
And then he betrayed
them, didn't he?
[DEZEL]
That's right.
Once they had served
their purpose,
he was only too happy
to turn on them.
The man is a monster.
There are some people
who deserve to be killed.
Monster or not,
I don't think anyone
deserves to be killed.
Edna?
[EDNA]
I'm going to let Sorey know.
Must the weak always
be helpless and obedient
to those who abuse power?
This way of life is the only
one Rose has ever known,
so what right do you have
to tell her to give it up?
[EDNA]
Mibo?
I'll go tell Sorey
what we learned here.
You follow Dezel.
[MIKLEO]
Sorey!
[gasps]
[LAILAH]
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
It's Mikleo. I heard his voice.
[SCATTERED BONE 17A]
We know which room
in the castle is his.
He's guarded at all times
by approximately ten men.
We never kill anybody
other than the target.
That's our vow as
the Scattered Bones.
Then we'll just
have to find a time
when the prince's guard
isn't at his side.
We've been waiting years
for this opportunity.
We will take him out.
Yeah, Prince Konan
is going to die.
It's time for my revenge.
[ROSE]
Come on. Let's find him.
[PRIEST 17A] These arrived
yesterday while you were away.
I think you'll be pleased
with what you see.
[KONAN]
And what of the shipment
that was intended for Hyland?
[PRIEST 17A] Wrapped and sent
for delivery as scheduled.
If we move quickly,
we should have
a lot of buyers for this batch.
This is a special formula,
one that contains no
additives whatsoever.
Then let's not waste any time
getting these
bottles distributed.
You'll find no buyer
more eager than an addict
who's desperate to
feed his addiction.
[EGUILLE]
That must the tainted elixir
that's been showing up
in town recently.
Unlike the pure stuff,
it's highly addictive.
Supposedly, the formula
is a closely guarded secret,
known only by a small
fraction of the church.
[ROSE] So the church
is part of this, too.
[ROSE]
Seriously. Too many bad guys.
Now that everything's in hand,
I shall depart tomorrow.
I don't know how long I'll be,
so proceed as usual in my stead.
You can put your faith
in me, my prince.
Enjoy tonight, because it's
going to be your last.
I sense your worry.
You fear that hearing
Mikleo's voice
means something is wrong.
[SOREY]
Of course.
I don't know how I know, but I
know he's searching for us.
This is the fastest
road to Pendrago.
He's bound to catch up.
Sorey!
[gasps]
Mikleo!
We need to go.
Hurry, there's not much time!
I knew something was wrong.
We'll move faster
with you inside me.
[fabric rustling]
[SERGEI]
Where is he going?
A note?
[SERGEI] "I'm sorry, but
something urgent came up,
and I need to make a detour.
Please continue on
to Pendrago without me.
I'll catch up. Sorey."
[SOREY]
Rose, an assassin? Are you sure?
[MIKLEO]
Positive.
The Sparrowfeathers are a front
for the Scattered Bones,
a group of hired killers.
[GUARD 17B grunts]
[GUARD 17A grunts]
[EGUILLE]
Don't lose yourself.
No matter who the target is,
finish the mission quickly
and professionally.
That's what it means
to be the leader
of the Scattered Bones.
Right, Rose?
[SOREY]
Edna!
[EDNA]
Sorey!
Hurry, we have to get to Rose!
[gasps]
No! Please.
[SOREY yells]
[gasps] Rose!
[SOREY]
No...
Wait!
Being the Shepherd
must be tough.
[gasps]
[KONAN gasps]
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
Impossible! No one
could survive that!
[ROSE]
So, you don't remember me?
Let me help you with that.
Does the name Brad,
leader of the Windriders,
ring any bells for you?
[KONAN]
That band of mercenaries.
[ROSE]
You've got a terrible memory.
You don't even recognize
your fiancée's face.
[KONAN laughs] Do you honestly
believe I'd rule this kingdom
with mercenary filth at my side?
Yeah, I know. I was naive.
"Immediate justice over
unreachable ideals."
That's what he always said.
Till one day, he did
reach for those ideals.
And there you were, ready and
waiting to take advantage.
You bastard.
It looks like you've gotten
in over your head again,
but maybe I'll spare
your life if you bow down
and grovel for forgiveness.
Like I'd ever believe
a word you said.
[laughs]
[yells]
Die!
Sorry, but I need you to move.
[DEZEL] I'm sick of your
holier-than-thou act, Shepherd.
The fact is, some people
need to be killed.
[DEZEL]
That's why we're here.
We're doing the world a favor.
Rose, go on! Do it now!
[gasps]
[MIKLEO]
Sorey! Open your eyes!
Please, Rose...
Stop.
[SOREY]
You don't need to do this.
It's wrong!
No matter what he did!
[panting, grunting]
[yelps]
[SOREY]
Wait! Stop!
Rose, no!
It's Sorey...
...and Mikleo's...
[BOTH]
...one minute cooking show!
Today's dish: a frozen
favorite prepared
by none other
than Master Mikleo!
Hi, I'm Mikleo,
Seraph of water.
Today we will be
making shaved ice.
Since we're not busy
fending off any hellions,
we'll avoid sharp icicle summons
go for a square block instead.
Good plan.
We don't wanna poke ourselves.
Do you have any
advice for people
who can't use Seraphic Artes?
Well, you can try making
friends with a water Seraph
or find yourself a nice glacier.
Then either get your
new friend to help
or use your weapon of choice
to shatter the ice.
And, if that's too much trouble,
you can always go
to the store instead.
Add a little syrup
and you're done
It's so easy!
Next week:
Miss Edna will teach us
how to make dog food!
Look forward to it!
[EDNA] All right, boys,
stop playing around
and do the preview properly.
Next week: "Justice at
Hand rather than Ideal
beyond One's Reach."
Look forward to it.
I don't mind cooking
something, though.
[BOTH] I don't think
I'm gonna be hungry.