[SOREY]
I think we're here!
Ah!
[SOREY] There it is! We've
finally made it to Ladylake!
[SOREY]
There are people everywhere!
This is amazing!
Wow. So many humans
all in one place.
[ROSE]
It's a security checkpoint.
Oh. A tourist, huh?
The Sacred Blade
Festival always brings
a lotta newcomers to the city.
I'd hurry if I were you.
They're closing general
admissions soon,
but your pass should
still get you in.
[SOREY] And, where would
I get one of those passes?
You don't have one already?
[SOREY]
Well... No.
You really are new.
You can probably still
get in without a pass,
but it could take a while.
[SOREY]
Oh, really?
[ROSE]
Hm...
I might be able to help you out!
[ROSE] We're a caravan
of merchants who enjoy
the protection of
a free trade treaty.
The Sparrowfeathers.
[ROSE] Basically, we can
freely enter any city.
[laughs]
Well, you're in.
You can wander around
the city all you want.
So?
What?
It's time to settle up.
That'll be 500 gald.
I would say that's fair.
You don't get anything
free, ya know.
Gramps says human transactions
usually require money.
[gasps]
Jeez, are you broke, too?
What about that
pack you're carrying?
You've gotta have something
to trade in here.
Hey-- Uh-- Excuse me.
[ROSE] There! I'll take
this and call it even.
You can't have that.
I need to return it to someone.
[ROSE]
All right, I won't keep it then.
This seems like fate, somehow.
So let's just say you owe me
one and leave it at that.
You got lucky this time.
Great. Thanks a lot!
Well? Is Ladylake all
you thought it would be?
[SOREY] I'd heard that
it was an incredible city,
but I never imagined this!
It's pretty impressive, huh?
Yeah.
There are a lot more
people than usual.
What with the Sacred
Blade Festival, and all.
[ROSE]
Oh. Whoops!
Nice as this has been,
I've gotta get going.
Big city festivals can
bring in a lot of money
for merchants like us.
Which means I need
to get to work!
Have fun. This is
Ladylake at its best.
Thanks. I definitely owe you.
Sorey.
Now that we're here, we should
start looking for Alisha--
[groans]
You all right?
Something isn't right.
It's the malevolence.
Ladylake is thick with it.
[SOREY]
You feeling any better?
[MIKLEO]
Yeah. I think I'm all right now.
I'm glad.
[SOREY]
Down there! That Hellion!
[VILLAGERS yelping]
[LUNARRE yells]
[LUNARRE yelling, laughing]
Huh?
Sorey!
What do you want with Alisha?
[LUNARRE grunts]
[SOREY] Isn't that why
you came to Elysia?
To get to Alisha?
Tch. Is that why
you're worked up?
Well, then you can calm down,
because I won't be
targeting her any longer.
Then what are you
even doing here?
I kinda like the
little princess.
She's a feisty one, for sure.
A good fighter, too.
Hanging around her should
prove to be very entertaining.
[laughs]
[LUNARRE]
In fact, being a spectator
could be even more fun.
It's true that I've decided
to stop hunting her,
but you're a fool if you
think that nobody else is.
There's a price on
the princess's head.
As long as the contract
is still active,
she is very much in danger.
And the one who has
taken this contract...
...always delivers.
The only question is: when?
[cackles]
[ALISHA] Master, has anyone
been back to Griel?
[MALTRAN] Yes, and sadly,
no survivors were to be found.
[ALISHA sighs]
I must admit I'm
having a hard time
believing your story.
It's true, all of it.
[MALTRAN]
Is that why you oppose
Chancellor Bartlow
so forcefully?
Because of what
happened in Griel?
You're sure it isn't
because you and he had
a prior disagreement about
conscripting young people
who had come to the city
for the festival?
[ALISHA]
Yes.
I'm quite sure, Master Maltran.
We must not fight.
There's already enough
darkness in the world.
It doesn't matter
which side you are on,
the victorious or the defeated.
Either way, the main
product of war is hate.
We must avoid it at all cost.
I mean it.
Unless our opponent
strikes us first.
We'll make no move to attack.
Perhaps.
But you know as well as I do
that the upper brass
will never accept that.
[MALTRAN] I'd advise you to
think carefully before you act.
[EGUILE]
That does sound extreme.
[BARTLOW] I didn't expect the
princess to be this foolish.
To say we must allow
the enemy to strike
before making any
move of our own
is ludicrous and irresponsible.
[EGUILE]
Well. What action did you take?
[BARTLOW]
Obviously, I argued against her.
But she's always
been headstrong,
so she didn't listen.
What's more, rumors
have recently surfaced
suggesting that Princess Alisha
has secret ties to Rolance.
[EGUILE] So you're implying
that she might have
a personal motive for wishing
to forestall an attack.
[ROSE] We came here
so we could determine
whether or not the assassination
of Princess Alisha
is justifiable.
We arrive at that
decision by considering
how many innocent lives
might be spared
if hers were to be taken.
For the Scattered Bones,
it is a question of honor.
If that's the case,
I can assure you that
her actions are dangerous.
If she prevails,
many people will die
who would otherwise have lived.
She is advocating an
exclusively defensive policy.
In other words, she would
sacrifice the common folk
for her ideals.
[ROSE]
So soft.
Chancellor Bartlow.
You request the assassination
of Princess Alisha.
We accept the contract.
Hm...
Oh, dear.
[MALTRAN]
Today is the fifth and final day
of the Sacred Blade Festival.
We will now begin the
Rite of the Warrior.
[applause]
[SOREY]
Huh?
Mikleo.
I see her, too. There's
a Seraphim down there.
[SOREY]
You know what that means?
She must be the
Lady of the Lake!
The legends really are true!
[KNIGHT 4A grunting]
[LAILAH]
The malevolence is so strong.
Darkness is rising.
[CROWD cheers]
[applause]
Fellow citizens!
As you're all aware,
we have refrained from
holding our beloved festival
for several years.
Because these times are
so dangerous and uncertain.
But this year,
the Sacred Blade Festival
was held once more, thanks
to the grace and wisdom
of our Princess Alisha.
[applause]
This just gets more
entertaining by the second.
So that's truly the
secret blade of legend?
[MIKLEO] My guess is
that when you touch it,
the Lady of the Lake judges you.
And if she thinks you're
worthy of being the Shepherd,
you're able to take
it from the stone.
Worthy, huh?
[KNIGHT 4B grunting]
I think this is
the last of them.
I wonder how the princess
intends to bring
a graceful end to this farce.
[applause]
[gasps] There's Alisha.
What do you think
she's gonna do?
[ALISHA]
In closing,
I would like to say a few words.
But first I ask that we
take a moment to recognize
those who participated
in the Rite.
[applause]
[ALISHA] Unfortunately,
there was no Shepherd
chosen during this year's
Sacred Blade Festival.
We all know the legend:
that the Shepherd will arrive
in the world's darkest hour
to cleanse it of malevolence
with the help of the Seraphim.
However, blind belief in these
tales is not the reason
I wished to revive the
tradition this year.
Rather,
I'd hoped this parable
might teach us something.
Give us the strength we need.
There are some who believe
that this festival
was created to boost
morale before a war.
But I disagree with that.
In the legend, it was
only by working together
that humans and Seraphim
were able to hold
those dark forces at bay.
I believe the lesson we
should learn from the story
is that we are stronger when
we work with our neighbors.
Rather than fighting them.
[MIKLEO grunts]
What's the matter?
[ALISHA]
We must be strong.
With chaos and despair
taking over the world,
we need to band together.
I know this is hard to hear,
but even if Rolance
does invade Hyland,
we cannot strike first.
We must wait until
they attack us.
It's getting worse.
The audience's
disappointment and despir.
Their fear...
Their disillusionment...
All feed the malevolence.
[MALTRAN]
This could turn ugly.
Alisha!
What is going on here?
Come on. We have to
get out of this place.
[CROWD screaming]
[CROWD chattering, screaming]
A hellion! This is bad!
[HELLION roars]
[ALISHA yelps]
[CIVILIAN 4A]
Do you see that? The fire!
I'll be back!
Sorey!
[gasps]
[SOREY]
Alisha!
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
Sorey?
[SOREY screams]
Are you okay? Why are you here?
--[rumbling]
--[gasps]
All this fire...
Where is it coming from?
[SOREY]
I guess it's not surprising
that you can't see it.
Wait here!
Sorey!
[SOREY]
Lady of the Lake!
[LAILAH]
Who are you?
My name is Sorey.
Is there nothing you can do?
That Hellion could
kill everybody here.
Nothing at all.
I can't purify a Hellion.
Not without a Shepherd.
Shepherd...
[HELLION growls]
The Seraphim.
He really can see them.
He wasn't just humoring me.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[grunts]
Alisha!
[ALISHA]
Who are you?
[ROSE] You are guilty of
endangering your people's lives.
[whispering] What?
[BARTLOW]
Wait!
The princess is
perfectly capable
of defending herself.
Your concern should
be getting the audience
out of here safely.
Do you understand?
The same goes for all of you.
That's an order!
[MALTRAN yells]
[gasps]
[SOREY grunts]
Stay out of this, Sorey!
[gasps]
Let me handle this
fight on my own.
I need you to take care of
whatever that other
thing is, okay?
I don't think I can do it.
But you can.
You're the one I've
been looking for.
Go on. Please.
Wait, before you
touch the blade...
Clearly, you have a
connection to the Seraphim.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
be able to see me.
It's even possible that
you're able to draw the sword.
But first,
there is something
I must ask, Sorey.
Why do you want
to be a Shepherd?
Before I answer, may I
ask for your name?
Ah. Of course.
I am Lailah.
Lailah, my goal is
to travel the world
investigating ancient ruins.
And I truly believe
the artifacts of
the past hold clues
about how humans and Seraphim
can live in harmony.
That's what I dream of.
A world where our races can
come to know each other again.
Purifying the Hellions
will help to defend
humans and the Seraphim.
And I've got a feeling
that it's connected
to the dream that I'm chasing.
[SOREY] So there you
have it. That's why.
[LAILAH]
You must not go into this blind.
To become my sword
is to serve as a vessel
for me to dwell in and to
assume the Shepherd's burden.
You will be blessed with
the power of purification
and abilities beyond human ken.
But you will also be cursed
with despair, hardship,
and the scorn of others.
Some of the decisions
you are forced
to make will be agonizing.
Your battle will be lonelier
and more difficult
than you can imagine.
[SOREY] To be the Shepherd
is a heavy burden.
[LAILAH]
Yes.
I'll carry it.
If being your sword means
I can save these people,
then count me in.
If it brings me one step closer
to realizing my dream,
it's worth the price.
I'll do it.
I'll be the Shepherd!
[HELLION roars]
[gasps]
[SOREY grunting]
[SOREY]
"Fethmus Mioma." Is that you?
[LAILAH]
Yes. That is my true name.
[HELLION roars]
[LAILAH]
All right. This is it.
Harness the energy
flowing within you.
Unleash the power
of the Shepherd!
[LAILAH]
Now!
[SOREY yells]
He's the Shepherd...
No! Impossible!
[groans]
[gasps]
[MIKLEO]
Sorey!
I'm excited. This will be fun.
Don't you think so?
The three of us
traveling together.
Yeah, we're glad
to have you along!
[MIKLEO growls]
Hey, Mikleo, why aren't
you saying anything?
And what's with that
face you're making?
You said I had to
make funny faces
if you became the Shepherd!
Oh... Did I say that?
Guess I forgot.
Seriously. Well, it's
nice to meet ya.
t's nice to meet
you, too, Mikleo.
Why don't you tell us
somethin' about yourself?
Sure. I'd be happy to.
Any hobbies?
[LAILAH] I enjoy making
origami and sending
letters to my friends.
Do you have any
favorite snack foods?
Well, since I am
a Seraphim of fire,
I like making baked goods.
It utilizes my talents.
Can you tell us what
Fethmus Mioma means?
That's an excellent question!
It means "Lailah the Pure."
What's your weight?
That's a secret.
Your age?
The title of the next episode?
That's a secret.
That's not the kind of
thing you can keep secret!
Next time: "Destiny
of the Shepard."
Look forward to it!