Can you hear me?
Sorey.
Alisha?
[ALISHA]
Can you hear my voice?
[SOREY]
Yes. I hear you.
Ladylake is in trouble,
and I can't handle it alone.
I need your help, Sorey.
Can you come immediately?
It's bad. There's
another tornado!
[SOREY]
A tornado? Alisha?
Sorey?
Lost him.
[ALISHA] Are there any houses
in the tornado's path?
[SHILLER] There are a few
in and around Sithole.
[ALISHA]
They'll be destroyed!
Princess!
We may be in luck.
It's dissipating.
What? It's just gone?
But how?
[SHILLER]
That was the third one so far.
We're lucky they haven't
caused much damage yet,
but each one seems to be
getting stronger than the last.
You're right, and
they're not showing
any sign of stopping.
If an even stronger one
reaches the city...
Our priority is now Sithole.
We need to evacuate
the whole area.
[SHILLER] But, Princess,
is that a good idea?
[ALISHA]
What do you mean?
[SHILLER] Bartlow will likely
anticipate that move
and send men there
to intercept you.
You may be playing
right into his hands.
[ALISHA]
Honestly, I don't care.
Bartlow can do
whatever he wants.
But those are my people,
and I'm going to help them.
Right.
[IAN laughs] That sounds like
the princess we know and love!
No matter what happens, you
always stay true to yourself.
After you.
You lead and we'll
follow, Princess.
Thank you.
[KING] Have you been able to
get in touch with Alisha yet?
[BARTLOW]
No, sir.
We've made many attempts
to communicate with her
but haven't succeeded.
We implored her to see reason,
to return to her rightful place
and serve Hyland, but so far,
she has ignored our pleas.
[BARTLOW]
I regret to tell you this,
but the most recent message
I sent was met with violence.
The princess and her
people took up swords
against my messengers.
After the battle, she
gathered her force and fled.
I have men out
searching for her,
but she has yet to be found.
That is hard to hear.
[KING]
Whatever she may have done,
I want you to try to
bring her back alive.
I am an old man, and not
as strong as I once was.
I would like to see
her one last time.
[BARTLOW]
I understand.
I will let my men know
that she is to be brought
in alive, if possible.
I was already very old
when Alisha was born.
Her mother was a commoner,
but I loved her.
I made her one of my wives
and did what I could but,
ultimately, I wasn't able
to give her the life
or the attention she deserved.
[coughs, wheezes]
Quickly! Bring the physician.
The king needs his medicine!
Good evening.
Has your stay helped here
you to see the error
of your rebellious ways or
will you remain intractable?
Admit to your crimes
and repent them.
Do that, and I may be able
to lighten your punishment.
[BARTLOW] You still have
nothing to say to me?
We'll see how long you can
remain silent and stoic.
Princess Alisha and
her band of traitors
are still hiding in the
outskirts of Ladylake,
but not for much longer.
We'll capture her soon enough,
and this will all be over.
[BARTLOW] Without her master
there to guide her,
I doubt she'll put up
much of a fight.
That's where you're
wrong, old man.
Alisha and her soldiers are
brave, with or without me.
If you think they'll surrender
to you, you're a fool.
That could be problematic.
I can't promise her
safety if she resists.
In fact, the princess may
not survive the skurmish.
The king has accepted
the tragic truth
of his daughter.
He has left her punishment
entirely in my hands.
[BARTLOW]
If she behaves herself,
perhaps she'll be joining
you down here in that cell,
but I wouldn't
get your hopes up.
[MALTRAN]
Fight, Alisha.
[ALISHA]
Here, I brought you some water.
Try to rest.
[GIRL 20A]
Thanks.
[SHILLER]
I finished scouting.
No sign of any further damage
on toward the mountains.
Excellent. Thank you
for checking.
If you're not too tired,
can you please help
with the injured?
Absolutely.
[gasps]
[BARTLOW SOLDIER 20A]
There she is!
That's the princess!
Well, that didn't take long.
We don't wish to
fight our countrymen,
but we will if you
give us no choice.
We survived Glaivend Basin.
We won't fall to you.
Consider that a warning!
[BARTLOW SOLDIER 20A]
You don't frighten us.
Charge!
[BARTLOW SOLDIERS yell]
[IAN]
You traitors!
This is how you
serve the kingdom?
By attacking your own princess?
And you call yourselves
knights of Hyland.
[ALISHA]
I don't want any of them killed.
[SHILLER, IAN]
Got it!
[BARTLOW SOLDIER 20A] You're
the traitors here, not us!
Forward!
[BARTLOW SOLDIERS yell]
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
Shiller, get back!
Hellions. Lots of them.
Get moving, everyone.
Take the injured and retreat!
[ALISHA]
Ian!
[yells]
I guess I can't purify them.
[IAN]
Are you coming?
Get out of here, now!
[gasps]
What's happening?
[ALISHA yelps]
[ALISHA]
Who is that?
[gasps] A Seraph!
[ZAVEID] So, I take it
you can see my kind?
Yes.
I've been able to since
becoming Sorey's Squire.
[ZAVEID]
That's you, huh?
Well.
You seem like a good fit
for our soft Shepherd.
Are you a friend
of Sorey's as well?
I wouldn't go that far.
I heard a dragon had shown up,
so I figured I'd
come check it out.
Never thought I
would see Ladylake
so full of malevolence.
What are you humans
doing to this world?
I wish I had an
excuse for this.
What now?
Even if the Shepherd were here,
I don't know how he could help
unless he's figured out
how to purify a dragon since
the last time I saw him.
[ALISHA]
Dragons can be purified?
This isn't a problem that's
gonna go away on its own.
Question is what to do about it.
Oh, well, if worse
comes to worse,
I can always use this
to finish it off for good.
What is that?
[ZAVEID]
This?
This is Siegfried,
a very special object
with a very special purpose.
It's the only weapon
that can kill a dragon.
Of course, it may not
do any good this time.
Knowing the Shepherd,
he'll probably
want us to let the dragon live.
[laughs]
[gasps]
So, what's your name, anyway?
Oh, sorry, I'm Alisha Diphda.
All right, then.
Do me a favor, Alisha.
When you see our
mutual friend again,
tell him Zaveid says hello.
[ALISHA]
I will.
Thank you for your help.
[ZAVEID]
See ya 'round.
[ALISHA] It seems like the
tornadoes plaguing Ladylake
are a punishment.
The heavens are retaliating,
striking down us
humans for our sins.
Not only have we
refused to give up war,
we've begun fighting
our own countrymen.
If only we could find a way
to end this civil war.
Maybe that would put
a stop to these tornadoes.
But, even if I believe that,
it will be hard to
convince anyone else.
Which leaves us with one option.
Sorey's the only person
who can help us.
We have to wait for him.
We'll hold out
as long as we can.
Buy time until he can
come to our rescue.
[IAN]
Princess!
[panting]
[IAN] There is something
I have to tell you.
[ALISHA]
Calm down. Catch your breath.
[IAN]
Right, sorry.
Okay, what is it?
Did you take down a prickleboar
with one shot again?
I don't know how to say this.
It's about Lady Maltran.
She's in the fountain
plaza in Ladylake.
They've crucified her!
You can't be serious!
They've strung her up
in front of everyone,
and she's to be kept there like
that till you turn yourself in.
Bartlow's behind this.
I'm so sorry, Master.
We have to think this
through carefully.
Lady Maltran's
crucifixion is a trap.
That's obvious.
Our first instinct is
to ride to her rescue,
but that just gives
them what they want.
What do you suggest we do, then?
How long will she last
if we abandon her?
We just need a plan.
I'd say we have three days, max.
Beyond that, she won't survive.
But, you know they
won't let her go easily.
If we want to save her, we'll
have to face Bartlow's troops.
We'll be fighting our own again.
I understand the situation.
What I don't know is
what to do about it.
Stay here to save as
many lives as possible,
sacrificing my Master,
or fight my own
countrymen to save her?
I wish I knew.
I'm sorry if it's out of line,
but I have to ask.
[SHILLER]
What do you want us to do?
Should we continue to
fight without killing,
or do we have leave to kill
if it's absolutely necessary?
I need to know where
we're drawing the line
so I can inform the men.
Give the order,
and no matter what it is,
every one of us will obey you.
Yes. We'll back
any call you make.
[ALISHA gasps]
Where'd you come from?
Always lovely to
see you, Princess.
You know, you humans truly
are a piece of work.
It's quite impressive
how your kind always finds
new ways to be cruel
to each other.
[ALISHA]
What are you doing here?
What? I can't say hello?
I've been keeping a close eye
on you for a while now.
First at the festival, then the
little trip you made to Marlind,
the battle with Rolance
at Glaivend Basin,
and then that scuffle with
your own men at Ladylake.
I have to admit,
you're doing better
than I'd expected.
You've been watching me?
You stopped a war that probably
would've taken
thousands of lives.
All those men are
still breathing
thanks to you
and your friends,
and how do they show
their gratitude?
By hunting you down
and branding you a traitor.
It's Bartlow's fault, of course.
The old fox has been
telling everyone that Hyland
could have won the war,
if only the meddlesome Princess
Alisha hadn't interfered.
Hypocritical fools.
If you're on the losing side,
then war is an atrocity.
But if you're the victor,
well, in that case,
war is a perfectly
justifiable demonstration
of your inherent superiority.
Can you imagine the
reaction if you'd ordered
the men who are after
you to the front lines
instead of stopping the battle
and saving their skins?
Somehow I doubt they'd
be wasting their breath
crowing about the wonders
of war if that had happened.
[LUNARRE laughs]
Humans are weak
and always have been.
That's not something
anybody can deny.
Weakness comes in so many forms.
People with weak minds and
weak hearts are easily swayed
by those in power, no matter
how corrupt they might be.
You understand that,
and yet you wanna
continue fighting for them?
That's exactly why
I have to keep fighting.
Inaction is a greater
sin than ignorance.
[LUNARRE growls]
Think what you will.
I don't care if I sound naive.
I have a duty to all my people.
As their princess, I can't pick
and choose those I want to help.
[growls]
[BARTLOW SOLDIER 20A]
Huh?
Decoys! Find them!
They couldn't have gone
far without us knowing.
[BARTLOW SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[IAN] Good intuition, Princess.
We could be dead by now.
True, but we've still got
our work cut out for us.
Bartlow has had a long time
to prepare his defenses.
This will not be easy.
Are we ready?
We are.
It's time to make our move.
Let's ride! For Ladylake!
[BOTH]
Right!
[ROSE]
Sorey, wake up!
What is it? What's wrong?
Come and look at this!
See, up there!
[SOREY]
A tornado!
[MIKLEO] And do you see
the direction it's going?
It's unstopable and
it's headed for Ladylake.
Then we need to
get there right now.
Ready?
[SOREY]
We're coming!
Has there been any sign
of Princess Alisha yet?
[BARTLOW SOLDIER 20A]
No, sir, I'm sorry.
It won't be long.
When she hears how I've
tormented her beloved master,
she'll come running
to the rescue.
[LUNARRE cackles]
How fun.
[cackles]
Yes. Fun!
[IAN]
Take my hand.
I've got it, thanks.
We have until sunrise
to execute our plan.
If everything goes
the way it should,
Ladylake will be ours again.
We'll do this without
killing anyone.
Understood?
I really appreciate
the help earlier.
How can I pay you back?
It's no problem.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't see anyone with you.
Do you always travel alone
like this, Zaveid?
Yeah. I go where
the wind takes me.
I'm bound by nobody.
I live as I please
and journey freely.
Traveling alone is my style.
I'm sorry.
That must be extremely
difficult for you.
I don't think you get it.
I enjoy being on my own.
It's okay, you don't
have to hide from me.
Really, I can tell
just by looking at you.
Huh?
What can you tell?
Just that... you've
had a hard time.
Bad enough to travel alone
and then to have somebody
steal all your clothes?
Wait a sec! No one robbed me.
This is how I dress!
Please just give me a moment.
I will go and find
a shirt for you to wear.
Alisha! Get back here!
Sorry, I forgot.
Next time: "Purification."
Look forward to it!
No, hold on. That's
not what I meant.
This is a fashion
statement, okay?
I don't need a shirt!