That bastard.
You allowed her to
become a dragon?
Symonne put her trust in you!
You truly are a monster!
It is done.
I make my way to the
center of the world
to begin the end of all things.
Well? How is she?
[DEZEL]
Unconscious, but alive.
[SOREY]
Thank goodness.
All right, everyone!
Let's head down the mountain.
We're going after
the Lord of Calamity!
Is she doing any
better than before?
[DEZEL]
Not really.
She still has tremors
all over her body.
[ZAVEID]
I'm sorry.
I assumed she must've improved
since you'd left her side.
[DEZEL] Just for a moment. Sorey
is giving her his blessing now.
I came to ask a favor of you.
A favor?
Your gun.
I need to take it off your
hands and slay some dragons.
The next battle we face
may well be our last,
but we can't hope to purify
every one of those monsters
and still have the strength
to reach the Lord of Calamity.
We only able purify
the dragon at Ladylake
by the skin of our teeth.
It took everything we had.
I understand what you're
saying, but look--
[DEZEL]
Sorey is strong.
In time he may even
be strong enough
to purify that many
dragons, but he isn't yet,
and we don't have the
luxury of waiting.
We must face them now.
If we lose to the
Lord of Calamity,
he will consume
the entire world.
[DEZEL grunts]
[ZAVEID] Rose isn't the only
one who needs to recover.
You should get some rest, too.
[DEZEL]
I'm fine. I don't matter.
Don't say that.
Zaveid, please. I need that gun.
[DEZEL]
It's something Rose said.
Given the amount of
malevolence gathered here,
winning this battle could change
the course of the entire world.
How can we pass up
a chance like that?
More than anything,
I want her ideal world
to become a reality.
This isn't something
you're doing for yourself.
[DEZEL]
No.
[ZAVEID]
Take it.
Why are you stopping?
Wait.
[IAN]
He's dead.
[SHILLER]
What is he doing out here?
[IAN]
I don't know, but he's smiling.
[SHILLER]
What should we do?
[IAN]
We can't just leave him.
Let's see that he gets
a proper burial.
[SHILLER]
Agreed.
I didn't expect to see this.
A town so far north?
Melshio.
According to the Record ,
that was its name.
Beyond here is the
Kiraraus volcano
and that's where the
Earthpulse nexus is,
and where we'll find
the Lord of Calamity.
Apparently it used
to be a vibrant city,
but obviously no more.
[MIKLEO]
Now it's just ruins.
[GRIMOIRE]
No, not just ruins.
Though all of the humans have
been gone for some time.
[SOREY]
Who are you?
Grimoire, one of the Normin
Seraphim, Sir Shepherd.
[SOREY] How did you know
I was the Shepherd?
Don't look so surprised.
One doesn't get to be my age
without picking up
a thing or two.
And I know you've come here
to find the Lord of Calamity.
We did.
[GRIMOIRE] A blizzard really
isn't the best place
for a civilized conversation.
Why don't we go inside?
[ATAKK] I didn't think we'd find
you here after all this time,
Grimm, but I'm
sure glad we did!
It's like a miracle!
I'm relieved to see that all
of you survived, as well.
It must've been tough.
Can I ask you something?
[LAILAH]
Of course.
You've read this book of
Shepherd Michael's, haven't you?
I have.
What he describes about
the structure of the world,
about Seraphim, is all
of that really true?
[LAILAH]
To be specific,
you're asking about Innominat
and the Empyreans?
Right.
[LAILAH] Yes, as far as I know,
every word of it is true.
Michael certainly believed so.
Innominat and the Empyreans.
They are the highest
ranking of all Seraphim.
Once they were
worshiped by mankind.
Their temples lay at
the Earthpulse's nexus.
[SOREY] Somehow, I don't
think it's a coincidence
that's where the Lord
of Calamity's heading.
This book has me so confused.
I mean, it was Velvet's hatred
that started us on
this path, right?
Without her hate, this age of
chaos may never have begun.
In which case,
Artorius is to blame
for having attempted
to save the world
by sacrificing Velvet's brother.
Of course she would
hate him for that.
Except, as horrible
as what he did was,
he believed he was
saving thousands of lives
by taking one.
So in the end, which
of them was right?
Which of them was wrong?
A hard question.
What do you believe?
I don't know.
Just that if only they had
understood each other better,
things could've been different.
I don't wanna repeat
what came before,
but I'm not sure I know
yet how to avoid it.
You have come a long way,
and you've learned a great deal.
You don't know everything,
but your eyes and
heart are open.
Maybe that is enough.
I hope so.
[MIKLEO]
Hey, I bet you're pretty hungry.
Now that you mention it...
[MIKLEO]
How does soup sound?
It sounds great. Let's eat.
[ATAKK] So, even after
everything that's happened,
you still think there's
a future for us Normin?
As long as we stick by
this Shepherd, yes, I do.
Well of course
we'll stick by him!
[chuckles]
[SERGEI]
And that's what malevolence is.
So, what do you
make of all of it?
To be honest, it's a
bit hard to swallow.
Would you like some tea?
[SERGEI]
I would, thank you.
[GROODMAN]
Come, Sergei.
Is that any way for a
brave knight of Rolance
to drink his tea?
Let me show you.
[GROODMAN, BLACK NORMIN cough]
[OTHERS laughing]
That you, Alisha?
Yes. How are you?
I've been better.
Did the armatization
knock me out again?
[ALISHA]
That's right.
You spent a much longer time
fighting in armatus form
than I did.
It was impressive.
Are you hungry?
We have some soup.
Not now, thanks.
[DEZEL] So tell me, you ever
asked yourself why we're here
or why Seraphim
should even exist?
[ZAVEID]
Sure, who hasn't?
I think the question first
crossed my mind 500 years ago.
[DEZEL] Of course it did.
With age comes wisdom.
Well, you manage to come
up with any answers yet?
Only more questions.
The humans used to pray to us.
We would bless them,
thus maintaining the
balance in the world.
But is that truly
all there is to it?
We were born solely to
receive humans' prayers?
[EDNA] Idiot. Why even bother
thinking about that?
Comes from watching Rose.
She makes me wonder about it.
About what it means
to feel alive.
I'll don't know what
I'll do if she dies.
[SOREY]
Based on what it says here,
Velvet and her companions left
this place a thousand years ago.
That's pretty incredible, huh?
Almost hard to believe.
Sorey,
do you really think you're
gonna be able to purify him?
I don't know.
I wish I could say, "Yes, I do."
The malevolence
was unbelievable.
I can't imagine how powerful
he is. It's kind of terrifying.
[SOREY]
Yeah.
So what happened to
Velvet after that?
Where'd she go?
No idea. The book
doesn't really say.
That's the last time
it mentions her.
Oh.
[DEZEL]
The way things are going,
she may not be able
to fight at all.
[gasps]
With how slow her recovery is,
it may be best to
leave her here.
That might be a good idea.
[ROSE]
Over my dead body!
Rose, I--
Princess. Hand over that soup!
[ROSE growls]
[grunts]
[ROSE]
I might not be in great shape,
but don't even think
about abandoning me here!
I'm still gonna armatize, too!
We're going together, and
that's final. Understood?
[DEZEL laughs]
Fascinating!
I didn't think you were
capable of actual laughter.
[DEZEL]
I leave it to you, Rose.
All right, we stay together.
[ZAVEID]
Dezel, what are you planning?
[VELVET] Have you ever
wondered why birds fly?
It's simple, really. They fly
because they want to.
They need no other reason.
They remain among the
clouds until the day they die,
because it's where they belong.
Birds fly for themselves,
not because it's what somebody
else expects of them.
Follow your own path
and no one else's.
[gasps]
Was that...?
[ALISHA]
I don't understand.
Did you know him, Princess?
Yes. I'm shocked to see him.
Sorey.
Yeah.
[SOREY] From this point forward,
we will travel alone!
[ALISHA] Thank you all
for coming this far.
[ROSE]
We'll take it from here.
Good luck! You got this!
Stay sharp, now.
We're going to hold our own.
I know you all can't see them,
but we have five great
Seraphim friends at our side.
I could never have
done this without you.
It was a long journey,
but we made it together.
You proved humans and
Seraphim can coexist.
For that... I am far more
grateful than I could ever say.
Thank you.
Now, let's go.
We'll purify the
Lord of Calamity
and rid the world
of his darkness.
[ROSE]
What is that?
[DEZEL] It's like a
path of malevolence.
I guess they're sending
us an invitation.
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
Dragons!
We're surrounded!
All right. Everyone ready?
Do you really have to ask?
[DRAGON roars]
Where did that one come from?
[DEZEL]
That one there, it's Symonne.
Just wait. It won't be long now.
I'm going to end this.
Listen, if you try to
purify all these dragons,
you won't have anything left
for the Lord of Calamity.
I know that.
Still, we have to get
past them to reach him,
so what choice do we have?
[DEZEL]
Well, about that...
...I have an idea.
Wait, that gun!
[EDNA gasps]
You gave him Sigfried?
Yeah. I asked him to
let me borrow it.
I can use this to finish
off the dragons.
[SOREY]
No!
[DEZEL] All that matters is
purifying the Lord of Calamity.
That's what will
save this world.
Think, Dezel!
All those dragons
used to be Seraphim.
It's too late.
There are too many.
There's still a chance
for us to purify them.
[DEZEL]
It won't work.
How do we know unless we try?!
[MIKLEO]
Hey, we got this.
We follow your lead, Sorey.
I've got you covered
on defense this time.
And I will handle
the malevolence.
[ROSE] Well, sounds like
they've made up their minds.
I'm with them on this.
Damn.
You're all a bunch of push-overs
when it comes to this guy.
Still, I was kinda expecting
something like this to happen.
[SOREY]
Dezel?
It won't matter what I say.
Nothing's going to convince
you to kill them, huh?
[SOREY]
No.
[DEZEL]
Tch.
All right then. I won't, either.
You have my word.
Hey, Zaveid!
Thanks anyhow.
[ZAVEID]
Don't mention it.
Well, Shepherd.
We'll do this your way.
None of the dragons will die.
I'll use my winds to blow
them out of the way.
The rest of you, just do
your best to stay clear.
Take care of Rose, okay?
Give her the world she deserves.
Hey, Rose? Ready to armatize?
You know it.
[DEZEL]
Heh.
[ROSE]
Lukeim Yurlin!
[DEZEL] Listen carefully.
We've only got one shot at this.
I want you to fly us into
the center of the dragons.
After that, just support me.
[ROSE]
The center, got it.
[DEZEL]
Now don't screw this up.
[ROSE] Who do you think
you're talking to?
Now, go!
[yells]
[gasps]
[DEZEL]
Rose! Are you all right?
[roars]
[ROSE]
I can do this. I can!
There we go. The center!
This good enough?
[DEZEL]
It'll have to be.
This is quite a view.
[DEZEL]
Yeah, no kidding.
Listen.
It's my time to become the wind,
to release all the
power I have left.
Rose, thank you for everything.
[ROSE gasps]
What's wrong? No one
ever thanked you before?
Why are you thanking me?
And why now?
Something's wrong. Talk to me!
[DEZEL]
Look out!
[ROSE]
Damn it!
[DEZEL]
Do it!
[yells]
[yelling]
[ZAVEID]
Dezel.
[ROSE]
Dezel?
Dezel.
[DEZEL]
Rose.
Are those tears?
[ROSE]
No, of course not!
Heh.
Well, don't cry, okay?
Not on my account anyway.
You've only known me
for a few months.
But it feels longer.
[DEZEL]
For me it has been.
I've known you since you were
a scrawny thing only this tall.
So then... maybe... maybe
it's okay if I cry a little.
Do me a favor.
Make sure Sorey knows
it's not his fault I died.
That's important.
I was the one who chose
this path of my own will.
He shouldn't think
of me as a sacrifice.
Besides, I feel good right now.
All right.
[DEZEL] I'm leaving this
world soon, but before I do,
I need to confess
something to you.
The thing is, when
I possessed you...
...I forced Brad's
ideals on you.
I made you chase after
someone else's dream
and it led to a lot of
pain you didn't deserve.
What's worse is...
I used you... to kill.
[ROSE]
You've got it wrong.
However it may have started,
this is my dream now.
If you're the one who gave me
the opportunity to chase it,
well then, thank you.
You and Brad fought so long
and hard for this dream.
I couldn't be more proud
of everything you've done.
Dezel. I won't stop fighting
till our dream is realized.
I promise. Okay?
I know. You don't
know how to give up.
So thank you, Rose.
Yeah!
[chuckles]
[DEZEL]
Good luck out there.
Right.
And keep on keepin' on.
I will!
Dezel.
[ROSE crying]
How awful.
Poor Rose. Will she be okay?
Of course. You know
how strong Rose is.
She is going to
get through this.
Hm? Oh, Rose.
Sorey. I want to thank you.
Huh?
Thank you for agreeing
to make me your Squire.
Because if you hadn't,
I never would've been
able to see Dezel.
Of course.
I know it'll be like a
part of myself is missing,
but still, it feels like he's
looking out for me, ya know?
[wind blowing]
There, see?
It's like he's telling us all
to keep on keepin' on.
I can still hear the
sound of his voice.
He'll always be
with us, in the wind.
Please, Dezel, watch over us.
Now then.
Next time: "The Chosen Answer."