[LAILAH] You always said
that you wanted to eliminate
all malevolence from the world,
that doing so was
your duty, your calling,
your true purpose in life.
The era of chaos has deepened
its hold on the world.
I fear It won't be long now
before all is
swallowed by darkness.
However, not all
hope is lost, not yet.
I'm on a journey
with a new Shepherd,
and perhaps he will find
the path to our salvation.
There's so much
for him to discover.
So many questions to ask.
What answers will he find?
Michael. Please watch over us.
Watch over the journey
of Shepherd Sorey.
[ROSE inhales]
This isn't half bad.
You know it's a good deal.
Just about everything is
hard to come by these days
and that's quality stuff,
not something you could
get from just anybody.
How much are you
trying to unload?
Eh, 30 boxes of 2,000 each.
What all ya got?
There's sage, verbena,
rosemary, red sage,
and some red rosemary
in there, too.
It'll be easy enough
for us to find other buyers.
So, you don't wanna waste too
much time thinking it over.
[ROSE] Can I get a look
at the others, too?
[SOREY]
Rose is really in her element.
[MIKLEO] I kind of didn't expect
her to be a proper merchant.
Really, why not?
Dunno. Just didn't.
All right, then.
These guys, though,
does something about them
strike you as
a little suspicious?
Oh, finally noticed, have we?
[TRADER 14A]
Come on, lady.
Haven't you looked
through enough of 'em?
I guess, they seem fine to me.
[TRADER 14A]
Okay. So, we have a deal, then?
Yes, we do.
The Sparrowfeathers
will make the purchase.
Pay the man!
[ROSE]
Five thousand gald.
Five thousand?
You gotta be kiddin' me.
You saw for yourself,
our stuff is good quality.
Y'know, I'm curious.
These days, not many people
are having any luck
growing herbs.
So, where did you get these?
Um, where'd we pick
these up, again?
Uh, I don't know.
I think maybe it was
back in Hawken, wasn't it?
Far as I know, the only
people growing herbs
in that area are
the Kelly family.
Are you sure that's
where it was?
I'll tell ya what.
Take the 5,000 gald and leave.
You do that and I'll stop
grilling you for answers.
Well, when you put it like that.
[TRADER 14A] I'll be happy
to take the 5,000 gald
off your hands and if you leave
the rest of your money behind,
I might just let you
get outta here alive.
[TRADER 14B]
Easy choice.
What good is money
to ya if you're dead?
[sighs] I had a feeling
this was coming.
Piece of advice:
I'd do what she wants
if I were you.
[TRADER 14A]
Get her!
[TRADERS yell]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[TRADER 14A groans]
[gasps] Are you okay?
[ROSE]
You ready to give up?
[TRADER 14B] I vote yes.
Can we give up, please?
Not a chance.
We can't back down now.
[ROSE] You seriously wanna
go another round?
[SOREY]
You don't. I promise you don't.
[ROSE]
Okay, let's see what you've got.
[TRADER 14A groans]
[TRADER 14B panting]
[TRADER 14B yelping]
Don't mind me.
Just thought I'd help a little.
[ROSE] That'll be the last
time you sell stolen goods.
I need somebody to get word
to Kelly's farm for me.
Let them know
the Sparrowfeathers
will purchase the goods
that were stolen from them.
Honestly.
I can't have Kelly's
going out of business.
That would mean a hard time
for a lot of customers.
[AYN FELICE hums]
And now we wait.
The most important thing
is steeping time.
It has to be perfect.
Take a moment to breathe.
Don't rush. Be patient. Hm?
[gasps]
Whatever.
I'm thirsty.
[AYN FELICE] Those are
high-quality tea leaves
you're abusing!
[ROSE] Where's Sorey?
We should give some to him.
The last time I saw him,
he was by the water
playing with fire.
[LAILAH]
Hate, pain, rage.
Malevolence is
shapeless, endless.
But the emotions that drive
it are very real indeed.
There are many shapes
of purification.
And now, I will accept all
malevolence into myself
and forge forgiveness.
Malevolence contains
contradiction
and fissures create darkness.
Water, our mother!
[LAILAH]
Fire, our life!
Fire, burning inside water.
Fire in water. A contradiction.
[gasps]
We've still got
a little work to do.
[SOREY grunts]
[clapping]
Impressive, Sir Shepherd!
That a training thing?
[SOREY] I'm trying to
build up my recognition
of the forms of malevolence
so that I can learn
to accept them.
Whoa.
Hey, listen, I just got an idea.
Why don't we turn that
into a traveling show?
We'll make a bundle!
[laughs] You're a businesswoman
first and foremost, huh?
[chuckles] So, yes?
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
People enjoy a good show.
We make tons of money.
Everybody wins, right?
I guess so.
Sorey, you're a
heck of a pushover.
You know that, right?
[SOREY]
Huh?
Well, that might insult
the dignity of the Shepherd.
The princess wouldn't like that.
Alisha, angry? Heh.
Scary thought.
Okay. We should
probably get to sleep.
We'll be entering
Lastonbell tomorrow.
[ROSE]
Come on! This way.
[gasps]
[SHOPKEEPER 14A]
Miss! We're glad to see
you retuned safely
from Glaivend.
How was your journey?
You're doing well?
Yep. All in one piece.
And we scored some herbs
from the Kelly's
on the way back.
Ya think you can use them?
Those will be a big draw
at the great market.
They'll go for a good price.
Just leave it to me.
Young sir. Welcome,
it's a pleasure.
Thank you very much.
Lastonbell is such
a vibrant city.
Like Ladylake, but different.
[SHOPKEEPER 14A] Mm-hm.
We're located on the border, so,
trade is very important here.
Lastonbell is one
of the largest centers
of commerce in Rolance.
They're prosperous here.
I can understand why
Bartlow wanted Rolance.
So, this is your hideout, huh?
[ROSE]
Do you have to call it that?
It's our warehouse and office.
[SPARROWFEATHER 14A]
Rose! It's good to see you!
Good to see you, too!
Think you can go help out
with the unloading?
[SPARROWFEATHER 14A]
Sure thing!
Oh. One sec.
Is Glenn around somewhere?
[SPARROWFEATHER 14A]
No, he's not here yet.
Huh, that's a little
weird for him.
Woah.
In order to run
a business like ours,
you need bases like these
all over the world.
We use them to safeguard
goods, store supplies,
and even sometimes
to make sales.
[SOREY]
Pretty impressive.
[ROSE]
I know, right?
[MAVIN]
Rose?
Uh-- Hey, Mavin!
[BOTH grunting]
What a nice surprise!
I heard you were going
to be in Lastonbell.
Got here soon as I could.
We just got in, too.
There's something
I wanted to show you.
Guchaga twins.
We found 'em in
the Krishana ruins,
200 meters below ground.
When I saw them, I thought
for sure you'd be interested.
You said you'd like to focus
more on antiquities, right?
Oh, well, um, yeah.
[MAVIN] You don't know
what they are, do you?
Wow, these are a good find.
He found these in
the Krishana ruins?
I've never seen
the style before.
Who's he?
Ah. Sorey, the Shepherd.
[MAVIN]
No kidding!
I heard you roasted a dragon
and ate it whole, bones and all!
I'm Mavin.
Nice to meet you,
Shepherd Sorey.
Mavin here is an explorer.
Not to mention a storyteller.
A storyteller?
Kind of like a teacher,
spreading knowledge
of history and mythology.
Woah, you must
know a whole lot.
[ROSE]
He better!
Mavin is over 100
years old, you know.
[SOREY]
Really?
That's right, shepherd.
There are things outside of the
ruins that are spectacular, too.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[FARMER 14A]
Rose, you in there?
[RANCHER 14A]
Hey, look! Rose!
There you are!
[FISHERMAN 14A] Where've
you been? We missed you!
[RANCHER 14A] Welcome back.
It's good to see you!
[FARMER 14A]
You've been gone too long.
We were so worried about you!
I saved you my best ham.
Wait till you try
this dried fish!
This radish crop
is my best one yet!
I've got a new brew
people will go crazy for!
Check out the wheat.
We had an especially
good harvest this year.
When do we talk deals?
Hey! I was here before you.
[FISHERMAN 14A]
Oh, yeah?
'Cause it sure as heck
didn't look like it to me!
[BREWER 14A] Back off!
She's talking to me first.
[FARMER 14A] I don't
think so! You can all wait.
I've got important
business to discuss
Hey! Stop! Order, I say!
We're gonna do this
one at a time.
She's popular. Everyone
seems loves Rose.
Rock-paper-scissors,
people. Ready?
Now watch the master at work.
She goes the extra
step and makes sure
she knows the value of
whatever she's selling.
Good or bad,
she's always honest about it,
so everybody knows
they can trust her.
A regrettably rare
quality in a merchant.
Oh, hey, has anyone
seen Glenn around?
What? He hasn't shown yet?
But he's the one who told me
you were coming today.
I figured he would've
beat me here.
That is just so unlike him.
Glenn is a very stubborn man.
He names his own prices
and won't budge a bit,
no matter the market value.
That said, you can always trust
the quality of his goods,
so they're usually worth it.
So this Glenn--he's the guy
you wanted to introduce me to?
He sure is.
Glenn knows a lot about
the legend of the Shepherd.
I was hoping,
if I introduced you,
he might be willing
to negotiate his prices
a little bit, y'know?
[laughs nervously]
[ROSE] I thought getting
to meet someone out of legend
might soften him up for us.
Are you honestly
saying you brought
the Shepherd here
to help you haggle?
[LAILAH, MIKLEO sigh]
[SERGEI]
Excuse me!
[SPARROWFEATHER 14A]
Who are you? Stop there!
I'm here for Sorey the shepherd.
My name is Sergei Strelka.
Commander of the
Platinum Knights.
I seek the boy known as Sorey.
[RANCHER 14A]
Who's he want?
[SOREY]
You're looking for me?
[SERGEI]
Indeed, I am.
Please, Shepherd Sorey,
come quietly.
I'm required to detain you.
Care to explain why?
[SERGEI]
I was at Glaivend Basin.
I saw your power and now know
what you are capable of.
[SOREY] I didn't come here
intending to do harm to Rolance.
Even so, anybody with
the type of power you have
is a potential threat.
I can't sit idly by
while you are here.
You know. I don't buy it.
If you were at the
battle of Glaivend Basin,
then surely you know that
Sorey didn't kill anybody.
Sorry, who are you?
I'm the person in charge
of the building in which
you're currently trespassing.
I get that Rolance
is a military nation,
but it still has laws.
So how can you come
here and arrest Sorey
when he hasn't done
anything wrong?
He's simply too dangerous
to be left on his own.
[ROSE] Come on,
you're being ridiculous.
Sorey stopped a war
without killing anyone
and this is how he's treated?
Thanks, Rose.
Don't go, Sorey.
This bully here can't make you.
[SERGEI]
Even if what you say is true,
I still have a duty
to my country.
So, what do you propose?
Going to take on the Shepherd?
If that is how it must be.
Say, is anyone else
thirsty? I sure am.
So many people gathered
to welcome Rose back,
it's like a party. Why ruin
such a nice occasion?
Rose, what d'you say
we all have a drink?
Okay.
[MAVIN]
You heard her!
[RANCHER 14A]
Don't have to tell me twice!
[GRAIN FARMER 14A]
Rose, you're the best!
[BREWER 14A]
Don't mind if I do!
[ROSE]
I never said it was free!
[ROSE] I have to make
a living, you know!
Get out of my stores! I mean it!
Put those bottles down!
Come on, you big
moochers! Shoo, shoo!
Ugh, do you know
how much that one cost?
[MAVIN] There's a story
behind the Guchaga Twins.
Care to hear it?
[SOREY]
Of course.
They say you should
turn 'em to face each other.
then put 'em at opposite
ends of a room.
Supposedly all fighting
in between them stops.
Nice, eh? What do
you think, Shepherd?
Like the sound of that idea?
I love things like this.
I've explored ruins
ever since I was a kid.
This seems pretty heavy
for its size, though.
Oh, yeah?
Interesting.
I wonder if it's a statue
from Asgardian times.
It might have a great
technology embedded in it.
Something that's been long
hidden just waiting to be found.
But then how would
we unlock it. Uh...
[laughs] I kinda like you, kid.
You're fun to have around.
Too bad you're so busy being
a Shepherd and everything.
[SOREY]
You must know a lot of things,
for as much as you've travelled
Yeah. I'd say so.
Have you ever
heard anything about
how to purify a dragon?
A dragon, is it?
I've been lucky enough
in my long life
never to encounter
one of their kind before.
I hear there have been
sightings recently.
First in Ladylake
and then in Marlind.
[SOREY]
Yes, and Rayfalke Spiritcrest.
[MAVIN]
I see.
That's something
that hasn't happened
in the last hundred years.
They say we're in
an era of chaos,
the world plagued
with natural disasters
and unnatural darkness.
It's easy, these days,
to believe
we might truly
be facing an end.
[SOREY] If you have
even the smallest hint,
anything at all...
No, sorry.
[SOREY]
Oh.
However, I do know a story.
A long time ago, I met a man
who was called a Shepherd.
[gasps] Really?
[MAVIN]
I don't know if it'll help,
but I'll tell you
what he told me.
"Bad thoughts dwell inside
every person's heart.
If we call those
thoughts malevolence...
[MICHAEL] ...then it
exists within me, too."
The concept of malevolence
is so immense,
I don't know how my mind
could comprehend it.
There are many questions,
and the answers are unclear.
For example, if I do
harm to one person
in order to save many others,
is that a malevolent act?
Do we all embrace malevolence
the moment we admit
the existence of
a necessary evil?
Impossible question.
I could never answer it.
[SERGEI]
Exactly!
[SERGEI] It's unfair to ask
that kind of question.
There's just no way that
anybody could answer it!
What do they want?
We're imperfect people
doing the best we can
in a difficult time!
Oh?
I figured a knight like
you would see the world
in black and white,
not shades of gray.
You figured wrong.
I've sacrificed.
There are things
I've had to give up
in order to protect the things
I can never give up.
[SOREY]
Uh...
[SERGEI]
Ah!
What I'm trying to say is
that getting the job done
is about a lot more
than being tough.
[MAVIN laughs]
[SERGEI]
Hey! Where are you goin'?
Sorry, but I've got training,
and I can't skip it.
I'm not running off.
Hey, you--
Whoa, a little wobbly there.
You're a real lightweight,
aren't ya? Another?
[SOREY]
Sorry I'm late.
Rose?
[SOREY] Dezel. Where is
she heading off to?
[DEZEL] Somewhere our innocent
and pure Shepherd
doesn't need to know about.
I'll be protecting Rose tonight.
What did he mean by that?
[ROSE] Tonight, in the name
of the Scattered Bones.
We will confront the
Bishop Gasparo Leno.
We must put a stop
to the evil deeds
he has committed out
of a twisted sense
of self-importance.
[TEMPLE KNIGHTS groaning]
[TEMPLE KNIGHTS
grunting, groaning]
Who are you?
[AIGUILLE]
Greetings, Bishop.
We are the Scattered Bones.
You will answer our
questions. Are you ready?
Your questions? What is this?
[AIGUILLE] Are you saying
you are unwilling to answer?
No, I will. Go ahead.
[AIGUILLE]
You'll tell the truth?
Yes. I swear.
[AIGUILLE]
I have three questions for you.
First, tell me this.
What is the task of a bishop?
That's simple enough.
To guide and to lead, justly.
To ensure the people of this
city have a prosperous future.
I make all decisions
regarding my flock.
[AIGUILLE]
Second question.
You have amassed
a significant fortune
that you keep hidden.
Where did it come from?
What are you talking about?
I have no "hidden fortune!"
[AIGUILLE]
Is that so?
Then what is stashed
under this cathedral?
Shall we go look at it?
[GASPARO]
There's no need.
I'm afraid you have the
wrong idea, young man.
The age of chaos is upon us,
so I'm merely managing
the fortunes of Lastonbell's
citizens in preparation.
[AIGUILLE] Now we come
to our final question.
Deeper underground,
we found dozens of bodies.
Would you like to explain
what they are doing there?
If you're simply making
an emergency stockpile,
why silence the witnesses?
No, it wasn't me. I did
not kill those people!
[AIGUILLE] As you said,
it's your job to lead.
You are the one who makes
the final decisions.
[gasps]
[ROSE]
No more questions.
We're done here.
How do ya like
Lastonbell so far?
It's great, such a
vibrant and exciting city.
There are a lot of things
I've never seen before.
Hey, listen.
I'm gonna release
a new item soon.
Try it and give me your opinion?
Sure.
It's a mabo curry bun!
Great, I'll give it a try.
How about a bite for me?
So, what do ya think?
I feel like it's missing
a little something.
Delicious!
Such a pleasant aftertaste.
[EDNA]
Hmph. Not bad at all.
Eh. Maybe you could add
another spice in there.
Something like turmeric or
nutmeg to accent the flavor.
Sorey!
Oh, don't mind me,
just my opinion.
That's a brilliant idea!
Thanks for your input!
I'll try it now. Bye!
[ROSE]
Actually, there's one more thing
I need you to try for me.
I'll be right back with it.
You wait here.
Okay, sure.
Great!
That's Rose for you.
Always passionate
about business.
No kidding.
Next: "Wind Seraph, Dezel."
Look forward to it!