[MIKLEO]
About time you woke up.
We've been worried!
So, how are you feeling?
What's going on? What happened?
You've been unconscious
with a high fever
for three days.
Seriously?
When you became my vessel,
I think your body must
have gone into shock.
We're just lucky
Alisha saved you.
It could have been much worse.
She saved me?
Ah-- What happened to
her after the trial?
You're awake!
Alisha, you're safe!
I'm glad you're better.
We've all been so worried.
[SOREY]
Wow, that was a feast!
[ALISHA] I'd say you're
past the worst of it.
You can't be feeling too
poorly if you ate that much.
Plus, everything was delicious!
Thanks for taking care
of me these past few days
while I've been sick.
I owe you one!
No, I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
You pulled out the sacred blade,
just like the legend said.
I'm still not entirely
sure what you did next,
but I do know that
you saved us all.
It was the most incredible
thing I've ever seen.
It felt like
everything was going
to be all right.
Because you were there.
Does that sound silly?
Nah.
[ALISHA chuckles]
Anyway, there's something
I wanna give you.
As a token of gratitude
for everything you've done.
[door clicks]
It's perfect!
[laughs]
[ALISHA] The Shepherd's outfit
looks even better on you
than I thought it would.
I agree! You look
positively heroic, Sorey!
Oh, look, the pig's
wearing lipstick!
Just admit it: you're jealous
of how dashing I look.
I am nothing of
the sort, thank you.
[laughs]
[ALISHA]
Who are you talking to?
Are there Seraphim there?
Oh. Sure are.
This one here is Mikleo.
[MIKLEO grunts]
Hey! Uh--
Ah! Sorey!
[SOREY]
And this is Lailah.
The one everyone calls
the Lady of the Lake.
She's much better
looking than Mikleo.
I felt it when I met you.
Part of me knew you were
going to become the Shepherd.
Now here you are.
You can wield the sacred
blade and see the Seraphim.
but I feel powerless to help.
[LAILAH] But, Alisha,
you aren't powerless!
She can't hear us, you know.
[LAILAH growls]
Let's try something.
I want you to go over there
and hold Alisha's hand.
[SOREY]
Uh...
You're going to be a conduit.
A channel for our voices.
I'll send them to
Alisha through you.
Ah!
Alisha!
Do you think holding
your hand will help?
[SOREY]
Mm!
Hello, Alisha.
Can you hear me? I am Lailah.
[MIKLEO]
Doesn't seem to be working.
She can't hear a thing.
[LAILAH]
Hm...
Ah! All right, let's try
this. Close your eyes.
[SOREY]
Okay.
Uh... Hi, Alisha.
Can you hear my voice?
Still no luck.
[MIKLEO] Maybe Sorey isn't
concentrating hard enough.
How is this my fault?
Focus, Sorey! Keep your
eyes closed tight.
I think you may also
need to pinch your nose
and hold your breath.
[SOREY]
What?!
What's wrong?
Sorry. This might
look a little weird.
[inhales]
Hello, Alisha!
[gasps] I heard it!
That was a girl's voice!
You heard her?
And that sounded like a boy.
Was it Mikleo?
Uh. Y-Yeah, it is.
[ALISHA]
Greetings, Seraph Mikleo!
I humbly beg you to
forgive my rudeness.
[MIKLEO]
Uh-- Y-You've never struck me
as being particularly rude.
Please remember, most
humans can not see us.
But we Seraphim can
see into your hearts.
It is vital that your kind
not forget the Seraphim.
As we are forgotten, the
malevolence strengthens,
and with that,
calamity shall rise.
I heard you in Elysia.
I know that you haven't
forgotten about us, Alisha.
[SOREY] Seriously, there has
got to be a better way!
[gasps, inhales]
[SOREY pants]
Can we please try it
one more time?
[SOREY laughs nervously]
Seriously! There has
got to be a better way!
It'll get easier.
Blocking your senses
helps you concentrate.
As you gain more experience,
you may find it
becomes unnecessary.
Are you serious?
You mean that one day
I could actually deliver
the voice of the
Seraphim to everyone?
To the entire world?
No, Alisha's special.
She was born with talents that
most humans don't possess.
Oh, I see. Sorry, I guess
it isn't that simple.
Still. I was able to
talk to the Seraphim.
To hear their voices at last.
I can't tell you how
much that means to me.
It's like a dream.
All of your doubts are gone?
Yes!
[knocking, door clicks]
[MAID 5A]
Pardon me.
Forgive the intrusion,
Your Highness, but it's time.
I'll leave shortly. Thank you.
Well, I have to be on my way.
I'm sorry, but I'm
expected at the castle.
It's okay.
Why don't we go, too?
I think it would do you good
to explore the town a bit.
Huh?
[SOREY]
What's all this?
Word has spread quickly
about the arrival
of the Shepherd.
The flags started going up.
No one ordered it done.
In their hearts,
the people have been
waiting for the Shepherd.
They were just
too afraid to hope.
[ALISHA]
What is it? Is something wrong?
[SOREY gasps]
Well, uh...
Honestly, when you talk
about it like that,
it kinda starts
to make me nervous.
[MIKLEO]
Really?
I didn't think you were even
capable of getting nervous.
I am.
[SOREY]
Thanks for the ride.
That would've been a long walk.
It was no trouble at all.
I'll see you soon.
Let's have a look around.
[groans]
Are you okay?
Sorry, I just... felt kinda
sick all of a sudden.
But I'm sure it'll go away soon.
Earlier you said you
were feeling much better.
Were you just pretending?
I swear. I was doing
fine this morning.
But... it got worse
as we came into town.
[LAILAH]
It's the malevolence.
Your body is reacting to it.
Malevolence? Like home...
I think... it's a
separate malevolence.
From another source.
[LAILAH]
Where is the source?
I wish I could tell you,
but I don't know.
You are the Shepherd now.
You can do this. Try to feel it.
Close your eyes and concentrate.
[SOREY]
It's down there.
If you're up to it,
I think we should
go take a look.
Don't worry, I'll be okay.
I mean, I don't feel great,
but not nearly
as bad as before.
I want answers, too.
Why are these ruins so
full of malevolence?
[BARTLOW]
Your Highness.
We understand you
have been sheltering
the so-called Shepherd
at your private estate.
We ask you to hand him over.
Hand him over to you?
What does that mean?
[BARTLOW]
He has immense power.
It would be best if
he were kept someplace
where we can easily control him.
Surely you see that.
I'm afraid not.
You're willing to
defy the collective
will of the council?
Yes, if I must.
I will not put the
Shepherd into your hands.
[knocking]
--[hollow knocking]
--[gasps]
There's definitely a door here.
I agree.
But there's no sign of a
handle or a lock anywhere.
Can only mean one thing.
[SOREY] It means that we've
found a sealed door.
A sealed door? What do you mean?
Like a hidden passage.
I'd say there's something
behind this wall
that somebody doesn't
want people to know about.
If it is a kind of
seal, there should
be some key or trigger
nearby that'll open it.
How 'bout this?
Ha, ha!
Well, I'm impressed!
How did you even know
what to look for?
[SOREY] When you spend as
much time exploring ruins
as we have, you pick
up some stuff.
Look at this!
[SOREY] The crest of
Hyland's royal family.
[gasps]
Ah! Is something wrong?
I completely forgot to
give this back to Alisha.
[gasps] Wait, this might just
be what we need to open it.
Pretty lucky for us you're
such a scatterbrain.
[SOREY]
Let's go!
This is quite a place.
[SOREY]
Yeah.
Feel the malevolence?
It's so strong here.
[gasps]
A dragon statue?
Certainly wasn't expecting that.
Mm.
Aren't they supposed
to be bad luck?
They're far worse than bad luck.
They bring evil. Harbingers
of death and destruction.
You don't put up a statue
like that by accident.
There is definitely something
wrong with these ruins.
[SOREY] The malevolence
is a lot thicker here, too.
Is it the statue? Is that
where it's coming from?
[LAILAH]
No.
The statue's not the source.
It's coming from something else.
Something nearby.
It feels like... a Hellion.
--[bats squeaking]
--[wings flapping]
There!
[gasps] What is that?
[SOREY]
Bats?
[grunts]
[SOREY]
So many!
[MIKLEO]
A whole colony, and they've been
turned into Hellions.
Quick, Sorey!
I got it!
[SOREY grunting]
Hah! I got 'em!
[MIKLEO grunts]
Help Mikleo!
[SOREY grunts]
[SOREY]
You okay back there?
Yeah.
It's no good.
There are too many.
I have an idea.
Run toward the Hellions
and disperse them again.
Then I'll try to purify
them all using my fire.
Let's do this!
[SOREY yells]
Lailah!
Dance for me, bright flames,
in a crimson storm.
Flare Vortex!
That was awesome, Lailah!
Thank you.
Are you holding up all right?
Yeah. Not a scratch on me.
Maybe not, but I'm
sure you're tired.
It makes sense.
Being bonded to me must be
a drain on your own energy.
[SOREY]
Mm.
[LAILAH]
I can make it easier on you.
If you find yourself
getting tired,
simply ask me to go inside.
What's that mean?
[gasps]
Whoa!
[LAILAH]
Does it make sense now?
You can carry me inside
yourself, like this.
[SOREY]
Okay. I get it!
It's freaky, but I get it!
[SOREY pants]
[SOREY]
You coulda warned me first.
Also,
there may be times when you
will need to form a pact
with other Seraphim.
Such pacts will grant you
great power, as ours does.
But you must remember that
there will always be a cost.
Don't worry.
There's much to learn,
but you'll learn it.
[SOREY]
Thanks.
It does feel
overwhelming sometimes.
Sorey.
I feel it, too.
We may have got the bats,
but the malevolence
isn't gone yet.
Let's keep going.
Whatever the source is.
It's deeper inside.
It's so dark here.
[gasps]
What is this place? It's awful!
[LAILAH]
Now you see.
This is why the ruins
have been kept sealed.
I don't understand.
What happened?
You know, don't you?
These people were killed.
They rebelled against
their rulers,
and as punishment, they
were secretly slaughtered.
They left darkness
in their wake.
Desires, fierce, hate, all of
that has become the malevolence.
All of that has
spawned the Hellions.
But why here? Why weren't
they buried properly?
[gasps]
As I said, their deaths
were kept secret.
So many bodies.
There are things rulers
don't want the people to see.
[SOREY]
What about Alisha?
Does she know?
You knew this. You must have.
You brought me into
town to show me.
The Shepherd has
one ultimate goal,
and that is to purify the
source of all malevolence.
The Lord of Calamity.
I've never heard
that name before.
[LAILAH] The Lord of Calamity
is no ordinary person.
He is more dangerous
than you can imagine.
The amount of malevolence
he releases is great enough
that it can alter the very
workings of the world.
So defeating him
is my true goal.
Just tell me how and
I'll do anything I can.
[LAILAH] There is still
so much you do not know.
If you were to encounter
the Lord of Calamity now,
you would simply be engulfed
by the malevolence.
I'm sorry.
I can help by guiding you,
but I can't tell you what to do.
That's an answer you're going
to have to find for yourself.
And how do I do that?
[LAILAH]
Travel the world.
Learn about it and yourself.
Seek knowledge.
When the time comes,
when you have discovered
your own answer,
then you will be ready
to shatter malevolence.
Should be simple enough as long
as you don't overthink it.
You just go around the
world learning about stuff.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIKLEO]
It's wet. Everywhere.
[SOREY]
But how? Where'd it come from?
[water splashing]
Can't be...
This is malevolence.
It's gotten so thick, the earth
has become drenched with it.
We need to get above
ground. Quickly!
[LAILAH gasps]
The ceiling! It's caving in!
[grunts]
We gotta go!
It hurts. The earth suffers.
The malevolence has poisoned it,
and now it's writhing in agony.
We should run faster.
Yeah!
[SOREY grunts]
Sorey!
[yelps]
[gasps]
[SOREY]
Thanks, you two. That was close.
We must keep moving!
Lailah!
Is the malevolence causing
this storm, as well?
Yes! But it's strong.
Too strong to be
ordinary malevolence.
Sorey, look! There!
[gasps]
[MALTRAN]
This may be the most stubborn
I have ever seen you.
And that's saying something.
I know I'm making
things difficult.
[MALTRAN] Don't worry,
I'm not scolding you.
Your integrity helps
to keep Ladylake strong
in this time of
chaos and despair.
I'm proud of you for it.
You realize...
...Bartlow and the others on
the council want the Shepherd,
but that's not their endgame.
Yes.
I'm the one they're truly after.
Their goal is to
remove me from power.
If you know, there's not
much else I need to say.
However, I do wish
I knew what Bartlow's
next move is going to be.
I think he'll
send me to Marlind.
and if that's what he wants
to do, I'll accept it.
[ALISHA] The sickness is hitting
them hard, and they need help.
If someone must go
to offer them aid,
it might as well be me,
as a representative
of the royal family.
[MALTRAN] You don't have
to carry every burden.
Try to remember that.
One person can only
do so much on her own.
Yes, Master.
--[thunder booming]
--[wind howling]
The winds are unusually
strong tonight.
I hope they don't
cause much damage.
[gasps]
Alisha!
No, it can't be!
Looks like we're
taking a little break!
So we're going to a hot spring.
It'll be nice and relaxing
[LAILAH]
Sorey, Mikleo, I'm here.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Thats okay. So, ready to go?
Yes. Well, almost.
We should do the preview
first, don't you think?
[SOREY, MIKLEO]
The preview?
Yes.
For this show,
Tales of Zestiria the X ?
Right?
Yes.
Wait. I was pretty sure we
were taking a break next week.
So, Lailah.
Do you know what the
next episode is about?
♪ La, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la. ♪
Hey. That's not an answer.
I don't know if I like this.
Sorey, you don't think we're
being written out of the show,
do you?
Don't be so paranoid.
Of course we aren't.
Lailah's just being mysterious.
You know, building suspense,
that sorta thing.
Okay.
Now, let's go.
Lailah, hurry up or
we'll leave without you.
Wait. I'll just be a second.
Next week:
"The Dawn of Chaos."
Look forward to it!
I still don't like this.