[ALISHA] Tell me!
Please, are you a Shepherd?
[gasps]
[SOREY]
Nope. Just a regular human.
[ALISHA]
Oh, I thought maybe...
Well...
[SOREY]
Sorry.
You're human too, right?
This is the first time
I've ever seen
another of our kind up here.
[gasps]
This place--
Do you know if it was once
called the Capital of Seraphim?
I think so.
Well, if that's the case,
there should be a Shephard here!
[SOREY]
Mm-mm.
There's nobody else.
I did find a mural, though.
Of the Shephard
raising the holy blade.
[ALISHA]
Nothing but a mural?
Then I guess it really was
just a fairy tale after all.
The world can't be saved.
The darkness wins.
Bad idea.
You'll get in trouble
for letting a human in.
She needs help.
What do you expect me to do,
just ignore someone in danger?
Be reasonable.
She won't even
tell you her name.
Don't you think
there's something
a little bit strange about that?
She must have her reasons.
She seems like a
nice enough person.
Thank you for helping me.
Oh, no! Don't worry
about it, really!
I just hope you're ready.
Gramps is not gonna be happy.
Ah...
[ALISHA]
Is something wrong?
Uh-- No, not at all.
Come on, let's go.
Even when she's
looking right at me,
she doesn't see anything.
It's exactly like
Gramps said, then.
What an incredibly
beautiful place!
Is this truly the
home of the Seraphim?
So you really do call
them Seraphim, then?
Why, is there something
wrong with that name?
[SOREY]
Mm-mm.
Gods? Spirits? Monsters?
What are these shapeless
supernatural beings?
Out of reverence and fear,
humans dubbed them the Seraphim.
I read that somewhere.
[ALISHA]
In the Celestial Record !
You've read it, too?
You mean...
You've heard about it?
I have. I've read it many times.
Sorey, if you don't
mind me asking,
where exactly are you taking me?
My village. Elysia.
[ALISHA]
Elysia...
I'm gonna go report to Gramps.
I guess we can't just keep
this between us, can we?
[MIKLEO]
I'll see you later, Sorey.
[SOREY sighs]
Huh?
[laughs]
Everyone, let me introduce...
...a new friend.
Seraphim, please!
I can't see you,
but if you are here,
I ask that you heed my words!
As prophesized, the world
has been enshrouded by darkness.
Chaos and disaster reign
throughout the land.
We humans are trying,
but we can't do this alone.
If we're going
to save the world,
we need the help
of your kind as well.
Please give me whatever
aid is in your power.
Without you, the world
will be lost!
I beg you! Please, seraphim!
Please won't you answer me?
Sorey.
Send her back where she belongs.
She'll only bring trouble.
[GRAMPS]
You reckless idiot!
What were you thinking,
bringing a human into
our lands like that?
But, Gramps...
You did promise that
you'd here him out.
At least a little.
Very well.
Sorey, would you care
to explain to me why
you so egregiously
broke the rules?
[SOREY] I'm sorry. But I
couldn't just leave her.
[GRAMPS sighs]
You know you cannot undo
what has already been done.
However, you must send her back
to the realm below at once,
do you understand me?
For the good of
all who live here,
she cannot be allowed to stay.
Humans bring only disaster
to our lands--you know that.
Yeah, but... I'm human, too.
However, you've lived
among us for a long time
and acquired the ability
to see us and speak to us.
That isn't something any
ordinary human can do.
This girl that you've brought
to our village isn't like you.
She doesn't belong here,
and if you just think about it
for a bit, you'll
realize I'm right.
[SOREY]
I don't understand!
If that's how you really
feel, then why did you
give me the Celestial
Record to read?
Sorey...
It talks about a better past.
Things weren't always like this.
Humans and Seraphim used
to live happily together!
Why can't we go back to that?
[GRAMPS]
Because the past is the past.
Still, she believes in Seraphim,
and she asked for help.
[GRAMPS sighs]
I'm sorry about my
outburst earlier today.
Talking at thin air
like the Seraphim
actually exist.
You must have
thought I was crazy.
Mm, no.
[SOREY] Tell me about you.
Where do you live?
[ALISHA]
The capital.
Capital?
The capital city of Hyland.
Called Ladylake.
That sounds familiar somehow.
Ah! Of course! The legend
of the sacred blade!
The blade is protected
by the Lady of the Lake,
and whoever pulls it out
becomes the Shepherd!
Yes.
Except the legend's never
actually come true.
No one has pulled
the blade free.
[SOREY] What are you doing?
Lurking around out here?
[MIKLEO]
Gramps sent me with a message.
He says there's no knowing when
the human will cause a disaster.
However,
chasing her out could
cause trouble as well.
Human beings are unpredictable
and can be very dangerous
when they're provoked.
Therefore, he says
that she can stay
until she's ready to leave.
Happy now?
[SOREY] Ha! Awesome!
Tell Gramps I said thanks.
And you, too. Thanks a lot!
I know why he helped
the girl, Mikleo.
Sorey's a kind and honest
boy, with a good heart.
That's what worries me.
Too much kindness
can lead to trouble.
[SOREY]
Steady.
Got it!
It certainly is pretty here.
Have you lived in this
village for your entire life?
[SOREY]
Mm-hm! That's right.
This place is the only
home I've ever known.
[ALISHA]
Really?
It must be difficult,
living on your own like this.
[gasps]
[SOREY]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just had the feeling
I was being watched
for a moment there.
[SOREY]
Oh. Maybe there's someone here
who wants to know
more about you.
[ALISHA chuckles]
It's nice of you to humor me.
Playing along.
Pretending that there
actually are Seraphim here.
[ALISHA gasps, pants]
What was it?
Nightmare. But I'm fine now.
[SOREY]
Oh. Good, I'm glad.
[ALISHA]
That's the Celestial Record .
[SOREY] Mm-hm. I must have
lost count of how many times
I've read it since I was a kid.
It's been a dream of mine
to travel the world
and visit all the ruins I can.
Of course,
most readers of the
Celestial Record say that.
We all dream of
wandering the world.
Except, now...
...the way things
have been lately,
doing that is likely
to get you killed.
[ALISHA] For a while now,
incomprehensible calamities
have been occurring
throughout Hyland.
[SOREY]
Calamities?
[ALISHA]
Recently,
I was directly involved in one.
Although I still have
a hard time believing
everything that happened.
I'm sorry.
A large number of people died,
and I couldn't do
anything to help them.
Several of my friends
were among the dead.
I can't seem to get the
image of those events
out of my mind.
The legend. When darkness
engulfs the world,
the Shepherd will appear
to restore the light.
So that means you're here
hoping to find the Shepherd?
I am. The legends were the
only hope that I had left.
And now I don't even have that.
[ALISHA]
None of what they say is real.
They're nothing but fairy tales.
[sighs]
[ALISHA whimpers, cries]
[knocking]
[SOREY]
Mikleo!
Sorey?
[SOREY]
Finally! I'm sorry!
But I need it back, right now!
Wait. Need what?
Huh?
This looks like...
Thanks, Gramps.
[GRAMPS exhales]
[SOREY]
Come on! Over here.
[ALISHA]
A mural?
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
It is.
I've never seen one
this grand before.
[SOREY] If it was really
all just a fairy tale,
do you think someone would
bother making something
this awesome about it?
And let's not forget about
the huge temple, either.
I don't know.
And while exploring,
I found this!
The Mark of the Shepherd!
[SOREY]
The Shepherd is real!
More than just a legend!
So, you see, there's
still hope after all.
[gasps]
Steady...!
[SOREY] If the world below
is being engulfed in darkness
like you said,
the Shepherd will arrive.
The legend will come true.
I don't doubt it for a second.
You believe.
You really do believe what
the Celestial Record says.
I do.
You told me your dream.
Well, mine is to see a world
in which humans and Seraphim
live happily together again.
I think it's possible.
People like us just have to want
it enough to make it happen.
Here, you should take this.
Keep it as a reminder that
the Shepherd will come.
Thanks so much for this.
And I'll try to have faith.
Faith that someone will
pull out the sacred blade
and lead us out
of this darkness.
Are you sure you'll be able
to find your way home?
[ALISHA]
Yes.
All right then.
Take care.
You truly have
been a great help.
Alisha.
Huh?
[ALISHA] That's my name.
It's Alicia Diphda.
You were willing to help me
without knowing who I am
or even asking my name.
And I was too
cowardly to tell you.
As a knight, that
was shameful of me.
Sorey. I ask for
your forgiveness.
[SOREY]
Uh-- It's no big deal, really!
[ALISHA]
And before I go.
there is one more thing
I would like to admit.
I believe there are
Seraphim here in Elysia.
[gasps] You really do?
[ALISHA] They didn't respond
to my words, it's true.
And although they can't be
seen, I felt their presence.
To tell you the truth,
I can still feel it now.
[ALISHA]
The Sacred Blade Festival
will begin soon in Ladylake.
It will feature the
Rite of the Warrior
as it's depicted in the
legend of the Shepherd.
Sorey, you should
consider participating.
[gasps]
[ALISHA]
And while I thank you,
I believe you should
hold onto this instead.
But why?
Because of what you said.
That you dream
of a world in which
Seraphim and humans can coexist.
That sounds right
to me, somehow.
Do you know what I mean?
Like something...
...the Shepherd out
of legend would say.
[ALISHA]
Goodbye, Sorey.
Sorey...
[GRAMPS gasps]
What's wrong?
[GRAMPS]
Somebody has invaded my domain.
The intruder masks his presence.
Listen, everyone!
I've detected an intruder.
Quite possibly a Hellion.
Search, and be ready to fight!
Let's get going!
Gotcha!
[growls]
See that!
We need to hurry!
[BOTH gasp]
[gagging]
[gasps] Let him go!
[LUNARRE]
Interesting.
I was under the
impression that only
the main course was
supposed to be here.
And now it looks like
there are two more
annoyances to deal with.
A Hellion!
This is no place for
worthless filth like you.
Leave at once!
[LUNARRE laughs]
[LUNARRE]
And how exactly do you think
you're going to
make me, do that?
If you try it, you'll only
end up like this one.
[grunts]
Come here and I'll show you!
[laughing]
[SOREY grunts]
[LUNARRE laughing]
[yells]
[LUNARRE laughs]
Water. Pierce the enemy!
Sorey, stand back!
[LUNARRE laughing]
[growls]
[LUNARRE groans]
[LUNARRE grunts]
[LUNARRE growls]
He's not hurt at all?
[SOREY gasps]
[gasps]
[SOREY]
Gramps?
Be gone.
Leave from here, evil one.
Huh?
[LUNARRE]
Heh. Well,
I've already wasted
enough time here,
and I wouldn't want the
main course to get away.
[SOREY]
Gramps... I'm sorry.
I brought that
human into Elysia,
and then that thing came, too.
This was all my fault.
No, it isn't.
That Hellion is not
your responsibility.
Nor was it hers,
for that matter.
Mikleo is right in this, Sorey.
He is?
[GRAMPS] Keeping the
human out of our lands
might have prevented the
evil one from entering.
But that must not be
our sole consideration.
It is a selfish impulse
to believe that only
our own safety matters.
For good or ill,
peace in this realm
is connected to
the outside world.
We must not allow
ourselves to forget that.
That thing...
I've already wasted
enough time here,
and I wouldn't want the
main course to get away.
[gasps]
What he said about
someone getting away--
that must be the reason why
he was here in the first place.
Because he's after Alisha.
[SOREY] They'll probably
be mad at me for leaving
without saying anything...
[SOREY]
I'm sorry, everyone!
Okay!
[MIKLEO]
Going somewhere?
[gasps]
How did you know I was leaving?
Maybe because I'm not an idiot.
Give me some credit.
Why're you here?
Because of what
that Hellion said.
It seems pretty clear that
he's hunting after Alisha.
[SOREY]
So you picked up on that, too.
[MIKLEO]
Of course. Look at this.
What is it?
Gramps sent me
back to the ruins.
He wanted me to look around
for any clues about Alisha.
That's the symbol of
the royal family of Hyland.
This Alisha Diphda--
she's no ordinary knight.
Having this should help.
We can use it to
find her in Ladylake.
Something tells me
you hadn't thought--
[SOREY]
You're coming, too?!
I'm so glad I'm gonna
have you with me.
I couldn't let you go
out in the world alone.
It's too dangerous out there
for someone as naive as you.
[SOREY] I bet Gramps is
pretty mad, though, huh?
[MIKLEO]
Actually, he sent a message.
"Walk the path you believe in
and live your life
to the fullest.
Do these things, and I know
you will not go astray."
[gasps, laughs]
[SOREY]
The world's waiting. Lets go!
Wow, the capital,
home of the legendary
Lady of the Lake! Amazing!
Look at all the people!
Indeed, it's very impressive.
According to legend,
someone's going to pull out
the Sacred Blade and
become the Shepherd.
I wonder what they'll be like.
Probably a wise man like Gramps.
Someone serious and dignified.
Or, it could be
a girl, like Alisha.
She's pretty amazing.
No one would see that coming.
[MIKLEO]
Hmm. I don't know.
Whoever it is will
have to be strong,
not to mention courageous
if they're gonna be fighting
all those Hellions.
I guess so.
So... I'd say that
rules you out, then.
What do you mean?
It could totally be me!
Not a chance.
That's just mean!
If it is me, how
will you apologize?
Well, let me think...
How 'bout I make you a whole
bunch of vanilla ice cream?
Nope.
It'll take a lot more than that
to forget your cruel insult.
Fine, then what do you want?
You have to deliver
all the Previews
with a funny face.
Huh?
Next time:
"Mikleo's Funny Face."
Look forward to it!
No! That's not the title!