[SERGEI]
Welcome, Sorey.
[SOREY]
Sergei, hey.
I'm glad to see
that you're safe.
Your disappearance
was so sudden.
I was worried about you.
I'm happy to see
that you're free.
Pleasant though Groodman's
hospitality may be,
I grew a bit tired of it.
Looks big.
Yes, a fitting home for
Emperor Doran of Rolance.
[SOREY] So, this is where
the emperor lives?
Indeed, and as such, this
estate is beyond the reach
of Groodman and his
Blue Storm Knights.
Your majesty.
[DORAN]
You must be the Shepherd.
[SOREY]
I am.
It's an honor to meet you.
The honor is mine.
Thank you for travelling
so far to aid us.
You're welcome in Rolance,
as are your friends.
Please, your majesty.
There was no need
for you to come out in
the rain at this hour.
Shall we go inside?
[DORAN]
Don't concern yourself, Sergei.
I invited the Shepherd
here, after all.
Greeting him is the
least I could do.
Please, Shepherd, follow me.
[EGUILLE] Well, here we are,
honored guests of the emperor,
ruler of Rolance, and Prince
Konan's father. What now?
Nothing. Konan's dead.
We have our revenge.
I don't care about
what happens next.
[EGUILLE]
How can you say that?
What's happened to you?
They've taken the
Shepherd to another room.
I wonder what the emperor
wants to talk about.
[door opens]
Much nicer in here, yes?
Yes, thank you.
Sir Shepherd, I have a question.
Looking at Rolance
from your persepctive,
how does it appear to be doing?
To be honest, sir,
not very well.
[DORAN] You haven't been
here long. Are you certain?
Yes.
[DORAN] And is malevolence
to blame for it?
[gasps]
[SOREY]
Hold on, Your Majesty.
Are you saying you
can see malevolence?
[DORAN]
No, it is invisible to my eyes.
[SOREY] Then how could
you have known to ask?
The night is still young.
Perhaps we can chat a while.
The imperial family
of Rolance has worked
tirelessly over the generations
to ensure that our lineage
would remain unbroken.
We fight to remain in power
not out of ambition and avarice,
but a sense of duty
to preserve the empire
we were destined to lead.
There's a legend regarding
the history of the world
known only to the
imperial family.
We must protect that
secret and pass it on.
It's not a task we take lightly.
From the legend,
we've learned a great deal.
It taught us of malevolence.
Though, like most, we cannot
see it with our own eyes.
Where did you first
hear it--this legend?
[DORAN]
How we came to learn it
is its own tale.
Tell me, Shepherd.
On your travels, have you
heard of the Storyteller?
[gasps] Yeah, Mavin!
[DORAN]
Indeed.
Mavin is actually a title
given to the Storytellers
that have existed
since ancient times.
Years ago, they broke an oath
when they revealed a secret
to my family, one that told much
about how the world came
to be what it is now.
The legend you mentioned before.
The Storytellers' secret
had something to do
with malevolence?
[DORAN]
Yes.
It's a tale that goes back
several thousand years.
[DORAN]
According to the Storytellers,
someone attempted to rid
the world of malevolence
by stripping the emotions
from all of humanity.
As we know,
though malevolence is
born of human emotions,
it is invisible to
the human eye, and so,
all those years ago,
it had spread through
the world quickly,
unnoticed by the very people
whose hearts had
given rise to it.
But then, something happened
that would change the
course of the world.
[DORAN] To combat the plague
that had infected the world,
a figure who is known now only
in legend performed a ritual.
The ritual was designed
to steal all human emotion
in hopes of
eliminating malevolence.
But one person
remained untouched.
According to the legend,
that person's name
was Velvet Crowe.
Please, Your Majesty, go on.
Crowe hated the one who
had performed the ritual.
That hatred became
an all-consuming fire.
So it began.
Crowe's rage gave rise to
this era, one rife with chaos.
Hey, Dezel, you there?
Right here.
I don't like it,
being blind to so much.
Is there some way I can
learn to see malevolence?
[DEZEL]
Why would you wanna do that?
All I've ever wanted
is to help the weak.
I still do.
If you're serious,
there is a way.
At ease, soldier.
I'm Groodman, captain of
the Blue Storm Knights.
I request an audience
with the emperor.
In truth, what I seek
is an end to the conflict.
Doesn't matter how
many wars you win,
another one always
seems to follow.
I want what is best for my
empire, and that means peace.
We've received word of a
growing conflict in Hyland,
where civil war has
apparently broken out.
From the reports,
it seems Princess Alisha
has been arrested for treason.
How can that be?
[knocking]
Enter.
[SERGEI]
Pardon me.
Sire. Captain Groodman
of the Blue Storm Knights
is here requesting
an audience with you.
[DORAN]
I'm rather popular tonight...
All right. What's the plan?
Back to Hyland?
[whispering] First we have
to see to Pendrago.
Believe me, I'm
worried about Alisha,
but I can't leave Rolance
when it's in this much danger.
Your Majesty.
Are you leaving us?
Yes. Thank you for everything.
I must hurry.
We need to cleanse
Pendrago of malevolence
as quickly as we can.
[DORAN]
In that case,
I hope you will
allow me to escort you.
Uh...
You see.
I've heard that the cathedral's
doors have been barred.
Why would that be?
Unless the church
has something to hide.
If you wish to begin
your investigation there,
I suspect that my presence
may be of some use to you.
Sergei, speak with Groodman.
Let's allow him and
his Blue Storm Knights
to witness what happens.
Sire!
So, is that acceptable to you?
[gasps]
What is it?
[ROSE]
Sorey.
We need to talk.
[ROSE]
All right, listen.
I want to negotiate
a deal with you.
[SOREY]
A deal?
[ROSE]
Mm-hm.
There is something I want
that only you can give me.
In return, of course, I mean
to offer you something, as well.
It would be a fair deal.
[SOREY]
Hm.
You know what I do now.
I kill people--those who
spread evil. All this time,
I believed what I was
doing was righteous.
Thought I was making
the world a better place.
But...
I'm beginning to see that some
things can't be fixed that way.
Malevolence--
that's what's tearing
the world apart right now.
But, how am I supposed
to fight something
if I can't even see
it with my own eyes?
Turns out there's a way.
If I want to continue to change
the world for the better,
I must become your Squire.
I know the Shepherd
is the ultimate savior,
but still, no matter how
great your powers may be,
you're just one person.
Even you must need
help sometimes.
A Squire? You sure?
It makes sense.
I would get to continue
my fight, and in return,
you would have my support.
Tell me all there is to know
about becoming a Squire.
All the benefits and hardships.
[LAILAH] Actually, it might be
better for me to answer that.
Lailah.
[gasps] You're sitting
right there, aren't you?
[LAILAH]
Listen carefully.
You say that what you want is to
fight the darkness in the world
and if you choose to
become Sorey's Squire,
you would be abe to do
all that and more.
[ROSE] Mm-hm. I got
that part on my own.
What else?
Power has it's cost.
The task is to aid Sorey.
As his Squire, you'd
help purify malevolence.
But even with help,
he may yet fail.
He could die before
reaching his goal.
And if Sorey's life were
lost, yours would be, too.
That's the cost.
[LAILAH]
Yes.
With the pact comes great power,
but the price you pay
is your life.
I didn't know about that!
It's a greater price than
I would ask anyone to pay.
Alisha... She should've
known the risks.
But she did.
Alisha knew exactly
what she was getting into.
She knew it might cost her life.
But even with all these
dangers, she still insisted.
All right, is there
anything else?
There is more.
You might see the power you'll
be granted as a benefit.
That's not always the case.
Sometimes, you'll find it
more of a burden.
Get to the point already.
Among the Squire's
powers is the ability
to take some of the malevolence
that the Shepard accepts.
But there's no guarantee
that it won't be far more
than you can handle.
How does it work?
During purification,
the Shepherd becomes a vessel.
He accepts malevolence inside
him, and if he has a Squire,
they can assume
a portion of this
after it has passed through him.
I gotta say, you're
not makin' the job
sound terribly attractive.
Anything else I should know?
No. That's more
than enough for now.
All right.
It sounds like
a fair arrangement.
What do ya say, Sorey? You in?
There is one more thing
you should know, though.
With each additional Squire,
the burden on you will increase.
Though, given your
current powers,
I don't think you'll
experience major difficulties.
[SOREY]
Tell me, Rose.
When you look out at the city,
what does it make you feel?
I don't really know.
I guess it's pretty
gloomy out there.
Right now, my chest feels tight
and my every sense is on fire.
My insides are all twisted up.
This isn't something
I wanna force on anyone,
and if I'd understood before,
I wouldn't have.
I should bear this
pain on my own.
[ROSE]
Should you?
See, when I know there's
a threat out there,
I always prefer
to face it head-on.
I'm not the only one.
I'd bet our princess friend
would say the same thing.
[grunts]
[LAILAH]
The emperor was right.
It's coming from the cathedral.
[SOREY]
Yeah.
It's thick. Practically solid.
So, is this malevolence?
You can feel it now, right?
I don't know how to explain,
something just seems wrong.
She feels it. She can
sense the malevolence.
It resonates within her.
Consider it, Sorey.
If she becomes your Squire,
she could greatly
enhance your powers.
[SOREY]
Lailah.
Yes?
I didn't understand the price
she would have to pay.
There's no way I can
ask this of her.
But...
If she believes this is the
way to fulfill her purpose,
so be it.
Good.
Well, Shepherd?
[SOREY]
Your Majesty.
Is this the place
you're looking for?
Yes. This is it.
There's darkness within.
[MASEDRA]
Your Majesty. I beg your pardon.
It has been so long.
How may I serve you today?
Hello, Masedra.
To start, drop the
pretense of respect.
It doesn't suit you.
I'm here accompanying
the Shepherd,
who has graciously traveled
to our land to lend us his aid.
[MASEDRA] What an honor
to meet you, Shepherd.
Welcome to the
capital of Rolance
and to Pendrago's
great cathedral.
I am its leader, Masedra.
Something's wrong here.
Please hurry. There's no time.
Right.
We'd like to see inside
the cathedral, please.
Unfortunately, the interior
is off-limits at the moment.
Perhaps I can offer you
a tour of the grounds
or the perimeter
buildings instead?
[DORAN]
Masedra!
This is not a request.
I'm sorry. I can't...
Enough already!
[MASEDRA yelps]
[SOREY]
Let's go!
Stop!
It's coming from over there.
[SOREY]
This is it.
[gasps]
[ROSE gasps]
[ROSE]
What is that?
It was a dragon.
It's gone now. There's
no more life in it.
[LAILAH]
The malevolence is astounding.
Even though it has
passed into death,
it still pours from the dragon.
There's so much pain here.
Even death and time
couldn't erase it.
Too strong.
Sorey, what are you
going to do with it?
Purify it.
I don't know if it'll
work, but I have to try.
Not alone.
If you and Rose work
together, perhaps then.
Not happening.
[LAILAH] If she became your
Squire, she could help you.
That's a separate
discussion entirely.
I'll do this on my own.
What do you see here?
What does this place look
like through your eyes?
It's a fog.
A fiery mist
surrounding everything.
Malevolence.
[ROSE]
Hearing you describe it,
it sounds pretty
terrifying, actually,
but no matter how
frightening it may be,
I still wanna see it.
You're sure?
Basically, my job would
be to help you out
and keep you from dying.
Oh, and, if there's
too much of it,
take some of the excess
malevolence off your hands.
Does that about cover it?
I agree to the terms.
So, we have ourselves a deal.
Do I get one of those
true names now?
How do you know about the--
All right, then.
But, you can still take
some time to think it over.
I don't need to.
It won't be easy.
I don't expect it
to be. It's okay.
'Cause the most important
things in life never are.
Ready, Lailah?
Yes.
Now, please grant
Rose a true name.
You are Wilkis Wilk.
[ROSE gasps]
This is what you were seeing?
To get rid of it,
I must purify the dragon.
Will you carry the
malevolence with me?
Yes, I will. Go.
Hear me, lost soul.
The Shepherd has come
to guide you to eternal rest.
[yells]
[gasps]
[grunts, yelps]
Sorey!
Grab hold.
I need to send some of
the malevolence your way.
Yeah, got it.
[BOTH grunting]
Just stay focused.
We'll hold the others off.
How long is this
going to take, anyway?
Ha! Thanks a lot, guys!
Rose, let's go!
Right!
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH yelling]
Incredible.
This is the Shepherd's work?
[SOREY panting]
You okay?
[DEZEL]
Rose!
We should never have
asked her to try
against so much malevolence.
Dragons are fierce
even in death.
No! She can't die!
[ROSE]
Come on.
You guys really think
it's that easy to kill me?
No way!
You're safe.
Hey, Dezel. So that's
what you look like.
[ROSE grunts]
Jeez, I'm sore all over.
That was tough.
And you usually handle
this type of thing alone?
You deserve a
medal or something.
You, too.
[ALISHA]
Can you hear me?
Sorey.
[DEZEL gasps]
Was that Alisha?
[ALISHA]
Can you hear my voice?
Yes. I hear you.
Is something wrong?
I'm listening.
Can you hear me?
Yes. Loud and clear.
I'm glad I found you.
I'm with allies on the
outskirts of Ladylake.
I heard a rumor that
you'd been arrested.
[ALISHA]
I'm free for now.
That's a relief.
[ALISHA] However, Bartlow has
charged me with treason.
My friends and I are fugitives.
More importantly,
Ladylake is in trouble.
I need your help, Sorey.
Can you come immediately?
It's bad. There's
another tornado!
A tornado? Alisha?
It's time to go, Sorey.
The princess is waiting.
Right. Let's go.
We ride for Hyland.
So, Mikleo, can you make
soft-serve ice cream?
Sure can.
Cool!
Let's open an ice cream shop
together and make a fortune.
Yeah, maybe no.
[EDNA]
Excuse me, as Mibo's manager,
all business deals need
to be approved by me.
I did not hire you
as my manager.
It'll be 10,000 gald a month.
Mibo is basically an
ice cream machine on two legs.
I would call that a fair price.
Why aren't you listening to me?
That's a ridiculous price.
Six thousand.
Nine thousand.
Seven thousand.
Eight thousand.
That's my final offer.
Take it or leave it.
I suppose I could
go as high as 7,500,
but that is my absolute ceiling.
[EDNA]
Hm.
[ROSE]
Hm...
It looks like we have a deal.
Take good care of Mibo!
Don't worry, I will.
I'll make him into a real man.
That's it! This
conversation's over!
Next time: "Ladylake."
Look forward to it!
'Kay! Time to get down
to business, Mikleo!
Pretty sure I said no, Rose.