Lailah! Inside the tornado!
Oh no.
Is that...?
It looks like a dragon.
[MIKLEO]
It's moving!
[MALTRAN]
Alisha! Hurry!
Get inside!
It's coming this way!
[ALISHA]
Guards! Where are the guards?
[MIKLEO]
It's heading towards the castle.
Alisha.
Anyone who seeks shelter
inside the castle
will be granted it, understood?
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, ma'am!
He's here.
Sorey!
[LAILAH]
You can't fight that.
She's right. It's too dangerous!
There's something about it.
I'm not sure what,
just something.
What's that mean?
Is it really gone?
[MIKLEO]
Dragons. Calamity incarnate.
Harbingers of death
and destruction.
That dragon, how was it formed?
Is it a product of malevolence?
Yes. Malevolence.
It's almost too
horrifying to believe.
An actual dragon,
right here in Ladylake.
[ALISHA]
Sorey!
[SOREY]
Alisha!
You saved us. We owe you
our lives twice over.
Oh, no, it wasn't actually...
Sorey. Look down there.
[MAN A] Did you see that?
The tornado is gone!
[MAN B] I can't believe it!
He really saved us!
[MAN C]
Shepherd!
[MAN D]
Thank you, Shepherd!
[SOREY]
Wait, hold on!
Uh... You don't understand.
It just went away. I--
[BARTLOW]
Oh, Lord Shepherd!
How can we ever thank you?
That dragon might've killed us
all had you not used your powers
to chase it away from the city.
[SOREY]
I really didn't do anything.
[BARTLOW chuckles]
[BARTLOW]
You're too modest, surely.
Now, Lord Shepherd,
if you will permit me,
I have a small request.
I would like to get
to know you better.
Perhaps we could share a meal
together and speak more.
I'd be honored to have you.
What's this about?
What are you up to?
Why, nothing. Such a
strange thing to ask.
The Shepherd is weary.
I am simply offering
my hospitality
so he can rest after the
trials of the past few days.
That's nice of you. I accept.
[BARTLOW chuckles]
[BARTLOW] The Shepherd has
accepted my invitation
to remain in the city!
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Sorey.
How 'bout you?
Can you come along, too?
[SOREY]
Sorry, can we stop the carriage?
It's awful.
Yes.
[LAILAH] Ladylake hasn't
been completely consumed
by malevolence yet.
But it's only a matter of time.
The darkness grows.
[SOREY]
We have to do something.
[OFFICER A] Welcome,
Lord Shepherd. It is an honor.
Oh.
If you will remain in the
carriage, Princess Alisha,
it will escort you.
Escort me?
[OFFICER A]
It will take you directly
to the palace, Your Highness.
The king wishes to speak
with you immediately.
--I haven't heard an--
--[OFFICER A] We must hurry.
[OFFICER A] You don't want
to keep the king waiting.
It appears that someone
doesn't want Alisha
to be present for this.
Sorry. I have to go now.
It's all right. I understand.
Please follow me, Sir.
[BARTLOW]
Does the food look satisfactory?
[SOREY]
Yes, thank you.
Forgive an old man
his curiosity,
but what's your connection
to the princess?
I'd say we're friends.
How fortunate.
We haven't known each other
long, but I trust her already.
I'm really glad I met Alisha.
Yes.
And what about you and I?
Do you think we might
become friends?
So this is all
about friendship?
Yes.
Heh. Not what I was expecting.
Let us toast to friendship.
[MIKLEO]
Sorey.
Be careful of what he gives you.
It's good.
Oh, wow. So good!
It's a specialty here in Hyland.
And one of our chief exports.
Though production has
been severely limited
as recent disasters have
taken a toll on the harvests.
What did you want to talk about?
I was merely wondering
about your future plans.
You've already done
so much for our city,
and we would be overjoyed
if you would consider remaining
in Ladylake to aid us further.
Thanks, but there's
something I must to do.
Oh. Indeed. Perhaps
you could elaborate?
I intend to go after the dragon.
Really? And what will
you do if you find it?
To be honest, I don't really
know the answer to that yet.
They say dragons
represent ill omens.
If I can find it,
maybe that could be the first
step toward healing this world.
[LAILAH]
Sorey.
[SOREY]
Hey!
Could you use another
pair of hands?
[ALISHA] The sun is going down.
We should wrap things up here.
Sorey, I am going to be
leaving soon for Marlind.
It is a direct order
from the king.
You're going away?
Was it really the king, or was
that Bartlow guy behind it?
[ALISHA] I don't know. But
it doesn't matter either way.
The people of Marlind
are suffering.
I want to help if I can.
[OFFICER A]
Was that a wise idea?
Allowing the Shepherd
to walk away?
If he wishes to leave
Ladylake, let him go.
He'll be out of our hair and
we won't have to shed any blood.
True. And our preparations?
For the war?
We must proceed.
Lailah, can I talk to you?
[LAILAH] Is something wrong,
Mikleo? You seem upset.
Well, when I look at Sorey,
I can only think things are
gonna be different now.
He's accepted his
destiny as Shepard
with absolutely no hesitation.
You feel like his new identity
has created a distance
between you?
I don't know. Maybe that's it.
And now,
Sorey has his destiny,
but what is yours going to be?
I wish I knew. I feel lost.
Everything changed the moment
he pulled that sword
from the stone.
Yes.
Sorey is the legendary Shepherd.
I'm happy for him,
but what about my life?
I left home to help him
search for Alisha.
I never expected all this.
Do you wish to
return to Elysium?
[MIKLEO] No. That thought
did cross my mind, but...
Sorey has a mission.
To gain experience
as a Shepherd,
he has to travel the world.
How can I leave him
to do that alone?
He means a lot to you.
Sorey has been your beloved
friend for a long time now.
We were just sort
of stuck together.
And now you're frustrated
because you aren't
sure you can help him.
But you know, there is a way.
[SOREY] Come on. We have
to go after Mikleo!
What if he should happen
to run into a hellion
and he's all on his own?
What was he thinking?
He should know better!
I can't believe he'd
take off like that!
[SOREY yelps]
[SOREY] I guess he must've
had a good reason.
Mikleo would never
just run away.
So you've decided not
to go after him?
He'll be okay, and I have
a lot of work to do
to become a real Shepherd.
[LAILAH] If you're looking
for a mission of your own,
I can give you one.
Leave the capital and
travel far to the north.
In time, you will come
to a large lake.
There, you will find what is
known as the Galahad Ruins.
Inside the ruins is
an ancient treasure,
a legendary Divine Artifact.
[MIKLEO]
Artifact?
Yes. Similar to what the
Sacred Blade is for me.
A relic of great power.
That may be the answer
to what you seek.
So with it, I would be
able to help Sorey?
[LAILAH]
I believe so.
[SOREY]
Ready to head out?
Good, you're here!
I need to get to Marlind.
The plauge's not going to wait.
Before you go, take this.
Is that...?
Mikleo found it in the ruins.
I'm sorry it took me so long
to finally put it back
in your hands.
Thanks so much!
I'm glad he found it.
It's very precious to me.
Sorey.
Well, feel free to say no,
but would you ride with us?
Maybe even just partway,
as an extra guard.
I'd love to!
[ALISHA] Seeing a dragon
for the first time,
the people shrank back in fear.
No longer just a legend,
it had become terrifyingly real.
[SOREY] You think there's
a clue in this story?
[ALISHA]
Yes. Rayfalke Spiritcrest.
A precipitous mountain.
It appears numerous times
in dragon legends.
[SOREY]
All right then, I'm going there.
They are called "trangelongs,"
unique to this forest.
They're watching us.
Don't worry. These are
gentle creatures.
[chuckles]
[MIKLEO]
Hm?
[rustling]
Damn. What kinda
hellion is that?
A snake? Lizard?
[MIKLEO screams]
[ALISHA]
How does everything look?
Great, thanks.
And are you sure that Lady
Lailah does not need to eat?
We have more than enough.
[SOREY] She's fine,
but thanks for asking.
[ALISHA]
She should at least try this.
I made it from some fruit
that I found nearby.
I just ground them up and
then steeped them in hot water.
[gasps]
Wow, that's sour! And yet--
Tasty?
Yeah! It's really good.
[LAILAH]
Sorey.
[SOREY]
Yeah.
Alisha, please?
Can you hear my voice?
Yes, Lady Lailah.
Thank you for the drink.
It was lovely.
[ALISHA]
Of course!
--[thud]
--[SOLDIER B yelps]
But the trangelongs don't
ever attack humans!
[LAILAH]
Sorey.
Yeah, that creature...
...is a hellion!
[ALISHA] We'll pass two more
villages and cross a wide river,
then we'll be in Marlind.
[SOREY] Tell me about it.
What's it like?
[ALISHA] It has the
second highest population
in the kingdom, after Ladylake.
It's known as a city
of culture and learning,
with the highest literacy
rate in the country.
My father took such pride in it.
[SOREY]
But that was before the plague?
Do you think the city
will be able to recover?
It's hard to know, really.
I'm not sure how much help
these doctors will be.
I'd love to know more about you.
[SOREY]
Like what?
[ALISHA]
Well, you said you've
never left Elysium
before, right?
[SOREY]
Right.
It's been my home for as
long as I can remember.
There was a big fire
when I was just a baby,
and Gramps saved me from it.
I guess you could say Elysium
kind of adopted me.
I didn't have the
chance to talk to him,
but Gramps sounds
like a good person.
[SOREY]
Yeah, he is.
We all knew we were safe
because we lived
under his blessing.
I can see how important
that was now.
How do I put this?
Um, you are human, right?
Of course.
But you see the Seraphim.
Have you always been
able to do that?
I don't know about always,
but for as long
as I can remember.
Actually, according to Gramps,
I learned how to hear and see
them by living among them.
I'd love to learn
about the Seraphim.
Are there some things
you could teach me?
[SOREY]
Hmm.
I wonder where I should begin...
Some stuff you know.
Like how The
Celestial Record says
that humans lived among the
Seraphim and could hear them.
Did you also know
that the Seraphim
used to live all
throughout the world?
They were the living embodiments
of earth, wind, water, and fire.
They used their power to support
and sustain the world itself.
[ALISHA]
Earth, wind, water, fire.
[SOREY] Yeah. Seraphim aren't
all-powerful, you know.
They have strengths
and weaknesses.
Lailah is a Seraph of fire,
and Mikleo's element is water,
so they have different talents.
[ALISHA]
There's so much I don't know.
Like, why did we stop being
able to see the Seraphim?
What happened?
And when they left, is that
what caused this era of chaos?
[SOREY] Grandpa said people lost
reverence for the Seraphim.
Their doubt and fear turned
to anger and hatred.
They began to fight each other,
and their negative emotions
polluted the world
with darkness.
So you mean, we're
the ones responsible?
The calamities that are tearing
apart the world are our fault?
[SOREY]
I'm not sure.
What I do know is that the world
is full of malevolence now.
The air is thick with it.
And the disasters will only keep
getting worse and more frequent.
Back when we were in Elysium,
you said your dream
was to create
a new world, a better one.
Humans and Seraphim together.
I remember you telling
me that very clearly.
Though, I didn't
understand it at the time.
I didn't know yet that you'd
been raised by Seraphim.
The only human,
but you never felt lonely.
It makes sense that you
became the Shepherd.
[SOREY]
Lonely?
I don't remember ever feeling
lonely growing up in Elysium.
Everyone was always
there for me.
Mikleo was always there for me.
If Lailah was right,
the ruins should be near here.
And the divine artifact
should be within.
He's not gonna beat
me to it this time.
Looks like it's
not much farther.
Rayfalke Spiritcrest.
Let's go.
Well, looks like I
beat you to it, Sorey.
I guess I beat you
to it again, Mikleo.
[LAILAH] The moon is
beautiful tonight, isn't it?
It is.
I bet you Mikleo's
looking at it, too.
Yeah.
[gasps]
[SOREY]
What's wrong?
You've got such a serious
look on your face.
Oh, hi, Sorey.
Sorry, I've just been
thinking about purification.
Purification.
That's pretty hard.
Yeah.
'm still inexperienced
as a Shepherd.
Honestly, purifying the
world sounds so difficult;
I'm not sure if
I'll be able to do it.
I'm sure you'll learn.
Still, I will try my hardest,
training as we journey
around the world.
And maybe someday
I'll be strong enough
to banish all the malevolence!
If you've been thinking
about it as well,
then maybe you can help me!
[SOREY laughs]
Well, I am the Shepherd!
Purifying's my job.
[LAILAH gasps]
Something wrong, Lailah?
I finally got it!
Huh? Got what?
Purification! I figured it out!
[SOREY]
Hm?
Come now, Sorey.
I don't understand why
you'd wanna fight Mikleo.
Really, it's pure nonsense.
Get it? It's pure nonsense.
This was all a set-up
for a bad pun?
Next episode,
"Rayfalke Spiritcrest."
Look forward to it!
Hey, Lailah.
Who was that just now?