[MIRA]
Please, who are you?
My name is Shiro Kamiki.
That's what I'm called
in this world, anyway.
But in your world I believe
I called myself Shijuro Sakaki.
[gasps]
[MIRA] You're Shijuro Sakaki
from 21 years ago?
[KAMIKI]
Now, answer my question.
You came here from
a different place.
A different world.
What do your eyes see?
Is this world alive
or dead to you?
I really don't know.
[GHOSTS chanting]
Kill them... Kill them...
[KAMIKI] It's starting.
The nightmare has begun again.
It binds the real world
to this world of shadows.
This false world that's
shackled to the past.
I don't understand.
Real or not, I'll protect them.
Using whatever means necessary,
eliminating anyone
who poses a threat.
I'll spare nobody.
Nobody. Even myself.
[footsteps tapping]
[grunts]
[ALBERT] Mabuchi, ghosts are
appearing along with the fog.
I've removed everyone
to the hotel.
What is this thing?
[ALBERT] It's a transmission
device, provided by Ellie.
[ELIZABETH] Yeah, and you
better not break it.
Thanks, you wanna trade
for my piece of scrap metal?
Oblivious little
fool's probably still
sitting in the
study reading books.
[ELIZABETH]
What are you planning to do?
I'm gonna catch one of
these damn things,
and then get it to take
me to the Numbers.
[WATER GHOST grunts]
[grunts]
[WATER GHOST roars]
[KYOMA]
I don't feel any resistance.
[KYOMA grunts]
[WATER GHOSTS growling]
[KYOMA]
They move with the fog.
What kind of an idiot is he?
Those things aren't solid.
You can't just catch a ghost!
[BOTH gasp]
[panting]
[KATO]
Chef Muroi?
Get over here! Hurry up!
[gasping]
[gagging]
[KATO]
They've got him!
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[screams]
[ALBERT]
Is that you, Makita?
Uh--
[WATER GHOST roars]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[door slams]
[ALBERT] All right, I made
it to Sakaki's study.
There's no sign of Mira
in here. What about you?
Are you having any luck
over in Mabuchi's room?
[ELIZABETH]
Not yet.
[ALBERT] Sakaki knew
the relationship between
the ghosts and coil.
That's why he was able to
prevent them from appearing.
Which means, he probably
kept something nearby
that he could use against them.
There must be something
we missed. But what is it?
[KYOMA gasps]
[KYOMA]
Al, it's water!
[lock clicks]
Oh, no!
[KATO screams]
[chain rattling]
[MIRA]
I am a robot.
Right now, I exist
in this strange,
shadowy world because
it perceives me.
But that's just data.
[laughs]
[MIRA]
Everything here...
The chains I'm wrapped in,
the violence I've seen...
Everything is a false image.
It's not real.
[MORINAGA]
How does it feel?
All that metal digging into you?
[MORINAGA laughs]
[MIRA] What if I die
like this? What will happen?
Will I be trapped
in this world forever
like the accident victims are?
I can't wait to see
you get ripped apart
limb from perfect little limb!
[MIRA] I am a robot. I won't
change if I'm restarted.
[MORINAGA]
By the time it's done,
you'll be even more
torn up than me!
[MIRA] I'll still clean, still
do laundry, still get yelled at
by Kyoma, still collect
coils for Mary,
still do my best to follow
Father's instructions...
[MIRA] But even so,
will that really be "me"?
Won't it be a different
"me" than I am now?
[MORINAGA]
Rip you apart! Tear your flesh!
I wanna see!
[MIRA]
That's not what I want. I am me!
I don't want there
to be any others!
[gasps]
[MORINAGA]
How?
Perception is the key.
My logic was stronger,
so it overrode
the logic of this world
and rewrote it.
No way. That's impossible.
No one can do that!
[gasps]
What are you doing here?
After all this time...
[alarm rings]
Get off!
--[WATER GHOST groans]
--Let go!
[coughing]
[WATER GHOSTS moaning]
They can only take form
in the fog of Lake Yasogami.
To disperse them,
you have to use water
from a different source.
That's why there are sprinklers
installed all over the building.
[KYOMA] We know it was these
things that killed Sakaki.
And that means, the water in
the dispenser must have been
switched with water
from Lake Yasogami.
[BLUE]
We've almost got it.
The Numbers coil
is inside this dam.
It looks like she froze.
Huh. Her coil
seems normal, though.
I can't get in? No way!
I guess I'll just
have to restart her.
[KATO]
And it's okay to do that?
--[MIRA screams]
--[KATO, ELIZABETH gasp]
--[MIRA] The bathroom? I'm back!
--Jeez, what was that?
You scared me!
I have to hurry and find Kyoma!
Slow down!
Shouldn't you at least
put a coat on?
--[MIRA grunting]
--[zipping]
--[thud]
--[MIRA yelps]
What the hell are you doin',
you piece of junk?!
Where were you when you
coulda been useful?!
[KYOMA groans]
Listen to me! I know
where they are!
I can lead us to the
Numbers and Marisa!
[groans]
[KAMIKI]
Don't worry, Enamori. I'm here.
I'll protect you
as I always have.
[KYOMA]
Well, hurry up. Get in.
[MIRA]
Right! Coming!
[engine revs]
They've got more of those
flying disc things
at the dam's
administration offices.
[MIRA gasps]
--What do we do?
--Nothing at all.
Uh, but--
So, he brought out the
big one. Good choice.
It's almost like old times again
with me watchin'
your back, isn't it?
This is just like I thought.
Those guys had
Professor Kuroda's notes.
Good news, Papa.
I know where it is.
[LOSER] Doesn't matter.
I'm calling it off.
We're retreating.
Why? It's almost ours.
[LOSER]
Because of the second Grendel.
He's far too interested in us.
Huh. Who cares about him?
[LOSER] I'm afraid going up
against two of the Beasts
could prove to be
exceptionally challenging.
Even for us.
[ALBERT]
How unpleasant.
When I came here I didn't
think I'd end up working
with Loser's little sidekick.
Mabuchi, you'd better
make this worth it.
[MIRA] Shiro Kamiki is Shijuro
Sakaki from 21 years ago.
But he only exists now in
the world that was stored
in Dimension W by the Numbers.
[KYOMA]
What a damn hopeless mess.
You're tellin' me
this guy's past self
killed his present self...
People wonder why I
hate coils? This is why.
[MIRA] What was stored wasn't
simply an event from the past.
It was another
possibility in which
Kamiki's friends didn't die.
Because in that world,
he was able to save them.
[KAMIKI] This is the perfect
way to show people
what coils can do.
It's so important.
They're the solution to
all our energy problems,
and it's time for people
to realize that.
With technology like this,
there's no need for a dam.
And the village will be saved!
Exactly!
[MITANI chuckles]
What happened?
Why's your arm bandaged?
This? I just got a little cut.
You should be more careful.
You've always been such a klutz,
ever since we were little.
And you've always
been a crybaby,
ever since we were little.
Oh, shut up.
You know, we're gonna
have to work
on your sense of humor--
[MITANI]
You two sure get along well.
Stop that, Mr. Mitani.
You're supposed to be
covering the coils, not us.
[MITANI laughs]
Who's that guy?
Just some journalist.
He says he's filming a report
on the coil or something.
I figured a little
publicity can't hurt.
[STUDENT 5A]
Enamori!
[BOTH]
Hm?
Could you do me a favor
and check the power supply?
Yeah, sure. Will you
let Mr. Mitani know
where I'm going?
[KAMIKI]
Hmph.
[ENAMORI] What's wrong?
Concerned about interference?
I'm more worried about
what the weather's gonna do.
I'm gonna go take a look.
There wasn't anything
in the forecast, though.
[KAMIKI] I'll be back before
the Professor comes.
[WORKER 5A] Hey, you really
think this is okay?
[WORKER 5B]
Discharging the dam?
We're just letting a little
water out, that's all.
They'll run away quick enough.
[WORKER 5A] And the
siren'll go off, right?
Who's on duty today again?
[WORKER 5B]
Uh... Kato, poor sap.
I wouldn't wanna be him.
[KAMIKI]
Ugh. I gotta go let 'em know!
[shrieks]
I can't believe you'd think
we'd broadcast
a report on coils.
It's a damn good thing
you're pretty, sweetheart.
Please! Just leave me alone!
[MITANI]
Don't you get it?
An infinite energy supply
would cause a lotta people
a lotta problems.
Stop it!
You can't just go
solving the energy
crisis overnight.
That's not the way things work.
[screams]
This report is never
gonna be seen.
That was decided before
I even got here.
[whimpering]
[MITANI]
Give up already!
[ENAMORI grunting]
--Let go!
--[thud]
[KAMIKI gasps]
No! Are you okay?
Tell me what happened!
It's too horrible. I--
I can't say it.
Kamiki... I killed someone!
[thunder booms]
[sighs] You didn't
do anything wrong.
It was self-defense.
But... he's dead!
[KAMIKI]
Listen to me!
They're planning to
discharge the dam upstream
to drive everyone away.
What?
[KAMIKI]
You go and warn everybody
that they need to
evacuate to the hotel.
Aren't you coming, too?
[KAMIKI] First, I'm gonna
do something about that.
Don't tell anyone
what happened here.
Kamiki--
[KAMIKI] There's no time
for this! Get going!
[KAMIKI] They were only planning
to let out a little water.
Just enough to scare us.
But thanks to this guy,
that'll have to change.
[splashing]
[KAMIKI]
Any evidence will be washed away
when this place is flooded
with muddy water.
I don't care what happens to me.
I must protect Enamori.
[MARISA]
Once I've warned everybody,
I need to retrieve the coil.
[screams]
Ah.
[KATO'S FATHER sighs]
[KATO'S FATHER groans]
[alarm blares]
[STUDENTS screaming]
[tires screech]
[STUDENTS yelling]
--Look! Is that Kamiki?
--[MORINAGA] Help us, Shiro!
Go find help and get
us out of here!
[KAMIKI]
Why are they still down there?
Where's Enamori?
[gasps]
[KAMIKI] Should I try and save
them, knowing I might die, too?
Should I run away and live?
What would she do?
[KAMIKI] It's hard to describe
what happened next.
There was no sound,
just a bright light.
And the passage of
time warped somehow.
The next thing I remember,
I thought I'd saved everyone.
But that happened in
a world that isn't real.
[KAMIKI] So many deaths,
and they were my fault.
This world may be fake,
but it doesn't matter.
It's the only world
in which we still exist.
So, I will protect it.
No matter what it takes.
[KYOMA] That's an
illegal coil. Hand it over!
[KYOMA, KAMIKI grunt]
[KAMIKI yells]
[groans]
My legs are soaked
in spring water.
Now, time to say goodbye.
Your world is ending.
Our world is stronger
than you think.
It's made of Enamori's memories.
Her thoughts sustain us.
Give us form and life.
We are immortal!
[MIRA]
That is incorrect.
[gasps]
[MIRA] Your world is
not what you think.
It is not made up of Enamori's
thoughts or memories.
Don't touch her!
What the hell is
going on? Where is she?
[MIRA]
The world you exist in
is your other
possibility, Kamiki.
My other... possibility?
[MIRA]
That's right.
An alternate world in which
you saved your friends
and grieved Enamori's death.
A world that could have been.
What're you--?
[MIRA]
You believed she was dead,
but Enamori was
actually still alive.
You're lying.
You don't see it, do you?
That's not Marisa.
That's Enamori.
No, that's Marisa.
That's my sister, it has to be!
No, it isn't.
You spent so long believing
Enamori was dead,
that you can't see what's
right before your eyes.
[SAKAKI] That's right.
The real Marisa is dead.
There was a car accident
14 years ago.
This isn't possible.
[SAKAKI]
I abandoned my friends
and went after Enamori instead.
I was able to save
her from drowning.
She lived, but she
forgot everything
from before the accident.
I left Yasogami Village
and changed my name
in order to lead a quiet,
private life.
I hoped that we could somehow
leave the tragedy behind us.
But Enamori was
tortured by nightmares.
In her dreams, she could see
that those who died in the flood
had become ghosts and
were attacking people.
[SAKAKI] Professor Kuroda
helped me understand
what was happening.
Three threads tied
the real world to the
world of the ghosts:
the coil, the water from Lake
Yasogami, and Enamori's dreams.
In order to be free
of her nightmares,
she had to be separated
from the coil
and the water of Lake Yasogami.
[KAMIKI]
I don't understand!
You could have just destroyed
the coil, couldn't you?
Why did you have to trick us
and hide it in the dam?
That's why we did it.
That's why we killed you!
It's not that simple.
Think about what
would have happened
if I'd stopped the coil.
[KAMIKI grunts]
My dead friends lived
on in another world.
I wanted to protect it.
I wanted to protect them.
[KAMIKI gasping]
Look, Kamiki. You should
be able to see Enamori now.
Your perception of her
death had to be changed,
that's why you couldn't
see it before.
[KAMIKI]
Enamori?
I can't believe it!
I've waited for so long.
And now, here you are.
[sobs]
[KAMIKI]
It's true? You really survived?
I did! But it was
all so horrible!
I couldn't do anything!
I just watched while everyone
suffered. I felt so lost!
I could never help anyone,
but I was always,
always watching.
[KAMIKI] I'm so sorry. I thought
I was doing it for your sake,
but all I did was hurt you more.
[ENAMORI]
No, that isn't true!
I'm not hurting, now.
I'm happy because I'm
finally with you again.
[KAMIKI] I've caused so much
pain. It's time. Let's end this.
[rumbling]
[KYOMA]
What's that sound?
[MIRA] The alternate world
created in Dimension W
is converging with reality.
When the Numbers go wild,
they create cracks
in Dimension W. Each crack, in
turn, creates a copy of reality.
And every world created
holds a different possibility.
That's confusing.
Copies usually disappear almost
as soon as they're made.
But in this case, the coil
continued to function,
so this world was
able to remain.
[KYOMA]
Hm.
[KAMIKI] It looks
like our time is up.
This is goodbye.
Yes. I have to go back, too.
Can I ask you something?
[KYOMA]
What?
If I told you
I could see Heaven,
would you believe me?
Not a chance.
I've always heard that people
who kill themselves go to Hell.
Huh. Is that so? I guess
we'll see, won't we?
[KYOMA]
Hey.
[MIRA]
Yes?
What are you doing
with your tail?
[MIRA gasps]
Oh, well,
there could be serious
consequences if the coil stops
before the convergence
is complete.
To prevent that,
I'm controlling it.
It's embarrassing. I would
prefer it if you didn't watch.
Since when do robots
get embarrassed?
--You stupid piece of junk.
--[MIRA grunts]
There was no sign
of Albert or Ellie.
Guess they both
must've left already.
[KYOMA]
I guess so.
I still don't understand
why we're going
when the case hasn't
been completely solved.
Uh-- The police are
the ones who solve cases.
All we do is
collect coils. Got it?
[MIRA]
Right. Of course.
Kyoma is still such a mystery.
What kind of person is he?
What happened to make
him hate coils so much?
And another thing:
Why would someone who
hates coils choose a job
that revolves around them?
[KATO] Yes, I did what
the voices told me to.
I emptied the water dispenser,
then I replaced it
with water from Lake Yasogami.
I had to. For my father.
He was on duty at the dam
administrative building
21 years ago when it happened.
[KATO] All this time,
he's been out there.