[car horns honking]
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER 1A]
With this latest increase,
the gas tax has now
exceeded a rate of 400%.
The cost per liter is expected
to continue its steady rise,
as markets anticipate
the phasing out
of all non-electric vehicles
within the next three years.
In other news. As the
World System prepares
to mark its tenth year
of operations,
the fate of Dr. Shido Yurizaki,
inventor of the coil and former
CEO of New Tesla Energy,
remains a mystery.
Now missing for more
than two years, many believe
the hopes of finding
the doctor alive are slim.
[phone rings]
[KYOMA grunts]
[ringing continues]
[KYOMA sighs]
[MARY] You waited
long enough to pick up.
[KYOMA]
You got a job?
[MARY]
We can talk tonight.
Pay me a visit.
Nine p.m. sharp.
[phone clicks]
[KIDS gasp]
[KIDS yelp]
--[JIN] Let's get outta here!
--[SHOTA] Let's go! Run!
[sighs]
[NARRATOR] In the year 2036,
a fourth dimensional axis
beyond X, Y, and Z
was proved to exist.
Dimension W.
Inter-dimensional
electromagnetic
induction devices,
known as "coils,"
were developed to tap the
inexhaustible energy supply
that exists in Dimension W.
Sixty giant towers
spread across the globe
are used to stabilize the energy
drawn from Dimension W.
They are responsible
for supplying power
to the entire world.
This network developed
by New Tesla Energy
with the cooperation
of the global community
is known as the "world system."
It has altered the very core
of civilized society.
Mankind has discovered
what it has always sought.
A limitless supply of energy!
[boat horn blares]
[BOATMAN 1A]
This is your stop.
Perfect. Thanks for the ride.
You be careful, now.
And tell your dad I said hi.
[BLIMP ANNOUNCEMENT 1A]
A message from New Tesla Energy:
The use of illegal coils
is punishable by law.
Please always use
official coils.
[footsteps tapping]
[door creaks, clicks]
[footsteps creak]
[SHIDO]
Is that you, Mira?
I'm sorry, Father.
I was trying not to wake you up.
I just went out for a bit
to grab some medicine
and other things we needed.
[SHIDO] Are you alright?
Did anything happen out there?
[MIRA]
No.
Don't waste your energy
worrying about me.
I'm just fine!
[SHIDO]
I'm a weak, selfish old man.
I hope you don't
resent me too much.
[CROWD cheering, yelling]
[RING ANNOUNCER] A decisive
tackle by the challenger,
Buffalo Gale!
The champion's in trouble now!
I don't think
he saw that coming!
[cheering, yelling continue]
[RING ANNOUNCER]
Coil break!
It looks like we have
a new champion, folks.
[MAN 1A grunting]
[MARY]
Have a seat.
Go on and look over
the job specs.
It should be a pretty
straightforward gig.
The Won brothers,
Every and Jony.
Petty thugs based
out of Shadow City.
According to my intel,
these two have managed
to procure a decent
number of illegal coils.
Your job is to
collect them for me.
As far as my
payment's concerned.
Same as always. Half in cash,
half in gasoline.
I'm the only reason you're
able to get by in this world,
hating coils the
way that you do.
[MARY]
I'm expecting results.
Kyoma Mabuchi.
You'll get your results.
[engine revs]
[MIRA chuckles]
[MIRA] I'm just going out
to buy some drinking water.
[MIRA gasps]
[JONY cackles]
Look what I got, boys and girls!
Illegal coils!
Man, are those for real?
If they are,
that's a major score.
[JONY] Other than the X's,
they're just like legit coils.
Check it out! Hah.
Uh...
[LEADERS gasp]
[JONY cackles]
[explosions]
[MIRA gasps]
[gasps]
[MIRA yelps]
[LEADERS gasp]
[JONY]
Whaddaya think?
These things pack some
seriously wicked power!
Just look at the damage it did!
And that was with a water gun!
You better not get
too attached to 'em.
[door clicks]
[EVERY]
I'm back.
[JONY]
You're late, Every!
Hey, what the hell
are you carrying?
[JONY]
A chick?
[EVERY laughs]
[EVERY] She was standing
out in the hall.
[JONY]
Eavesdropping, huh?
A spy from the south district?
[FEMALE LEADER 1A] What are we
supposed to do with some girl?
I'll do whatever
I want with her.
Finders, keepers, right?
[EVERY]
Ah!
Huh?!
[JONY]
What was that?
[KYOMA]
I know how this is gonna look,
but I didn't actually
come here for the girl.
See, I'm a Collector.
[JONY, EVERY growl]
Hand over the illegal coils.
If you don't,
things are gonna get ugly.
Whatever. Bring it on!
[JONY yelps]
Dammit!
[KYOMA] None of you clowns
have the stones
to handle illegal coils.
If they destroy you...
...don't blame me.
[JONY growls]
[JONY]
Get 'im!
[GUARDS chuckle]
--[MALE GUARD 1A yells]
--[gasps]
--[KYOMA grunts]
--[MALE GUARD 1A groans]
[GUARDS groan]
[MIRA]
Where am I?
[MALE GUARD 1B groans]
[MIRA]
Is that... a human?
[EVERY groans]
I hope you learned
somethin' today.
I was only going out for water.
[footsteps tapping]
[gasps]
[JONY]
Stay right where you are!
Wanna see this pretty
little girl get hurt?
Don't think I won't do it.
I'll blow her eyeballs
out of her skull!
Already told you I'm
not here to save the girl.
It's not my job.
I'm really gonna do it!
[KYOMA]
Go ahead.
[JONY grunts, whimpers]
What's wrong? Aren't you
gonna shoot her?
[JONY grunting, whimpering]
Dammit, dammit, dammit, dammit,
dammit, dammit, dammit...
[MIRA]
Father.
Damn it all!
[MIRA]
I'm sorry!
[JONY yells]
[LEADERS groaning]
I failed you, Father.
I couldn't obey
your instructions.
Hey, did you know she was
a robot this entire time?
No, I didn't.
[MIRA grunts]
[KYOMA]
Hm?
--You're a lowlife jerk!
--[KYOMA grunts]
[ALBERT]
Mabuchi.
Mabuchi!
[gasps]
Hey.
Albert Schumann.
Just perfect.
Seeing you on the
losing end of a fight's
not something that
happens every day.
What kind of a monster
were you up against?
[KYOMA sighs] I really
don't wanna talk about it.
What's the DAB doin' here?
[ALBERT] As a matter
of fact, I just became
chief investigator of Qi.
You'll see me a lot.
So what's up?
This case isn't big enough
for the Bureau's elite
to dirty their hands with?
This is the sort of thing
you Collectors take care of.
Your bread and butter, right?
Come on, what are
you lookin' for?
[ALBERT]
That's confidential.
Though if you came
to work for me,
it might be a different
story entirely.
[KYOMA]
Thanks, I'll pass.
[ALBERT sighs]
Rejected again, huh?
I see you still detest
coils as much as ever.
By the way, as of now,
this is the property
of the Dimensional
Administrative Bureau.
[KYOMA]
Go ahead and take it.
[ALBERT]
Do me a favor, will ya?
Don't tell Mary I'm the one
who made off with the coil.
[KYOMA]
Sure.
I don't know, sir.
Is it really okay to
let him go like that?
Don't worry about him.
There're threats to
New Tesla out there,
but Kyoma Mabuchi's
not one of them.
He lives in the past.
He may die there too.
But he'll never do anything
to betray this world.
He may not realize it,
but I will make him mine.
[MARY]
Stop screwin' around!
Information's not free,
you know!
[KYOMA]
It's not my fault.
Once the DAB showed up,
there was nothing I could do.
[MARY] What was the
Bureau doing there?
This job wasn't supposed
to be that big.
Something must be up.
[KYOMA grunts]
You're a lowlife jerk!
Hey, Mary, the robots
they make these days.
Can they shed tears?
[MARY]
That's a random question.
[KYOMA]
Forget it.
[engine revs]
[KYOMA]
I'm overthinking it, that's all.
[brakes screech]
[KYOMA]
Wait a sec.
[MIRA gasps]
[tires screech]
[MALE TROOPER 1C]
I'm not getting any
dimension-specific reaction.
[MALE TROOPER 1B] Let's expand
the search to one block ahead.
[MIRA] I'm disobeying
Father's instructions again,
but this is no time
to be playing human.
[MIRA]
I have to get these to Father.
For his heart.
[MIRA]
Wait for me.
I'm coming.
[SHIDO panting]
[SHIDO] So, you've finally
sniffed this place out have you?
I need time.
Just a little more
time, that's all.
[SHIDO]
But if it's come to this...
[MIRA gasps]
[KYOMA]
Well, look who it is.
Thought I might
find you up here,
sneaking around
the edges of the Qi
boys' search grid.
[MIRA]
You're the man from earlier.
Yeah, and you're the
thieving little robot.
You were after
those illegal coils
from the very beginning,
weren't you?
I'm guessing you, no,
the one pulling your strings
must also be a Collector
after New Tesla's reward.
Am I right?
No, you aren't!
[KYOMA]
Quit lying, puppet.
[grunts]
[KYOMA] I'll admit it.
That was a good trick.
Send in a robot that looks human
and have it play the victim
until it sees an opportunity
to snatch the coils and run.
I get it now. The tears
and emotional outbursts
make it easier to
deceive the target.
It's just smart programming.
Thing is.
I got to those
illegal coils first.
They're my prey.
Unless you wanna
be disassembled,
I'll take them back.
Now hand 'em over, robot!
You can't have them!
I apologize for
hitting you earlier,
but I can't give
the coils to you.
[KYOMA]
Get back here!
[gasps]
[ALBERT]
You're sure this is the place?
[MALE TROOPER 1A]
Yes, sir.
There's a sophisticated
anti-scanning field being
deployed from this building
which is unusual tech
for this location.
Is the area clear?
It's been evacuated, sir.
Alright, our target
is the professor.
He's not to be harmed.
Take care with
his research, too.
[gasps]
[MALE TROOPER 1D] Facial
analysis confirms a 96% match.
It really is him.
Dr. Yurizaki. We represent
New Tesla Energy.
We've come in hopes
of reconciling with you.
Reconciliation?!
After what you did to my family?
Is this some kind of a joke?
Two years ago, you people
broke into my home
to steal the research
my wife and I had done.
But taking that wasn't
enough for you, was it?
You bastards murdered
my wife and daughter!
New Tesla took everything.
All that's left is anger.
[ALBERT]
That was a regrettable error.
The previous bureau director
misunderstood the
board's orders.
Although it hasn't
been made public,
the bureau director and those
involved were punished,
and the board of
directors admitted
that they made a mistake.
Wouldn't it be for the best
to put your anger aside?
[SHIDO]
It's too late for that.
I have a moral obligation.
As the one who created the
world system, I am responsible.
Even if it kills me.
Still.
It must be done.
What is that?
Is it some kind of coil?
You want me?
Take this instead.
This is my answer!
[MIRA gasps]
Father, no!
[KYOMA]
I gotcha.
[MIRA]
Please, take these off of me!
--[KYOMA grunts]
--[MIRA yelps]
[grunts]
You might as well
stop resisting them.
Even a chainsaw couldn't
cut those wires.
Let me go!
I have to get home quickly,
or Father will--
[KYOMA]
Be quiet.
That trick's not gonna
work on me again.
You're a robot.
I'm not gonna feel
sympathy for you.
So who is this Father guy
you're squawkin' about, anyway?
Your puppeteer?
--Or is that just a cover?
--[MIRA] Please untie me!
[KYOMA]
Tears again?
What'd I tell you?
I'm not fallin' for that.
[KYOMA]
What the--?
No! Wait! You can't
do this, Father!
[ALBERT grunts]
[TROOPERS grunt]
All units abandon
your equipment and retreat!
[SHIDO groans]
What is this?
What the hell are
you doing, Doctor?
[SHIDO] This is it!
This is the beginning!
[KYOMA grunts]
It's hot.
[mechanical groaning]
[SHIDO]
I'm leaving the rest to you.
[MIRA]
No! Wait!
[SHIDO]
Mira.
[MIRA]
Father, please.
[TROOPERS grunt, yelp]
[ALBERT yells]
[KYOMA] Sure enough.
She's just another robot.
When her coil
burns out, she's done.
[KYOMA]
What'd I expect?
[KYOMA] I don't wanna leave
anything behind for Al, though.
[KYOMA] She's gotta be worth
some cash at least.
[MARY]
Are you kidding me?
I send you out for illegal coils
and you bring me back
this crazy thing?
[KYOMA] What? It's just
a little souvenir.
Have you figured
anything out, Koorogi?
To be honest with you
Mary, I'm surprised.
At what, you ask?
The fact that our friend here
could be stupid enough
to think that this
magnificent specimen
is the property of
an ordinary Collector.
Tch.
First off, Collectors
aren't exactly known
for their spectacular wealth.
There's no way one could
make or buy something
this expensive
and sophisticated.
This kind of specialty
work would easily cost
as much as a satellite.
The basic body construction
is the same as Four over there.
But underneath
the artificial skin
is a layer of subtle
silicone foam,
and high-polymer artificial
muscles laid over
a skeletal frame filled with
nanomachines for self-repair.
Then there's the
coil on her chest.
It controls all the actuators
with a wireless
local energy network.
Not that there aren't
plenty of this type of
maintenance-free robot,
but they're all copies
of the original.
They usually contain traces
of compromise or streamlining.
But this baby doesn't
have any of that.
It's so complete it's annoying.
Is it really
that big a deal?
Well here's the thing.
As far as I know,
the only one who could make
something like this
is Dr. Yurizaki.
[KYOMA grunts]
[KOOROGI]
And, click.
[MARY] Who said you
could turn it on?
Won't it send
information to New Tesla?
Not if it's an official
coil used in a legal way.
No specific information will
be transmitted from the unit
if it meets those requirements.
Hey. You sure about this?
Maybe we should just
turn it back off.
[KOOROGI]
She's not going berserk.
Let's just wait and
see what happens.
--[MIRA shrieks]
--[KYOMA grunts]
What's happening? Where am I?
Where did my clothes go?
Oh, whoops.
Thanks for that.
[MIRA]
You again! What's going on?
[KYOMA]
Quit the confused act.
And while you're at it,
be a good little robot
and switch off the attitude.
Would you please stop
referring to me as a robot?
I'm a girl, thank you very much!
[KYOMA grunts]
You weren't kidding.
This is an incredible machine.
It almost makes you wonder
if there's a real
person inside there.
If you want I can open up
the head and check it out.
Though I have no
idea where to start
making sense of these protocols.
Between that and
the organic structure,
I probably couldn't put it
back the way I found it.
Heh, heh. Honestly,
the easiest way to learn more
would be to ask the
one who made her.
[MARY] Dr. Yurizaki?
That I would like to do.
Can you take us to him, robot?
Please just let me help you.
I'll do anything you say.
Anything.
I beg you.
Let me stay here and help
you collect illegal coils.
It's something I have to do.