[gas glugging]
[engine revs]
[KYOMA grumbles]
[kicks lands]
It feels like a damn
sauna out here.
[MIRA]
Hm.
[sighs]
[MIRA]
I just want a shower.
[ANNOUNCER 2A] We've got an
excited crowd gathered here
outside the Central 47
Museum of Art.
Everyone is impatiently
awaiting the appearance
of the notorious would-be
thief known only as Loser.
[ELIZABETH]
They're callin' your name, Papa.
Do you hear it?
[LOSER] Let's give them the
show they're waiting for.
[NARRATOR]
In the year 2036,
a fourth dimensional axis
beyond X, Y, and Z
was proved to exist:
Dimension W.
Inter-dimensional
electromagnetic
induction devices,
known as "coils,"
were developed to
tap the inexhaustible
energy supply that
exists in Dimension W.
Sixty giant towers
spread across the globe
are used to stabilize the energy
drawn from Dimension W.
They are responsible
for supplying power
to the entire world.
This network developed
by New Tesla Energy
with the cooperation of the
global community is known as
the "world system."
It has altered the very core
of civilized society.
Mankind has discovered
what it has always sought.
A limitless supply of energy!
--[CROWD chattering]
--Whoa...
[MIRA]
Look at the size of this crowd!
I've never seen this many
people in one place before!
A newspaper? Not your
usual reading material.
"Little is known about Loser,
a mysterious thief
who generally targets artwork."
He broadcasts his
thefts by hijacking
communication devices,
and while the public adores him,
none of his heists
have been successful."
Really? I get it now.
That must be why
they call him "Loser."
"Due to this fact,
some believe that the victims
are working with Loser to
stage these so-called heists
as a means of advertising."
If that's true,
it would explain why
he goes to the trouble
of broadcasting everything.
Still. If he doesn't actually
steal anything or hurt anybody,
he isn't much of
a criminal, is he?
There are a lot of police here.
Are you helping them catch him?
[KYOMA] Loser's MO is
to broadcast his heists.
However he manages it,
you can bet
that illegal coils are involved.
I'm a Collector.
It's not Loser I care about.
It's his coils.
And we're taking them.
Oh! Of course.
[MIRA]
What's this?
[KYOMA]
Clothes from Mary. Get changed.
Ooh! What do they look like?
Just go get changed.
[MARY] You're telling me
you wanna be a Collector?
Yes.
Why would you wanna do that?
[MIRA] Because of something
my father said.
"When I die, follow the illegal
coils." That's what he told me.
By "father," you mean
Dr. Yurizaki, that right?
Yes.
He told me if I saw a pillar
of light, I would know
he was no longer
in this world, so...
That light earlier today.
I can't bring him back,
but I can follow
Father's final instructions.
If you'll give me the chance.
Please! I have to know what
it was he wanted me to find.
And what about Dr. Seira?
Yurizaki's wife.
Do you know where she is?
Somebody murdered her.
[KYOMA, MARY, KOOROGI gasp]
This was two years ago.
It happened on the
same day I was born.
Whoa, she's cool!
Have you picked out
her name yet, Mommy?
[SEIRA] Actually, I thought
you could do that.
--[ICHIGO] I like the name Mira.
--What the hell's going on?
[KOOROGI laughs] Seems our
robot friend hacked into
this room's system.
[ICHIGO whimpers]
Mommy!
[SEIRA] Who are you people?
You can't just barge in here!
--Wait, what are you doing?
--[ICHIGO screams]
Stop it now!
[gasps]
[MARY] That recording isn't
something you can just
go around showing people.
It's dangerous. Remember that.
[MIRA]
Okay. I'm sorry.
Delete the log. I don't
want any record of this.
We didn't see anything.
There was never
any video. Understand?
Consider it done.
[KYOMA]
It was New Tesla.
[MIRA gasps]
The people who
killed the doctor?
Yeah. There was
someone I recognized.
A guy I saw before at
joint training exercise.
I'm completely certain.
If that's the case,
then this is even bigger
than we thought.
If those people were New Tesla,
it means the world's
biggest corporation secretly
killed the world's greatest
robot engineer and
her young daughter.
More than that, they killed
the wife of Dr. Shido Yurizaki.
The father of coils and
New Tesla's own founder.
What I would like to know
is why the doctor
chose to go into
hiding instead of
making this information public.
And why all he left
behind was this girl
and some cryptic last words.
You can't do this, Father!
[MARY]
All right, then.
You get your wish, girl.
I'll put you to work.
[gasps]
[MARY] However, Kyoma
will supervise you.
Huh?
[MARY]
She'll chase after illegal coils
whether we take her on or not.
Better that she be somewhere
where we can watch her
than running around on her own.
You must know if she gets
caught, then that's it for us.
We can play innocent
all we want,
but our lives won't
be worth a damn.
[KYOMA grunts]
Thank you! Thank you so much!
I promise I won't let you down!
[laughs]
This is priceless!
The die-hard
coil hater
is getting a robot
for his partner!
[MARY] Hold on. Aren't you
forgetting something?
Huh?
Why's it have to be me?
You're the one who brought her.
I'd say that makes her
your responsibility.
You kids have fun now.
[footsteps tapping]
[MIRA]
Okay. I'm ready.
Well, what do ya think?
Is this a good look for me?
There's one thing, though.
I couldn't hide my tail.
Is that a big problem,
do you think?
[KYOMA]
You'll have to ask Mary.
[MIRA]
Huh.
[CURATOR] Although I will
say that by doing so
he has demonstrated
excellent taste.
This statue is much admired
for its unsettling beauty.
Once in the exhibition
of the late
Earnest Aurenche, this piece--
[KYOMA grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[LOSER] Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
[CROWD cheers]
Here we go. Looks like
the show's starting.
[LOSER]
Tonight's target is the statue,
Angels of Black and White Wings.
It's Loser! I think he's coming!
[rumbling]
[GUARD 2C groans]
[MAN 2A]
Over there! That's gotta be him!
[MIRA] Now that he's here,
what do we do?
The range for this
kind of hijacking
is roughly two kilometers.
Somewhere in that area, there'll
be jammers with illegal coils.
Find them.
[MIRA] Okay, but do you
think you could tell me...
...how I'm supposed
to do that exactly?
[GUARD 2D]
Stop!
[GUARD 2D groans]
[GUARD 2E groans]
[LOSER]
Hm. He's fast. Who is that guy?
[ELIZABETH]
Hang on. I'll find out.
I think he's a Collector,
so if I can just
extract his ID then
I should be able t--
Whoa, hold it! Guess we
can forget about an ID.
This guy doesn't have
a single coil on him.
[LOSER]
Not one? Really?
None at all. It's crazy.
It's like he's a relic from
another age or something.
[LOSER] I've heard of a
Collector from Central 47
who's extremely good,
but hates coils.
That must be him.
[ELIZABETH]
What now?
[LOSER]
What do you think?
[GUARD 2H]
03, 05, stop him!
[GUARDS]
Sir!
[LOSER]
Time for a real show.
[GUARDS groan]
[CROWD cheers]
[LOSER]
I've cleared the front gate.
[alarm blares]
[ANNOUNCEMENT 2A] Warning:
Deploying adhesive pellets.
[KYOMA gasps]
[LOSER]
Leg boost!
Looks like the route's blocked.
[ELIZABETH] They're trying
to steer you somewhere.
[KNIGHTS]
Intruder. Stop where you are.
[LOSER] I suspect I could do
a lot worse than to have
someone like you fighting
at my back, Collector.
I'm not interested in fighting
with you or against you.
Tell me where your coils are
and we'll call it a day.
[LOSER]
And deprive my fans of the show
they've been waiting for?
I couldn't possibly do that!
[MAN 2B]
Who's that other guy in there?
[MAN 2C]
Some kinda rival?
Yeah! Go Loser!
That guy's got nothin' on you!
Well, he may be a bad thief,
but he sure is popular.
But that's enough gawking.
I've got a job to do.
[MIRA]
No good.
I can't use anything
but my optical sensor.
Probably because of
Loser's fireworks.
[MIRA] I need to find
all the jamming devices
in a two kilometer range,
but how can I do that
if I can't trace them
or use my scanner?
[gasps] I just need a
different perspective.
I'll go somewhere
else and try again.
Someplace high up where the
fireworks won't interfere.
[LOSER] You have so much
raw physical ability
you don't even need coils.
I'm impressed, Kyoma Mabuchi.
You know me?
Who the hell are you?
[KNIGHTS crash]
[cars honking]
--[MEN grunt]
--[car horn blares]
Oops. I'm sorry!
I don't feel like I jump
as well as I used to.
Maybe from switching
to a regular coil?
[wind howls]
[MIRA gasps]
[MIRA]
That's a long way up.
It should put me far enough
away from any interference.
Then I can get to work.
[LOSER]
I know plenty of things.
For example, I know that
a legendary special ops unit
known as Grendel
fought in the last war.
You were part of that unit.
We live in an age of
unmanned warfare.
Yet you were taught to fight
with your body and mind,
a real-life superhero
trained specifically
to counter coil weapons.
The war came to an end,
and Grendel reportedly vanished.
But, you see, I know
what really happened.
I know about the final mission
and why they disappeared.
Yeah? What makes you so sure?
[LOSER]
Personal experience.
I know how New Tesla operates.
They hide any major
accidents involving coils.
[gasps]
Hideous, isn't it?
I lost my face, arms, and legs.
But worse than that,
I lost my wife.
Loser's never taken off
his mask before!
[MAN 2C]
Let us see!
[GIRL 2A] Can anyone
hear what he's saying?
[LOSER]
Get out of here, Collector.
The people who killed
my wife will pay.
One way or another, the truth
will be brought to light.
What do you mean by that?
[footsteps tapping]
[POLICE OFFICER 2A]
Police! Don't move!
[KYOMA groans] They choose
now to start doin' their job?
[KYOMA coughs]
Nice exit.
[POLICE OFFICER 2A]
Turn around slowly
and keep your hands
where I can see 'em.
[lock clicks]
[POLICE OFFICER 2A] Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Open up!
[GUARD 2I]
I'm sorry, sir, but why are you
locking out the police?
[CURATOR] I don't want anyone
seeing what I'm about to do.
--[GUARD 2I] But sir--
--[CURATOR] Enough! Be quiet!
[CURATOR]
My reputation's at stake, here.
I refuse to become
Loser's first victim.
That kind of thing
could ruin me!
[KYOMA] He wants revenge,
so he becomes an art thief?
If there's a connection there,
I don't see it.
[KYOMA gasps]
[KYOMA] None of his planned
heists have been successful.
So they say, but is it true?
[ELIZABETH] It's very faint, but
we're getting a positive signal.
I'm sure of it.
That's a key coil.
One of the Numbers.
[gasps] Papa, look out!
Are you alright, Papa?
Can you hear me?
[MAN 2B] Lame! Why did
the broadcast stop?
[CURATOR] I'm sorry,
but we're going to have to
cut your show a little
short tonight, Loser.
What's about to happen isn't
suitable for television.
Shall we get on with it?
[LOSER] It doesn't look like
these lovely ladies of yours
are powered by official coils.
I've got a question for you.
Tell me, curator.
What do you know about Numbers?
What are you talking about?
Is this some kind of joke?
[LOSER]
It was a stupid question.
Obviously you don't know
anything about coils.
Look at their chests.
[CURATOR gasps]
[LOSER]
They aren't glowing red because
they're using illegal coils.
Isn't that right, Collector?
Yeah.
Don't you know red is
the color of death?
You've got some top priority
Collection targets there.
[CURATOR gasps] Don't just stand
there! Kill him! Protect me!
[ROBOTS]
As you wish. Master.
[KYOMA]
Thanks for the lift.
[CURATOR] No! That's
impossible! My robots!
My precious robots...
They were defeated so easily!
[KYOMA]
Move it.
[CURATOR grunts]
[KYOMA] So that's what
you're really after?
[LOSER]
I seek the Numbers.
If you want to understand,
then you will.
Eventually.
I'm getting sick
of your riddles.
[banging]
[POLICE OFFICER 2A]
This is the police!
--Curator, open up! At once!
--[CURATOR gasps] No!
[CURATOR] They'll find out that
I've been using illegal coils!
I've got to get them out
and hide them somewhere.
If the police see
them, that's it! Ah!
You don't know
what you're doing!
[ROBOTS groaning]
Master... Mas--
Papa! Come on,
please say something!
Uh, what now? I could
restart the program.
Maybe that would help. Hold on.
Why are all the
jammers in one spot?
--I can explain that for you.
--[ELIZABETH gasps]
[MIRA] It wasn't easy,
but I'm pretty sure
--I caught all of them. See?
--What the--?
[gasps] Whoa, you're a robot!
Oh, no! I'm not a robot.
I, uh... I'm really a Collector.
Yeah! That's me. Ha, ha.
[ELIZABETH]
You have antennae.
You mean these?
They're not antennae.
No, these are just hairpins.
They're on the big side, I know.
[ELIZABETH]
Hairpins?
Anyway, I'm really impressed.
You did a good job with these.
There are pigeons everywhere,
so you could plant your devices
into a real flock
without anyone noticing.
But how did you figure it out?
Those birds look exactly
like the real thing!
Not to sound immodest,
but I have a little talent
with manipulating coils.
I admit, I didn't
see them at first.
But as I kept watching,
I noticed that there were some
that kept flying back
to the same positions.
Impossible. Nobody in
the world could do that!
Not impossible. Just difficult.
Anyway, once I
pinpointed the pigeons,
I used surveillance
camera logs to determine
where they were flying from
and that's what led
me to this place.
Amazing. Are you
sure you're a human?
Yes. Of course I am.
How many times
do I have to say it?
[ELIZABETH]
Then get outta here, Collector.
[gasps]
[ELIZABETH] Well, I mean, you
got what you wanted, didn't you?
So go on! I don't
have time for this!
[MIRA gasps]
Hey! What are you up to now?
A dimensional collapse.
This is bad.
[ROBOTS groaning]
Master... Master...
The shifted dimension's
already starting to overflow.
[CURATOR whimpering]
[LOSER] Goodbye for now.
If you survive this,
let's meet again.
[CURATOR screams]
[KYOMA]
Come on! Let's get outta here!
[ROBOTS groaning]
Master... Master...
[screams]
[groaning continues]
Master... Master...
[screams]
Can't say I didn't try.
Don't go!
[screams]
[POLICE OFFICER 2A]
What the hell happened?
[CROWD murmuring]
[gasps] What was that explosion?
A dimension collapsing.
Huh?
[ELIZABETH gasps]
You're okay!
[LOSER] What's more, I got
what I needed. Let's go home.
Right!
[MIRA]
What about Kyoma?
There was a man
who went in after you.
Did he survive too?
[LOSER] I'm glad to see he
has a good partner as well.
And don't worry.
It'll take a lot more than
that to kill a man like him.
[sighs]
It's over now, but how
much damage was done?
[CURATOR gasps]
Wh-What? What happened?
I don't understand.
I was just trying to
get the coils out.
What happened to me?
You shouldn't
have touched 'em.
As for your mess, it'll just
cool down and harden.
We're with the DAB.
Stay where you are.
This area is under our
management as of now.
[ALBERT] The materialization
of Dimension W.
Not something you wanna
see more than once.
Hey, Mabuchi.
You know, you look
good on the big screen.
I figured I'd be
seeing you here.
[ALBERT]
This is a Class C accident.
It'll take five days or so
to ascertain the extent
of the dimensional damage
and another eight months
to repair it.
However, New Tesla promised
mankind eternal light.
And it will keep that promise.
This incident will
not be made public.
I had hoped by coming here I'd
get to meet the infamous Loser.
Too bad.
[ELIZABETH] Looks like
the DAB is here, Papa.
[LOSER]
Yes. We should hurry.
Can you wait for
just a second?
There's something
I wanted to ask you.
Do you know who's
making illegal coils
or where they're
being manufactured?
You must know something!
Even if it's not much, please
tell me. It's very important!
[LOSER]
I cannot help you.
What you're asking
is forbidden knowledge,
even in the underworld.
But I can tell you this.
I will get my revenge!