[LWAI]
Salva! What is that thing?
[LOSER]
This is Sophia?
[SEAMEYER] Technically,
it's a monster created
from a bunch of corpses,
using Sophia as its foundation.
He's lying...
[SEAMEYER] If it's any
consolation, some parts
of her body are still alive.
Her heart, for example.
And her hands.
The transporter requires
biometric authentication
for it to work,
so I hung onto
the necessary bits.
You're in quite a
predicament now, Julian.
If only you had Genesis.
You could fully rematerialize
her with memories intact.
So, you have a choice.
Work with me, or join your
wife in the other world.
Which one will you choose?
[LOSER] You think those
are my only options?
That's where you're wrong.
First I'll defeat you.
And then I'll take
Genesis for myself.
Ha! Oh, really?
[LOSER]
I will save Sophia.
And restore the
honor of Adrastea,
which was blamed for
the war that you started!
I can't wait to see you try!
[LOSER] I know your weakness
and how to exploit it.
There are limits to
what you can do.
You can't close
that gate, or move it.
Do that, and you'll
really be lost.
The transporter will
disappear from your side
and you'll be stuck for good.
Hurry up and get to the point!
[LOSER]
I have all five Numbers now.
Do you know what that means?
It means I can open up
a gate of my own.
Go on, Papa, do it!
[gasps]
[gate static]
[SEAMEYER]
He's opening a gate here?
It won't do any good.
Neither you nor Sophia's heart
will be able to return.
[LOSER]
That's why...
[grunts]
[LOSER] ...I'll settle
for bringing you through
to this side instead.
Have a taste of the pain
you inflicted on the people
whose lives you
gleefully sacrificed!
Julian.
[LOSER]
Sophia...
[LOSER groans]
[SEAMEYER cackles]
You let yourself be distracted
by such an obvious fake?
How pathetic!
Papa! Say something!
You made the wrong
choice, Julian.
You could've cooperated with me,
but now, it's too late.
Onto the next
order of business.
I'm coming for you,
Kyoma Mabuchi!
[MIRA]
Can you get up?
[KYOMA]
Why bother? It's over.
I had no right to any of
this in the first place.
I didn't deserve to
come home again.
I wasn't worthy to return and
stand before Miyabi's grave.
I couldn't save anybody.
Except my own sorry self.
I don't understand why
you're acting like this.
Wallowing in self-pity
isn't like you, Kyoma.
You should stop talking.
[MIRA] You should
pull yourself together!
The Kyoma I know is violent,
rash, and blunt.
He acts without thinking.
He makes no apologies to anyone.
And he is always
true to himself.
Even though he hates coils,
he saved a robot from the void.
It hasn't even been six
months since we first met.
I may not know
everything about you,
but some things I do.
And one is that you're a
person who never gives up!
Not as long as there
is a possibility!
Be quiet!
All this is the result
of me holding onto
a possibility that's not real!
[MIRA] What happened here
wasn't your fault.
[KYOMA] You don't get it.
I remember now.
I know what happened.
[KYOMA] With this coil,
anything could be possible.
That's what I thought
to myself when I held
Genesis in my hand
that day. With it,
Miyabi could truly be saved.
She could be made whole again.
That's when I made my decision.
I would bring Genesis
with me through the gate.
For Miyabi's sake.
Even if I died and my
body was torn to pieces.
There was still a
chance that the coil
could be used to help her.
That's what I believed,
the reason I jumped.
We know how well
that turned out!
Next thing I knew,
I was in the hospital.
Miyabi was dead, and my
comrades had been annihilated.
Couldn't remember what happened,
but I was certain
coils were to blame.
They'd taken everything from me.
That's the lie I kept
telling myself.
That's awful. I'm sorry.
[KYOMA] I don't know what
it is you want me to do,
but I can't do it. I don't
have power over possibility.
So save your pep talks
for someone else.
[MIRA] What now? You're just
going to run away?
[KYOMA]
Why should I stay?
There's nothing on this
island for me to fight for.
That's not what I mean.
I'm talking about Miyabi.
[KYOMA]
Huh?
[MIRA] The accident during
Miyabi's operation
happened at the same time
as the destruction
of Easter Island.
That's always bothered
you. Hasn't it?
[KYOMA] That doesn't have
anything to do with you!
[MIRA]
Yes it does!
Will you please listen to me?
My body was originally
created for Miyabi.
Which means if she were
still alive, I wouldn't be here,
not in the form that I am now.
If it weren't for you,
I would never have been made.
I was born because you and
she chose the possibility
of giving her a new body.
So I would say this has
a lot to do with me!
Wouldn't you?
[grunts] What do you want?
You still don't
remember everything.
Let me help. Let me honor Miyabi
and the possibility
that she believed in.
What would she want you to do?
Are you going to give up
or keep fighting?
[grunting]
[MIYABI]
Don't worry, it'll be okay.
Whatever happens, I'm on your
side and I always will be.
Hey, Kyo. Thanks for waiting.
Before you go, my name
is Miyabi Azumaya.
[pants]
[MIRA grunts]
[MIRA]
Uh? Hey. What are you doing?
That's my hand. Kyoma!
Damn. You're identical.
Right down to the
lines on your palm.
[gasps]
[KYOMA]
All right.
How do you plan to
help me remember?
I suspect your
memory was damaged
as a result of your
interaction with Genesis.
Something broke in the
memory center of your brain.
There was just
too much happening
that it couldn't process.
So I should just need
to fix what was broken.
Hey, I'm not a robot.
I can't just be "fixed."
[MIRA]
There must be a way to do it,
otherwise, why would
Seameyer be targeting you?
What's broken is the link
between your memories.
If I can successfully
repair that connection,
you should remember everything.
[KYOMA]
How will you do it?
By simply tracing your memories
and knitting them back together.
I analyzed the device
that Seameyer teleported
into your ear, so I can
use that as a reference.
I learned some things
from my experience
in Yasogami, too.
Don't worry. I feel very
confident I can do this.
[sighs] All right.
How do we get started?
Well, about that...
I'll have to put you into a
deep sleep, which may require--
[KYOMA]
You can stop right there.
I know what to expect.
You've put me to sleep before.
Don't you remember?
Yes, I do.
How could I forget the
first time we met, Kyoma?
This will be a little like that.
[cracking]
[snaps]
[MIRA]
All right. Begin tracing.
[KYOMA]
What is all this?
[MIRA] Oh, so you can see
what's going on, too?
[KYOMA]
These fragments are my memories?
[MIRA] Yes, but they've been
scattered, as you can see.
If I can reestablish
the links between them,
they should be restored.
Are you going to
continue hiding?
Then I'll just have to find
you by tracing your memories.
One way or another,
I'll get what I came for.
Now, where are you?
[cackles]
[MIRA] Dimension W lies
beyond the third dimension.
It's difficult to access.
In order for this to work,
I have to be very aware
of Kyoma's memories.
[grunts]
[KYOMA]
What's wrong, piece of junk.
Don't worry. It's nothing.
There was just some strain
on the coil, that's all.
[KYOMA]
Are you sure?
The lines on your body
are turning red.
[MIRA] It'll be all right.
We're almost there now.
[MIRA] The preparations
to connect are complete.
[KYOMA]
All right. Do it!
Okay!
Go on, Mabuchi, do it.
[SOPHIA] It's too powerful!
No one can have it!
Kyoma!
[KYOMA] These are memories
from that day.
Images of people in different
places, all overlapping.
[KYOMA yelling]
[KYOMA] The island.
It's being swallowed up.
[MIYABI]
Kyo?
[gasps]
[KYOMA]
The hospital?
[SEIRA] Impossible!
The transplant operation
went perfectly. Why is she
on the verge of death?
[KYOMA]
On the verge of death?
[DOCTOR 12A]
Doctor!
We're getting abnormal
readings from the coil.
Her consciousness
is dissipating.
It's flowing away from the coil.
Does this mean that
the brain alone
isn't enough to
hold onto the soul?
[DOCTOR 12D] Hurry,
Dr. Seira. We need to run!
[KYOMA] Damn it! Why can't
I get any closer?
[DOCTOR 12A]
The coil's at its limit!
We can't hold it back.
[KYOMA]
I know!
I have to find a way to
get Genesis to them.
With this, they could do it.
They could save her!
[gasps]
Is it really you?
[inaudible]
[KYOMA] It's too much.
The world is breaking?
So. You want me to...?
It's the right thing
to do. Isn't it?
All right.
[inaudible]
[KYOMA grunts]
[KYOMA gasps]
Miyabi, I...
This is how it should be.
Thank you. I'm glad it
was you. Goodbye, Kyoma.
[KYOMA] Yes. That's right.
That's what happened.
It wasn't just me.
We made the decision together.
[KYOMA]
I can remember all of it now.
And I'm glad I can remember.
[KYOMA]
That's enough.
You can wake me
up now, I'm ready.
Where'd you go?
Hey. Piece of junk?
[KYOMA grunts]
Damn it.
Gotta stop punching
myself in my dreams.
Doesn't feel too good.
[KYOMA]
She's gone and I think know why.
Hey, Kyoma! Doin' okay?
--Fine. You guys all right?
--[DEBBIE] And up we go!
[KYOMA] Your Highness.
I'm glad you made it.
I very nearly didn't.
Fortunately, these two
were there to save me.
Loo, everyone's all right here.
[LWAI sighs]
What a relief!
[SALVA] We're alive,
but we're not any closer
to solving our problem.
That monster of his is enormous.
How can we defeat it?
[KYOMA] I've got an
idea that might work.
[LOSER]
You think we should tie it up.
Yes, that would be effective.
Provided we're able to
pull it off, of course.
[SALVA]
You're still alive.
[LOSER] There should be the
cable of a particle accelerator
buried around the outer
circumference of Adrastea.
I think that would
suit our purpose.
Well, if digging
is what you need,
we're here to help!
[LWAI] Then I can use my
Ras Dashen to carry it.
[LOSER]
All right.
But how do we get Seameyer
to stand still long enough?
He wants to know where
Genesis is, right?
Let's give him what he wants.
[MIRA panting]
This coil is about to go wild.
I have to get as far
from Kyoma as I can.
Or he'll be caught up in the
materialization of Dimension W.
[yelps]
[SEAMEYER cackles]
I finally caught one of them!
Now, let's see my prize.
Huh?
[yelps]
It's not human. This is a robot.
They've made a lot
of advancements
since I've been gone.
Right, I remember now.
Yurizaki's wife
was into robotics.
That explains it. Hello, robot.
I'm going to take you apart
and use you to make
my arms and legs.
Since you're not alive,
you can move in and
out through the gate.
[MIRA] He hasn't noticed
how close my coil
is to going out of control.
I could get closer
to the center of the system
and let it go wild.
If I did that,
I could save everyone.
No one else would
have to get hurt.
[KYOMA] Easy, now.
Don't do anything stupid.
Well. Hello again, Seameyer.
Mabuchi! You're here!
So, what are you waiting for?
I've got what you want.
Just come and get it.
What are you doing here?
No, never mind. Just leave, now!
My coil's going--
[KYOMA]
Be quiet.
Nobody's expecting you
to sacrifice yourself.
Just let me take care of this.
[MIRA]
But what about the coil?
Gonna need you to deal with it
for another ten or 20 minutes.
Assuming you don't want
me caught up in it.
I'm sick of running.
I don't wanna do it anymore.
If you wanna see my memory,
I'll show it to you.
You're planning
something. What is it?
[KYOMA]
Aw, what's wrong, Seameyer?
Are you scared?
Are you afraid to learn where
your prized possession is?
I thought you were dying
to know what happened.
Who I gave Genesis to.
[SEAMEYER] You gave my
coil to somebody else?
Show me! Let me
into your memory!
All right, He took the bait!
[SEAMEYER pants]
Where is it? Where's Genesis?
Where's the bastard who has it?
[KYOMA] Take a look.
It's been me the whole time.
What? You didn't
have it, though.
--I would've known about it.
--[clatter]
Huh?
[screams]
I considered using it,
but I didn't.
Miyabi and I decided
that nobody should.
Not ever. That's why
I destroyed it.
The shock from the
destruction of Genesis
must have sent me
back to the island.
That moment is lost
forever, though.
I don't think anybody
could restore it.
You created something amazing.
There's no denying that.
Truly amazing.
But it will never be used again.
It's gone, and
that's the reality.
You have to accept it.
And so do I.
[SEAMEYER screaming]
[gasps] What's going on?
How could he get any more
insane than he already was?
[SEAMEYER screaming]
There was no reason!
My whole life was pointless!
This is the end of everything!
I have no need for a planet
I can't return to.
I'll destroy it!
I'll trigger
materialization so massive,
it will swallow up the Earth
and kill everything on it!
The whole planet will be a void!
He's wielding an enormous
amount of energy.
I'm not gonna let you do that.
Not a chance in hell.
What is this? A cable?
All right, Kyoma. Let's do it!
What's happening?
Was this your plan Julian?
Nice try. I'll just
cut this apart and--
[SEAMEYER gasping]
[SEAMEYER]
It's coming through!
[screams]
No! No! No! No!
--[KYOMA] Seameyer.
--Huh?
[growls]
There's still one thing
I wanna say to you
before this is over.
[KYOMA] Why do you like those
things so much, anyway?
What's so great about 'em?
[MIYABI] Mm... I just think
there's something special
about stuff people leave behind.
It's proof of the
lives they've lived.
Like parts of them remain
even after they're gone.
It might sound silly to you,
but by treasuring the past,
we can make the present
shine even brighter.
Our lives are full of
failures and tragedies.
But each one is the source
of a new possibility.
What you did was truly horrible.
And I lost everything in the
world that was dear to me.
But do you know what?
If that hadn't happened,
there are possibilities
that wouldn't have
been realized.
So I don't have any regrets.
And I'm not giving up.
[MIYABI]
You know what I hope?
I hope that someday
I get to be somebody's
precious memory. I like that.
Because it means that I'll
help create the future!
Nothing that either of
us did was pointless.
Don't you see? Not a thing.
[growls] Shut up! Don't talk
like I'm part of the past!
I'm alive!
Here, Kyoma! Take this!
It's a piece of my Papa!
You have to win!
It's time to finish this.
[screaming]
This has to be done.
The last spin dart
I'll ever use.
[KYOMA]
Goodbye, Haruka Seameyer.
You've done enough damage
in this lifetime.
Return to the sea
of possibilities!
[gasping]
[SEAMEYER gasps]
[SEAMEYER whimpers]
[LOSER]
You did it, Kyoma Mabuchi.
There is a hole in
the gate. That sphere.
The space made by Dimension W.
All of it will be
extinguished soon.
My Sophia's soul will
be released as well.
She will finally be free again.
And before long, I'll join her.
I love you, Ellie. Thank you.
Damn it! I think I might
be in a little trouble.
Kyoma!
Your coil!
[gasps]
[SALVA gasps]
[LWAI gasps]
[HARRY, DEBBIE gasp]
The island's engulfed
in green light!
You did it, didn't you,
Mabuchi? You succeeded.
[SHIDO]
Mira. Mira. Listen carefully.
It's time now. I can finally
entrust this to you.
Take it.
And learn about the human heart.
Go on, Mira. You're ready.
[MIRA]
Father...
[SHIDO]
You did well.
[MIRA]
Please, Father, wait!
Father! Wait!
--[KYOMA screaming]
--[gasps]
Thank you, Father!
Who do you think
you're calling Father?
[MIRA] I was all wrapped
up in green light.
Father was there.
[KYOMA] You should just
focus on staying alive!
[gasps] Alive? You never
called me that before.
Damn it! Now's not the time.
You wanna take a look around?
[LWAI]
Kyoma!
[KYOMA grunts]
That was close. Are you okay?
We're coming, Kyoma!
I'll probably have some
bruises, but I'll be fine.
[SALVA]
You're all right?
[DEBBIE]
I was so worried!
And what about you, Mira?
Are you okay, too?
Yes! Thanks, it's
nice of you to ask.
[gasps]
[ELIZABETH sobbing]
Papa! Papa!
[SALVA]
I hope Loser found his peace.
Me, too.
That he was reunited with
his wife on the other side.
[MIRA gasps]
[sobbing]
[heartbeat]
Huh?
[KYOMA] All those Collectors,
and none succeeded.
We didn't find the first coil
to start working on the island.
And it turns out, I'd
already destroyed Genesis.
[SALVA]
Yes.
I had thought we might
be hunting for something
other than Genesis, but it
looks like it came to nothing
either way.
I failed, Lwai. I'm sorry.
[SALVA sighs]
You're right.
There's no point in regretting
what can't be changed.
There's work to be done.
We'll have a funeral
for the dead.
And good wine for the living.
[CASSIDY gasps] That was close!
I thought I was a goner!
[SANCHOS grunts]
[zipping]
That was it, wasn't it?
The last battle of our
war has been fought.
[KYOMA]
Yeah.
Thanks for your help, Mira.
[gasps]
Sure.
[KYOMA]
Let's go home.
[MIRA]
Okay. Oh. Kyoma, wait.
Look up there.
On top of that hill!
At the bottom right
of the Moai statue.
There's a flower blooming. See?
[KYOMA]
I don't have robot eyes.
[MIRA]
Ah!
The void's gone now, remember?
No surprise that flowers
have started to bloom.
[KYOMA]
Thank you, Miyabi.
[KYOMA] This is how I am,
how I've always been.
Trouble and danger
come looking for me.
Like I'm some kinda magnet.
[MAN 12A]
Yee-ha, ha, ha!
[MARY]
Don't screw up, you two.
This guy is bad news.
He's already killed
three people.
[KOOROGI] His left arm
is completely mechanized,
and his bottom half has
a reinforced exoskeleton.
Won't be easy to take him down.
[chuckles]
[KYOMA] Probably would've
turned out even worse,
if Miyabi hadn't come along
to give me a new path.
Get ready! He's headed your way.
[KYOMA] That's why I'm
gonna keep doing this job.
New paths. New possibilities.
Besides, this is what
I am: a Collector.