[MIRA] This is so strange:
like we're on another planet.
[MIRA gasps]
Even the microorganisms
must have been wiped out.
That would explain how corpses
like this haven't rotted away.
Take a good, long look
around you, piece of junk.
This mess is what lies beyond
the culture of coils.
[KYOMA]
Well, how'd it go?
I tried, but I can't
make contact with them.
[MIRA] There was a big storm
over the ocean that died down
a few minutes ago.
Is it possible they
decided it would be safer
to turn back around?
Something tells me that prince
wouldn't let a storm stop him.
What do we do if we
can't get a signal?
Radar's not gonna do
us any good, either.
Let's forget technology
and rely on our eyes.
If it's a set of eyes you're
looking for, leave it to me.
My vision's excellent, you know.
I can see almost as
far as a satellite.
--[MIRA] Hey!
--How well do think you'll see
--What are you doing? Stop it!
--if your coil's not working?
[ALBERT] Modern AIs are
pretty incredible, huh?
They seem more and more
human all the time.
Ha. Whatever may have
happened to the rest of 'em,
I'm still going.
[car doors click]
You better be careful. I can't
come save you this time.
[chuckles] I think I'll be fine.
--[engine revs]
--[KYOMA] See ya!
[engine roars]
Ah, the sound of a V10 engine.
Just listen to that roar.
Try not to die
out there, Mabuchi.
[WORKER 8A]
Your Majesty!
We are so honored that you came!
[MAURA]
Mm.
[WORKER 8A]
Salva! Come over here, please.
His Majesty the king
has arrived.
The king? And he
wants to see me?
So, you're young Salva, are you?
Yes, Your Majesty.
It's an honor to meet you.
As they told me,
you are a promising boy,
with a good look to your face.
I do not have a son
of my own, you see.
I would have you
become my child, Salva.
From this day forward,
you will be known to all
as Salva-Enna-Tibesti.
Will I be... a prince?
[MAURA] Do you see
what they're building?
That's New Tesla Energy's
60th tower.
It's a symbol of the future
that awaits our country.
Metal essential to the
manufacture of coils
can only be found here in Isla.
That metal is the reason
our country has developed
so swiftly in recent years.
As long as we can
continue to supply it,
our future will be secure.
[SALVA]
But for how long, Father?
Our mines will
run out eventually.
Our neighbors are already
jealous of our prosperity
and the wealth of our resources.
Shouldn't we try to find a more
reliable base for our power?
So that we aren't so completely
dependent on one export?
[MAURA]
You really are clever, Salva.
Far wiser than your years.
But remember this:
if you hunger for power,
you invite your own destruction.
That's one reason I host
banquets for our neighbors:
to promote good will and show
that we are not a threat.
At times you may see me
acting docile or foolish.
It is because, if I do not,
I cannot protect this country.
[SERVANT 8A]
Your Majesty, it is time.
You' re showing
your weakness, Father.
That isn't right.
[SERVANT 8B]
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Good news! It's a blessed day!
The queen is pregnant!
[MAURA]
Is this true? Take me to her!
Cancel all my appointments!
[crying]
[MAURA laughs]
Listen to my son!
Such a good, strong cry!
I will call him Lwai.
Lwai-Aura-Tibesti!
[MAURA laughs]
[MAURA]
Now, Salva, you must look after
your younger brother and
support him in all ways.
because someday, this child
will be king of Isla.
Yes. I will look after him.
I promise you, Father.
[LWAI] Why are you always
staring outside?
Are you looking at the clouds?
[SALVA] No. I'm looking
at New Tesla's tower.
The tower? Why?
Can I tell you something?
It's about a dream I have.
[LWAI]
Yes, please! Tell me about it.
[SALVA] I'll make the throne,
and you'll sit in it.
I'll shape the world,
then hand it over to you.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
That will be best.
I'm sure of it.
Become king of Isla, Lwai.
It sounds scary! Being the king.
[K.K. panting]
Damn it.
[CHRYSLER] I would never have
imagined that Grodia would fall.
Where are the others?
Are we the only ones
who made it?
I don't see anyone.
They must have been
left behind on the bridge.
A-A-Achoo!
I'm soakin' wet!
Dry clothes, Sanchos!
I don't think he can
help you right now.
Hey! What happened to him?
[CHRYSLER]
That sphere touched him.
I don't know what it did,
but it left him like this.
[CASSIDY]
What was that thing?
Who knows. But at least the
coils started working again.
[K.K.]
He's practically dead.
There's no point in
lugging him around.
Hey, don't be a bastard, K.K.!
[CHRYSLER gasps]
Where did an Islero
robot come from?
And you see who's operating it?
That's the first prince,
Lwai-Aura-Tibesti.
Please, I need help!
It's Salva and Lasithi!
Something's wrong with them.
[CHRYSLER] It's understandable
that he's distraught.
This is his brother.
What do we do?
Go home. What else
can we do now?
You really gonna leave it like
that after comin' this far?
Listen to me, Lwai!
You will save me.
I know you will!
[CASSIDY]
Kid. Ya look dazed.
Are you all right?
[LWAI]
Uh, yeah.
[CASSIDY]
These three are freezing.
Their body temperatures
are scary-low.
[LWAI]
Until my brother recovers,
I will be in charge here.
Does everyone understand?
From now on, I speak
with Salva's voice.
What he would want, is for
the contest to continue.
That's exactly what
I was waitin' to hear.
Well that's it, then.
[K.K. grunts]
[LWAI] First, we will cross to
Easter Island and find a place
for Salva and
the others to rest.
Honestly! My poor hair.
What was that sphere-thing?
[LOSER] There are actually
three possibilities.
One of them is that
which we desire most,
but I can't be certain yet.
Hold on a second, Papa.
You know what that creepy
thing back there was?
[LOSER] I might. But much
is still unclear.
The truth is sleeping
at ground zero.
So, is that what
we do now, then?
Go to ground zero?
[LOSER]
Easier said than done.
[ELIZABETH]
Hm?
It just turned off!
[LOSER] Beyond that is
the void, coils stop working,
life itself comes
to a standstill.
We have to choose our
route very carefully.
[ELIZABETH] But our
destination is right there!
[ELIZABETH] Hm? What? Why are
you looking at me like that?
Papa?
[LOSER]
Come, Ellie. Let's go.
I will do what I must.
I have no choice
but to continue.
[door creaks]
How is it?
I don't see anybody.
And it's still in good shape.
It doesn't look like it got
caught in a protrusion.
Not a sign of life anywhere.
[K.K.]
Hm...
[K.K.] Well, now that we're here
what's our next step gonna be?
[YURI] First things first.
Let's talk about the reward.
No offense, but if your brother
doesn't snap out of it,
who's gonna pay the winner?
[LWAI]
I won't answer that question.
I'll let Salva do it himself.
He took steps to ensure
the contest could continue
even in his absence.
Greetings, intrepid Collectors,
and welcome to Easter Island.
I made this recording
in case unforeseen
circumstances should arise.
Because on this island,
it's only natural
to assume that they will.
This is the only
place in the world
that has ever fallen
completely into the void.
So we have no concept of what
it means to recover from that.
Nor do we know how such a thing
could even be made possible.
[grunting]
Damn rocks.
We might have been better off
with a four-wheel drive vehicle
that had a higher suspension.
[KYOMA]
Shut up.
Huh?
Quick, Kyoma, I think
you'll wanna see this!
Even Dr. Yurizaki himself
had difficulty theorizing about
the return from the void.
So anything we now learn
will be well worth the price
we have to pay.
Wait, is this broadcasting live?
Whew. Getting here sure
wasn't the easiest thing
we've ever done, was it,
Brother? Huh? Prince Salva?
By this point,
I've already told you
what I want you to collect as
well as the reward I'm offering.
That reward remains valid,
even in the event of my death.
I'll be monitoring
all of you very closely.
So do not attempt
to either run away
with the coil or destroy it.
[CASSIDY] Come on, Sanchos,
wake up already!
We don't have time for sleep!
The reward was 50 million.
Even if you split it five ways,
that's still ten million
dollars for each of us.
You mean work together?
I don't think so.
I can collect that coil
all on my own, no problem.
And I'll save Sanchos,
too, while I'm at it.
[CHRYSLER] Good answers.
I was hoping you would say that.
There's one more matter
to warn you about.
Dr. Yurizaki speculated that,
once freed from the void,
that which was frozen
will regain motion
as new possibilities
assert themselves.
This applies to living
and non-living entities.
Living beings will
have sustained
extensive damage to their cells,
which will likely result
in the significant impairment
of both body and spirit.
Impairment? What's that
supposed to mean?
[MAN moaning]
[CHRYSLER]
It's in the basement!
[MAN moaning]
[CASSIDY]
Is that a zombie?
[LWAI]
No, he's just become unfrozen.
[CHRYSLER] So, the island
started moving again?
Did we trigger it
just by coming here?
[K.K., YURI gasp]
[OCTOPUS ROBOT 8A]
Eliminate. Eliminate.
[YURI]
What is that?
A robot?
We've got another thing
that came back to life?
[LWAI]
Hm.
[CASSIDY]
Good defense!
[CHRYSLER]
An energy shield.
It must've diverted the energy
from impact into Dimension W.
The rest of you, go.
Get out of here!
[LWAI, CASSIDY panting]
You'll take care of
things here, right?
[CASSIDY]
What? Hey!
Wait a second.
What's he talkin' about?
Looks like it's
decided, Cassidy.
Huh?
We leave this place
in your hands.
What the hell're you sayin'?
Where are the other guys?
[CHRYSLER] Yuri and K.K. took
off on their own a while ago.
Those cowards,
sneakin' away like that.
I'll stay a little longer
to watch the prince fight,
but then I'll be going, too.
Good luck!
Come back here! You!
[CASSIDY gasps]
This thing again?!
[LASITHI]
Leave it.
Physical attacks like
that aren't going to
do you any good.
It will only cause it
to strike back at you.
Just try to stay still.
As far as I can tell, it only
seems interested in men.
It looks like you
were right. Good call.
[MAN moans]
What the hell is that thing?
Well, that was unexpected.
[LWAI]
All right then.
The sphere again!
[LWAI] Good. It seems
no one was harmed.
Lasithi, it's me.
Yes, Prince Lwai.
[LWAI] I'm so glad
you're awake! How's Salva?
[LASITHI] I'm sorry, Prince
Lwai. He is still insensible.
We were rendered unconscious
by different means.
It wasn't the sphere
that knocked me out,
but a physical attack.
I may be wrong, but it
seemed like the sphere
was looking for something.
Go now, my prince.
You must find out
what that thing is,
and do whatever you can
to save your brother.
Please fight for him.
Remember his dream,
Your Highness.
Remember my brother's dream...
Okay, I'll do it.
And not just for Salva,
but for Isla and Africa.
Whatever happens, I will
not forget why I'm here.
You are a kind boy, Prince Lwai.
I wish you success.
[gasps] Hey, look out!
There are two armored
robots up ahead!
[KYOMA] Things've already
started movin' again, huh?
[GUARD ROBOTS]
Proceed no further.
You may not pass.
I thought something
like this might happen.
[engine roars]
Speeding up?
[GUARD ROBOT 8A]
Warning! Warning!
[engine roars]
[tires screech]
[shrieks] I can't see anything!
You could have warned me
you were going to do that!
Those robots weren't the only
ones you blinded, you know!
Your eyes'll heal, right?
They won't! Fine, yes they will.
But that's not really the point
I'm trying to make, here.
I just think you could try to be
a little more considerate of me,
that's all.
Huh?
You know, just forget it!
[gasps] Be careful.
There's a disturbance.
I sense fighting
one kilometer ahead.
[explosion]
[OCTOPUS ROBOT 8A]
Eliminate. Eliminate.
[DEBBIE gasps]
[HARRY]
Debbie, get into the hole!
[DEBBIE]
'Kay!
[HARRY grunts]
Too slow! I'm over here now.
[HARRY grunting]
[HARRY yelping]
[HARRY] Aha! Let's see how it
does with a hole in its head!
Uh?
[yelps]
Hey, look out! Above you!
Gotcha!
[HARRY]
Whoa!
That was close.
Are you all right?
Phew!
[KYOMA] Taking on an armored
robot with a shovel.
I don't think I've
seen that one before.
Thanks for all the help and
all, sir, but who are you?
Just a Collector who
happened to be in the area.
Wow! Not too bad
looking, are you?
[MIRA] Oh, I'm Mira, by
the way. Nice to meet you.
Looks like it's getting
ready to attack!
[MIRA]
Take that!
Huh. Not too bad, I guess.
That won't work. It's shielded!
Yeah, I noticed that.
What's he doing?
Are those wires?
The shield deflects my
skewers but doesn't detect
the wires attached.
This robot isn't dexterous
enough to untangle itself.
It's not even smart enough
to know it should.
There, I think
that oughta do it.
Handsome and smart. Yeah,
I'm in love. He's amazing!
[KYOMA]
I haven't lost my touch.
That's something, at least.
[KYOMA]
Hey, piece of junk.
Right!
Just give me one second.
I've retrieved the coil.
What do you want me to do now?
[KYOMA]
What kind is it?
Well, it's pretty old,
but it looks like
a normal coil to me.
[KYOMA]
Toss it.
Uh--! But it still
seems to work just fine.
You heard me.
[MIRA]
Aw. Okay.
[KYOMA] There'll be more
where that came from.
Assuming we make it
over this protrusion.
[MIRA] It doesn't look
like we'll be able
to go by car this time.
Sure we can. We just have to
find an underground tunnel.
And you think there's
one around here?
There was five
years ago, at least.
The route we used
on the mission.
[DEBBIE]
Sorry for interrupting.
But if it's a tunnel
you're looking for,
then maybe we can help.
See, we're pretty good
at digging holes.
[HARRY]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
[YURI] A couple more seconds
and I'll blow you to pieces!
[YURI yelling]
[groans]
Just playing the game. Sorry.
Damn it, K.K.
What'd you do to me?
[K.K.] I've been waiting
this whole time
to get one of you alone.
It took longer than I thought.
Wait, stop.
Don't worry.
It's a simple operation.
[DEBBIE]
Ha, ha!
Whoa!
[KYOMA] Damn it. This is
wrong. Just plain wrong.
Well, what else
could we do?
There are only two seats.
They did find the tunnel for us,
so I think we
owe them, don't you?
[KYOMA grunts]
Personally, I like the
way things turned out.
We're all in this together now!
Tch. When I find that
coil, I'm not planning
to hand it over to anyone, and I
won't let it go without a fight.
I will destroy it. It will
never function again.
You have any idea where it is?
If I did, I'd be a lot
more relaxed right now.
Kyoma, in 600 meters
we'll reach an area
of total darkness and it will
continue for roughly 800 meters.
The void.
Yes, that does seem likely.
The car will be fine,
but we humans won't.
We've got ten or 20
seconds at the most.
You'll wanna hang on
tight up there.
[DEBBIE, HARRY]
Whoa!
[MIRA]
Four hundred... Two hundred...
Very soon, all coils will
stop working. Including mine.
I'm frightened.
I'll enter a death state inside
the void, and that scares me.
I mean it, Kyoma.
I'm very anxious. I--
[KYOMA] Robots shouldn't
have anxiety issues.
You're over-programmed.
[KYOMA] It's like all the blood
is draining from my body.
My arms and legs are numb.
Very soon. I'll be unconscious.
[HARRY, DEBBIE grunting]
[gasps]
[tires screech]
[HARRY, DEBBIE yelp]
[car door clicks]
Can you stand?
Uh. I'll try to.
Do I still have legs?
I'm scared of dying,
just like everybody else,
so this will be
difficult for me, too!
Um, Kyoma.
You're not in the car.
So, everyone made it then.
[MIRA]
You were worried about me?
Why would I be?
[MIRA]
So many robots destroyed.
[KYOMA] It's proof that
Grendel came through here.
Just a little farther now.
And then we'll be
at ground zero.
That's right.
We're about to
visit the birthplace
of Easter Island's destruction.
What kind of a facility was it?
Honestly, there isn't
much I can remember
about the place.
Except for one thing:
It was called Adrastea.
That's an unusual name.
[KYOMA] That's what the
commander called it, anyway.
Well, none of the
robots are operational,
and there's no sign of
the void. Let's try to, uh--
What's wrong, Kyoma?
[KYOMA]
Damn it. Get ahold of yourself!
You came here to settle things
for good, didn't you?
You came to erase doubt,
to kill all the
"maybes," to make sure
she doesn't have
to wait anymore.
[KYOMA]
Get ready! We're goin' in!
Uh, right!
[KYOMA]
What the hell? Loser?