[motor humming]
[MIRA] I don't know if
this is such a good idea.
Maybe we should turn around.
[KYOMA]
Huh?
[MIRA] Well, I mean,
that incident 21 years ago?
And, you know, the sightings?
Quit babbling.
What're you even saying?
Look out, Kyoma!
[tires screech]
Huh? I swear there
was a girl here.
She was wearing a
white dress. I saw her!
You broken again already?
Wait! There should
be an image in my log.
What? There's nothing there.
That doesn't make sense!
Maybe it really was a ghost,
like I was saying.
Robots aren't afraid
of ghosts. Now get in.
[MIRA]
Uh--
[MIRA gasps]
--[car horn blares]
--[yelps]
Coming! I'm coming!
Don't leave me!
[door clicks]
[tires screech]
--How's it going, Mabuchi?
--[KYOMA] I'm leaving.
[MARY]
Have a seat.
I'm here in an
official capacity.
New Tesla has a job
it needs done.
Here, take a look at this.
A report about an
incident that happened
at Lake Yasogami last week.
The man who died
was Shijuro Sakaki,
known for his grotesque
mystery novels.
The incident occurred
in the study of his home,
which serves as the local hotel.
The cause of death was drowning.
There was no sign of
anyone coming or going
from the room.
The novelist was alone
save for the housekeeping robot.
The room contained
a water dispenser,
which was empty at the time
the body was discovered.
So, what happened, then?
The robot forced the
water from the dispenser
down his throat?
[ALBERT]
For a robot to kill,
it would have to run
on an illegal coil.
An official coil would
submit a report
to New Tesla and shut down.
Of course, the case gets a bit
more complicated than that.
If this was simply a matter
of an illegal coil,
I wouldn't have
bothered you with it.
[KYOMA sighs]
[ALBERT] Here's the video
recorded by the robot's camera.
[SAKAKI] I'd like some water,
Keebo. Get it for me.
[KEEBO]
Yes, sir. Right away.
Here you are, sir. Your water.
Keebo?
--[SAKAKI grunting]
--[mechanical groaning]
Seems like an
inconvenient time
for the video to cut out.
Very. And it doesn't return
until two minutes later.
[knocking]
[door creaks]
[KATO] Pardon me, sir.
Mind if I come in?
I brought your...
[gasps]
[KATO screams]
We inspected
the coil, of course,
but, like the robot,
we found no problem with it.
No trace of an illegal
coil being used, either.
Which means that whoever
killed Sakaki may have
some way of circumventing
New Tesla's security.
That's where you come in.
I want you to find whatever
was used to interfere
with the robot and
collect it, if possible.
Why not do it yourselves?
We'd rather outsource.
It's the ghosts, you see.
[KYOMA]
Hm?
[ALBERT] Lake Yasogami
is a manmade lake created
when a dam was built
21 years ago.
Its rushed construction and
bad weather led to an accident
that claimed a large
number of lives.
Ever since that tragedy,
the area has become famous
for sightings of the paranormal.
Spooky, don't you think?
[KYOMA]
Tch. Ghost stories, Al?
Anyway, we're taking
this job. You on board?
You ask that like I
actually have a choice.
Listen up, ya heap of metal.
Yes?
[KYOMA]
There'll be other guests here.
So you need to act
like a normal robot.
Don't cry or laugh
or get scared
of stuff like ghosts, okay?
Right. I'll do my best not to.
Thank you for waiting,
Mr. Mabuchi.
Welcome to our establishment.
If I might take just a
moment to introduce you.
[MAKITA]
This is Ms. Marisa Sakaki.
She is the current
owner of this hotel.
Please forgive my appearance.
It's been a very trying week.
Ms. Sakaki's elder brother
was the late Shijuro Sakaki,
the hotel's previous owner.
[KATO] You must be getting
tired, ma'am. Shall we?
And should you need
anything at all,
I am Makita, the hotel manager.
[HAGEYAMA]
Hey!
How much longer
do I have to wait?
You're a lousy maid,
you know that?
It won't be long, sir.
I'm very sorry.
My sincere apologies,
Mr. Hageyama.
Whatever you may need,
I'll see to it personally.
That's more like it.
Hm?
Ah. And I guess you two
must be the Collectors
from New Tesla. Very brave.
Aren't you worried
you'll meet the same fate
your predecessors did?
[HAGEYAMA laughs]
That was the journalist,
Mr. Hageyama.
He is doing research for his
biography of Mr. Shijuro.
[gasps]
[ELIZABETH]
Oh, hello.
Some new faces, I see.
[KYOMA]
Who's this?
[MIRA]
She's cute.
My name's Elizabeth
Greenhough-Smith.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[MIRA] Why do I feel like
I've seen her before?
[yelps]
You really shouldn't stare
at people like that, you know.
It's terribly bad manners.
Uh...
That's a very well-made
robot. I'm impressed.
[KYOMA grunts]
[MAKITA] If you will come
with me, Mr. Mabuchi.
I would be happy to
show you to your room.
Oh my, is this your room?
What a coincidence!
Coincidence my ass.
--If you will excuse me, sir.
--What are you doing here?
I'm on vacation.
I had planned an island getaway,
but at the last minute,
I decided that coming here
would be much more interesting.
So, I made a few changes
to my itinerary.
Is this the partner you've
recently acquired, Mabuchi?
I believe her name was...
Ah, Mira, isn't it?
There's a similar robot
at the tower front desk.
Nice piece of work.
--[KYOMA] What're tryin' to say?
--[MIRA] Act normal. Act normal.
Only that you really
ought to be more grateful
for everything
Mary's done for you.
After what happened,
you were practically a shut-in
until she helped you return
to society as a Collector.
And you repay her by
running off to Dendendo
and keeping her out of the loop?
You had me followed?
I have to admit,
you surprised me.
I wasn't expecting you
to ask about Numbers.
[growls]
[KYOMA, ALBERT grunting]
[ALBERT]
What, was it something I said?
[KYOMA grunts]
[gasps]
[shoes squeaking]
[KYOMA grunting]
[MIRA]
What would a normal robot do?
[KYOMA]
Get the hell outta here!
What are you doing?
This is the third floor!
Sadly, that's not high enough.
Tomorrow at 9pm. The lounge.
We'll have a drink
and chat a little.
I'll see ya there.
Wow. He's amazing.
[KYOMA]
Of course he is.
That goes without saying
for a beast of Grendel.
[MIRA] Sorry, what's
a beast of Grendel?
[KYOMA]
Just a name, that's all.
Something that's
part of my past now.
Hm?
[KYOMA]
Huh.
So, sleeping arrangements...
[KYOMA]
I'll take the bed in the back.
You can help yourself
to the sofa.
Right. That's what
I was thinking.
[laughs]
[RED]
Well, Blue. The fog's rising.
[MARISA sighs]
I'm so sorry.
[birds chirping]
[yawns]
[KYOMA]
Hey.
Oh, good morning!
Is it time to get up now?
How much sleep can
a robot possibly need?
Piece of junk.
P-P-P-Piece of junk?
[KYOMA]
Let's get going.
Y'see all these books?
I want you to scan through them.
[MIRA] Wouldn't it be easier
if we just downloaded them
from the internet?
Don't be stupid.
We're not gonna find
the clues we need online.
[door creaks, clicks]
[sighs]
[car engine humming]
[MIRA groans]
[KYOMA]
Hey.
[screams]
Jeez! Don't sneak up
on me like that!
What did I tell you about
being scared of everything?
I know, I'm sorry!
But I store information
in images, and that makes
reading books a very
immersive experience.
[KYOMA] Yeah, whatever.
Just hurry up and finish.
[MIRA]
Okay, but--
Mira. It is not enough
for you to store
data in your memory.
As you process a
piece of information,
use it to create an image.
If the information
seems incomplete,
fill it in using memories
you've already stored.
When you're given
new information,
you must access all the images
that are related to it
and rebuild them accordingly.
I miss you, Father.
--[pop]
--[gasps]
Th-That's just the house, right?
I'll pick up the pace a bit.
[splashing]
[HAGEYAMA panting]
[HAGEYAMA yelping]
[gurgling]
[KYOMA grunts]
[KYOMA sighs]
[KYOMA] Bastard. You knew
one of the Numbers was here
the whole time, didn't you?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
What, and talk about
Numbers in front of Mary
when you'd already
avoided doing just that?
Heh. Look, just have a drink.
Here you are.
Thanks for waiting.
The accident you mentioned.
Only one of the dead was part
of the construction crew.
The rest were students,
and there was a coil involved.
This wasn't a
simple accident, was it?
[ALBERT]
Why do ya say that?
[KYOMA] Twenty-one years ago,
there weren't any towers.
Which means the coil must have
been one of the Numbers.
Unstable and unpredictable.
The Numbers caused
a horrific accident,
and the students
were its victims.
Obviously, New Tesla
covered the incident up.
But they still haven't
managed to retrieve the thing.
[laughs] Glad to see you
haven't lost your edge.
You're only half-right, though.
The accident was just that.
A tragic, but otherwise
unremarkable event.
Seriously?
But, around the same time,
one of the Numbers
was activated in this area.
That's the part of this
unfortunate story that
you've got correct.
[ALBERT] This is Kenjiro Kuroda,
professor of physics,
and his student Haruna Enamori,
a native of Yasogami.
At the time, Numbers
coil 189 was on loan
to Kuroda's laboratory. Enamori
used her access to borrow it.
[KYOMA] So, she was probably
the one who activated it.
And hers was the
only body not found.
The Bureau sent out
search parties twice
in the years that followed.
But both times, the teams
apparently encountered ghosts.
Their bodies were
found later, drowned.
All of which was the result
of the Numbers going crazy.
[ALBERT] That does seem like
the obvious conclusion.
As you guessed,
they never found the coil.
But the ghosts stopped
appearing ten years ago.
So, no more teams were sent out.
But when Shijuro Sakaki
was murdered,
you assumed that the
ghosts had reappeared.
And wasn't it ten years back
that he came to Yasogami?
That's just too much
to be a coincidence.
You think he knew something
even the Bureau didn't?
Something about the Numbers?
That seems likely, but
unfortunately, I have no proof.
[KYOMA]
Hmph.
'S pretty good.
[ALBERT] Yeah, it was the
chef's recommendation.
[MIRA] I can't take it.
His novels are too gruesome!
He describes pain
and suffering
with so much detail,
it's sickening.
It all felt so real.
I could almost smell
his characters' fear.
Still, despite all that,
I did notice something.
His books' settings are
reminiscent of Yasogami Village
as it looked in the past.
[MIRA grunts]
[MIRA] This is the image
I've created of Yasogami
as it appeared 21 years ago.
There's a clue here somewhere.
I'm sure there is.
If I can just find it--
[yelps]
[groans]
[MIRA] Ugh, I was concentrating
so hard on the image
that I forgot where
I was for a second.
--I didn't know I could fall.
--[MORINAGA laughs]
[MIRA] Can't let Kyoma
see me like this.
He'd probably call me
a piece of junk again.
[gasps]
[door clicks]
[MIRA] Gone. Is somebody
playing a joke on me?
[MIRA]
The room looks different, too.
[MIRA] An error?
My functions aren't working?
[gasps]
Uh...
[MIRA]
What's going on? Where am I?
[MIRA gasps]
[MIRA grunts]
It's not a very
pretty sight, is it?
Take a closer look. You can
see where the barbed wire...
[MIRA] Why can't I move?
It's like I'm frozen.
[MORINAGA] Would you like
an arm that matches mine?
[ALBERT] You and I know
first-hand the tragedy
that Numbers can cause.
The inexplicable horrors.
You were the only one there
that day who survived.
That's why I chose
you for this job.
Not only because of your
strength, but because you know.
[phone rings]
[KYOMA]
Find anything?
[KOOROGI laughs]
Do you really need to ask?
This is me we're talking about.
Of course I found
something. It was easy.
[KYOMA]
Spit it out. Al's here, too.
Okay, cool.
Put your phone next to his,
we're gonna need it.
I'll project what I've got.
It'll drain that old-school
battery of yours in no time.
All right, here we go.
[ALBERT, KYOMA grunt]
This is the more complete
version of the video
taken by the housekeeping robot.
I restored it as
much as I could.
This is what happened during
the missing two minutes?
[KOOROGI] That blackout out in
the original occurred because
the memory was
overwritten in real time.
The original data stream
was so large that the robot
could only record
bits and pieces of it.
Whoever those people are,
their appearance
has something to do with a coil.
[ALBERT]
Are they real?
[KOOROGI]
They have no mass.
If they did, we'd be in trouble.
The materialization
of Dimension W.
Wait. There should be
an image in my log.
Hold on. It's not there.
So she really did see something.
Koorogi, can you
compare these people
to the ones who
died 21 years ago?
[KOOROGI]
Huh? Sure, gimme a sec.
[KYOMA] From what we know so
far, I wouldn't be surprised
to find a connection between the
victims and Sakaki's killers.
I see where you're going.
You think the Numbers
sealed up the tragedy
and everyone who was
involved within Dimension W.
Huh.
[MIRA] Somehow I've been
dragged into memories
from 21 years ago!
[MORINAGA laughing]
[MIRA] When did it first
happen? In the bathroom?
No, before that. It's been
happening since I got here.
The world of the past is layered
on top of the real world.
And now... I can't get out!
[gasps]
[GHOSTS screaming, moaning]
[MIRA] This isn't truly
a memory, though.
Nothing as simple as that.
[GHOST screams]
[MIRA] It's like something
out of one of Sakaki's novels.
[MIRA screams]
[laughs] You entered
my darling's room
without permission, and now
I'll watch you suffer for it.
[MIRA] I can't do anything
as long as I'm bound
by the logic of
this world. I'm helpless!
Please, Kyoma!
I need you! Help me!
[KOOROGI]
Bingo, Kyoma. That's it!
[KYOMA grunts]
[KOOROGI] Other than that
Kamiki guy in the middle,
they're all students who
died years ago in the flood.
Shiro Kamiki?
[KOOROGI laughs]
Yep. The plot thickens.
Seems Sakaki was a pen name.
Please, Mr. Mabuchi,
you're needed at once!
It's Mr. Hageyama!
[footsteps tapping]
[ELIZABETH grunts]
[creaking]
Rigor mortis has already set in.
He's past saving, unfortunately.
Why are you here?
Are you a Collector?
[ALBERT]
You've called the police?
[MAKITA] I've been trying to
reach them for some time now,
but I can't get through.
[KATO screams]
[ALBERT]
Mabuchi!
That came from the hotel!
[KYOMA] Where's that piece
of junk when I need her?
She better not
be sleeping again.
[door creaks]
[MARISA]
Who's there?
I see you've woken up.
I'm afraid that doesn't
work for us, Miss Sakaki.
We'll need you to
go back to sleep.
No...
[BLUE] I've been doing
a little reading, you see.
So I know that your
dreams are necessary
to connect to the other side.
You'll be safer under
our supervision.
Until we get the Numbers,
you're our hostage.
[gasps]
[BLUE grunts]
[MARISA groans]
[BLUE groans]
[MARISA gasps]
[KYOMA grunts]
[KYOMA]
Tch...
[ALBERT grunts]
[ELIZABETH gasps]
They won't get away.
[KAMIKI]
Take a look around you.
How does this world
appear to your eyes?
Is it past or present?
Is it dead? Or is it alive?
Please, who are you?
My name is Shiro Kamiki.
That's what I'm called
in this world, anyway.
But in your world, I believe
I called myself Shijuro Sakaki.
[gasps]