[LOSER]
I seek the Numbers.
If you want to understand,
then you will. Eventually.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[gasps]
[KYOMA grunts]
[KYOMA]
Damn it.
[NARRATOR] In the year 2036,
a fourth dimensional axis
beyond X, Y, and Z was
proved to exist. Dimension W.
Inter-dimensional
electromagnetic
induction devices, known
as "coils," were developed
to tap the inexhaustible
energy supply
that exists in Dimension W.
Sixty giant towers
spread across the globe
are used to stabilize the energy
drawn from Dimension W.
They are responsible
for supplying power
to the entire world.
This network developed
by New Tesla Energy
with the cooperation
of the global community
is known as the "World System."
It has altered the very
core of civilized society.
Mankind has discovered
what it has always sought.
A limitless supply of energy!
[MARY]
That's quite a haul.
You got them all on your own?
[MIRA]
That's right!
I tracked all of them down
and collected them myself.
Impressive.
That Loser guy must have a
good engineer working for him.
Oh, yes. I was especially
surprised when I realized
a child was controlling them.
Yeah?
Four, bring the
briefcase over here.
[MARY]
Your payment for this job.
Six million. Would you
like to count it?
Wow! That much for me?
What am I going to
do with all of it?
[chuckles] You don't see
cash too often these days.
New Tesla was impressed
that you saw through
the pigeon charade
and found the devices.
No wonder Kyoma
looks like a kid
who was sent to bed
without dessert.
[KYOMA grunts]
[MARY]
You did well,
but don't let it make you
cocky or complacent.
If they find out what you really
are, we'll all be in trouble.
Just remember that.
You can't let your guard down,
even for a second. Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
[MIRA giggles]
[KYOMA grunts]
[MIRA]
Actually, this is for you. Here.
What're you givin' me that for?
I'm paying my rent.
Uh?
Even if it is just
a corner by the door,
I'm renting a portion
of your home.
It seems only right that
I should pay you for it.
Although to be honest, I would
really appreciate a bed
and a closet and maybe
someplace private to change.
[KYOMA]
You don't need that stuff.
I need the same basic living
conditions everyone does
so I can keep my parts clean
and in good working order.
My body is full of
nano-machines that circulate
through it like blood circulates
through your veins and arteries.
In order to keep me
at peak condition,
those machines are
continually making repairs.
Of course, the
nano-machines themselves
are also continually
detaching and reconfiguring.
You might not realize it,
but repairs can only
be made so quickly.
That's why it's recommended that
I take regular breaks for sleep,
though the amount I need
varies according to my activity.
So, you see, I need
sleep just like you.
And just like you, I prefer to
sleep in a bed, not standing up.
I can't rest well
unless I'm lying down.
--[tires screech]
--[MIRA yelps]
[MIRA] What are you doing? This
isn't where we normally exit.
Where are we going?
My very own trailer! Thanks!
[KYOMA] You bought it
with your own money.
--[MIRA gasps]
--[KYOMA] Don't thank me.
[door creaks]
It's roomier than I thought.
[MIRA gasps]
[MIRA giggles]
[sighs] A place of
my own. Finally!
[MIRA]
Hm?
Hold on...
[water rushing]
Hey, Kyoma?
I had a quick question.
About the plumbing
situation in my trailer...?
[sighs]
Uh--! Ah...
Uh, this is just
routine maintenance.
I use water for cooling off and
circulation of my nanomachines.
It needs to be
replaced periodically.
Maybe we should
take steps to avoid
another embarrassing moment.
Fixing the lock on the door
would help, but I think
it might be better if I had
my own bathroom, don't you?
[SHOP OWNER 3A]
Here you go. Your change.
[MIRA]
Oh, great!
I don't think I can remember the
last time I gave somebody coins.
[MIRA]
I appreciate it.
[SHOP OWNER 3A] I've got all
the things you purchased
out here like you asked.
But are you sure you don't
want them delivered?
Thanks. I should
be fine, though.
Somebody's coming to pick me up.
Oh, well that's nice.
[MIRA]
Yes.
[sighs]
[screams]
What's wrong? What's happening?
U-Uh--?
Huh?
[MIRA sighs]
He seemed like a nice man.
I hope he didn't
think I was weird.
I'm not used to
shopping like this.
It really is inconvenient
to use cash for everything.
[MIRA]
All right!
Hm?
--[JIN] Who is that?
--[MIRA] Just a group of kids.
[KYOMA] Hey. Those punks try and
come in here, chase 'em away.
[MIRA] How come they're
here in the first place?
Do you know them?
No, but I can tell you
why they're here. For that.
[MIRA] Why do you think
they're so interested in a car?
[KYOMA]
It's a gasoline powered car.
You don't really find 'em
that much outside of museums.
It's certainly not the kinda
thing a kid sees every day.
I'm sure the novelty of it
is what draws them.
Wow, you really don't care
much for coils, do you?
Clearly the car doesn't use any.
And I don't see any
coil-powered products here.
--[car door opens]
--[MIRA] Hm?
Are you going out?
[car revs]
He could have at least
said goodbye.
Someone should teach
him some manners.
♪ Wash, wash, wash it up,
wash it till it shines! ♪
♪ 'Cause cleaning is fun
and when I'm all done, ♪
♪ my home will be so fine! ♪
[MIRA whines]
[MIRA]
I wonder what I should do.
Kyoma would probably yell
at them and run them off.
But I don't know.
That doesn't seem like a good
way to behave toward children.
[ringing]
[MIRA] Oh, Mary? Yes,
of course, I can talk now.
[MARY] We've got
another job lined up.
You and Kyoma come
pay me a visit tonight.
[MIRA]
Sure, we'll see you then.
Oh, before you go, there's
something I wanted to ask.
[MARY]
What is it?
I was wondering why Kyoma
hates coils so much.
I thought you might know.
[MARY] I couldn't say.
Why not ask him yourself?
[MIRA] I tried that,
but he wouldn't tell me.
[MARY] Then he probably
doesn't wanna talk about it.
I'm hanging up now.
Don't you think he ought to tell
me, though? I'm his partner,
and partners should be
honest with each other.
[MARY] Touch your chest
and ask yourself
why he might not wanna tell you.
Touch my chest? What for?
[MIRA gasps]
--[click]
--[gasps] And she's gone.
It doesn't seem like
she noticed us.
Infiltration successful.
Come on, let's look around.
I think we should go home.
If someone finds us here,
we're gonna be
in serious trouble.
[SHIORA]
Aw, don't be such a chicken!
Now, follow me!
[HAM, SHIORA gasp]
[HAM]
Ah! She saw us!
What are you two doing?
This property belongs
to Mr. Kyoma Mabuchi.
Coming here without
permission is trespassing.
What're you doin' here?
Who're you?
I'm Mira Yuri--
Mira's fine.
Okay. I'm Shiora!
Very nice to meet you, Shiora.
Now, both of you listen to me.
This place is off-limits.
Do you understand?
You guys can't come in here
unless you're invited.
[SHIORA]
Why're you allowed in?
I have permission.
I live here,
and I'm Kyoma's partner.
Is that like sayin'
you're his wife?
His wife? No! I mean...
Why do you ask?
Does it look like I am?
[SHIORA]
Hey, I've got another question!
Yes, what is it?
If you live here, does that
mean you're doin' it?
Are we doing what?
[gasps]
[SHIORA]
So, what's this?
Is it where you and
Mabuchi go to shack up?
[MIRA]
No, actually.
--It's my own space, not
--[SHIORA] I'm gonna go
--something Kyoma and I share.
--check it out!
Which brings me
to my next point.
I think it's important for
you kids to understand
that Kyoma and I
are work partners.
It's nothing personal. Okay?
[SHIORA]
Oooh! So soft!
Are you even listening to me?
I'm trying to explain
something to you.
[JIN imitating car sounds]
[HAM] What are you
guys doing? Are you crazy?
Sorry, can't talk now.
Can't you see I'm drivin' here?
[JIN]
Vroom!
Oh man, if someone finds us,
we're so totally dead.
[JIN laughs]
[SHIORA pants]
This was fun!
Let's play again sometime.
Oh, okay. But about that
misunderstanding earlier...
[crash]
[MIRA gasps]
[JIN, SHOTA gasp]
[HAM grunts]
[MIRA gasps]
[HAM grunting]
[KIDS groan]
[KIDS gasp]
Uh-oh!
[MIRA]
I'm not going to make it!
[crash]
[SHIORA yelps]
[gasps]
[SHIORA screams]
[KYOMA] I'm lookin' for a
phone that's been modified
to run on a battery.
So, you still hate coils
as much as ever,
do ya? What else?
We both know you didn't come all
the way down here just for that.
Out with it.
What do you wanna know?
All right, what does the term
"Numbers" mean to you?
Aren't you still workin'
for that scary old witch?
Why don't you find out from her?
All right, all right.
Before the towers
were completed
researchers around the world
were given various
experimental coils
ranging in size.
They had a few different names.
Some called 'em "beta coils,"
some called 'em "micro-gates."
But nowadays it's simpler.
People just call 'em "Numbers"
because of how they look.
Whatever you wanna
call 'em, though,
they're a big deal. Considered
top-secret collection targets.
How're they different
from other coils?
[DENDENDO OWNER 3A] Coils these
days rely on the towers.
They're built to pull energy
from the surface of Dimension W,
designed to get
the power they need
without penetrating
the top layer.
Numbers are a
different beast entirely.
They reach into the abyss
deep inside Dimension W.
A region unknown and unexplored.
[DENDENDO OWNER 3A] Obviously,
if something goes wrong
down there, it goes
really wrong. In fact,
most of the large-scale,
inexplicable accidents
New Tesla covers up are said
to be caused by Numbers.
[DENDENDO OWNER 3A]
Here.
[gasps]
[DENDENDO OWNER 3A] You ask me,
Numbers are too dangerous.
They're not something this
world has any need for.
[whistle blowing]
[breaks squeak]
[tapping]
Hey, this gas station
belong to you?
Yeah.
And what about those
scrap cars over there,
are they yours, too?
And what if they are?
[POLICE OFFICER 3A] We got a
call from some kids saying
a few of those old
cars had fallen over
and pinned someone underneath.
Damn it.
[POLICE OFFICER] Well. We didn't
find anyone under there.
So it looks like
everything's just fine.
You know how kids can be
about this stuff, though.
They probably just
panicked and thought
the worst had happened.
We treated them for light
injuries and minor shock
and sent them all home.
They'll be okay.
[KYOMA]
Hm.
So we're done here, then?
Actually, sir, I'm afraid
there's the issue of liability.
You're responsible for
managing your property in a way
that doesn't pose an undue
risk to the community.
[KYOMA grunts]
[car horns beeping]
[KYOMA sighs]
[KYOMA]
You there?
[MIRA]
Yes. Come in.
[door creaks]
[KYOMA] Well, there's no
denying you're a robot now.
Can you help?
I seem to be a little
broken at the moment.
Little more than a little.
We'll need to call in
Koorogi for this one.
I can't stop thinking about
the children's eyes.
When they saw what happened,
they were so frightened.
[JIN gasps]
[screams]
[JIN, HAM scream]
[JIN yelps]
They were in shock,
but it made me a bit sad.
Whatever they saw, I guess
they must not have said
anything to the police.
If they had, there would've
been an investigation,
and New Tesla would
be coming for me.
[KYOMA]
It's not just you they'd want.
They'd take me and Mary, too.
Mary warned me
very clearly not to,
but I still let myself
get complacent.
I've never had much contact
with humans outside of Father.
It was such an incredible
feeling to interact
with people and feel accepted.
I should thank them.
If I see them again, I'll thank
those kids for treating me
like a person and
keeping my secret.
[door clicks]
[KYOMA]
It's Kyoma.
[MARY]
You're calling me?
It's usually the other way
around. I assume it's about her?
[KYOMA]
What do you know so far?
[MARY]
Well, I know I'm still alive
and not in New Tesla custody,
but that's about it.
We've got repairs to make.
I'll need Koorogi.
[MARY]
He's all yours.
All right, good deal.
And thank you for sorting
things out earlier, by the way.
[MARY]
For sorting what out?
[KYOMA] Weren't you the one
who got me released?
[MARY]
No.
As much as I like doing
business with you,
I'm afraid I can't
claim the credit
for springing you from jail.
Well, who was it, then?
[MARY]
Believe it or not,
the COO of New Tesla
Central 47: Claire Skyheart.
If you'll come this way, please.
[KYOMA grunts]
[CLAIRE] I don't believe
we've ever met before.
Have we, Mr. Mabuchi?
[KYOMA]
So you're her?
COO Claire Skyheart.
I hope I didn't keep you waiting
long, but I'm a busy woman.
You're looking well,
after recent events.
What business do
you have with me?
Why'd you get me
released from custody?
Because it seemed
to me that the fault
did not lie entirely with you.
Even if that's true,
you're a New Tesla exec.
Is a minor civilian
incident like this
--really in your purview?
--[SHIORA] Granma!
[SHIORA giggles]
[CLAIRE chuckles]
So that's it.
[CLAIRE]
This is Shiora Skyheart.
She happens to be
my granddaughter.
I only found out about this
"minor civilian incident,"
as you called it,
because of her.
It would be an exaggeration
to say I had you released,
but Shiora and the others
told me about you.
They said you'd warned
them many times
to stay away from those cars.
I asked the police
to make a fair decision
based on that information.
And, to be honest,
I did think it might afford me
the chance to look upon
a beast of Grendel in the flesh.
Well, you've seen me.
Are we all done here now?
[SHIORA]
Hey! Hold on!
[whispering] I didn't think
Granma needed to know about
everything that happened.
So tell Mira not to worry an'
just hurry up an' get better!
I don't think I'll be able
to play anymore, though.
[SHIORA giggles]
I read your final report
about the Yurizaki incident.
The results were as we
had expected them to be?
Yes.
More disturbing than any
destruction is what is absent.
Dr. Yurizaki's remains
have simply vanished,
along with everything
that was near him.
We're currently considering
the possibility
that the strange coil he had
with him on that balcony
was capable of creating
a small black hole.
[CLAIRE] You're speaking
of the double coil
mentioned in the report?
[ALBERT] Yes. I've never
heard of a coil like that,
not even in academic papers.
Who knows what it
may be capable of?
What I am most
interested to know is
what was the
doctor's end-game?
He despised us as
the soulless monsters
who took everything
he had from him.
I would not be surprised
if he continued his research
for the sole purpose
of getting revenge.
With him gone for good now,
I suppose we'll never know.
I believe I have
everything I need now
to make my report to the board.
You've done good work,
thank you.
Oh, and I've had an
interesting encounter.
I thought you'd like to know.
I met the other
beast of Grendel.
And what did you think?
I'd heard that
he'd been damaged.
That he was unable to return
to society for quite some time
after the incident occurred.
But nothing he did today
suggested he has
any lingering issue.
In that case,
I take it you approve?
[CLAIRE] I'm comfortable
leaving it to your discretion.
That's excellent.
Thank you very much.
Ending transmission.
[CLAIRE]
This world we've built;
it could so easily be destroyed.
[NEWSCASTER 1A] At last,
we may have some answers
about the recent explosion.
New Tesla Energy has issued a
statement regarding the cause.
It seems there were
chemicals illegally dumped
at the site of
an abandoned plant.
Those chemicals
reacted with the ones
already present at the plant,
leading to an explosion
and the appearance of a
strange pillar of light.
[MIRA]
Huh?
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
Now, in other news...
[MIRA]
Hm?
[KIDS]
Hey! Look up here!
--[HAM, SHOT] Hi, Mira!
--[JIN] How are you?
[SHIORA] It looks like
you're all fixed up, huh?
[gasps]
[MIRA yelps]
Hey! What did you do that for?
Stop thinking that
you're a human.
You're just a walking,
talking heap of metal.
J-Just a heap of metal?
You're not very nice!
Jerk!
[laughs]
[KIDS laugh]
[footsteps]
Pardon me, sir.
Mind if I come in?
I brought your...
Are you there, sir?
[gagging]
[gasps]
[MAID screams]