[LOSER pants] That light
is so bright. Is it...?
Yes. Yes, it is.
I thought that staying
out of your range
would be an effective strategy.
[CHRYSLER groans]
But it looks like
my suit broke first.
I'm the loser this time.
[LOSER] That's what
happens when you rely
too much on coils.
[LOSER groans]
[LOSER]
No time for weakness.
Finally, the fifth Numbers.
I have all the key
coils now. I'm ready.
[LOSER screams]
[ELIZABETH]
Papa!
Are you okay? Papa!
[LOSER] Yes. I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[LOSER]
Let's go.
I have more than one body.
That makes me
pretty hard to kill.
Hold on. Are you saying
that you're a robot?
[LWAI]
Mm-mm. No, I'm not.
There was an accident,
but because of it,
I lost use of my entire body.
But I am still human.
My original body is
back home, safe in Isla.
So you control
this one remotely?
[LWAI] It's a system that Salva
designed especially for me.
There's no lag
because the connection
goes through Dimension W.
It's plugged directly
into my consciousness,
so I can control this body
as if it were truly my own.
I'm amazed Salva was
able to create this.
And for the most part,
it works flawlessly.
The only catch is, if my
consciousness becomes
too deeply linked
to the body I'm using,
I have a hard time
separating from it.
So if you're not
paying attention,
you could get stuck
there permanently?
--[LWAI] Yeah.
--[DEBBIE, HARRY gasp]
[LWAI] When Yuri attacked
me, I lost awareness
of what was going on
outside my body.
I was distracted, so I became
unable to operate objectively.
I tried to get things
running properly again,
but nothing seemed to work.
As a last resort,
I killed that body.
[KYOMA]
So, that's what happened.
You coulda warned me first.
[LWAI] I wasn't sure whether
or not it would even work.
Technically, Salva's
the only one
who is authorized to do a
forced termination like that.
But he's asleep,
and I don't know when,
or if, that'll change.
We should have said
something sooner!
We know how to wake him up.
[CASSIDY] You were right.
Here it is. Damn, that's creepy.
Prince Salva! Can you hear me?
[grunts] Lasithi, what happened?
You came back to us!
Removing it worked!
My brother is awake!
Good!
[LWAI] So, now that
you know, do you hate me?
[gasps]
Do you think you can
be friends with someone
who's part-robot, Kyoma?
[KYOMA] Don't worry, kid. I
don't care what body you're in.
As far I'm concerned,
you're you. You got that?
Well, let's go.
[DEBBIE]
What about those two?
Should we bring 'em with us?
They can stay here. Who knows?
Yuri may still wake up.
It's up to him.
I think you and I
have done this before.
This feels very familiar.
We've met. Well, sort of.
[SALVA] Yes, that's right.
I remember now.
You wandered into my dream.
[KYOMA] I can't say whether
it was your dream or mine.
Can you, your Highness?
Just Salva.
There's no need for
titles or ceremony
between us, my friend.
I owe you a great debt.
[KYOMA] Loo is a good kid. And
you seem like a good brother.
I thought you were only using
him for your own ends,
trying to gain power
by controlling the boy
who's in line for Isla's throne.
I'm glad to know I was wrong.
You don't owe me anything.
Now then, let's keep moving.
I don't know about you,
but I'm ready
to put an end to this.
So, that's it. That's where
the light's coming from.
[MIRA]
It's Adrastea.
[DEBBIE]
Whoa, look at that. So many!
It's that same door
over and over.
The materialization
of Dimension W.
[SALVA]
Hm.
How do things look, Loo?
My radar doesn't show anything
to indicate functioning robots.
And the energy from
Dimension W is stable, too.
I think we're all clear, Salva.
[SALVA]
It's decided. We'll go inside.
Once Dr. Yurizaki knew
the capabilities of Genesis
and the consequences of its use,
he sealed off his own research,
but what we'll find
beyond that door
is anyone's guess.
I had a feeling you
knew more about this.
Um, what's Genesis?
It's an incredibly
powerful coil
with the ability to make
something from nothing.
That coil is the reason I came.
I must find it for Lwai's sake.
And to continue
the royal bloodline.
[MIRA] The term Genesis
doesn't sound familiar to me.
I don't think that's
the name Father gave
to the project
he was working on.
Are you sure about this?
I'm not finding a single mention
of that coil in my database.
No, you wouldn't.
Its existence is classified
as top secret intel.
Knowledge of it is forbidden.
If you're using
an official coil,
it will immediately delete
any reference to Genesis.
I'm only able to
talk about it here
since we're outside
tower control.
I would recommend not speaking
of it to anyone else.
[CASSIDY] I don't care what the
coil does or how secret it is.
I'm just in this for
the reward. The offer stands
after everything
that's happened, right?
First Collector to the coil
gets 50 million dollars,
that's what you said.
That was before. Now I'm
offering twice that.
One hundred million
to the person
who gets me the real Genesis.
See ya later, guys.
I've got a date with a coil.
That hundred million belongs
to Scorpion Cat Cassidy.
[DEBBIE]
Hey, you sneak! No fair!
[MIRA gasps]
Look out, Cassidy!
[SANCHOS, CASSIDY yelp]
[CASSIDY yelping] Go away!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
[LWAI]
Salva!
Hurry up, get going!
I'll use my two Ras Dashens
to hold them back.
All right. We'll be
counting on you!
You heard him. Let's go!
[SALVA grunts]
[LASITHI grunts]
[DEBBIE, HARRY yelp]
[yelps]
[gasps]
Ugh. Come on, Harry.
Let's take care of this guy.
[yells]
[grunts]
You guys go on!
We'll be takin' a cut
of the money, though!
Done. And thanks!
What do we do?
[KYOMA]
We keep going!
Shouldn't we stay
and help, though?
I'd be better than them
at holding off those robots.
Don't worry about
those guys. They're pros.
[MIRA screams]
I'm not sure how
it's connected,
but I think all this has
something to do with you.
Genesis. The term that's
deleted if it's observed.
Probably has something to do
with the gaps in your memory.
Especially where the
doctor is concerned.
Many of your memories
would have been erased
when you began using
an official coil.
The only thing that
remained totally clear
was the message from the doctor
about following
the illegal coils.
Yes.
[KYOMA]
When he created the message,
why did he choose
that specific word?
He didn't say "find."
He said "follow."
That's been bothering me
ever since you told us.
[MIRA]
Is that why you brought me here?
So we could figure out what
Father's message meant?
[KYOMA]
The doctor wasn't a stupid man.
Don't you think he assumed
that the word "Genesis"
would be deleted?
[gasps] Yes, you're right.
Is it possible this
was Father's method
of implicitly commanding me
to come to Easter Island?
Seems probable to me.
He wanted you someplace
free from New Tesla's
surveillance.
And now you've gotta
figure out why.
I came here to confront
the truth of that day,
whatever it might
turn out to be.
Once I've done that,
settled this,
I'll finally be able to
stand in front of her.
[MIRA grunts]
[SALVA] This is it. The entrance
to the main chamber.
Right. This guy.
There's a few things I need
to settle with him, too.
[gasps]
[LOSER] You came.
I can't say I'm surprised.
[KYOMA]
Of course you're not.
You knew everything, didn't you?
[LOSER]
Yes, all of it.
The accident occurred because
the transporter went wild.
There were two people
operating it at the time.
One was my wife Sophia.
The other was Haruka Seameyer.
So your true identity
is Julian Tyler.
But how is that possible?
How could you have survived?
[LOSER] Yes, I was on this
island the day of the accident
and, through an
ugly twist of fate,
I was allowed to live. Look.
A space-time distortion.
[LOSER] Yes. And do you
know what that means?
A gate made by the
transporter is open.
Five years ago,
the wild transporter
teleported Adrastea and
everything around it.
In doing so, it depleted
the surrounding area
of all Dimension W energy,
dropping it into the void.
And the transporter?
Did it disappear into the void
with everything else?
[LOSER] No. The transporter
itself was not teleported.
[SALVA] Well, then, what
happened to it? Where did it go?
There are a lot of blanks
that still need filling in.
Something was restored
from the void.
What was it? Genesis?
[KYOMA]
I'm running out of patience
with this game of yours, Loser.
I want you to tell us
everything you know
about what happened.
[LOSER]
Very well, then. I'll tell you.
If you really think you're
ready to witness the truth.
[KYOMA, MIRA gasp]
[ELIZABETH grunts]
[gasps]
[SOPHIA]
Julian.
[MIRA gasps] Wow, so we're
inside Loser's memory?
Looks like it.
This should be fun.
[SOPHIA] This is perhaps our
most fundamental equation.
It shows that Dimension W energy
is equal to possibility
times mass times the
speed of light squared.
Essentially, the energy
from Dimension W
expresses itself in our universe
in the form of possibility.
Using this theory,
we can also solve
for the speed of light
and see that it equals
the rate of renewal
for possibility.
[JULIAN] That was a really
good lecture. You're a natural.
[SOPHIA]
Oh, thanks.
[SHIDO] Hello, Sophia.
It's good to see you again.
[SOPHIA]
Oh! Dr. Yurizaki!
--Father's here!
--It's good to see you too, sir!
[SOPHIA]
I'm so honored that you came.
Of course I came.
I heard there was a big
discovery made at Adrastea.
Yes.
Let me introduce you.
[growls]
This is Haruka Seameyer.
He's an exceptionally
promising student of mine.
I think of him as my protégé.
I've taught him
everything I know.
Hello. I'm so glad
Dr. Yurizaki brought me.
It's a pleasure to
meet all of you.
Nice to meet you.
We're glad to have
you here, Seameyer.
I'm Julian Tyler. It'll be
good to work with you.
[SEAMEYER] Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
[JULIAN] As you can see,
we have three boxes here.
One contains a live mouse,
one contains a dead mouse,
and one contains a toy mouse.
[JULIAN]
This teleportation experiment
doesn't involve relocation.
They're supposed to
rematerialize in the same place.
And in two of
the cases, it works.
Yes, I see.
The dead mouse and
toy mouse remain,
but it can't rematerialize life.
Imperfect as it is,
there'd be many
practical uses for the device.
but I'm hesitant to continue
when there's a major flaw
we can't explain.
If you want an explanation,
I can offer one.
Even though the
energy of the mouse
is drawn out with the coil, the
possibility of the mouse is not.
I believe, if we could
better understand that,
we'd be one step closer
to comprehending
the mystery of life.
You think it's that
significant? Honestly?
[SHIDO]
Absolutely.
After years of research
and experimentation,
I'm certain that
life and Dimension W
are deeply connected.
Possibility cannot be observed.
Sophia, can you
tell me why that is?
[SOPHIA] Because when a
possibility is observed,
it becomes a reality.
It's along the lines
of Schrödinger's cat.
[SHIDO]
Exactly.
Even if we can
predict a possibility,
we can't observe it
because in doing so,
we alter its very nature.
And although possibility
can never be seen,
we are, nevertheless,
certain it exists.
Tell me why that is.
As intelligent beings,
we ourselves are
creatures of possibility.
[SHIDO]
That's precisely right.
It's hard to pinpoint
what it is exactly
that makes up our intelligence.
However, we do know that
all life is capable
of perceiving possibility
and reflecting it.
So, whether we can see it or
not, it is part of our being.
The coils we have
now are incomplete.
They're inadequate in the
face of life's profundity.
Of course, a coil that could
encompass the complexity of life
would have to be
utterly flawless.
If it existed, it might
lead us to the truth
of everything.
[SOPHIA gasps]
[SALVA]
Genesis.
[LOSER] That's right. Genesis.
The ultimate coil.
The one that could
control everything.
We threw ourselves
at the problem
and quickly became consumed.
In our effort to complete
Genesis, we made five Numbers.
Seameyer devoted
himself entirely
to formulating the theory.
But then, the inspectors came.
Hey! No!
That's my laboratory! My work!
You can't just barge in there!
The development of Genesis
has been judged to
carry too great a risk.
Everything related to it
will be confiscated
and safely sealed away.
We strongly urge you
to be cooperative.
Now please, stand aside.
You can't do this to me!
[SHIDO]
I know this is hard, Seameyer.
Cooperate. I approved all this.
I don't understand, Doctor.
We've worked so hard.
You said yourself that we were
close to completing it!
We can't stop!
I'm sorry.
Your theory. You completed it.
That's why this is happening.
Come on. There's no
need for you to be--
Shut up! Get away from me!
[LOSER]
I believe that was the moment
when Seameyer snapped. His
curiosity twisted into madness.
Whoa! Where's the floor?
It's there. I just can't see it.
The completed transporter.
Is that what we're seeing?
Let us out of here!
What are you doing?
I thought you were going
to use the transporter
to take back the
documents they stole.
That's what you said!
[sobbing]
Mama.
[SEAMEYER]
And you believed me?
How very gullible of you.
I formulated my own
working theory for Genesis
a long time ago.
I don't need help from that
traitor, Shido Yurizaki,
All that remains is
to verify my theory
and make some final adjustments.
But in order to proceed,
I required access
to this transporter,
which necessitated some
deception on my part.
There is nothing I wouldn't do
to see Genesis complete.
No matter how many
lives it might cost.
Kyoma, is that Genesis?
That's it. The reason
for all of this.
[SEAMEYER laughs]
We have reached
the final phase of testing.
Genesis will be complete when I
can successfully teleport life.
How many people it will take?
I guess there's only
one way to find out, eh?
You're evil. How can
you do this?
Shut that pretty little
mouth and cooperate.
Don't forget my
insurance policy.
I'm saving him for last.
Fight me and he will suffer.
No, don't listen to him, Sophia.
Don't do what he asks. He's mad!
[screams]
That's enough
out of you, Julian.
[LOSER]
I was a hostage,
powerless to do
anything to help.
I could only watch as life after
life was carelessly thrown away.
Let's begin.
[SECTION CHIEF 9A screams]
[gasps]
--[SCIENTISTS scream]
--No luck?
Next up.
[WOMAN 9B screams]
[SEAMEYER]
Nope. Next.
[MIRA]
This is awful.
[SEAMEYER]
No good. Next.
[KYOMA] That psycho.
I remember it all now.
The scene was enough
to make anybody sick.
[LOSER] Yes, it's coming back
to you isn't it, Mabuchi?
Because it was around this time
that Grendel landed
on the island.
[MIRA, KYOMA gasp]
Wow! It's Kyoma
from five years ago!
[SEAMEYER]
Yes, this will do nicely.
I've got a great view from here.
Hello, everybody.
Hi, just dropping in.
You don't mind a teensy
interruption, do you?
Stop screwing around and get
the hell out here, Seameyer!
If I could get to
where you are,
I'd have done it long ago.
[LOSER]
You aren't actually here.
Where are you, then?
[SEAMEYER] Hm... Your voice
is a bit distorted,
but I still recognize it,
Julian. So good to see you.
[LOSER]
Answer me!
Where am I? Come on,
isn't it obvious?
Same place I've
always been. Adrastea.
Well, to be more specific,
the larger fragment
of the lost Adrastea.
[MIRA]
Adrastea was split?
[SEAMEYER]
Yes, it broke into two pieces,
and the smaller fragment
was sent someplace else,
along with my right arm,
and, more importantly,
the completed Genesis.
So you really completed it,
after all those people died?
[SEAMEYER]
Indeed I did.
And the evidence is
standing in front of you.
There. Julian Tyler
is living proof.
[SOPHIA]
Julian.
Don't worry about him.
I'll take care of Genesis.
but I need you to keep living.
Stop it, what are you doing?
No! Don't do it, Sophia!
[SEAMEYER] After so many
attempts, Julian's successful
teleportation proved that
Genesis was complete.
[LOSER] But you don't
have it. It was lost.
[SEAMEYER]
That's right. It was lost.
Thanks to your damn wife
and her ridiculous heroics.
After her moving speech, darling
Sophia switched the circuits
to the five Numbers and made
the transporter go wild.
She was going to kill Seameyer,
even if it meant her own death.
[SEAMEYER] That stunt was
annoying enough on its own,
but somebody else had to
come along and interfere.
I mean you.
[gasps]
[SEAMEYER] Yes, you, Kyoma
Mabuchi, Beast of Grendel.
Get it out of here, now!
Quickly, before the gate closes!
We need to get Genesis
away from this madman!
[gasps]
[growls]
Give it back right now!
Adrastea can still
be rematerialized!
Don't just stand there!
Throw it outside the gate!
No! It's too powerful!
You can't let anyone have it!
This is it.
Wait!
[KYOMA yells]
[yells]
[SEAMEYER screams]
I don't understand.
Why did you take
Genesis and disappear?
[SEAMEYER]
Do you remember now?
Is it all coming back? You stole
the power of God from me
and then ran away
like a coward?
And do you know what I saw?
In the very last moment
before the gate closed.
[KYOMA]
I came back.
I left them all behind.
[LOSER] It's like I said,
you're the key.
As the only one who returned,
you should know better than
anyone what happened that day.
Don't you think the report
would have mentioned it
if Kyoma had Genesis with him?
[SEAMEYER]
If anyone wants my opinion,
I'd say he left it on the
lost fragment of Adrastea.
But that's just a guess.
He's the only one
who knows for sure.
With access to his memory,
I can finally locate Genesis.
I don't understand any of this.
Why would I leave like that?
Abandon my commander,
my friends. How could I?
You've got to pull
yourself together, Kyoma!
[laughs] I'll get what I need.
There are many ways to
follow somebody's memories.
[LOSER]
Seameyer!
Sophia, my wife. Where is she?
Be realistic.
Do you really think I'd
let her go unpunished
after what she did to me?
[LOSER]
Tell me where my wife is.
[SEAMEYER] If you wanna
see her that badly,
I can arrange it for you.
[MIRA]
Kyoma!
[SEAMEYER]
There.
May I present to you,
your darling Sopia!
[LOSER gasps]
[ELIZABETH gasps]