[AKI]
It sure is hot out today.
Uh?
[NANA]
Huh?
[AKI]
Uh...
Wait. Who was that?
[AKI]
Uh. Did I get the wrong room?
My bad, my bad.
I didn't see anyone in here,
so I just went inside.
It's fine, right? I mean, it was
my room up 'til March, anyway.
[AKI]
Mm?
[NANA] Surprised someone's
usin' it already!
But guess I shouldn't be.
Excuse me.
[NANA]
Whoa! Check this out!
This is, like, a sixth
grade textbook!
I'm legit nostalgic right now!
Oh my god, this is so funny!
I remember this cover!
[AKI] She's clearly got
no shortage of energy.
But man, I totally forgot
how hot it gets in here
with no A-C unit.
Better strip down.
[AKI]
What's even left?
Aw, I'm just kiddin'!
Young guys always freak out
so hard, I can't get enough.
[AKI sighs]
Oh! By the way, I'm Nana.
And what should I
call you, little buddy?
I'm... Aki. Aki Shiina.
Okay so, are you
a girl or what?
No, I'm a guy!
[NANA] Hm? Really?
I'm gonna have to check.
[AKI gasps]
An older woman's trying
to get your pants off.
Not so bad, dontcha think?
[AKI gasps]
[door clatters]
[YUZU]
Will you be quiet, Shiina?
Just because it's summer
break doesn't mean you can--
Uh. Nana? What?
[NANA]
Oh hey, it's Yucchi! What up?
Um. I think I'm just gonna go.
Don't leave me here, Prez!
[NANA]
Oh, no you don't!
Uh, Long time no see, and stuff.
Way too long!
Oh, I totes forgot!
I've got something I wanted
to show you, Yucchi!
[AKI, YUZU]
Huh?
[YUZU gasps] So, um, we're just
gonna go wait in the hall.
[door clatters]
[NANA] Hm? Sure, whatever makes
yah comfortable.
[AKI sighs] So I take it you
know Nana from somewhere, then?
She was the last
student council President.
Huh? I'm surprised she'd
be anyone on the council.
Aren't you picked based on
academic performance?
Well, she's strong in
more ways than one.
[AKI]
Strong?
And she's Ayaka's--
[NANA]
You can come back in now!
Eh, you'll find
out soon enough.
[AKI]
Huh?
[NANA]
Tada! So, whaddya think?
[YUZU]
You look great!
[NANA] I know, right?
I just love how it's got that
classic high school
girl feel, y'know?
[AKI gasps]
[NANA]
Hm? Take a peak!
[AKI grunts]
[YUZU]
Shiina, don't you dare!
[NANA] Aw, but I want
him to check me out!
You want it too, right?
Uh. I wouldn't
say that. I just--
[YUZU] Will you stop teasing
the poor guy so much?
Oh? Why do you care?
Are you guys together?
[YUZU]
Of course not!
Now I'm ranked the highest
here at Sunohara House,
and I'm not gonna let you get
away with whatever you want.
Them's fightin' words.
You wanna go?
[YUZU]
I should warn you,
I'm not the same girl
I was last year.
Oh, gimme a break, as if I'd
ever lose to a middle schooler.
[NANA, YUZU grunt]
[AKI]
What are they doing?
[YUZU]
Solve for X and Y!
Three X plus eight Y equals 5,
and X plus Y also equals 5!
That's easy! X is seven
and Y is negative 2!
"I stand amid the roar of
a surf-tormented shore."
"And I hold within my hand
grains of the golden sand."
"Please Excuse My..."
"...Dear Aunt Sally!"
[YUZU] Sine equals
Opposite over Hypotenuse!
[NANA] Cosine is Adjacent
over Hypotenuse!
Hydrogen, Helium, Lithium,
Beryllium, then...? Ha!
[YUZU] High school material.
That's a low blow!
[AKI]
I guess that means Nana won?
Uh!
Come here my prize.
Now Aki is all mine!
[YUZU gasps]
[AKI] What do you mean?
No one agreed to that!
[YUZU] We weren't competing
for Shiina in the first place!
Don't be such a sore loser,
it's not a good look.
Akkun. Yuzu. I don't want
to see you two fighting.
Hey Miss Caretaker? You think
you could help me out?
Oh, it's Nana!
--[AKI gasps]
--[NANA] The one and only!
When did you get here?
If you'd told me ahead of time,
I would have gone to
meet you partway.
[NANA]
Don't worry about it.
I know how busy my sister is,
and it was kinda fun
walkin' around by myself.
[AKI gasps]
Sister?!
[NANA]
Mmm! Mmm!
Man, I'd forgotten how
delicious your food is!
My cooking isn't even
close to comparing yet!
Mind if I have seconds?
[AYAKA giggles]
Not at all.
How long are you planning
on visiting, Nana?
[NANA] Hm! Well, it's summer,
so a while.
Plenty of time for us
to have fun, Kazamin!
That goes for you too, Sumichi!
That sounds nice.
That should be fine, as long
as you don't do anything
that goes against
our public morals.
[NANA] We wouldn't do
anything like that! Right?
You're always invited to join
in on the fun too, Yucchi!
[YUZU]
Think I'll pass.
Since it's summer break,
we should go to
somewhere classic!
You feel me? Maybe the pool?
Ooo, or a festival!
Are you all right, Akkun?
What's wrong?
Nothing, I was just thinking
about how you and Nana
are sisters, but you're so
different from each other.
And you said she was a fighter?
Do you really think
we're so different?
I mean, a little bit!
Y'know, Nana is
kinda aggressive,
or should I say energetic?
[AYAKA giggles]
That may be true,
but she's also a
really good person,
and incredibly kind. Here.
I got an idea. After dinner,
we should bathe together like
we used to, just us sisters!
Wanna join, Aki?
[AKI shouts]
[YUZU]
Resist her wiles, Shiina!
[giggles]
[AKI]
Ah... Huh?
[NANA snores]
[AKI gasps, yells]
Why was Nana lying
in my bed with me?
[NANA grunts]
[NANA]
Mornin'.
[NANA] Huh? What are
you doing here, Aki?
Ah... Never mind,
don't tell me. I know.
If you wanted to
sleep with me so bad,
all you had to do was ask.
[AKI]
You know this is my room, right?
[NANA]
Hm?
Oh yeah, my b! I guess I went
to this room out of habit.
Y'know, muscle memory
and all that jazz.
[AKI grunts]
Huh?
[NANA]
Hm? What are you starin' for?
You're gonna make this girl
blush if you keep that up.
[gasps] What was I thinking?
I forgot I just woke up!
He saw me without makeup!
[door clatters]
[AKI exhales]
It's game on, boi!
Couldn't you at
least knock, please?
Oh yeah. Ayaka still hasn't
found my top secret stash.
I didn't know there was
a hiding place up there.
You can use it to hide your
dirty mags if you want.
I don't have any of those!
You should hear my sister.
"Only one hour of beep boop
time a day, okay?" Like, what?
I'm surprised.
I never would have thought you
were a fan of video games.
Well, I have been told I
give off a studious vibe,
so I guess I can't blame you.
[AKI] You give off more of
an outdoorsy vibe to me.
Have you ever played
this game before?
It's an oldie but a goodie!
To tell you the truth, I haven't
played any video games before.
[NANA]
No... way.
Hmm...!
[AKI]
Hm?
So, in other words,
that means I'm going to
be your first, doesn't it?
[AKI]
What is that supposed to mean?!
[NANA]
Don't worry!
You've got me here
to show you the ropes.
You'll be a pro in no time!
Get over here!
What, you want me to
sit between your legs?
I'm not asking.
[AKI]
O-Okay... Pardon me.
Ah! My snuggle buddy!
[AKI groans]
Yucchi resisted at first,
but I guess you're more
affectionate than that.
[AKI]
What am I, a cat?
--[NANA grunts]
--[AKI laughs]
[NANA]
There! There! A little more!
Yeah, yeah! No, not like that!
[GAME (SFX)] Three match!
Four match! Five match!
Six match! Seven match!
Eight match!
[NANA] Aw, you messed
up in the same spot.
You gotta stay focused, my dude!
If you don't, you'll never
beat this level.
[AKI] And whose fault
do you think it is
that I'm not able to focus?
Here's watcha you gotta do.
I could just hand it to you.
It's fine, now look
at the screen.
[AKI grunts]
[AKI]
Mm. She smells so nice.
What did I just say?
Sorry!
[AKI] Just focus on the game.
Just focus on the game.
Target in the center and rotate!
Just focus on the game. Just--
[NANA] Aw yeah! I knew
you could do it, kid!
[NANA]
Woah, hey!
[AKI]
Huh? Miss Caretaker?
[NANA]
Ah! You woke up.
Oh, it's Nana.
[AKI]
They really are sisters, huh?
The "fighter" thing worried me,
but she has the same air
about her as Miss Caretaker.
And she's pretty and kind--
O-M-G, I can't believe you
actually just fainted like that!
But you're fine. Next up's
this fighting game!
[AKI]
We're not done playing yet?
My friends aren't
into video games.
All we do is talk about
fashion and boys,
so I gotta take advantage of
this opportunity while I can!
Oh yeah?
So get ready for an
all-night game sesh!
[AKI]
It's not even noon yet.
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
[NANA chuckles] I win again!
I'm the queen of one-on-one!
[AKI] Was this what she
meant by "good fighter?"
I guess you aren't quite
ready for this challenge, huh?
[GAME CHARACTER A] You couldn't
beat me in a million years!
Oh, I'll get you this time.
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
[GAME CHARACTER A] You couldn't
beat me in a million years!
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
[GAME CHARACTER A] You couldn't
beat me in a million years!
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
Yay!
[GAME CHARACTER A] You couldn't
beat me in a million years!
Oh, Akkun. Breakfast is
ready if you're hungry.
[AYAKA gasps] Hey, only one
hour of beep-boop time a day!
[NANA] Way to invade my privacy.
You could at least knock!
[AKI] You didn't knock
when you came in.
[NANA] Hey, Ayaka. Can I
take him home to my place?
Huh?
He already has a caretaker,
so that'll be a no. Sorry.
[AKI]
Thank you?
[AYAKA giggles]
--[AKI] Hm.
--[NANA] Aki!
[AKI]
Huh?
[AKI gasps]
[NANA] Help me put on
some tanning lotion.
[AKI]
Uh...
[AYAKA]
Akkun!
[AKI]
Huh?
[AYAKA] Would you help
me with my sunscreen?
[AKI]
Miss Caretaker too?
[AYAKA]
Please?
[NANA]
You know you want to.
[AYAKA]
Akkun.
[NANA]
Aki.
[gasps]
Just a dream.
[NANA grunts]
[AKI gasps]
Again?
[YUZU] To the water slide!
[SUMIRE]
Yes, ma'am!
Oh...kay.
[AKI] At Nana's suggestion, all
of us from the Sunohara House
took a visit to the public pool.
[AYAKA]
Akkun.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I hope you're ready
to give today's
swimming practice your all.
Uh-huh!
[AYAKA gasps]
Right, sunscreen.
Hm! I forgot to put some on.
Wait here for just
a second, okay?
[AKI chuckles]
[AKI sighs]
[YUZU sighs]
[SUMIRE grunts]
[YURI chuckles]
[MAIKO]
Hey! Over here, big boy.
[AKI]
Hm?
[MAIKO]
You all alone?
[MEA] Wanna come have some
fun with us? We don't bite.
Guess you're more of a
little boy than a big one.
[AKI] What's happening?
The city is scary!
Naw, I'm here
waiting for someone.
Oh, don't be like that.
We're much more fun than
whoever you're waiting for.
[AKI gasps]
[NANA]
Hold it!
What do the two of you think
you're doing with my Aki?
Oh, good.
Wait, Mai? Uchifuji?
[MAIKO, MEA]
Uh... Nana?
[NANA laughs]
Oh my god!
Were you two actually
trying to hit on him?
[AKI] So, uh. You all
know each other, then?
Yup! Mai here!
I'm Uchifuji!
The two of us hang out
with Nana at school.
We're like, totally besties.
Our interests
include younger men
and some less important stuff.
How's it hangin'?
[MAIKO, MEA]
Yeah!
[AKI]
Have they practiced this?
Whoa, whoa. Hold on.
Is this the kid we saw in town
one time back in spring?
Oh yeah, you're totally right.
Told you he was a guy.
Aw! Clearly my
radar's outta whack.
How could I ever mistake such
an adorable boy for a girl?
So for real. Is this this cutie
like, your boyfriend, Nana?
What?
You really know
how to pick 'em.
[NANA] Nah, nah, nah.
It's nothing like that.
[AKI gasps]
He's more my like
my pet, or something.
I don't wanna put a label on it,
but either way he's mine.
[MAIKO, MEA]
Get it, girl!
[AKI] I don't even know
where to start with this.
[AYAKA]
I'm back. Sorry it took so long.
Who's she?
[NANA]
My big sister.
Oh, you two must
be Nana's friends!
Thank you both for
everything you do for her.
[BOTH gasp]
She shines too bright!
Is she her sister? Or Mom?
[NANA] Do you think you can
lend me Aki for the day?
I really need him.
[AYAKA]
What?
I kinda just told my
friends he was "mine."
I'll look like a liar if
I don't hang with him.
I don't know what to tell you.
We only agreed to come here
so Aki could learn to swim,
I can't just drop that.
Come on, just this once?
[MAIKO]
Nana? What's goin' on?
Nothing! Just chill
for a minute!
Oh, that's right!
We actually just agreed that
whoever wins a swimming race
gets to have Aki for the day!
[AKI]
What?
When did I agree to that?
[NANA]
Just go with it!
If you win, I'll leave you
alone for the rest of the day.
Promise.
[AYAKA sighs]
If you insist.
[NANA gasps]
Then let our aquatic
showdown for Akkun begin!
Hope you're ready
to get wrecked!
[AKI]
So what, I'm just a prize now?
[YUZU]
Woo-hoo!
[SUMIRE chuckles]
Get some quality product?
Uh-huh. You'll like these.
[YUZU] Hey! Hurry up
and get in already!
You're missing all the fun!
I'll have to take a look later.
[YURI]
Hm!
[NANA grunts]
[AYAKA grunts]
Welcome! Our main
event is up next!
The single lap swim
race for Akkun!
We're your esteemed hosts,
Maiko Osonoi.
And there's me,
Mea Uchifuji.
Thanks for comin', folks.
Man, how lucky are you?
Gettin' to sit between us.
Maybe next time we'll compete
to get you for a whole day.
[AKI grunts]
[NANA] Lucky for me we
were already at the pool
when this happened. I can't
beat her in many other ways,
but with sports, my youth
gives me that sick edge
I'll need to win.
In fact, I've got the
advantage because I
don't measure up to her. Yep.
'Cus the bigger your boobs, the
greater the water resistance.
[MAIKO]
On your marks!
[NANA]
Hm?
[AKI gulps]
Ready...
[NANA]
Not gonna dive, huh?
I don't mind if you
throw the match.
[MAIKO, MEA]
Go!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
We've got a backstroke, folks!
[MEA] Clever move. She's using
her boobs for buoyancy.
She was able to turn her
weakness into a strength!
Are you sure that's
really the way that works?
You don't speak from experience,
so I get why you'd doubt it.
[MAIKO]
Hm...? Hey!
Don't mind her 'kay.
You think bigger is better too.
[AKI, MAIKO groan]
[MAIKO] We're talking
about buoyancy here!
[NANA gasps] She's doing
better than I expected,
but I'm still winning.
[NANA]
Goal!
[gasps] Which one of us won?
You're not even looking!
Size isn't the only thing
that matters, is it, Aki?
Come on. He knows it's better
to be big than a twig.
[MAIKO, MEA giggle]
So I totally won, didn't I?
[MAIKO]
Huh? How am I supposed to know?
[NANA grunts]
[NANA]
Hey. One more race!
All right, that's fine.
[gasps]
[NANA growls]
Another race!
[AKI]
Uh, can we, like, maybe not?
[NANA]
Another race!
[MEA, MAIKO giggle]
[NANA]
Another race!
[ALL grunt]
[NANA]
Another race!
[MAIKO yawns]
Okay, I'm bored.
See ya 'round.
[NANA]
Another... race...
[YUZU] Hey.
We're heading out, you coming?
I guess so.
What are they doing
still swimming?
--[AKI sighs]
--[NANA] Another race!
[pants]
[NANA]
I can't.
Well. That means
I win by forfeit.
[NANA groans]
I have no idea where she
gets all of that stamina from.
Sorry for making you wait.
Now, with that out of the way,
let's begin your lesson!
Miss Caretaker, it's kinda
closing time already.
[AYAKA]
Oh, my.
This one'll be worth
about three digits.
It's priceless.