[pants]
[chainsaw revs]
[GIRL A gasps]
[yelps]
[yells]
[GIRL A groans]
I can't take it!
If you're that terrified,
why did you want to
watch this in the first place?
Cause scary shows are a staple
of the summer experience.
[MALE NARRATOR A] I believe
my point has been made.
Now, let us review
the footage. Shall we?
[ACTRESS B]
I-It's creeping towards us.
[ACTRESS C]
What is it? I'm scared!
[GIRLS scream]
[yells]
[YUZU whimpers]
Gimme a break, President,
it's ridiculous to be scared
by such cheap tricks.
[YUZU] I don't want to
hear that from you,
Mr. "Horror Movie Made Me Cry."
I didn't cry!
Watch yourself, if you
disrespect ghosts,
they'll curse you.
[whimpers] You don't have
believe everything you hear--
[NANA]
Boo!
[AKI]
N-N-N-N-N-N-Nana!
Geez. Please don't
scare me like that!
OMG! You two are such a riot!
I'd listen to her,
though if you wanna be safe.
This place has been
around a long time,
and lotsa people
have lived here.
You better believe it's haunted!
[AKI gasps]
[NANA chuckles] Oh my god,
I'm messing with you!
I didn't scare the poor
little baby, did I?
Are you gonna need me to
spend the night with you, now?
No! I'll be fine by myself.
[thud]
Huh? Okay. What was that sound?
Is it next door?
[thudding]
[AKI yelps]
[AKI] It came from over
that way, but...
That's what I thought,
there's no room here.
I must have imagined it.
[thudding]
[gasps]
[AKI]
I'm only here because, uh.
Yeah! I'm investigating the
cause of the noise. That's it.
[AYAKA]
One moment!
Hey. What's up, Shiina?
Oh, sorry! Am I at
the wrong room, or...?
[YUZU]
Hm?
I mean, this is the
Caretaker's room, isn't it?
Good evening, Akkun.
Something wrong?
[AYAKA]
A loud noise, huh?
Well, there is a storage room
on that side of your wall,
but it's strange. None of
the current residents
should be using it
at the moment.
A secret, unused storage room?
Has it always been there?
[AYAKA] Yes. You can't
get in from the hallway.
The only entrance is outside.
But the door is rusted,
so Grandma calls it the
"accursed storage room."
[YUZU, AKI scream]
Wait, I just realized...
What are you doing hanging
out in here, Prez?
[YUZU gasps]
[AYAKA]
If you can believe it,
Yuzu actually came to me wanting
to sleep together tonight!
Is that why you're here?
[gasps]
[AYAKA] She told me
you two were watching
spooky ghost shows earlier.
[AKI]
No. That's totally not it!
My...
Stay calm, it's okay.
It's in your head, that's all.
--[thudding]
--[gasps]
[AKI]
No choice left but to search
the accursed storage room.
I-It's fine!
A real man wouldn't be scared
by something like this!
[AKI inhales]
Huh?
I thought it was all rusty
cuz no one used it.
[AKI] The lights are on,
and it's pretty clean.
--[thudding]
--[AKI gasps]
Okay, someone's in here.
[gasps]
Oh, hey. What up Aki? I didn't
expect to run into you here.
I could say the same
thing to you, Nana.
I can hear the racket
you're making
all the way in my room, y'know.
You look a little too
relieved for someone
who's acting all pissed at me.
Uh!I uh, don't really
know what you mean.
[NANA]
Oh, I getcha now!
You def thought there was, like,
a ghost in your wall, huh?
You're so funny!
Why are you all up in my face?
Anyway, what is that
thing you were on?
[NANA]
It's a treadmill, duh.
My slammin' bod doesn't
stay this way on its own.
It requires a strict,
daily exercise routine.
You wanna work up
a sweat with me?
Together? Just us? All alone?
I appreciate the offer,
but I'll pass.
[NANA chuckles]
Your typical man would do it.
[AKI] Now that I look around,
there's lots of equipment here.
[NANA] Yup. Where I live
now has no space at all.
No one here's usin' this room,
so I cleaned it up and threw
all my workout junk inside.
My sister thinks most
of this exercise stuff
is a waste of money, so keep
this between us, will yah?
--[AYAKA] Do I?
--[NANA gasps] Ayaka?
[AYAKA]
Akkun told me about a noise,
so I thought I'd check myself.
Just look at all this stuff you
bought that you won't use!
You know I hate wasting money.
Until you learn some discipline,
only peppers, mushrooms and
rice for you.
[NANA groans] Please, Ayaka!
Anything but that!
I'll do whatever you want!
[AKI] I don't know what
I was so afraid of.
The scariest thing at the
Sunohara House isn't ghosts.
It's Miss Caretaker.
[NANA] So you feel me? That's
why I gotta find a new home
for all of the stuff in here.
It'd be a waste to just toss it,
so I thought you two could
hold onto it all for me.
If it's just one or
two things, I'm down.
As long as one of
those two things isn't
what I'm standing on right now.
[YUZU gasps]
--[YUZU groans]
--[AKI] You okay?
Oh, screw this thing!
Now I really refuse to hang on
to this piece of garbage!
[AKI]
She did that to herself.
Hey, that treadmill put a
pretty big dent in my wallet.
Don't just beat it up.
I will beat up what I want!
And if you care so much about
it, then keep it at your place!
I already told you, my place
is too small for it.
[gasps]
I know!
We have all this equipment here,
so why don't we have a
competition with it?
The loser stores it all.
[YUZU]
That's a ridiculous idea.
You have always been kind of
a half-pint, haven't you Yucchi?
I don't blame you for
thinking you can't win.
What? I can't let
that one slide.
I am so much more than the
little girl I used to be!
[NANA]
Hmph!
[growls]
[NANA, YUZU]
Bring it on!
[AKI]
Welp. They're at it again.
[NANA]
Without further ado.
The Nana versus Yucchi
strength battle will now begin!
The three of you'll
be acting as judges.
I know you can
win this, President!
[YUZU]
Yeah, I'm ready!
So is the president good
at physical activities?
Well, her grades in P-E aren't
exactly what you'd call "bad,"
but this is definitely going to
be an uphill battle for her.
[NANA]
First up is the ab roller!
I'll go first so you can see
how to use it. Watch and learn.
[grunts]
[groans]
Hey, I see you back there!
You're a judge, pay attention!
I guess it is my job to watch.
[YUZU grunts]
Nope.
[SUMIRE gasps]
Sweet! That's one for me!
[YUZU growls]
Next up is... this baby.
The balance ball!
It's awesome for Strength
and flexibility. It rocks!
Plus, you can arch your
back over it, see?
[gasps]
[groans]
[NANA] Caught you slippin'.
Do your job, Aki!
You're doing this on purpose!
[grunts, yelps]
Nope.
[SUMIRE gags]
That's another win for me!
Be-tee-dubs, Sumichi, I think
your judging is a little biased.
[SUMIRE] I'm sorry, she was just
so cute I couldn't help it.
Was that in the
judging criteria?
[NANA] We don't even need
to bother with the rest.
I clearly win this competition.
[YUZU grunts] All right,
then how about I pick
the next equipment we use?
Sure. Fine by me. So what
did you have in mind, kid?
Whatever those are.
[SUMIRE]
It's been five minutes now.
Tired already? I could
hang here all day.
I see!
The president is lighter, so she
doesn't have to try as hard!
Pretty smart of her to turn her
shortcomings into a weapon!
[NANA grunt]
I can't even!
Yup!
[SUMIRE gasps]
President, you won!
Look upon my skill
and tremble!
Careful not to be
too loud out here,
we don't want to
bother the neighbors.
Sorry, we'll lower our voices.
We got a little worked
up deciding whose room
to put the treadmill in.
Uh... If you put it
in one of their rooms,
it might damage the floor, and
I'd rather not have to fix that.
So why don't you just keep it
in the storage room for now?
[YUZU, NANA gasp]
[AKI] So there was no
point to this. Fantastic.
[AYAKA] It always feels
like it was just yesterday
that I cleaned this.
Oh, well. It's all done now.
Thanks for helping
me out, Akkun.
Hey, it was my pleasure!
[AKI]
Her shirt's all see-through.
It feels sort of good to get
your clothes a little wet
in the summer, doesn't it?
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA]
Hm?
Uh, should you be randomly
taking off your shirt
out in the yard like that?
[AYAKA chuckles] It's a bathing
suit, so I'm not worried.
[AKI] Yeah, well I'm
"worried" about it.
[AKI grunts] I'll get rid of
the water in this bucket
and then put it away.
I appreciate the thought,
but don't worry,
I'll take care of it.
But, it's so heavy! I can't
let a lady lug this around!
Aren't you just the
sweetest thing?
But, tell you what,
I'll borrow some of your
energy to do it myself.
There!
[AKI gasps]
[AKI sighs]
I really need to work harder.
Miss Caretaker acted like
today was no big deal,
but taking care of the
property is a demanding job.
If only there were
something I could do
to help make her life easier.
Looking for some advice?
[AKI yelps]
The walls have ears,
the doors have eyes.
And Yuri Kazami has
a second opinion.
[YURI]
Yeah, I get what you mean.
Ayaka doesn't have it easy
day-to-day, that's for sure.
[YURI gasps]
How about giving her a massage?
I hadn't thought
of that. Good idea!
Lucky you. I just perfected
a new massage technique.
So if you'd like, I'll pass
my knowledge on to you.
And to do that, I'll need
your cooperation, Sumire!
What does that mean?
[SUMIRE grunts]
[SUMIRE] Is there a reason I
have to be tied up for this?
Oh Sumire, dear,
you know you flail around.
Wait. You don't mean you're
going to do that again, do you?
[YURI] You make it sound
like it's something
you don't look forward to.
Ha! I've prepared for this.
It won't be so easy to get
a reaction out of--me!
[AKI]
Uh...
You sure about
this technique, Yuri?
Seems kinda weird.
[YURI] It'll loosen her
up and help her relax.
Just look at what
it did to Sumire!
Here, lemme show you how
it's done. Push here,
and apply a little
pressure there!
[SUMIRE gasps]
Don't try to
kid yourself, Shiina.
There's just no way an amateur
like you could do it for me.
Press right here?
[SUMIRE gasps]
[YURI]
Hm!
I don't feel any more
confident with that skill
in my repertoire.
But if it'll really help
out Miss Caretaker,
even the slightest bit...
Wait, how would I even go
about offering her a massage?
It'd be weird to run up
and start shouting,
"Hey, let me rub
your back, okay?"
It needs to be
natural and casual.
[gasps]
[AKI]
Hey, Miss Caretaker?
What's going on?
You actually caught me as I
was making you a little snack.
Here. This is for you!
[AYAKA gasps]
Is this a love letter?
What? No, it's nothing
like that, take a look.
[AYAKA]
Hm...!
Shoulder rub vouchers? Oh, my.
Um. I was trying to come up
with things I could do
to help you and
relieve some stress.
[AYAKA]
You're such a good boy. Hm!
Would it be ok if I wanted
to redeem one now?
[AKI]
Yes, of course!
[AYAKA] If you could go a little
bit harder, that'd be great.
Uh! Sure!
[AKI] Man, I can't figure out
when I should move on
from the shoulders.
I'll just have to be bold.
[AYAKA gasps]
[AKI gasps]
Uh, sorry!
I know that's below
the shoulders,
but I thought you
might have some knots
in your lower back that
I could fix too! So...
You're naughty, Akkun.
[AKI gasps]
[AKI] It's now or never.
Time for Yuri's weird technique!
Right there!
[gasps]
[AKI] Huh? She's not reacting
like Yamanashi did.
[AKI sighs]
[AYAKA gasps]
Akkun, I think that's enough.
But. I wasn't done.
Well, I already feel great!
Who'd have thought you were
such a good masseuse?
[AKI chuckles nervously]
Time to get back to work!
I'll have to make you an
extra good snack today!
[AKI] She was definitely
just saying all that
to be nice, I'm sure.
[sighs]
What do you mean it
didn't work on Ayaka?
It should have been an easy win.
Did you execute it precisely
like I taught you to?
Will you stop barging
in here? Please?
You'll never get me to--
[SUMIRE gasps]
I guess Sumire might be
especially susceptible
to the technique.
Or maybe Ayaka just did a little
better job of holding it in.
[MAIKO]
Please help us, Nana!
[MEA] We have so
much homework to do!
I'm down for helpin'
you guys out.
But are you so behind because
you've been procrastinating?
Of course! It's summer!
When else can we look at
half-naked young hotties
all the time and not be
called out for it?
[NANA] So you went to
the pool every day?
[NANA] What should we do?
Oh, I know...! Hey Aki!
[AKI yelps]
[MAIKO] OoH, it's your
little buddy from the pool
the other day!
How's it goin'?
Wanna have some fun with
three pretty girls?
[AKI]
This can't be anything good.
I've got an idea that'll
spark some motivation in you!
For every page you complete, you
get to have Aki for ten seconds.
[MAIKO, MEA, AKI]
Huh?
What does "have" me mean?
No thank you! Not participating!
But if you don't help give
them some inspiration,
then their homework might
not get done before it's due.
And if we don't finish,
I'm sure our peers
will quickly label
us as delinquents!
And it'll be all your fault.
[gasps, groans]
[AKI] Just don't do
anything weird, okay?
[MAIKO, MEA]
Yay!
Just did my first page!
[NANA]
Already?
Dang, girl, your focus
really increases tenfold
when a younger guy's
the prize, huh?
Man you're ridiculous!
But all right,
have your ten seconds.
[MAIKO giggles]
[AKI]
I guess this isn't so bad.
[MEA grunts]
Just got two pages done.
[NANA]
Then you get 20 seconds.
[AKI groans]
[MEA sighs]
[AKI gasps]
What an adorable reaction.
[MAIKO, NANA]
Aww!
[AKI groans]
[MAIKO]
I got three more pages done!
Wait! So 30 seconds?
[MAIKO]
Hm!
[AKI]
Okay, illegal use of hands!
The vitality of youth is
more easily absorbed
through direct contact!
You realize I'm not the
fountain of youth!
[NANA]
Okay, time's up. Enough.
Fine. I'm gonna get
a minute next.
Please have mercy
on me, I beg you.
[AKI] Things continued
like that for a while.
Go Mai. Go Mai. Go Mai!
[AKI] And their demands
continued to escalate.
[MEA]
Yeah. I think we broke him.
[NANA] Let's take a break, then.
You guys got a lot done!
I brought some tea!
Talk about
perfect timing, Ayaka!
We just decided to take a break!
Feel like joinin' us?
I wanna play the King's Game!
Why that game all of a sudden?
That's so out of nowhere!
You know my answer.
When else will I have an
opportunity like this?
[NANA] Man, Mai, you are so
thirsty for younger guys!
Are you sure you want
me to play as well?
[MEA, MAIKO]
Absolutely, girl.
Just one condition, no ordering
us to do our homework.
[AYAKA chuckles] Okay, as long
as you go back to work
after we're done. Oh!
Hold on. I'll be right back!
Now I'm a student,
just like all of you.
[NANA, MAIKO, MEA]
All right!
[AYAKA, NANA, MAIKO, MEA]
Declare your lineage, my King!
[AKI]
Why am I playing?
It's me. Let's see, what kinda
order should I give?
[NANA] What are you
sweatin' over there for?
[MEA] One and three,
Lady and the Tramp style.
I'm number one.
And I'm number three.
You bite the other end.
[AKI gulps]
[AKI] So close, so close,
so close, so close,
so close, so close, so close--
[AKI]
No way!
[NANA, MAIKO, MEA]
I'm jelly.
Let's agree to use the same
order for the rest of the game.
I wanna do that with Aki!
[AKI]
Why?
[ALL]
Declare your lineage, my King!
It's me this time! Let's do
the King and number two!
Show me Aki!
Oh! Looks like it's me again!
[MAIKO]
Aw, man.
[MAIKO gasps]
She smelled so good!
How you doin?
My goodness.
[ALL]
Declare your lineage, my King!
[NANA]
Uchifuji, your luck is so O-P.
The King and number three.
Oh dear, that's me again.
You're perfect.
Now, now...
[AKI] I can't blame them
for being drawn to her.
Hey. It looks like I get
to be the King this time.
How about numbers two and four?
[MAIKO, MEA gasp]
[MAIKO] I only just realized how
embarrassing it is to do this.
[MEA]
But it's the King's orders.
[AKI] I feel like I'm
taking crazy pills.
[yells] When is it gonna be my
turn to be King? This sucks!
[AKI grunts]
Aki, forget the rules,
let's just do it.
Come on!
[AYAKA]
My, look how late it's gotten.
I had better start
preparing dinner.
What about you girls
and your homework?
[GIRLS groan]
[MAIKO, MEA]
I'm exhausted.
By the way, Aki.
I heard you gave my sister a
massage recently, that true?
[AKI] Yeah. Yuri taught
me a few tricks.
A massage from a boy!
You'd totally give us
one if we asked, right?
Like...
[BOTH]
...if we asked you right now?
Uh... Oh, fine.
[GIRLS]
All right!
Here I go. I think
it was right here?
[GIRLS gasp]
[AKI]
Found it!