[AKI] Dear My Honored
Father in Shizuoka.
It's been one month since I
arrived at the Sunohara House.
I've had plenty of time to get
used to walking to school,
and my new life here overall.
Now that I'm back, I should
start on my homework.
Better to do it while
I'm still in school-mode.
I'm ho--
[AYAKA]
Hey! Welcome back, Akkun.
[AYAKA giggles]
[AKI]
However...
...tokyo is still full of things
I just don't understand.
[AKI]
Hm...
[AYAKA]
Let's go, let's go, Akkun!
[AKI grunts]
[AYAKA]
You can do it, Akkun!
[AKI groans]
A-K-K-U-N, go! Yay!
Excuse me! Are you trying to
cheer me on or just distract me?
Because the latter
is what's happening!
Also. You're a cheerleader,
I get it. But why?
[door slams]
[YUZU] Why don't you let
me explain it to you?
See, next week, our school
is planning to hold a--
--[SUMIRE] President!
--[YURI] Oh, no!
[YUZU groans]
You all right over there?
Fine, Mr. Shiina.
[AKI]
She's tough.
Now like I was saying,
the first big event
since you enrolled in our
school is coming up next week.
Have any guesses?
Lemme think.
We obviously already had
orientation, so a field trip?
No, probably not.
But what else is there?
No. It's not a
field trip, dummy!
[AKI grunts] That was a
surprisingly solid punch.
[YUZU] I'll just tell you.
The event is...
School!
Field!
Day!
It's the School Field Day!
[AKI]
They sure are enthusiastic.
Wait, Field Day?
Oh, I get it then.
[YUZU] Exactly. Field day
needs a cheer squad,
and a cheer squad
needs cheerleaders!
I actually made the outfit
for Sumire originally,
but she refused, so here we are.
Funny to imagine you wearing
that outfit, Yamanashi.
[AKI]
Uh...
Erase that image from your
mind right this second.
[AKI]
Uh. Yes ma'am!
[AKI] So if she's a
cheerleader for the event,
then she's coming to school
...dressed like that?!
[gasps]
A bit small, no?
[AKI whimpers]
[YUZU] Stop messing
around and listen to me!
[AKI]
Uh, okay!
Ahem, Luckily for us,
everyone from the Sunohara
House is on the same team!
In order to protect the
pride of our household,
we must claim victory!
As such, I'm having you
enter the parent-child
three-legged race with Ayaka!
[AKI] What? No one
asked me about that.
I have already instructed
Ayaka to train you diligently!
Tomorrow your practice begins!
Gimme a break.
[AYAKA giggles]
We've got this in
the bag. Don't we?
[AKI]
I guess.
[YUZU growls]
Unnecessary amount of contact!
I'm no expert in this,
so hopefully we'll
figure it out together!
Oh, trust me, we're definitely
in the same boat.
This is fun, it reminds
me of my school days!
So, first off, let's make
sure we stretch properly.
Uh...
[AYAKA]
Ready...? And stretch.
Good! That doesn't
hurt at all, does it?
[AKI whimpers]
No, it's totally fine!
That oughtta do it, you think
you could help me now?
Yeah, sure.
[AYAKA sighs] Akkun, you can
do it a little harder.
Uh... Okay fine, you got it.
[AYAKA sighs]
My... You're good at this.
[AKI] Can you stop making
those weird sounds?
[AYAKA]
There, all set.
Now. It's time we did
some actual practice.
[AKI]
Mm.
[AKI grunts]
Is this position okay for you?
It's fine. You don't
need to worry.
[AKI]
I'm sure I look silly like this,
but Miss Caretaker is so
warm and smells so nice.
I don't mind.
[AYAKA] I think it's for the
best if we start off slow.
Ready?
Uh, yeah!
Then here we go.
One, two... One, two...
[BOTH] One, two. One, two.
One, two. One, two. One, two.
You're really getting
the hang of this quickly!
You know what? I bet we're ready
to pick up the pace a bit.
Sure, I'm down.
[AYAKA, AKI] One, two. One, two.
One, two. One, two. One, two...
[AYAKA]
Perfect, just like that!
[AKI, AYAKA] One, two. One, two.
One, two. One, two. One, two...
[AKI pants]
[AYAKA sighs] We should probably
leave it at this for today.
Your stamina is totally
ridiculous, you now that?
Tomorrow we start
again at 5 am!
[AKI]
What is she, an Olympic athlete?
[AKI sighs]
[AYAKA]
Akkun?
[AKI gasps]
What? What is it?
Why don't you head inside
and get ready for a bath?
Uh... Okay.
[AKI] I guess I did
get pretty sweaty.
No surprise with how
long we were out there.
--[door clatters]
--[AKI] Huh?
[AYAKA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, why are you in
here again? Come on!
[AYAKA] It looked like your
hair had gotten pretty long,
so I thought I'd offer
to cut it for you.
[AKI]
That's very thoughtful, but...
It's a whole lot cheaper
and more convenient
than having to go
to a barber. Right?
[AYAKA] So. Have you always
worn your hair like this?
[AKI] Uh-huh. Since elementary
school, at least.
I can't say I've ever
thought about changing it.
Is that weird?
[AYAKA chuckles]
No, not at all.
I was just thinking how many
boys your age try to look "cool"
to catch the attention
of a special someone.
[AKI]
I've never done that before.
But y'know, I wouldn't be
against trying something new,
if there's a particular
hairstyle you think looks good.
[AYAKA]
Mm...
Uh! What I mean is, I don't
know the first thing about hair!
So letting you decide
on a new style for me
might just make more sense!
Oh, I see now. Since you're
depending on me this much,
I've got to help! I'm gonna
make you look very handsome.
Are you tired?
We practiced a lot.
[AKI]
Yeah, a little.
But I need the practice,
so I gotta do it.
I couldn't really get the timing
down for a faster pace.
No need to rush.
We'll figure it out together.
Miss Caretaker.
[AYAKA] And maybe we'll
even win on Field Day.
Maybe!
One snip here,
and another snip there.
[AKI sighs]
[AYAKA giggles] Sounds like
someone's getting sleepy.
[AYAKA]
Akkun?
[AKI]
Uh, yeah?
[AKI gasps]
I'm about done.
How's it look to you?
Great, it's so much better!
Ah, well, I'm glad to know
the effort was worth it.
If we wanted to
do anything else,
we could maybe part
it differently.
[AYAKA gasps]
How cute!
[AKI] I was hoping for "cool,"
not "cute," but all right.
[AYAKA] Now then. I'll shampoo
your hair too, okay?
[AYAKA] You don't have
any itchy spots, do you?
[AKI]
No. I'm good.
[AKI] This feels so nice!
Way better than when I do it.
[gasps]
Hey Akkun, look what I did.
[AKI]
Huh?
You've got foamy cat-ears!
[AKI]
Oh!
[AKI giggles]
[AKI]
Ah?
Uh...
[AKI groans]
[AKI sneezes]
[AYAKA]
Goodness. Let's warm you up.
[water drizzling]
[sighs]
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA] I apologize in advance
if it's a little cramped,
but I'm getting in now.
[AKI]
Mm? Ah!
Don't be so surprised, Akkun.
This is just another part
of our training together.
But. It's a three-legged race.
Yes, and the more in-sync
our breathing is,
the faster those three legs are.
And for that, we need to
spend some quality time
close to each other.
[AYAKA]
See? Makes perfect sense.
[AKI] Uh. That wasn't
a convincing argument.
Besides, I've already been in
here long enough as it is--
[AYAKA]
Splash!
[AKI yelps]
[AKI grunts]
[AKI] So every day until
the School Field Day...
...she and I are
gonna be that close.
[AKI gulps]
[AKI whines]
[AKI]
With each passing day,
our training to get more
in sync continued.
And got more intense
by the minute.
[AKI]
Until... Field Day arrived.
[YUZU]
All right. It's time.
Let's see some hustle
out there, Shiina! Uh...
[AKI groans]
He's spent this week
so close to Ayaka.
Such mental and physical
proximity is tough.
The strain must have
been too great for him.
Hey.
[AKI groans]
[YUZU]
What a dumb face he's making.
He's going to be
useless today, isn't he?
[YUZU screams]
Hey! What's wrong? Are you okay?
[YUZU]
Sp-- Sp--
Sp--?
[YUZU groans]
[YUZU]
Space, please!
There's a spider on
my wall. A big one.
[AKI]
Ugh!
[YUZU whimpers]
You're a guy, aren't you?
Get it, or kill it, or whatever!
I don't want to touch
it either. It's creepy.
We're gonna lose it!
Man, you are such a wimp!
Coward! Chicken! Have some guts!
I take it you're afraid
of spiders, President?
Not them specifically.
Just bugs in general.
Especially when they're almost
dead and twitching and stuff.
Ugh!
Ah! There's nearly dead bug
twitching over in the corner!
I'm just kidding.
That was too easy!
[thud]
[AKI groans]
[YUZU screams]
President!
[AKI grunts]
[SUMIRE] Are you all right?
What happened?
[YUZU whines]
[YUZU]
Spider... gross and--
Rest easy. I'm gonna
take care of this.
[SUMIRE] Focus your mind.
Sense the enemy.
[gasps]
The ceiling!
[gasps weakly]
--[YUZU, AKI grunt] Mm?
--[thudding]
[AKI]
It got Yamanashi!
[YURI] Huntsman spiders are
actually very helpful.
What do you mean?
While most people still
consider them a nuisance,
they very rarely bite,
and they eat lots of other bugs,
so you don't have
to exterminate them.
Thanks Yuri--
Even if she's right, I don't
want to leave it here.
[YUZU grunts]
[AYAKA]
Akkun?
Hey, what's up?
[AYAKA] I had a favor
I wanted to ask of you.
[AYAKA]
Hm!
[AKI gasps]
What a place to land!
[AYAKA]
Hello there.
[AKI] Wow. I guess she's
just not scared of it.
Okay. Akkun, are you busy?
[AKI]
Uh, no.
Thank goodness. Then would
you mind going out with me
and helping me with
some shopping?
[AKI gasps]
"Going out with" you?
[YUZU exhales]
Not like that.
[AKI] This'll be the first
time I've gone somewhere
with Miss Caretaker.
What should I wear?
So many choices.
[YURI]
How about this?
[AKI] I see! With this
I'll catch her attention!
But for all the wrong reasons!
But it looks good on you!
It's just shopping,
don't get so worked up.
You're such a kid.
[AKI grunts]
Look, a spider!
[YUZU yelps] Hey.
There's no spider, you jerk!
Wow Yuzu really does hate
spiders with a passion,
doesn't she?
Well everyone's afraid
of something.
Actually, come to think of it,
I don't know what scares Ayaka.
[YURI]
Hm?
[AKI] Yeah, she was totally
fine with that spider earlier.
You've got a new job.
While you're out
shopping with Ayaka,
try to find out what
she's afraid of.
We'll be here finishing
up dinner preparations.
[SUMIRE gasps]
[AKI] Wow Prez. I didn't
know you can cook.
Let's just say no one peels
a potato better than I do!
[AKI]
Huh.
[AYAKA] Thanks for
coming with me, Akkun.
No problem at all!
Let me know if there's
anything I can help you with.
We'll have lots of things
on the way back,
so I was hoping you could
help me carry it all.
It's too much for me.
Absolutely! I could
come next time, too.
[AKI]
Hm?
Could it be that when
we're together like this,
we look like boyfriend
and girlfriend?
[AKI chuckles]
[MAN A]
Mother and daughter?
Nah, maybe sisters.
[WOMAN A]
What a sweet thing to see.
[AYAKA]
Good afternoon, Yatsuho.
Hey, Ayaka, nice to see yah!
And, wait, I know you...
[AYAKA]
My, that's a surprise, Akkun.
What's a boy like you
doing at a liquor store?
[AKI] Oh, I just asked
her for directions once.
Hold on a minute.
Are you telling me that
you're actually a boy?
[AKI]
Uh, yes, I'm a guy!
[NISHIKI laughs]
Well, what can I do for ya?
[AYAKA]
I'll just take some Mirin
and cooking wine for today.
[NISHIKI]
Ah, the usual. Gotcha!
Oh, and thanks for agreeing
to help out with Beerfest
again this year.
Sure. I'm always happy to
help you out when I can.
What's a "Beerfest?"
[NISHIKI] Just what it sounds
like, a festival for beer.
Ayaka can actually handle
her liquor pretty well.
Though she's quite the handful
once she's drunk.
[AYAKA]
Oh, you're exaggerating, stop!
[AKI]
So Miss Caretaker drinks. Huh.
When I really think about it,
I don't know all that much
about Miss Caretaker yet.
Like what she likes,
or what she doesn't.
[AYAKA]
Let's go.
[AKI]
Uh...
[AYAKA sighs]
You were such a big help today,
I appreciate it.
I'll have to find some
special way to thank you.
Thank me? I didn't do much.
[AYAKA giggles] It'll have
to be something good.
[AKI]
Mm...
[AKI] What's happening right
now is more than enough.
[AYAKA]
We're back!
Ha! About time! Welcome ho--
[gasps] Don't think I
don't see those hands!
Stop corrupting public morals!
Have I warned you about
unnecessary contact or not?
[AYAKA]
You have.
[YUZU]
Well then let go...!
They're having fun.
So? How was your mission?
Did you find out what
Ayaka was afraid of?
Unfortunately, no, I didn't.
[YUZU]
Oh well. Time for plan B.
See how Ayaka reacts
to a scary movie.
Okay, and what's this thing?
[YUZU gasps]
[knocking]
Come in.
How's it going, Miss Caretaker?
I was just wondering if you
wanted to watch a movie with me.
[AYAKA] Ooo, a movie?
Sure, why not?
[AKI gasps] Um, why did you turn
all of the lights off in here?
[AYAKA] I thought it would
help with the atmosphere.
[AKI groans]
--[AKI whimpers]
--[static hissing]
[GHOST groans]
[whimpering continues]
[SAMARA screams]
Remember, it's not real.
How can the plan work
if you get scared?!
Whatever. Plan C. Yuri!
Yep!
[AKI] I'm lost. Why would
anybody be afraid of a jacket?
'Cause you're gonna wear
that with no clothes underneath
and open it in front of her!
[AKI] That would just
make me a predator!
Do you have any
brilliant ideas, Sumire?
What would scare me?
[whimpers]
[SUMIRE] It would be
terrifying to be torn apart
from you, President.
My stomach's in knots
just thinking about it!
You realize how specific
and personalized
that brand of horror is, right?
[YUZU sighs]
Guess that's it.
You're just gonna
have to ask Ayaka
what she's scared of directly.
About that, President.
I was sorta hoping that I could
stop doing these tests on her.
Don't you wanna know
her weakness? Because I sure do.
[AKI]
Hm? Her weakness?
[AYAKA gasps]
[AKI]
Ha!
[AYAKA gasps]
Wow, what a man! Love you.
[AKI]
You can count on me!
[ALL]
So obvious.
[AKI]
Miss Caretaker!
[AYAKA]
Huh? Is something the matter?
You seem kind of worked up.
Nothing's wrong.
And I'm just gonna ask you flat
out: what are you afraid of?
What am I afraid of?
Oh! So that's why you wanted
to watch a horror movie
all of a sudden. It's all
coming together now.
[AKI groans]
[AYAKA chuckles] Well if
you really want to know.
Hmm. If someone I wasn't
expecting came into my room
while I was sleeping...
...that would be pretty scary.
That's a realistic answer.
[AYAKA giggles]
I'm off to bed. Good night.
[AKI]
She is asleep, right?
Yeah, no way, I'm getting
out of here.
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA sighs] I was just
putting on a brave face
because you were so scared.
But the truth is, horror movies
usually scare me a lot, too.
[AKI]
Huh?
So I was having
trouble sleeping.
But if you'd stay here with me,
that'd make me feel better.
[AKI gasps]
What a cute sight.
[YUZU]
Hm? Ah!
Hey. Shiina!