Kay, let's see.
If North is this way--
[MAIKO] I'm starving.
Wanna grab some food?
I've got just the thing!
There's a new cake
place down this way.
Everyone's saying it's great,
so I've been meaning
to check it out!
[MEA] You always hear
about these things
much sooner than I do.
[AKI] What colorful characters.
That's Tokyo for you.
Hey. Did you see that cutie?
Uh. You mean that girl?
What? Pretty sure they're a boy.
There's no way.
One hundred percent boy.
Am I right?
[NANA]
Uh...
Good question.
[NISHIKI sighs]
[AKI]
'Scuse me, could you help me?
[NISHIKI]
The Sunohara House? Oh yeah.
Just keep going down this way
and take a right at
the second corner.
Go straight from there,
and you'll eventually find it.
I appreciate your help.
[NISHIKI] You wouldn't happen
to be moving into the dorm,
would you?
I am! I'm Aki Shiina,
by the way.
It's nice to meet you
it's been a pleasure.
Right back atcha, Aki.
You take care! See yah around!
[NISHIKI chuckles]
Such a cute kid.
Ayaka's gonna be pretty happy.
[AKI] Today's the day
I move into my dorm
for the middle school
I decided to go to.
Because of my feminine looks,
I wasn't treated like
much of a man back home.
But today's the start
of a new, masculine life!
To my middle school debut!
[AKI groans]
[birds chirping]
[AKI]
Can't I get a better omen
than a sudden
torrential downpour?
breathes deeply]
Good afternoon!
Or, not?
[AKI]
Maybe no one's home.
[AYAKA]
Ah! Guess who!
[AKI gasps]
What are you--?
Nice to meet you! I'm the
caretaker of Sunohara House,
Ayaka Sunohara.
[gasps]
Glad you're here.
Hope you like it!
[AKI]
The caretaker?
[AYAKA]
That's me.
I'm the keeper of
this place, if you will.
[AKI]
Uh. Okay.
And I take it that
you're Aki Shiina?
Hello? Hey.
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA] Well, honestly,
it really doesn't matter
who you are right now.
If you don't take off
those soaked clothes,
you'll catch a cold,
so let's go!
[AKI sighs]
Wait! This is no time
to be relaxing!
Nobody warned me there
would be a caretaker!
And such a young,
pretty lady at that!
But wait, if she works
here then that means
we'll be under the same
roof until I graduate.
I'll be living with that
beautiful woman
for three years of my life.
--[door clatters]
--[AYAKA] I'm coming in!
[yelps]
[AYAKA] It's long been a
tradition in this dorm
for the caretaker to wash
the new resident's back
on their first day.
Until just recently,
grandmother had been doing it.
But she stays at
the hospital now.
So starting this year,
the duty is all mine.
[AKI] Dear My Honored
Father in Shizuoka,
I trust that you're
in good health.
Know that your son
is healthy, too.
Tokyo is incredible.
So many sights to see!
Are you all right?
[pants]
Maybe you're used to
bathing by yourself,
but don't be embarrassed.
I mean, look. It's just
us girls in here.
No need to freak out.
All right. Let's get that
back washed, come here.
[AKI]
What? Just us girls?
[sighs]
Now, let's get started,
shall we?
[DEMON chuckles] Couldn't tell
you why, but this hot chick
thinks we're a girl
for some reason.
I don't see a reason to
correct her, do you?
We must! A real man
would tell the truth
and if we want to be
manly we will too!
You've got a point.
Now that we have a plan.
[BOTH]
Time to execute!
Miss Caretaker. I'm actually--!
[AYAKA]
Yes?
Oh, never mind.
[AYAKA]
Hm... Huh... Ah!
[gasps]
Okay I'll tell you. I'm a guy--!
I understand!
You're still so young!
Don't worry about size.
Everyone grows at
their own pace.
[AKI]
Listen!
[AYAKA] I see. That's quite
the misunderstanding.
You're the first boy to move in.
Up until now,
it's only been girls.
So I just assumed
you were a girl too.
Glad that's all cleared up but
now that you know I'm a guy,
why are you still here?
This is super embarrassing.
Don't be silly. I still
haven't washed your back.
I can't leave yet.
Getting a little close there!
[AYAKA] It doesn't matter
whether you're a boy
or a girl. At the end of
the day, you're still a kid.
And remember.
I'm the caretaker here.
I take care of you.
[yelps]
Goodness!
[AKI grunts]
Huh? Did I pass out?
For how long?
Whatever, it's fine.
For some reason I feel so
warm and cozy right now.
[AYAKA giggles]
[AYAKA] Hey now, don't move
so much, it tickles!
[AKI]
I can't see... her head.
[AKI gasps]
Whoa, I'm sorry!
I must have passed out in
the bath for some reason.
Uh. Yes. I was worried
that you might get sick,
laying there in the bathroom.
[AKI gasps]
[AKI] Wait, I have clothes on?
So, does that mean...?
You weren't lying when you
said you were a boy, huh?
Sorry about that.
Between your face and your name,
I really had no idea
until you told me.
I know it doesn't
quite make up for it,
but from now on I'll do all I
can to make your experience
here a positive one.
Thanks, but I don't need
special attention.
Besides, I kinda just want
to forget it happened.
[AYAKA gasps]
And don't you worry!
Your size is perfectly normal
for your age and body type!
Not that I would know.
Not helping things!
[AYAKA] Anyway, I should really
start preparing for lunch.
When everything's done and
ready, I'll come get you, okay?
Just be patient.
[AKI grunts]
Whoa, what are doing?
Just absorbing some of
your youthful energy!
[AKI] From the looks of it,
she's pretty skilled.
And she does all the
work here herself.
She's also really
pretty and kind.
It's just...
[AYAKA]
Oh! Little Aki!
[AKI] I have my doubts that she
plans to treat me like a man.
[AKI]
Um! Excuse me!
Can you do me a favor and
not call me "Little Aki?"
Aww. Why not? It sounds
so cute! Little Aki!
[MATSURI] You really do look
so much like a girl, Aki.
Why don't you let
your big sister
help you be one even more?
Uh...
Little Aki... Little Aki...
[AYAKA]
Little Aki.
Sorry!
[sizzling]
[AYAKA]
Oh! The soup.
[AKI] I thought by coming
to Tokyo, I could start over.
That I could make people
see me as a man.
But, I guess my life will be
the same here, after all.
No, it's too early to lose hope!
It's still the first day!
Maybe I can fix this!
And be treated like a man!
[AYAKA]
Go for it, Aki.
[AKI whines]
[AYAKA]
Huh?
[AYAKA hums]
[AKI] First step to manhood is
showing her that I'm reliable!
[AKI]
Miss Caretaker! I'll help you!
[AYAKA]
Oh?
[AKI] I just gotta hang the
clothes in this basket, right?
[AKI gasps]
Is this your bra?
I'll take that. I appreciate
your eagerness to help,
Little Aki, but this
is mostly my stuff,
so I'll take care of it.
So naughty, aren't you?
[AKI gasps]
If you really want,
you can hang up the
sheets that are in there.
Uh, yes! Will do!
[AYAKA chuckles]
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA giggles]
[AYAKA] Next up on the
list is the flower beds.
Oh, please! Allow me!
[yelps]
--[AKI groans]
--[AYAKA chuckles]
Now it's time to
scrub the floors.
Don't worry, I got it!
[AYAKA gasps]
Careful, there's wax on the--
[AKI groans]
Are you all right?
[AKI]
Yeah, I'm fine.
[AKI] It's just,
I decided to be manlier.
'Cause, ever since I was a kid,
my sister has been telling
me how girly I am.
I came to Tokyo alone
because I want to change
that about myself.
So I'm trying.
[AYAKA] You don't have
push yourself so hard.
I'm sorry I didn't
consider how you felt.
Obviously, I should be
thinking more before I act.
[gasps]
[AYAKA] From now on,
I'll call you Akkun, okay?
I guess that's better.
Akkun! Hm-hm!
[AKI] Though it's still
not my regular name.
Um. Could you also maybe
stop treating me like a kid?
Nope, sorry. Whether you like it
or not, you are actually a kid.
You don't have to
help with everything.
But if you really
insist on it... Hm!
Akkun.
[AKI]
Huh?
Give me a kiss right
here on the cheek.
And you'll get the full-fledged
adult treatment.
[AKI gasps]
[YUZU]
Ayaka says the new kid is a boy.
[YURI]
Really?
[YUZU]
That's never happened before.
Guess we'll just
have to show him
how things are done around here.
[AKI "Adult treatment,"
"Adult treatment,"
"Adult treatment," "Adult
treatment," "Adult treatment,"
"Adult treatment," "Adult--!
The Tanamachi School Student
Council has returned home!
[AKI, AYAKA]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[YUZU growls] What are
you two doing over there?!
[YUZU]
Stop, stop, stop!
Geez, Ms. Ayaka! I told you
to stop doing that kinda stuff!
What do you mean?
Nothing happened.
[YUZU]
I saw how close you were!
[SUMIRE] You're not alone.
All of us have dealt with that.
You're tall.
Did she do anything
extra weird to you?
[AKI]
Uh, "extra weird?"
Oh come on,
don't make me say it!
It's too embarrassing. A guy
dealing with a woman like her?
You've gotta be enamored.
[AYAKA sighs]
[AKI]
So wait. What does that mean?
The things she's been doing to
me, she does to every resident?
We told her to cut back
on the physical contact.
But it looks like that's
too much to ask of her.
[AKI sighs]
Like with the president. See how
small and adorable she is?
Ms. Ayaka is particularly
affectionate towards her.
Aw, don't be mad at me.
[YUZU] You're literally
doing it right now!
I do it too, but I only do it
secretly when she's asleep.
[AKI] But, I didn't exactly
hate what just happened.
Or what happened in
the bath earlier.
So what does that mean
for me and my heart?
There there, cheer up, buddy.
[AKI sighs]
[YUZU]
Now that I think about it,
I haven't introduced myself!
I'm Yuzu Yukimoto!
The Student Council President
of our middle school!
If you need help with anything,
please feel free to--
[gasps]
Hey! I was just getting
to the part that matters!
We have to set a good
example for the new kid!
I'm Sumire Yamanashi.
Vice President.
[AKI] Can you maybe take
care of that nosebleed?
It's spelled with "moon,"
"view," and "countryside,"
but read Yamanashi.
Isn't that crazy cool?
[SUMIRE gasps]
[AKI groans]
[YUZU whimpers] Hey, watch it!
We're gonna fall!
I'm Yuri Kazami. I'm the
Student Council Secretary.
No title, just call me Yuri.
[AKI] That's a relief. At least
someone around here's normal.
[AKI]
Here's your drinks.
Hm?
[YURI chuckles nervously]
[AKI] I'm Aki Shiina.
Looking forward to living here.
[YUZU]
Yeah, well, as your senior,
I guess I'll have to teach
you a thing or two.
[AKI chuckles nervously]
[AYAKA]
No you will not!
You know how it
works around here.
I take care of everyone's needs!
[YUZU]
You're too close again!
[AKI, AYAKA]
Aw...
[YUZU grunts]
[AKI] By the way, can I
ask you a question?
What's that little thing
you have on your head
supposed to be?
[YUZU gasps]
We only just met!
How could you ask me
something so personal?
[AKI gasps]
I apologize.
[YUZU]
Just kidding, just kidding.
You're a funny guy,
you know that?
[AKI]
She dodged the question.
Look at her go. So cute.
Whatever you say.
To answer your question,
she wears that in an
effort to seem taller.
But that's a secret, okay?
Okay. Weird though.
She seems to have a
complex about her size,
so she massages herself in
the bath to promote growth.
And drinks milk every day.
[AKI]
How do you know that?
[SUMIRE gasps]
You've heard too much, boy.
Your time is up.
[AKI]
But you told me!
Let's go... to our rooms.
Oh, yeah! Sure!
[AKI] Just judging
from their heights,
they could be mother
and daughter.
They're a good match.
Don't you think?
[AKI shouts]
Didn't see you there!
It's a real shame.
The three of us have known each
other since we were little kids,
but no progress.
Sumire's not very proactive,
so I can't say I'm surprised.
But this is the year!
I'm gonna make sure
they get together.
You'll help me, won't you?
Uh. Sure.
All right, you three.
I have to start making dinner,
so you should go ahead
and take your baths now.
I'm planning on making all of
your favorite foods today!
[YUZU] Yeah! Sumire, Yuri,
wanna bathe together?
[SUMIRE gasps]
--[YUZU laughs]
--[YURI] You're bleeding.
[AKI sighs]
[AYAKA gasps]
Akkun.
Would you like to pick
up where we left off?
[AKI gasps]
Um...
[AYAKA chuckles]
I'm just teasing.
Like I said, it's time for me
to make a ton of food!
Hope you're hungry!
[AKI sighs]
[AKI grunts] What was all
of that? I'm so confused!
If she acts that
way with everyone,
then I shouldn't overthink
anything she said.
[AKI]
Right?
[AKI groans]
[AYAKA] Akkun, today's the
school entrance ceremony.
Wakey, wakey!
I tried to play nice.
[AKI]
Whoa! Miss Caretaker!
It's your fault for not
getting up when I called you.
[AKI]
Okay, okay, I'll get up!
[YUZU]
Stop being so loud, it's early!
What's going on in here--?
[rooster crows]
Eh.
That kind of behavior...
[AKI] It's been a week since I
moved in to the Sunohara House.
It's the same thing every day.
But it's finally entrance
ceremony time!
So I've gotta focus!
[YUZU] The student council has
to prepare for the ceremony,
so we're leaving early.
But just 'cause you're alone
doesn't mean you can do
anything weird!
All right, see yah later!
Bye. Have fun.
The three of them
take their work
on the student council
pretty seriously, huh?
Yes. Apparently they're
admired by other students.
And they have lots
of friends, too.
[AYAKA] It's just the two of us.
Feels like it's been forever
since the last time
that happened.
[AKI]
I guess you're right.
[AYAKA]
What's wrong?
I'm having second thoughts about
my decision to come to Tokyo.
It's a new place
with new people,
none of which are my friends.
What if they all bully me
for being a country boy
or something?
Are you... even listening?
[AYAKA gasps]
Okay.
I think I have an idea
that's gonna help!
I'll be back in a minute
or two. Wait here!
Why do I have a bad
feeling about this?
[sighs, giggles]
[AYAKA]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Tada! What do you think?
This is my high school uniform.
Can you believe it fits?
[AKI]
I... Uh...
I know you're probably gonna
meet a lot of students today.
And talking to new
people can be scary.
[AKI gasps] I'm surprised to
hear that you get nervous
meeting new people.
But don't worry!
That's what me and this
old outfit of mine are for!
Imagine that I'm a girl in
your grade who you met,
and we'll have a conversation
so you can practice!
[AKI]
In my grade?
Wait a sec.
A real man would be able
to do this, no problem.
So if I nail this
practice conversation,
maybe she'll finally start
treating me like one!
Go time.
Uh. Hey there, nice to meet you!
You can call me Aki Shiina.
What's your name?
I'm Ayaka Sunohara!
Nice to meet you too!
[AKI]
She's committing to this.
[AYAKA] Oh hey.
You're new here, right?
Where did you move from?
Shizuoka, ma'am. Uh, I mean,
I'm originally from Shizuoka.
[AYAKA]
Really?
[AKI] She's guiding me with
questions to make it easier
to hold a conversation.
Luckily...
[AYAKA]
Let's see.. What else?
Oh! It's supposed to
rain this afternoon.
Did you bring an umbrella?
Do you like older women
or younger women?
Older women all the way!
Wait. Hold on.
This isn't how a real
conversation would go!
I have no choice then.
Only one thing left to try.
[AKI gasps] Uh! Why are
you taking that off?
--[AYAKA] Uh...
--[AKI] Mm..
I forget where
I heard it, but,
"male friends hide nothing
from each other."
That doesn't mean
we hang out naked!
[AYAKA]
Akkun, are you still nervous?
[AYAKA] The truth is...
I'm nervous too. See?
You can feel how hard
my heart is beating.
[AYAKA]
Mm.
[AKI yelps]
What are you doing?
This isn't helping!
[AYAKA chuckles]
Sorry I was just kidding
about being nervous myself.
But if you've got the energy
to get riled up like that,
you'll be fine.
[AKI] Yeah, 'cause my heart's
pounding for a different reason!
[AKI]
Oh man! It's already this late?
I need to head out.
I gotta go grab my bag.
[AYAKA]
You're fine, don't worry.
What?
I have many duties
around here,
and one of them is
keeping you on schedule.
You went into my room
without permission again?
[AKI]
I'll see you later!
[AYAKA]
Hold on, Akkun.
[AKI]
Uh?
[AYAKA]
Hm. You're going to do great.
I know you'll make
lots of friends today.
In fact, I guarantee it.
Good luck!
[AKI gasps]
[AKI] All day, nothing else
happened to make my heart race
as fast as that.
[AYAKA] Good. I'm glad your
self-introduction went nicely.
That's a great first step.
Thanks for our practice
this morning.
I didn't feel nervous when I
spoke in front of everyone.
And all the other kids in
my class seem really nice.
So everything's working out!
[AKI grunts]
You've been trying so
hard since you got here.
Such a good boy.
Miss Caretaker.
Remember, you're under
my roof now,
which means you can come to me
any time you have a problem.
When you're in Sunohara House,
you're taken care
of by a Sunohara.
[AKI chuckles]
Hm.
[AKI] And that's how
my new life in Tokyo,
or rather, in the
Sunohara House began.