[YUZU] Hey. What do you think
of age gaps in relationships?
I don't really see any
problem with it, honestly.
[YUZU]
Really? But like,
a teacher and a student
would be a huge no-no, right?
[AKI] Sorry, but can
I ask you a question?
You realize this is
my room, right?
Obviously you didn't
pay attention in science,
so let me explain something.
Kay?
[YUZU] You may remember that hot
air rises while cold air sinks.
And today is ridiculously
hot for May.
Our rooms are
on the second floor,
while yours is on the first.
You can figure out the rest.
[AKI] Then why don't you just
go hang out in the kitchen
or the living room?
Don't be such a grump,
you'll go bald from stress.
[gasps]
[YUZU]
Besides, I just like your bed.
[AKI]
Huh?
[YUZU sniffs]
It smells really nice.
[AKI] For some reason that's
really embarrassing.
[gasps, grunts]
[AKI] I'm just realizing it,
but right now,
we're alone in my room.
We haven't
acknowledged it, so...
[YUZU]
Uh?
[AKI gasps]
[YUZU] Why do you keep
glancing over here?
Don't know what you're
talking about.
[YUZU] Oh... You're curious
about my manga.
You should've said something!
Man, what am I
gonna do with you?
All right, come over here.
That's okay, I'm fine here.
Do you not know how to
respect your elders, kid?
I guess.
What about a president?
So what, you're ordering me?
[YUZU]
Yes! Hop-to, cadet!
Yeah yeah, I understand. Ma'am.
[YUZU groans]
[AKI]
Uh...
[YUZU] How can you see it if
you're all the way over there?
[AKI whimpers]
[AKI]
She's so close.
So this angle sucks.
Huh?
[YUZU sighs] I'll just sit
here and read like normal,
and you can look when you want.
[AKI]
This girl.
Well this is a problem.
Now I'm basically stuck here.
[AKI] Whatever.
Guess I might as well read.
[AKI]
It's not easy to see like this.
[AKI] So she's into
slice-of-life stories, huh?
[AKI gasps]
Wow.
There's some pretty
intimate scenes in this one.
She's kinda taking
forever to read this page.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU] I didn't expect there to
be a romantic scene like this!
[AKI]
Hm? Hey, President?
You're gonna turn the page
at some point, aren't you?
[YUZU yelps]
Yeah, just, gimme a sec.
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Shiina doesn't even register
as a boy to me, but still.
This totally looks like
I want him to do to me
what they're doing
in this manga!
[YUZU whimpers]
I'll just go ahead and turn
the page myself, okay?
[gasps]
[AKI gasps]
[AKI]
Uh...
Don't get any weird ideas, okay?
--[YUZU whines]
--[AYAKA] Huh?
[AYAKA]
I found some new recipes.
Feel free to snack on them.
Oh they look delicious!
Thanks, this is very thoughtful!
By the way, I just saw Yuzu
run out of here in a hurry.
Do you know what might
have caused that?
Your guess is as good as mine.
She was reading this manga,
then made me come read it
with her, and then she just
up and ran away suddenly.
[AYAKA]
Hm. How about this?
We'll recreate the
situation together.
Then maybe we'll be
able to figure out
what made her so upset.
[AKI]
"Recreate"?
First off, how were
you reading together?
Oh, okay. Uh... In hindsight,
it's kind of embarrassing.
I was like, sitting behind her?
Then let's try it!
Come on.
[AKI gasps]
Now read as you please, okay?
Uh, okay.
[AKI]
Easier said than done.
[AKI gasps]
[AKI]
I can't concentrate!
All right, I think
that's enough.
I completely understand now.
Really? Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Hey Shiina. I left my mang--
Are you two really
at this again?
The second I take
my eyes off of you!
How do you even
get into such--
[AYAKA] Oh goodness.
Have a cookie!
[YUZU]
Don't mind if I do!
[sighs]
Huh?
Just my imagination.
[AKI]
I'm back!
[AYAKA]
Welcome home!
[AKI sighs] All day it's felt
like someone's been watching me.
--[door creaks]
--[AKI gasps]
[AKI]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's wrong?
[AKI]
"What's wrong?"
You followed me
into the bathroom!
Well of course I did,
I'm observing you today.
[AKI gasps]
I've had this feeling all day
that someone's
been spying on me.
Don't tell me that
was you, Yamanashi.
For some reason, lately all the
President talks about is you.
I don't get it.
But I have to know.
What do you have that I don't?
[AKI]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SUMIRE]
Do not resist.
[AKI] Whatever it is, I don't
think it's tangible!
And let go of my shorts!
[AKI pants]
Wouldn't it be easier
to just ask the President
why she's talking about me?
She's a busy woman,
I couldn't possibly bother her
with something so trivial.
[AKI]
It's not trivial to you.
[AKI] Boy, Yamanashi's personal
brand of weirdness
is completely different
from the President's.
[sighs]
[sneezes]
[SUMIRE sighs] You can relax.
I won't get in your way.
[AKI] When she said
she was observing me,
I didn't think that included
in the privacy of my room.
'Kay, now where's
that dictionary?
[AKI]
I can't relax!
[SUMIRE]
What's wrong?
Your movements have
become rather awkward.
Is there a reason you're so
close to me all of a sudden?
[SUMIRE]
Mm?
[AKI sighs]
Shiina.
What do you want now?
This one here is wrong.
[AKI]
Uh. It is?
And this one.
This one over here, too.
[AKI gasps]
Are you listening to me?
Yeah, sorry about that!
You're really smart,
aren't you, Yamanashi?
I had no idea.
Well I am on the student
council, in case you forgot.
So of course I'm smart. We have
to set an example for others.
[AKI]
"On the student council."
Then the Prez is smart too?
What are you
insinuating by that?
[AKI] Nothing, nothing.
Nothing at all.
[SUMIRE] Right.
You've got the hang of it now.
[AKI gasps]
I did it!
Somehow when you
explain it to me,
it all makes sense,
and it's even kinda fun!
[gasps]
[SUMIRE] Wait. What am
I tutoring him for?
[AKI]
Huh?
I'm going to examine
your room a bit.
[AKI] Hm. Well, I suppose
that's less stressful
than having her hover
over my shoulder.
[AKI gasps]
[AKI] Don't mind me!
I'm not even looking!
I didn't see anything!
[SUMIRE gasps]
What's this?
Uh, that was just a
gift from someone.
I got it before I came here!
[SUMIRE sighs]
[AKI]
Do you like, need a moment?
No, I was just lost in thought!
[AKI] Does this mean you
like cute stuff like that?
[SUMIRE sighs]
I guess so, but I know it
doesn't really suit me. At all.
[AKI]
Hey now, that's not true!
[SUMIRE]
Uh?
Though it's not very manly and
it's a little embarrassing,
I actually like that
kinda stuff too.
I think you look cute with it.
[SUMIRE gasps]
That's right! You understand!
Who out there doesn't like
cute things! It's normal!
[AKI] Whoa, I've never
seen her so energetic.
Oh, Akkun? Here's your laundry,
all clean and folded.
[AKI]
Uh...
[AYAKA] My, oh, my!
Sorry for interrupting.
[AKI]
Nothing's happening!
I assure you, Ms. Ayaka,
there's nothing going on
between the two of us.
[AKI] Finally, someone who's
direct about misunderstandings.
We were simply revealing
the most shameful parts
of ourselves to each other.
[AKI] Never mind, she's just
oblivious in her own way!
Confiding in each other?
Well that's wonderful!
Don't you think so too, Akkun?
It wasn't anything weird!
[AYAKA]
Hm.
[SUMIRE] Shiina, I think
I'm starting to see why
the President has
taken a liking to you.
Cool, I guess.
[SUMIRE]
And if I look closely, then...
[AKI]
Yep. Very close!
On second thought,
don't worry about it.
That'll be enough for today.
I'm sorry if I bothered you.
[AKI]
"For today"?
No need to apologize, you didn't
bother me in the slightest.
[AKI]
Though I am insanely worn out.
[SUMIRE]
Oh, right.
Do me a favor and put your
more unsavory reading material
out of the President's reach.
I don't have any of that!
[YURI giggles]
[AKI]
Hey, Yuri.
What exactly happened to make
Yamanashi so depressed?
[YURI]
Well.
[YURI] It all started
when the three of us
went to the amusement park
together for a day of fun!
And indeed we found much joy in
our play. Until the incident.
[AKI] This interpretive
dance isn't helping.
I say we do that one next!
Um. There are plenty of others!
[YUZU groans]
[SUMIRE gasps]
[SUMIRE sobs]
[YURI]
You okay?
This is all my fault.
If I hadn't suggested
the amusement park,
the President wouldn't
be so humiliated!
I'll atone with my life!
Easy on the theatrics!
Now she's being
dramatic at home.
She always gets so emotional
when something happens to Yuzu.
[AKI] She seemed like the type
to roll with the punches.
We're running out
of options here.
Sumire says she's too
ashamed to face us
and Ayaka's out somewhere,
so you've gotta go in there
and cheer her up, Shiina.
[AKI]
Me?
But isn't it kinda inappropriate
for a man to barge into a lady's
room when she's upset
about something?
Well, You do have
a point, there.
But it's fine if
you're a girl, right?
[AKI]
I don't like the sound of that.
[AKI groans]
Again? Really?
Yes really. You look great!
Now get going!
[AKI exhales]
[knocking]
[AKI]
Sorry for intruding.
Who is it?
I'm Akiko?
What cute taste you have.
[AKI whimpers]
[AKI] This is
ridiculously embarrassing!
Huh?
[AKI]
Speaking of cute,
Yamanashi's room
is the definition.
I know she likes
feminine things,
but this is more
than I expected.
[SUMIRE] Did you come
here to see my room?
No, of course not!
I just wanted to help you
feel better and go back
to your usual self.
[SUMIRE]
My "usual self"?
I was my usual self earlier when
I hurt the President's feelings,
wasn't I?
Besides, I can't even get up.
[AKI] Well is there something
I can do to help you?
I'll do anything!
[AKI]
Hm!
[SUMIRE]
Help me get changed.
What now?
[sighs]
[SUMIRE]
That's so much cooler.
[SUMIRE] There're pajamas in the
second drawer of that dresser.
[AKI]
Uh, on it!
I'm in Yamanashi's room
with her practically
naked right now!
I have to get her changed quick.
Uh... This?
[AKI]
That's one less problem.
[AKI sighs]
[SUMIRE] Ugh. I never
carried the President
on my shoulders today.
I'm having withdrawal!
That's an unhealthy dependence!
[SUMIRE] I can't ask her
after what happened.
Guess I'll just die.
[AKI]
Uh?
Hey, uh... Could I
be her substitute?
Maybe... in that outfit.
[SUMIRE grunts]
[inhales]
[SUMIRE] I can feel the power
coursing through my veins.
I'll be okay now.
Apologies for worrying you.
I'm glad I could help somehow.
So, could you maybe
put me down?
[AKI]
This is so embarrassing.
I'm sorry to cause you concern.
I'm just glad you're better!
I don't know what I would do if
you stayed all gloomy like that.
[YURI giggles]
Plus, I haven't ridden
on your shoulders today
like I usually do. And that
just doesn't feel right.
[SUMIRE]
President!
Also. I'm not as easy to
break as you think I am.
I'm strong. Kay?
I've overcome all
obstacles so far.
You've always been there,
so you should know that
better than anyone.
And with that out of the way.
[YUZU]
Let's try again!
[SUMIRE]
Brilliant as always, President!
[YUZU chuckles]
[PARK EMPLOYEE A]
Yeah, no.
--[YUZU gasps]
--What cruel fate.
[YURI]
Hm.
Shiina.
Huh?
[YURI]
Shiina.
Where's that voice coming from?
[YURI]
Right here!
[AKI yelps] Geez, thanks for
the scare, Yuri!
[YURI]
Sorry about that.
I just have a favor
to ask of you.
Favor?
That's what I said!
It's something that only you
can really help me with,
so, I have to ask.
[AKI]
Huh? Something only I can do?
Does that mean she's relying on
me to be the man around here?
Not a problem!
If it's within my ability,
I'll do whatever you need!
And a man never goes
back on his word!
[YURI]
Hm... That's perfect.
Then without further ado, please
follow me over to my room.
Okay!
But wouldn't it be a little
weird for us to be in your room
without anyone else there?
Oh, it'll be fine. Like I said,
you're the only person
that can help me with this.
[AKI gasps]
Okay!
Come in. I'm sorry it's
a little bit messy.
I don't think it's very messy.
[AKI] This is the first time
I've even seen Yuri's room,
let alone gone in it.
I'm a little nervous.
[AKI gasps] This picture's nice.
Did you take it?
[YURI]
Sure did.
Wow, you all look so young!
Some words of advice: That's a
little rude to say to a woman.
Anyway, let's get
down to business.
Aw yeah, let's do it!
I'm down for anything!
Or, actually I can't help
with bugs, but anything else!
Then you won't mind
putting this on!
Huh?
You want me to wear this?
You know, you've dressed
me up as a girl a lot lately,
I'm starting to sense a pattern.
[YURI]
I make costumes as a hobby,
and I'd like to
see how they fit.
Yuzu is too small, and Sumire
and Ayaka are both too big.
So I thought about it,
and you're the only one I know
who's close enough to
my size for the job.
Yeah sure, but aren't
these clothes for girls?
Well yeah, technically,
but you're cute,
so it'll be fine.
Besides, you said you'd
do anything, if I recall.
[AKI]
Couldn't you try it on?
You said you'd do anything,
if I recall.
Uh... All right, all right.
I'll put on the outfit, so can
you please turn around?
[AKI] My sister used to make
me do this a lot, too.
[AKI]
But this is made for Yuri,
there's no way the
chest is gonna fit me.
Hold on.
[AKI whimpers]
I managed to get it on.
So how's it fit?
[AKI]
Strangely enough, perfectly.
[YURI] No surprise there, I did
make it for you from the start.
[AKI] Um. Now that you've gotten
a sense for the fit, can I go?
[YURI] Not yet. I need you to
try on all of these outfits!
[AKI] Wha-- All of them?
Isn't that a bit much?
[AKI]
This is a one-time thing.
Make sure to strike
a cute pose, too!
[YURI] Yeah, that's it.
That's great, Shiina.
Wonderful. Hold that position.
Yes, work it!
That expression's perfect.
Fantastic! So cute. So cute!
Adorable! This is everything
I hoped it'd be!
[pants]
[YURI]
Now for the last one!
[AKI gasps]
No way!
[YURI] Wait, it'll
look great, I promise!
[AKI]
I don't want it to look great!
I'm not putting that on, Yuri!
I never will!
--[YURI] Shiina, calm down!
--[AKI] Hey, stop!
I said it's not happening, so
give it a rest already!
[AKI]
It's way too small!
[YURI] Will you stop
running away from me?
[AYAKA] What's going on
up there? Is everyone all right?
[AKI] Miss Caretaker!
Red alert, emergency!
I can't let her see
me like this! Ugh!
That'll work!
[AKI grunts]
C'mere!
I'm coming in now.
[AYAKA]
Uh... What the...?
[AKI gasps]
Why are we--?
[AKI]
Shh!
[AYAKA] I guess I must have
been hearing things.
--[door shuts]
--[AKI sighs]
[YURI]
Hey.
[AKI]
Huh?
Do you have any thoughts on this
clichéd situation we're in?
What?
[AKI shouts]
[giggles]
[AKI grunts]
Aside from dressing me up, she
seems like a nice enough girl.
And she smelled really good.
[gasps]
Seriously. He's such a goof!
There. We still don't
have a picture of
all five of us together,
but at least I
have everyone now.