[AYAKA]
Akkun, it's almost time to go.
[AKI]
Huh?
[giggles]
[AKI] Woah. That's not
your usual outfit.
I'm sorry, are we doing
something today?
Yes, we're helping Yatsuho
out in the shopping district.
Didn't you already know?
I thought I asked Yuzu
to tell you about it.
Uh. Guess I forgot.
What a surprise.
Anyway, I wanted your help
the whole day, is that okay?
Yeah... Happy to be
of assistance!
Oh! She set up tables outside?
Uh-huh.
Sneak attack... Welcome!
I've been expecting you!
[NISHIKI laughs]
[AKI] Someone's been
hittin' the sauce...
[AYAKA giggles]
We're happy to help,
but don't work us too hard!
[AKI]
What are we helping with?
Oktoberfest. Yatsuho needs
some extra hands.
Lots of people show up
for an alcohol festival.
[AKI]
An alcohol festival?
Wait, is this that
"beerfest" thing
you told me about that one time?
Yup. Though,
all things considered,
it's still a relatively
small event.
C'mon. I'll show you around.
[AKI] Wow, there are so
many different kinds.
[NISHIKI] Yeah, my grandpa knew
a thing or two about liquor.
And thanks to that, I've got
one hell of a selection.
Please, try to give
yourself some credit.
You've been running
the place well
since you took
over his shop.
Keep complimenting me like that,
and you're gonna make me blush!
[AKI] Can't say I ever
got the impression
she was business-savvy.
This is a good opportunity.
Yatsuho suggests our newer
residents help out here
during the event.
That way they can get
accustomed to the area!
Yeah, that's what
I say on paper.
But really I just
need the extra help.
[laughs]
[AYAKA giggles] Well either way,
you've got us both here now.
That's right!
And one of you still needs to
change into your uniform.
[AKI]
Uniform?
Here yah go!
[AKI]
I saw this coming, but really?
I know, sorry. I've only ever
had girls help out in the past,
so I haven't had a
guy's version made.
But you're cute enough
to pull it off,
so no one will know
the difference.
Or, and hear me out here,
I could just not wear it!
[gasps]
Oh, right.
Trust me, you're gonna need
this at some point today.
When the time comes,
you'll understand.
[AKI] Yuri gave me
that backpack earlier.
I bet she saw this coming
and sewed me a men's unif--
Or not.
[AKI groans]
Adorable. It looks great on you!
How crazy is it that you
had a wig with you already?
[AKI groans]
[AKI]
It's kinda chilly.
All right, listen up!
Oktoberfest is a
German celebration.
Which means today...
...das ist Deutschland!
Yeah, only our costumes
scream Germany!
Whatever, let's open up shop!
[MALE CUSTOMER A]
You open?
Had to hit up our
favorite place!
Yup! We're ready to go!
Thank you both for coming.
We have customers this early?
[NISHIKI] Yeah, business really
began to boom once Ayaka
started helping me out.
They all seem to love her!
[NISHIKI laughs]
[AKI]
I think I know why.
[MALE CUSTOMER A]
Um, Excuse me, Miss!
We're ready to order!
Oh! Coming!
Here's where the
job really begins.
What would you like?
This one, and, uh,
this one, please.
[AKI]
Mm... What are they called?
The German names are
a bit hard to read.
[AKI]
Huh?
One Schöfferhofer Weizen ,
a pint of Paulaner
Oktoberfest Bier ,
and an order of boiled
weisswurst over here please!
[NISHIKI]
Got it!
Amazing!
[AYAKA chuckles]
You'll start to pick them up
the more you hear them,
so don't worry.
Okay! Thanks!
[AYAKA]
Hm!
[ATTENDEES chattering]
[NISHIKI]
Two goin' out.
Okay.
Geez. These mugs are
surprisingly heavy.
[ATTENDEES chattering]
[AKI]
Uh. Here are your drinks.
[AYAKA]
Coming behind you, watch out.
Here are your drinks, everyone!
[AKI]
She can carry four of them?
Here are your drinks!
[MALE CUSTOMER B]
Whoa!
Uh... I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
No big deal.
Seriously, you're fine.
Getting to see a cute girl
like you spill a drink is
practically a treat itself!
What do you mean, dear?
That's weird.
Let me know if any of it
got on your clothes.
I'll wipe off the
table right away.
Here are two fresh,
new glasses,
and naturally, your food
is on the house this time.
[MALE CUSTOMER B]
I almost feel guilty!
You basically did me
a favor, little lady.
[FEMALE CUSTOMER B]
Don't mind him.
Between you and me,
he's kind of a bonehead.
[AKI] I screwed up and Miss
Caretaker had to cover for me.
I knew I couldn't
do this. I suck.
Don't look so down,
we all make mistakes.
I'll be here to help you
every step of the way,
so don't be afraid
to keep trying.
Turn that frown
upside down! Okay?
[AKI]
Hm...? Yeah, you're right!
[NISHIKI]
Good work!
Man. You really saved my bacon!
You wouldn't need saving
if you'd put down the beer
Take my word for it,
you make one great waitress!
You should become my mascot, eh?
No way!
I only put the wig on cus
I'd die of embarrassment
if someone I knew
saw me in this!
Oh, Akkun. You're such
a good boy!
You were really cool
out there today.
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA chuckles]
[AKI gasps] You gave
Miss Caretaker alcohol.
What's the matter with you?
[laughs]
[NISHIKI] I had to, she worked
so hard! She'll be fine.
[AKI] Come on.
Gimme a break!
[NISHIKI] It'll be fine.
I only gave her a littel bit.
[NISHIKI, AYAKA laugh]
[AYAKA] Kyoto and Nara will
be lovely this time of year.
There better not be
any funny business
just cus you'll be alone.
What is that even
supposed to mean?
Have fun on your trip,
you three.
[GIRLS]
Kay! We'll see you later.
I hope I'm able to get
some good pictures.
I wanna see the big Buddha.
By the way, do you have
everything you need, President?
Yeah I double checked.
Ooo, and lots of temples!
[SUMIRE]
Yes.
We won't see them for a bit.
Yep.
It's going to be
pretty lonely at home
with no one but us around.
Ha, ha. Should we sleep
together tonight?
I, uh--! No, I'll be
fine on my own!
[AYAKA giggles]
[AYAKA] I guess I'll start
with breakfast cleanup, then.
I wonder what my three favorite
student council members
are up to right now.
My, it's gotten cold
awfully quickly.
[NANA]
Yo, Ayaka!
[gasps]
Thought I'd come
give you a visit!
[AYAKA] Oh, hey Nana!
Welcome home.
So what's the food situation?
Not gonna lie,
I'm pretty hungry.
Of course. What are
you in the mood for?
It's kinda chilly,
so something' hot!
What can I make
that'll be hot?
[AYAKA gasps] I know just
the thing! Hang on a minute.
[AYAKA]
Here you go!
[AKI]
Thanks a bunch!
Freakin' awesome,
roasted sweet potatoes!
Don't mind me,
I'm gonna chow down.
So good! And really sweet!
[NANA] Mm! That's what
I'm talkin' 'bout!
[AYAKA giggles]
Glad you like them.
There's something about having
these in the backyard
that's kinda fun.
[AYAKA]
Right?
The girls are on their field
trip right now, aren't they?
They're missing out,
this is way better.
This is tasty, but I don't
know if I would go that far.
I know, we should send 'em
a pic and make 'em jealous!
[AKI]
Hm?
--[NANA giggles]
--[AKI sneezes]
[phone beeps]
[YUZU] Hm...? Look I
got a text from Nana.
What'd she say?
[SUMIRE]
A sweet potato?
[YUZU] I guess they're
eating together?
[phone beeps]
Oh! There's Yucchi.
[AKI]
Huh?
[NANA] Those dango
look pretty good too.
[AKI chuckles] They seem
like they're having fun.
[AKI] Uh, though they sure
are eating a lot of food.
[AYAKA]
You can too!
We have lots more
where that came from.
[NANA] Do you know
how fat I would get
if I ate all those potates?
Which reminds me, you better not
be eating as much as these kids
in their growth spurts
or you'll get big, too.
I burn a lot of calories taking
care of the grounds here,
so it's fine.
[AKI, NANA]
To an extent.
[ALL gasp]
[AYAKA gapss] I know you just
said it's fun to eat outside,
but maybe it's time
to go in now.
[NANA] Yeah, you right.
Geez, my legs are freezing!
Would it be cool if I
use the bath, Ayaka?
[AYAKA] Sure. Want to
use it together?
[NANA]
Huh? For real?
[AYAKA]
Yeah.
[beeping]
I know I've been
slackin' lately,
but this is worse
than I thought.
I had a feeling you
were hiding something
with your baggy clothes.
Seriously? You noticed that?
Well, I am your sister.
[NANA scoffs] Then why'd
you immediately give me
something as high-calorie
as roasted sweet potato?
Hey, you liked it, didn't you?
Yeah of course, but that's
not the point!
I'm sorry, I just wanted
to give you something
you don't get to
have very often.
And I know you don't
make those yourself.
Ugh... You saw me,
so lemme get a look at you!
[AYAKA]
Oh my!
[NANA] Of course,
what did I expect?
You're as stylish
and slim as ever.
Actually....
[AYAKA yelps]
[Nana chuckles]
Can you please stop
pinching my side?
[NANA]
Girl!
[AYAKA]
Hm?
If you don't change something,
you're gonna be in trouble soon.
[AYAKA] Looks like you're about
to cause trouble with that face.
[AYAKA gasps]
You're gonna be in trouble!
Excuse you!
[NANA]
Trouble, trouble, trouble!
Better cut back on those
sweet potates, huh?
What are those two
doing in there?
--[phone beeps]
--Huh?
And what are those three doing?
[NANA]
Bye! See yah again soon!
[AYAKA]
Take care. Get home safe!
[yawns]
[clattering]
Huh?
[AKI] Nana already left,
so who's making that noise?
Could it be a thief?
[AKI] I'm the only one here!
I gotta protect Miss Caretaker!
[gasps]
Am I imagining it
because of Nana
or am I "in trouble" for real?
Umm, so which button is it?
Huh? Wait, what? What happened?
[AKI]
I was never here.
Plus, there's nothing wrong
with a little exercise.
[GIRLS]
We're home!
[AYAKA breathes weakly]
[AKI snores]
[AKI grunts]
[AKI gasps] Oh come on,
Miss Caretaker!
I appreciate you always
waking me up on time,
but do me a favor and maybe
call my name instead of...
[AYAKA panting]
Akkun...? It's morning.
[AKI] Hey, I don't
think you look so good.
President! Help!
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah!
What do you want?
What's the problem?
[AKI] It's Miss Caretaker,
she collapsed!
And she's breathing
all heavy and--
What do we do? I'm freakin' out!
Like, call an ambulance
or something?
I think that's what we're
supposed to do, right?
[YUZU] For now stop
rambling like an idiot.
And get out of my
room for a second.
[AKI grunts]
You think she's gonna
make it, right?
Stop being dramatic.
This isn't that serious.
You were flipping out so much,
I thought the situation
was way worse than it is.
But this is probably
just a cold.
[AKI gasps] Oh yeah, she was
exercising in light clothing.
I bet she that's
when she caught it.
More importantly...
[AKI grunts]
[YUZU] You gonna apologize
for bursting into my room
without even knocking earlier?
Yeah sure, I'm sorry.
We shouldn't force her
to walk elsewhere,
so I guess we'll have her
sleep it off in your room
for the time being.
--[knocking]
--[door creaks]
[SUMIRE] We found her some
pajamas like you asked.
I imagine she'll
sweat a decent amount,
so we got a second
set and a towel.
[YUZU] Good work. All right,
let's get her changed.
Sumire, Yuri,
gimme a hand, will yah?
[AKI gasps]
[YUZU]
And you... get out of here!
[AKI grunts]
[AKI whimpers]
[YUZU] Okay, Shiina.
Now the rest is up to you.
[AKI]
Huh?
We have to go. We have student
council business today.
It's important, so we need you
to nurse Ayaka back to health
on your own.
I'll tell the school what's
going on, so you're fine.
Though I admit, I'm a little
reluctant to leave the two
of you home alone.
Make me proud.
Understood, ma'am!
Not to toot my own horn,
but I definitely just sounded
like a strong, capable senior.
[AYAKA whimpers]
[YUZU]
Here's your piping hot stew!
And we're gonna feed it to you
while it's nice and scalding.
[YUZU, AKI chuckle]
What's gotten into you?
You're being cruel!
Yuzu, Akkun, please,
think about this!
It's hot!
[AYAKA gasps]
Just a dream?
Where am I? Wait, is this
Akkun's room?
It makes sense he's gone,
everyone should
be at school now.
Oh, Akkun...
[AKI] Hey, you're awake!
I was hoping you'd get up soon!
Didn't want this soup
getting cold on ya.
You didn't hear me, right?
No.
[AYAKA] Then never mind.
Wait, what about school?
You can't just skip classes,
we need to tell them why.
There's nothing to worry about.
The President's got my back,
she said she'd take care of it.
Besides, it's not like
I could leave you alone
in this condition,
someone's gotta look after you.
Today your job is
to rest and recover.
So if you need anything,
you can rely on me,
no matter what it is!
How could I ever rely
on a naughty boy
who's willing to skip school?
But... I...!
[AYAKA giggles]
I was just joking.
I'm grateful to have you.
[AYAKA] So
as for my first request,
do you think you could do
something about that soup
you brought me?
Yeah, sure!
[AKI]
Here you go.
Ah...
Ah?
[whimpers, gulps]
Kay. Ah. Ahh.
[AKI] I don't know why
I'm embarrassed by this.
[AYAKA]
That was wonderful.
Huh. Your clothes
are pretty soaked.
Better get changed.
Uh... don't mind me!
I'll just go out to the hall!
[AYAKA]
Oh, please wait!
[AKI]
Huh?
I don't think I can
reach my back myself.
Could you wipe it for me?
You want me to wipe your back?
[AYAKA] I'm not going to
force you to, of course.
[AKI]
Uh... Fine! Okay!
Great! The sooner the better.
[AKI]
Woah, woah! Hold on a minute!
[AYAKA gasps] Oh. Do you
need to go get a towel?
[AKI] Yeah, like that's
the problem here!
I don't believe you're that
out of it for a second!
That's a lot better. Just stay
facing that way, okay?
Not that I should have to
tell you that to begin with.
Yes, I understand.
[AKI gulps]
[AKI]
Calm down. Be cool.
You're just taking care of her.
[AKI]
Keep it together...
Keep it together.
You're doin' great.
[gasps] Sorry to ask, but could
you get a different spot for me?
[AKI]
Huh?
[AYAKA sighs]
[AKI gasps]
[AYAKA]
I'll hold them up,
so, could you wipe
me down here too?
[AKI shouts]
[AYAKA] Like I said,
I won't force you.
but it'd sure help me out.
Uh...
Yeah, whatever you need.
[AKI] That's right.
I'm just taking care of her!
Because if I don't,
then who will?
I've gotta do it!
Thank you, I appreciate
all the help.
[AKI]
You're... welcome.
Good morning everyone!
[YUZU]
Ah!
Sorry for making you all worry,
but thanks to your efforts,
I'm back and ready to work!
And Akkun deserves a special
thanks for what he did!
It was nothing.
You didn't take advantage
of the situation
and do anything weird, I hope.
Right, Shiina?
I'm sure something happened.
[AKI]
No, nothing did!
I only took care
of her, really--
[coughs]
Oh! Don't tell me.
Did you catch my cold?
Oh I doubt it. Dust got
in my throat, probably.
[AYAKA sighs] I'd like to
repay the favor sometime.
So how about this?
If you ever get a fever,
I'll wipe you all over.
Repay you?
As in...
You wiped her all over?
[AKI gasps]
You know what?
I better get to school early
to make up for yesterday!
Yup, sorry I can't
chat more, I'll see yah!