Hey, rifle heads,
what's a guy gotta do to get a little food in here?
Kars!
This man's mechanical.
You're Von Stroheim!
Double shock!
This is spookier than meeting a
ghost in a dark cemetery after midnight.
Kars...
And Von Stroheim, who I could have sworn was
blown into little, tiny bits back in Mexico,
they're both standing right in front of me.
Kars,
and Von Stroheim is here, too.
His hand looks like it's made of metal,
and his face is wrapped in some strange machinery.
The Germans must have been hiding this.
What incredible medical technology.
Could it be for some kind of military use?
I guess that's what saved your
miserable life, Von Stroheim.
JoJo, as you can see, I'm back from hell.
Should I be happy about it?
When you get down to it, he's not exactly a bad guy,
except for the fact that he's a damn German soldier.
And I don't like the way he struts
around like he's better than everyone else.
Still, I am a bit happy.
Why don't you make yourself at home on
the sofa and watch me while I do my work?
H‐he's glaring at me.
He knows that I'm the one who killed Esidisi,
and he hates me for it.
Even so...
Kars! Do you think I'm gonna just sit
here and let you try and psyche me out?!
JoJo, once I'm finished securing the stone,
I'm going to put an end to you.
It's too bad Wamuu is still off working in Greece.
I can't allow a hamon user who was
able to beat Esidisi to remain alive.
Tell me something, Kars. Do you speak as a warrior,
or are you after something else, like revenge?
Pay attention. You're fighting me.
I'm the one who is going to be your final opponent.
No machine can stop me.
Is that right?
Arms of flesh and blood can't bend like
that, which means they are mechanical.
Now for the fun.
Wait. He's...
His fingers squeeze at 1,950
kilograms per centimeter squared,
almost twice Santviento 's strength
you utter fool!
German science is the finest in the world!
These arms have such great power!
They were constructed based
on the abilities of Santviento!
And so, Kars...
We calculated exactly what we need to do to you.
In order to eliminate your power
and leave you in desperate agony.
I'm going to pluck you like a chicken, bit by bit,
and take you apart one square centimeter at a time.
Hey, JoJo...
Yow! Hey.
Don't you dare even think about feeling sorry for me.
My proud new form...
Is the very embodiment of the ultimate
peak of German science and engineering!
You see, I'm not merely human. I'm more!
Take this, Kars.
My machine gun can fire 600 rounds per minute,
and shred through armor plating like it was made of paper.
I'll whittle you down into tiny pieces in no time at all.
His body's mechanical, too?
...the hell was that?
It came from downstairs.
I swear the stone will be mine today.
Attempting to get it cost Esidisi his life.
I refuse to allow his ultimate
sacrifice to have been in vain.
That light.
The blade coming out of his arm is glowing.
I can control light.
Behold brilliant bone blade.
Impossible.
That blade is hardened bone and skin,
not weapons‐grade forged steel.
It shouldn't be able to deflect bullets like
that let alone slice them in half in midair.
His blade is amazing, but why is it glowing like that?
Here he comes. Here he comes.
Here he comes. Here he comes. Here he comes.
I... I know that sound.
Upon seeing the blade up close,
Von Stroheim was able to understand its secret.
It didn't have a simple edge.
Rather, it had a rotating blade moving at high speed.
Tiny, razor‐sharp claws slid quietly
along the outer edge of the blade,
ready to shred anything in its path.
Each claw was flawlessly polished to a mirror
like finish and refracted the faintest light,
making the blade look as though
it were glowing from within.
W‐we can't win this,
at least not with my weapons or
any modern technology that I know of.
We can't defeat him.
And what was Santviento?
Nothing but a weak child, a well trained guard dog.
He couldn't even compare to us.
Now I'll take that stone.
Kars. What the hell?
That ice‐cold sheen across his face.
A blade that can cut bullets in midair.
There's no way I could ever block
that thing with only my bare hands.
Even if I could concentrate all
of my hamon into a single blow,
that blade would still slice right through me.
To be perfectly honest,
I want to run away from here.
He's way too dangerous to take on directly.
I can't think of any way to get around that blade of his.
Then again, I can't just leave and let him take the stone.
If he obtains the stone's power,
he'd become practically invincible.
I'd never be able to defeat him.
Damn it all.
I have to get my hands on Wamuu's antidote.
Kars wants to kill me after all.
Why me? Was this in my horoscope?
What is this?
What's in this pocket here?
Oh. The Red Stone of Aja.
I have waited a long time for this, 5,000 years,
and at last the stone is mine.
Not that I ever doubted it would be.
It was destined to fall into my hands.
Kars!
Just be patient.
I'll kill you in a moment.
Damn, that bastard.
H‐he really hates everything about me.
Letting him walk away with the
stone would mean the end for everyone.
Kars, you fool.
Don't think you've beaten me,
because I'm not finished with you yet.
Huh?
German science is the world's greatest!
I will beat you!
Von Stroheim, you idiot, what do you think you're doing?
How can you sit there and boast at a time like this?
Ultraviolet beams, activate!
It's the stone!
Huh? Oh, no. The stone is sliding down the slope.
Ah, damn it, no!
We have to stop it.
The stone is sliding toward the cliff.
If it falls off, it could be lost forever!
What the hell? Look at this.
W‐what's happened in here?
Kars happened.
JoJo, you have to go after the stone!
Grab it while you still can.
Damn. He's catching up.
He's fast. He's focused on the stone like a laser.
The way he keeps accelerating, he must be
planning to grab the stone and fall off the cliff.
He won't be able to stop before he reaches the edge.
D‐damn it! The drop beyond that
cliff is at least several hundred meters.
With all his superior abilities,
Kars could survive the fall,
but it's as high as jumping off the
tallest skyscraper without a parachute.
It'd be certain death for me.
He's passing me.
JoJo plans to slow down before he reaches
the edge so he doesn't go flying off,
but not Kars. JoJo can't win.
There's no way I'm gonna let this
slime get his hands on the stone.
Go! Run hard, JoJo!
JoJo, when I reach down to grab
the stone, I'll be off balance.
With my flank open, I'll be vulnerable.
Is that when you'll do it? Is
that when you'll try to kick me?
Huh?
You'll attack me with your hamon, even if
it means the stone disappears into the abyss.
You think your plan will work, JoJo?
Look there. JoJo.
You're right on the nose, Kars.
Here it comes! It's the kick you ordered!
No!
Ah. He's used his legs to pick up the stone
right as JoJo kicked him. He's going to get away with it.
I don't believe it.
Now, Kars, what's with that ridiculously arrogant grin?
I mean, I'm the one who should be smiling here.
I guess I should have expected as much from you.
A trick like that really isn't good enough to fool me.
My kick wasn't aimed at your
vulnerable flank, but rather the snow,
and it worked just like a brake.
What do you know? Looks like I'm the
one who made the nice catch, not you.
Enjoy your trip, Kars.
Uhh! Aw, man. No way!
Aah! A blade from his foot?!
JoJo!
He's falling with Kars.
What's happening?
Kars's blade is starting to meld itself with my body.
It won't come out.
Y‐you son of a bitch!
It's 175 meters to the bottom,
five seconds until impact.
Damn. Falling to my death with this guy?
No, thank you.
Clinging hamon!
He's so heavy.
Hamon goes through fluids easily,
but ice and snow are solid and impede the hamon.
But water is trickling down the ice,
so the hamon can use that to flow around the solids.
Thus it's working perfectly.
I don't care what you do. The stone will be mine.
That's it exactly.
That tenacity of yours, it's what scares me the most.
I'm best at exploiting my opponent's negligence,
so a tenacious foe is the absolute worst for me to face.
Tenacity is the opposite of negligence.
It will be mine today!
More icicles up ahead.
Before I can do anything, I have
to get this blade out of my shoulder.
Wait. I can just send hamon through
the blade and directly into Kars.
Take this!
As I thought.
I knew you would try using my blade against me.
Just for that,
it's into the cliff wall with you!
And now...
N‐no. Wait.
He's gonna use that blade and cut me into pieces.
Kars is waiting for JoJo to
rebound before he starts cutting him.
There's no way he can dodge that.
Now I'm going to take great pleasure in
slicing you in half and picking up the stone,
at the bottom of the abyss.
You...
Now, you're not about to cut this, are you?
You wouldn't dare take the chance of
chopping the stone in half along with me.
I can use your own strength against you by letting
your tenacity act as a defensive measure for me.
Now eat this, Kars! Hamon kick!
Damn, he's trying to use the falling icicles as a rope.
He's clever...
But they're in a freefall, too.
He'll never reach the top.
In that case, allow me to lend a hand. Hold on.
Huh?
Caesar!
Hey, nice timing, don't you think, JoJo?
What the hell's going on?
And what are you two, some kind of a team?
Heh. Fusing falling icicles together to make
a rescue rope, I had nothing to do with that.
Only JoJo would try something that colossally stupid.
It was predictable.
At least you were able to think up
a stupid trick and then pull it off
in the nick of time. I'm proud of you, Caesar.
Eh? What was that?
Nice. Nice.
Real outstanding work, caesarino.
And, hey, if Lisa Lisa is up there, give her a message.
I've got the red stone, and it's safe.
I kept him from snatching it.
That was a close call.
All right, Caesar, you had better pull him up now.
Now, my German compatriot,
your body is even more durable
than any of theirs could hope to be.
Listen. If you can stop with the
snobbery, maybe we can work together.
JoJo, you're a lucky one.
I'll let you hold the stone for me
for at least another day.
So this is Switzerland's famous Saint Moritz, a
winter sports hub often referred to as sun valley,
chic, relaxed, and sophisticated,
a resort that the wealthy flock to during the holidays.
Even the cats look like they're owned by actresses
and are pampered at all the finest spas in Europe.
Aren't we fussy?
Not even a tiny glance for shrimp?
This little Princess thinks
she's the center of the universe,
but doesn't know a thing about the world at all.
All right, then.
Would this smoked salmon suit your snooty palate better?
There we go.
It seems I've found what you prefer.
That's it. Reach for it.
Just a little bit higher now.
Stretch up just a little more there.
I gotcha now.
Oh? Did I upset you?
Enjoy, you puny, pompous puffball.
That was pretty mean.
I don't know why I thought it would be a good idea.
It's just because I'm really on edge.
We only have five days until the ring dissolves,
and Kars is absolutely serious about killing me.
I can feel the threats closing in.
They're all around.
I have to relax.
This is ridiculous. I'm the one who's always
saying you can't sit around moping about stuff.
JoJo, what are you doing just sitting there?
Get up out of that chair, come
over here, and look at this.
Right. Be there in a second.
The building on top of that hill is
the address Esidisi put on the package.
It looks like the abandoned corpse of a shuttered hotel.
It would make a perfect hideout
for Kars during daylight hours.
Every doorway and window is boarded up.
No sunlight could get in there.
That's got to be it.
I'm sure Kars hides in there during the day.
I bet he's just sitting inside,
waiting for Wamuu to show up.
All right. So what is the plan?
Humph. That's a no‐brainer.
We should attack now.
Yes, I agree.
Kars can't go outside as long as the sun is up,
and that gives us a tremendous advantage.
What do you think?
Sorry, but...
I have to disagree with you.
You're looking at this wrong.
I think it's more dangerous to attack when the sun is up.
Just think about it. Kars has been
living like this for thousands of years.
He wouldn't have survived if he had
left himself defenseless during the day.
Oh, please!
Walking into his hideout and trying to
take him down right now would be suicidal.
I'm not going to do it.
It would be like a bug walking
into a spider's web on purpose.
Hah! Come on.
JoJo, this isn't like you. Are you scared or something?
I think I'm going to take sun tzu's advice this time.
Only engage in a fight when victory is assured.
Like I said, I'm not going in.
Oh, yeah? So you're chickening out?
I'm not afraid.
I'm just thinking straight.
I've got a cool head, unlike you.
Caesar, we have to wait for him to make his move first.
An assured victory is what you want?
Kars is all alone there. It's him against all of us.
That's a four‐to‐one advantage.
We have to strike now, before
Wamuu arrives, cutting that in half.
Calm down.
Don't go off all crazy now.
Try and keep your head together.
Just focus, and think it through.
If we go now, he'll cut us to pieces.
You can't approach this half‐cocked.
I am not half‐cocked!
I'm gonna end this!
I am going to finally finish the fight
that cut short the lives of both of our grandfathers!
I'm gonna destroy Kars!
You're going to finish it?
Right, and why bring our dead grandfathers into this?
Who the hell cares?!
Don't drag the dead into your little drama, you moron.
What did you say to me?
Family you've never met and that came
long before your time doesn't mean crap.
It's just foolish.
Only a complete idiot would die for something like that.
Caesar?
You watch your mouth, JoJo!
Hey, what was that for, you...
A sucker punch, huh?
Oh, it's on.
What the hell, Caesar?! What's wrong with you?!
Just shut the hell up!
Caesar, stop it. Now.
You too, JoJo!
Caesar!
You bastard, what's with you?
Have you completely lost it?
You're acting like some kind of a madman.
JoJo, I guess you won't ever understand the concept
of family honor and inheriting a battle like this.
Huh?
Enough. I'm going.
Caesar, JoJo is right.
It's far too dangerous.
We have no way of knowing what
might be waiting for us in there.
We'll wait for Kars to make his move.
That is an order, Caesar.
The only thing that matters now
is protecting the Red Stone of Aja.
No, coach, I'm sorry.
I can't obey this time.
You know this is a matter of blood and family honor.
It's a Zeppeli problem.
I just can't leave it unsettled when
I know exactly where Kars is hiding.
I can't sit here twirling my
thumbs, waiting for him to come to me!
What do we do?
Follow him, and do whatever you have to to stop
him from entering, even if it means using force.
Caesar, why are you doing this?
Why are you so damn grim and hotheaded all of a sudden?
Why can't you be patient and just wait a while?
You see, you've inadvertently touched
on a painful piece of his hidden past.
Although you didn't mean to, you've hit upon a dark place
where he harbors his saddest secrets.
Caesar has a hidden past?
W‐what the hell could it be?
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
I feel like I did back then when I was na ïve and poor!
I'll use my viciousness to destroy you!
Very well. You are worthy of
death at my hands, bubble user!