The hamon...
Has almost reached my head and brain.
Must do something.
Move, arm. Move!
Ohh.
Lord Dio.
We'll get a new body for you.
Excerpt from the December 4,
1888, edition of the London press
it has been reported that 73 of the 452 residents in
the town of wind knights lot have gone missing overnight.
The police have been pursuing lines of inquiry
based on certain witness accounts.
These accounts state that four outsiders were seen
burning a man's clothing at the base of a nearby cliff.
One of the four was reportedly wielding a large
hammer and using it to smash a curious stone mask.
Our work here is done.
Heir to the Joestar fortune,
Jonathan Joestar weds Erina,
only daughter of the pendletons.
The couple will travel to the Americas.
Nice.
Blazes!
Look what time it is!
Their ship's about to leave!
Oi!
Eh? Mr. Speedwagon!
You almost missed being able to say goodbye.
Sorry I'm so late.
So then, where are they?
They're both on board the ship.
Eh?!
It's about ready to sail.
What? It is?
Where are they? I've got to see them.
Now then, father styx,
we expect to hear great things
from your mission to Mexico.
I'll certainly do what I can.
Jonathan Joestar! Where are you?!
Watch where you're goin'!
What makes this thing so blasted heavy, anyway?
How should I know?
We been hired by that Asian
bloke, so we move it where he says.
Hmm?
Oi. D‐did you boys hear that?
Quit flappin' your blasted cake hole.
Now move it! We don't get paid 'til this job's done.
Ow. Ruddy hooligans.
Mr. Speedwagon.
Hmm?
Look. They're up there.
Hello!
Jonathan!
What a beautiful sight.
I wish you a long, love‐filled life.
I'll always be here for you.
If you ever need me, just call. I'll be there.
Though at the moment,
I'd just be in the way, eh?
Bon voyage!
Have a wonderful trip!
Poor little bird, all alone.
Did you lose your flock?
Erina.
Something wrong, love?
Dear, what are you crying about?
These tears that I'm crying are from joy,
joy that I am here with you.
Even as a boy, you strove to be a true gentleman,
a champion of others, no matter
the consequence to yourself.
And now that proud and noble Jonathan Joestar
is here in my arms.
And I have you.
When my heart was frozen in despair,
you warmed me and brought me back to life.
I am fortunate to have saved a world that has you in it.
I only wish father could have known you.
Erina, come. Supper is waiting.
Jonathan!
Um, I wanted to tell you to be
careful so you wouldn't bash your head.
Ah, I wish that today would last forever.
Damn, it fell into the engine room.
That's a filthy place to go after it.
I could just sell it,
but it brings in the shekels.
Dear lord.
You surely do seem to enjoy picking on me.
Oh. No.
I haven't the experience drinking a man does.
Just a bit, barely enough to get the taste.
It really isn't strong at all.
I think it's good.
Here.
Eh?
No. It can't be.
Jonathan?
Impossible.
There is no way.
He's here. Dio's alive.
Erina, go. Back to our cabin now.
And don't forget to lock the door.
Humph.
Eh?
Well, that's rather strange.
The lock's undone.
Queer bit of business.
I can see a metal catch glinting on the inside there.
But that would mean...
That this trunk is locked from the inside!
Halt!
You can't escape!
Where is...
My body?
D‐dio.
Jonathan is so upset.
Something is wrong.
JoJo.
Do you see the condition in which I find myself?
Your work.
There is a reason I display myself to you like this.
Why would I show my weakness to my deadliest foe?
Because though I once despised you,
now I have only the greatest respect for your spirit,
your valor in battle, your power.
I see it now, how incredible you are.
Dio.
JoJo.
If not for you, I would never have
obtained the power of the stone mask.
However, your damnable meddling cost me world domination.
If there really is a god,
one who plucks the strings of our fate,
I am certain that our fates
were bound together for a reason.
Our two existences were only ever intended to be but one,
and so I will take the body of
the only man on earth I respect.
Then I will live in eternal glory,
for that is the destiny which is waiting for me.
There will be no pain.
That is the final gift I bequeath to you.
No. No, those eyes. I can't...
Live on as my body, JoJo!
Jonathan! What...
Erina.
No. Jonathan.
Eri...na.
Oh...
A pity you wouldn't hear me.
If only you had remained still as I told you,
your death in fact would have been quite painless.
Torn from your little fairy tale into hell,
thrust into a reality you didn't know existed,
what will you do now?
Did JoJo never tell you of me,
the evil that dwells there in the darkness?
I may not look like much right now,
but surely you remember me, Erina Pendleton.
Wait.
It's Erina Joestar now, isn't it?
Dio!
The ship's full of monsters!
Run!
As you ordered, lord, I drained
the life of only one passenger,
and now most of the ship has joined our little family.
And now we will proceed to america.
Isn't that right, lord Dio?
I can't speak.
I can't even take a breath.
I have to move.
Erina. Erina.
I have to save...
Can't gather hamon.
Well, how the mighty have fallen.
This sniveling whelp can't even draw a proper breath now.
He'll be causing no more mischief with his hamon.
This is what he gets for crossing you, lord Dio.
Now we are going to play.
Or maybe I'll just sit quietly and watch
while he suffocates slowly.
Silence, wang chen.
There shall be no insult to JoJo.
Huh?
He is the one man capable of
bringing me to the apex of my fate.
You will show him all the respect which is due to him
by severing his head in a painless manner.
Of course, lord Dio.
The body of my dearest foe has become my future!
Jonathan!
He's up to something.
Be careful.
He might have one last trick up his muscle‐bound sleeve.
Bah, he's done for.
Lord Dio overestimates his "mighty power."
Well, Jonathan Joestar,
I'll scoop out what little brains
you have with my bare fingers.
Must...
Save Erina.
I have to use the last bit of
hamon left in me all at once.
Please work.
Careful.
Wang chen, look out.
Something broke inside my body,
something important.
What have you done?
Th‐this is the end,
the last hamon I have.
Too weak to destroy that zombie completely,
but it was enough.
What-what is he playing at?
JoJo has interfered with wang
chen's body, disrupting its functions
without bringing it to complete destruction.
He's made it seize tightly onto a piece of machinery,
and the device it clings to so immovably...
Is the paddle's screw shaft.
The strength of a zombie is
sufficient to arrest the paddle.
If the shaft is stopped,
steam pressure in the piston will build up inexorably.
Under such conditions, there is but one end.
The ship will explode!
Jonathan, what's happening?
Why is this happening to us?
Y‐you must leave, Erina.
Soon the ship will be destroyed.
I don't know how the things that
are occurring today are possible.
It's all too impossible to bear.
I don't know whether I should cry or scream.
Perhaps I should just faint dead away and block it out.
But there is one thing I know.
Erina Joestar...
Will remain with her husband.
In the warmth of these lips,
I feel the cool ebbing of his life.
Jonathan Joestar is dying,
but we are together.
I want to stay like this
until the ship explodes and everything burns to ash,
until everything is gone.
It's all right if you cry,
but you have to...
Stay alive and go on.
Just like in a storybook.
You want me to come to the aid of a
helpless child and escape to safety?
That's unfair, just sheer cruelty.
The only thing that I want is
to end my life here with you.
That woman died
trying to save her child until the last.
My own mother did the same thing for me.
Save yourself
take the baby. Hurry.
So your plan is to destroy this vessel, is it?
JoJo, you never give up or give
in, no matter the odds, but know this.
Determination is not just in you.
I will live. There is no one who can defy me!
I will take your body as my own!
Zombies, hither!
Devour wang chen's body, and
restart the piston once you have.
The end has begun.
Jonathan.
It's already blowing apart. But there's still a way out.
I was protecting myself from
the sun's rays well before this.
Let it explode.
I already have everything I need to survive.
Erina, take a good look.
Hah! Since JoJo can no longer use his hamon,
I'll remove his head and take his body as my own.
Then I shall walk over and lie down in my velvet boudoir.
That humble shelter is marvelously constructed.
It could withstand a ton of dynamite.
Goodbye, JoJo,
and welcome to you, my new eternal body!
Jonathan!
Dio.
As you observed,
it may be true that our fate is to be together.
I feel an odd warmth for you,
for now our lives are interwoven completely
and will end along with this ship.
Farewell to you, my beloved.
JoJo, let me go!
Release me.
Think of what we two can achieve.
You'd like a taste of eternity, would you not?
I can heal your wounds.
You and Erina can live together forever!
JoJo!
No. It's too late.
He's dead.
Jonathan Joestar passed away
into undeserved oblivion.
His life was an important part of history,
but invisible to ordinary people.
Most of humanity, for whom he sacrificed,
will never know of his noble accomplishments...
But his descendants will.
The life within me, newly created by Jonathan and I,
will certainly hear his story.
Erina Joestar was soon rescued
afloat near the Canary Islands,
and the book of the stone mask was closed for a time.
But that was only the beginning
of a new bizarre adventure.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over, we'll be there and we'll see you.
10 true summers, we'll be there and laughing, too.
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
it was in the fall of 1938.
It's good to see you again, Speedwagon.
You bastard! How could you have
possibly have known where they were?
Teach him a lesson.
Joseph Joestar.
My friends call me JoJo.