You're a poisoner, Dio Brando.
I have all the proof I require and then some.
He's found his proof. So be it.
This moment's been a long time coming, JoJo.
Now I finish what I started.
I tracked down the antidote.
Father took it moments ago.
Dio, this pains me greatly.
For years, you were my brother, and
now I have no recourse but to turn you in.
I'm sorry, really.
I'm sure you don't believe a word of it,
but I'm telling you the truth.
Even now, you show compassion.
JoJo, I've been a devil, but grant me this one wish.
Allow me to do the right thing for
once in my life and turn myself in.
What's this?
I thought once I confronted him, he'd
fight me tooth and nail like a cornered beast.
JoJo.
You should be dead in a gutter right now.
I must distract him long enough for
the knife and mask to find their mark.
My wicked deeds gnaw at me.
The poverty I knew as a child ate away at my
moral compass until greed was all that remained.
I'm the lowest of the low.
Your father took me in off the street,
and I repaid his kindness with poison.
The only reason I came back was to surrender myself.
If I'd wanted to flee, you never
would have laid eyes on me again.
I see your point.
Please allow me to make amends.
Dio.
Look alive, master Joestar.
He's trying to lure you in, like as not.
Right about now, you're probably wondering who I am.
Allow me to elucidate ya.
The name is Robert E. O. Speedwagon.
I had a hunch Jonathan's run of trouble
might not be done, so I followed him back home.
I like you, Jonathan, so I'm gonna
offer up this little tidbit pro bono.
Living in the gutter, you learn to spot
lowlifes pretty quick if you want to see tomorrow.
I've trained my nose to sort out the
bad ones from the good just from a sniff.
This fella reeks of brimstone and blood
worse than anyone I've ever laid eyes on!
He is pure evil right down to his very bones!
Is he a victim of circumstance, you're wondering?
Not on your life!
He's been evil since he drew his first breath.
But don't you fret, 'cause I brought you a friend.
Remember him?
This man confessed to selling
you the poison you used on father.
I've heard enough.
You break my heart.
Why, Dio?
From the day you arrived, I have
loved you as though you were my own son.
Father, you're too weak to be down here.
You're right. I'll return to my chamber.
I don't want to see my boy in chains.
Do what you must, JoJo.
I will.
Is this how it all ends?
He won't see the inside of a cell this night.
I read his face and the trio of moles on his ear.
The devil smiles on him and grants him luck.
JoJo, I want you to be the one to put the cuffs on me.
Please, brother.
All right.
Be careful. He's a crafty one.
JoJo, it was hubris that led me to this ignominious end.
This fall from grace has taught me well.
However one may scheme and dissemble,
my downfall this night is part of the human condition,
a condition I now forsake.
Wait. Forsake? What do you mean?
You see, I am about to become so much more!
Help me shed this mortal skin.
Mother's mask. But how?
Watch out.
Fire at will, men.
JoJo, your blood is the key!
Oh, my god.
Father!
Shoot that maniac!
JoJo.
Father.
This is all my fault.
I should have blocked his knife.
The mask. When I saw it, I froze up,
and you paid the price.
Take this ring.
It was your mother's, JoJo.
Father.
Damn it.
Ain't a doctor on earth who can fix that.
How'd that devil get the drop on us?
It's all my fault.
If only I hadn't listened to you, sir Joestar.
If I had run his father out of town years ago like
I'd a mind to, none of this would have taken place.
Hold on. Whose father?
Back when I first joined the force,
there was a never‐do‐well who tried to pawn
that very ring you now see on Joestar's finger.
The suspect was Dio's birth father, Dario Brando.
It's mine.
Of that, there's no doubt.
My late wife and I had them
made to celebrate our betrothal.
A local cutpurse by the name of
Dario Brando ‐ was trying to sell it.
Hmm?
Can it be?
Sir Joestar thought he owed his life to Dario,
but he was sadly mistaken.
Dario hadn't scrambled down to the mangled
carriage that fateful night to look for survivors,
but to root for ill‐gotten riches.
Huh?
You stay back.
This man, what has he said, inspector?
Did he ever tell you that I gave him the ring?
Aye. He swore up and down.
You filthy liar.
He swore with good reason.
I gave him the ring, just as he told you.
You have got to be kidding!
Eh?
He is innocent.
Let him go at once, inspector.
But, sir, this man stole from you.
But for providence's hand in my life,
I might as well have done the same.
Sell this ring if you may ease your family's burden by it.
Walk an honest path henceforth, and I give it gladly.
He knew he didn't owe Dario a damn thing,
and he took Dio in all the same.
Father, hang on.
The doctor is on his way now.
JoJo, don't hate Dio for what he's done.
I am to blame for this.
I was hard on you, because you are a Joestar.
I went too easy on Dio, and he
might have felt I didn't care.
Perhaps he did this for want of a father's love.
Please, see that he's buried next to Dario.
Father.
Don't look so sad, JoJo.
Where better to die
than in the arms of my son?
Sir Joestar!
We have lost much this night.
A noble man's soul has been taken from the world.
You're wrong!
All that was good in that man,
he passed it along to Jonathan, every bit of it!
You can be sure.
JoJo's gonna live an upright
life using what his father gave him.
Rich folks are rubbish.
Watching 'em flounce around, I wanna
throw the whole lot of them into the thames,
but not the Joestars.
They're heroic and merciful and just.
The whole damn lot are giants among men.
What the hell?!
The body!
Dio's corpse, it... it vanished.
Oi, copper! Away from the window!
JoJo.
The inspector.
No, that's impossible!
How's he alive?
He can't be.
We all filled him full of bullets.
Keep your distance, lads.
He's armed with something.
Was it the mask?
He's coming right at us!
What are you waiting for?
Hit 'em with everything you've got left!
Come no closer.
Not another step! I mean it.
Blow his brains out now!
Do it before he kills us all!
Mmm.
Shot 'em in the head, and it didn't even slow him down.
It doesn't make any sense.
With all the lead we put him,
he should be worm food by now.
How can this be?
JoJo...
I should thank you for the source of my newfound power,
your father's blood and the ancient mask.
He takes his very life.
But how is that possible?
Dio, you villain...
What sort of monster have you become?!
How did this happen?
Think, JoJo. Think.
The knife, father, blood, Dio, the mask,
my notes, the brain,
unknown abilities, unknown strength.
There is nothing human left of you, Dio!
Father.
Don't do it, JoJo!
You haven't got a chance in hell.
I never seen anything like this, lad.
He broke those coppers to pieces
like they was bleeding' twigs.
I know.
Honestly, I'm terrified.
All the same, I can't let Dio kill anyone else.
This demon must be annihilated!
Please, JoJo, I beg of ya.
He'll tear you apart!
That's it.
According to my research on the mask,
it was fabled to unlock the brain's hidden potential.
To vanquish Dio, all I have to do is...
This one's alive.
Your blood,
it smells so delicious.
Now I'm going to turn you inside out.
He was my brother.
Look at him now.
Father, please lend me the strength to do what I must.
Courage, JoJo.
Dio is powerful, but you know how to end him,
and end him you must!
Watch out!
It's over.
I'm not going to let you kill anyone else, Dio!
He caught the sodding' spear.
Right through the hand, and he don't even flinch.
No way. The hole from where I shot him in the head,
it's healed up.
That spear ain't gonna hurt him.
He's immortal.
You're such a weakling, JoJo.
On your feet, insect.
I've yet to gauge the full extent of my new powers,
so let's play a little longer, shall we?
I trust you'll be long since
dead by the time I figure them out.
Hmm?
Hiding, are we?
Hmm.
You were a fool to attack me.
I have disowned my weakness in favor of life everlasting.
You're behind the curtain, like Polonius,
and, like Polonius, it is there
that you shall meet your end.
No one's immortal, not even you.
He's able to heal faster than the flames can hurt him.
If that ain't immortality, then I'm the queen.
Fire hurts him, but not enough.
JoJo! What are you doing?!
Just get to safety, Speedwagon.
If Dio wants a fight, I mean to give him one.
What are you doing? Are you mad?
The flames are gonna box you in up there.
JoJo, you brave fool,
I hope to hell you've got a plan.
I'm waiting for you, Dio.
Know this. It ends here.
I will not allow you to leave this mansion alive.
No, that's lunacy!
Luring me away from the gutter rat?
How very noble of you.
No matter.
Hah.
I'll drain you dry,
and your blood will help me
mend from this little adventure.
You climb the wall in vain, JoJo.
In your haste to flee from me, all
you have done is guaranteed your doom.
You will be consumed tonight,
by the inferno below or by me.
Father.
Father, rest in peace.
Let the rising smoke guide your soul to heaven.
But first, please, lend me your aid one final time.
Let the fire burn with your strength.
What does he mean to accomplish up there?
No, that's crazy!
You're throwing' your life away!
Don't do it! Don't do it, JoJo!
Any moment now.
Useless. You fight as though you want to die.
In that moment, JoJo's short life flashed before his eyes.
My lonely youth,
my time with Dio.
You did me wrong time and again,
so now I'll settle the score.
The longer the fire burns, the
hotter it gets, and JoJo knows it.
He means to use the mansion as a funeral pyre and
burn the devil faster than he can replenish himself.
And now that the house is hot enough,
he's gonna knock him back in.
JoJo!
How dare you lay your hands on me, you insect?!
The only home I've ever known
will be in ashes before the dawn.
Father is dead, and I am alone.
I have nothing left to lose...
But my life itself.
We go to the flames together, Dio!
I'll gladly die if it means an end to your evil!
Die for nothing, fool!
All I lose by your sacrifice
is the blood I would have taken.
Blacken and burn among the bones
of your damnable father, JoJo!
I am a god in all but name.
With the powers at my command, I will rule this world.
Thank you, brother, for this great boon.
Damn it.
Dio! I'm not done with you!
Why won't you die already?!
There's no escape, Dio.
You brought this doom upon yourself.
This is the knife you used to kill my father!
So as you did to the man who
raised us both, I now do unto you!
I've crushed his arm bones to splinters,
and he's already ablaze,
but his grip on me is still that of a vise.
So be it, JoJo.
Consign us both unto the flames.
But perish knowing I will survive this moment.
For everything you have done,
even this inferno cannot devour me!
Father! Lend me your power!
His desperate cry echoed in the night.
Whether urged on by his departed father or
heeding an instinct borne of a long familiarity
with the home which burned around him,
he kicked...
And that put them right in line with...
What the...
The statue of the Joestar family's guardian angel.
How could a worm like you...
I... I forgot who I was dealing with.
Bloody his nose, and he comes back twice as fierce.
JoJo!
I had such plans for this world,
such plans...
JoJo.
It's over.
You're alive.
You lucky bastard.
He did it.
JoJo bested him!
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound
and in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
There it is.
Courage is to look your fear in the eye.
Dio's evil, yeah, but this guy is far worse.
Prepare for the carnage!
Who do I look like?
I beg of you, teach me how to wield it.