Phew, I think I used my head a
little bit too much last time.
My shoulders are real sore.
They feel so heavy.
The sun is up.
The tests are ending, and soon the two students,
Caesar and JoJo, will be making their way back here.
Signora Lisa Lisa.
Which blouse do you like today?
Oh, I don't know. What do you think?
Well, white is always nice, but I think
something colorful can be kind of fun, too.
I'll let you decide.
Okay, let's see.
I think the white one is pretty,
but I really like the lovely design on this one.
I wonder if JoJo and Caesar have passed their final exams.
I have a bad feeling.
I'm beginning to worry.
So today we're going to go with the pretty white.
Suzie Q...
Yes?
Please send Caesar and JoJo to
my room as soon as they arrive.
Yes, of course, signora.
Hmm. I know I said I like the white blouse,
but the other one is nice, too.
So which is better?
Oh, which do I choose?
White. But then again,
this is really nice, too.
Ai! What do I do?
The colorful one will do nicely. Thank you.
Excellent choice.
I'll just leave these here for you, all right?
I'll come back later and clean up
the broken glass. Be careful, okay?
I will. Thank you.
Hey.
Suzie Q.
Eh, what are you screaming for?
Be quiet, you stupid idiot.
W‐who-who are you?
Th‐there's a stranger on the island!
Hey, wait. You think I'm a stranger?
Huh?
It's me, you dummy,
Joseph Joestar.
Huh?
Hmm.
JoJo? No way.
When I saw you before, you were always wearing a mask.
Wow, what a surprise.
What? Are you telling me you've
never seen my face in all this time?
So? What do you think? Am I handsome?
Hmm.
Weird lips.
Guh! Well, they may be weird,
but if we were ever to fall madly in love with each other,
you'd be welcome to kiss them all you'd like.
Yeah, in your dreams.
Ahh!
Hmm?
What's the matter?
Uh, nothing at all, really.
Oh! Yeah, signora Lisa Lisa wants
you to go up to her room right away.
But she is taking a bath,
so you should probably wait half an hour.
Got it. I was planning to go anyway.
I've gotta tell her that they know all about the stone.
Huh?
Oh, no, you're not talking about her stone, are you?
Uh, don't worry about it. You really
don't want to get involved in all this stuff.
Believe me.
Uh, okay.
JoJo, wait a minute.
Huh? What's up?
You're actually pretty hot, you know?
Hmm?
Hmm.
Hmm. That's odd.
My shoulders feel like they've
suddenly started to loosen up.
The news I have to report is really
important, but Lisa Lisa is taking a bath,
so I'm gonna have to wait for
half an hour until she's done.
If I was told to wait, then waiting is what I'll do.
Now where to spend half an hour?
I think the best place is here by Lisa Lisa's door.
Would it really be all that wrong if I took a
peek through the keyhole to check things out?
Nice.
Uh, eh?
Suzie Q?
Wait a minute. What's she doing in there?
I didn't even see her go into the room.
That was really fast.
I thought she was still out on the docks.
Huh?
What the hell?
The doorknob is completely covered in some kind of goo.
Suzie Q, tell me, have JoJo and Caesar made it back yet?
Uh, Suzie Q?
Are you all right, Suzie Q?
What's going on? What did you do with the red stone?
Who are you?!
Tell me what you did with the red stone!
No. This is bad.
It seems something has taken over Suzie Q's body.
You, you have reduced me to nothing
but a brain with no body of my own!
But nevertheless I challenge you to one last fight!
I put the stone on the boat that just left the dock.
I am here to stop you from chasing it and getting it back.
I will not allow you to follow that postal boat,
no matter what!
The woman I am inside of is still mostly alive, you see.
There is only one way for you to destroy me completely,
and that is to take her life as well.
Can you do that? Are you capable of that?!
Esidisi!
JoJo.
You won't stop coming at us, will you?
You don't give up.
JoJo.
Eh?
Oh, Caesar.
Well, it's about damn time.
You, uh‐‐
so you managed to survive your bout with Esidisi?
You're a lucky one, that's for‐‐
JoJo. What the hell
were you doing in here with our coach?
Hey, cool it, you meathead.
It's not like that, okay? Just take a look at Suzie Q.
All right then.
What's going on?
It's Esidisi.
Damn him. He somehow figured out a way to make his brain
and blood vessels invade her body and take control of her.
Save me, Caesar!
Oh, please help me.
Everyone picks on me all the time.
But you'll never pick on me, Caesar, will you?
Don't fall for a word of it.
Suzie Q's not doing the talking.
Esidisi is manipulating her.
That's right. She managed to take
the stone and put it on a postal boat.
Leave this thing to JoJo and me,
and find that boat. Get the stone back.
If the red stone reaches venice
and is transferred onto a train,
we'll lose track of it and have
no way to know where it will end up.
You're not going anywhere, dickheads!
If you want to stop that boat or leave at all,
you'll have to kill me first!
A male voice.
I see what's going on.
His blood vessels must be controlling her from the inside.
Yeah, come on! Bring it!
Use your hamon, and kill me!
It should be a relatively easy task
for you to destroy me in my current state.
But then again, you must know that
this girl's heart isn't nearly strong
enough to endure a hamon shock and survive it.
Are you willing to snuff out this
girl's life in order to defeat me?
If you are, then hurry up, and do it!
Quit standing there and wasting
time, you stupid dickheads!
Hey.
I'm not softhearted, Esidisi.
All I have to do is end the life of one young girl,
and I'll be able to save the entire world from you.
I would consider it a small, but necessary sacrifice.
Wait a minute! Are you serious, JoJo?
Time to tear you into little, tiny pieces, Esidisi!
No, you can't!
JoJo!
I'm not kidding here! I'm really gonna do it!
Damn it all.
I just can't hit her.
The bastard.
I thought he'd pop out of her when I started
to make my move, but it didn't even faze him.
Enough of your bluffing.
You could never kill this girl,
no matter how hard you tried.
By now, I'm sure the stone has
already arrived on the main island.
You're too late.
Heh. And now...
The bastard. What is he doing to Suzie Q now?
Stop! Don't do this, Esidisi!
And now, just to make things interesting,
I will make this girl's body explode and cover
you all in blood that burns as hot as flowing lava!
Look out! His blood is boiling hot.
Suzie Q's body, it's beginning to fall apart!
If this keeps up, it won't be just Suzie Q
who'll be in trouble. It'll be all of us as well.
So we have no choice.
JoJo, you need to use your hamon on her right now.
Come on. No.
I don't wanna do this. Please don't make me.
I'm still having to deal with all the horrible nightmares
I get about the time I chopped Von Stroheim's leg off.
A different plan.
We need a different plan right now.
All right. I'll do it, then.
No, hold on a minute. Coach, let me do it.
Wait. Don't do anything. I thought of something.
Caesar, do you remember hell climb pillar?
We can give that a shot. It's
do or die, so let's go for it.
Eh?
You and me,
two types of hamon at the same time.
Two types?
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
You're right. Something like that might just work.
You know what to do then.
JoJo! Caesar!
Right, I understand.
JoJo, I want you to follow my breathing.
Let's go!
JoJo creates a burst of positive
hamon and surrounds Suzie Q with it.
Caesar creates a burst of
negative hamon focused on her heart.
At that point, the hamon is
both negative and positive zero.
It worked. You forced Esidisi out.
JoJo!
Don't worry. It's all right.
We'll just let the sun take care of the rest.
That lowdown, dirty scum,
hiding in a girl's body like that.
He's nothing but a coward.
No, Caesar. You don't get it.
I fought against him, so I understand.
You see, he gave all he had and even threw away his pride,
because he felt a duty to get the stone for his allies.
For thousands of years, he did as he pleased,
and he lived his life to its fullest.
Whether it was good or evil,
I respect his life and how he chose to live it.
JoJo.
Suzie Q...
While Esidisi controlled you,
you must have been at least
semiconscious most of the time.
Now tell me,
where is the stone headed?
Switzerland...
St. Moritz.
A package...
An envelope with signora Lisa Lisa's crest.
The address is...
Switzerland?
What about Kars and Wamuu? Are they there?
Mm. I just checked with my contact at the station.
A cargo train for Switzerland left not 10 minutes ago.
That's it. The stone has to be somewhere on that train.
They've got a big head start,
but we've got to somehow figure out a way to get
ourselves to St. Moritz before that train arrives.
We have to do everything we can to keep
the stone from falling into the wrong hands.
We might even have to do a little bit of dirty work.
A few laws might be broken as well.
Some of us may even end up in body bags.
Don't worry. I won't.
I wasn't ready before,
but now there's no way I'm gonna lose.
I'll eradicate every one of them.
Let's go!
Right. We're out of here.
Hey, Suzie Q, look over here!
It's goodbye for now, Suzie Q.
I don't know when or how, but I'll
be back in venice one day, I promise.
Really?
Yeah.
Heal those ugly wounds on your
face before I get back, will you?
Later!
JoJo, be careful!
Make sure you come back in one piece, okay?!
Don't get pushy.
You may be an old lady before
I get back, but I will return.
Oh, yeah?
You stupid jerk!
I'll be back a lot sooner than you think.
Hey, drive the damned car, will you?
Huh? What happened to your arms, man?
Huh? Aah!
Something's wrong with the
wheel, man! I can't get it to move!
Hmm.
Esidisi hasn't reported back.
He last said that he had learned
the stone was somewhere in venice.
I wonder if something has happened to him.
Hey, JoJo.
JoJo.
JoJo, wake up.
Huh? Wha...
JoJo, we've caught up with the train.
They're going through their customs check at the moment.
That works in our favor.
We're less than an hour from St. Moritz,
which leaves us enough time to get ready.
It's good we caught up.
Come on, JoJo. Look sharp.
Listen, I'm just saving up my strength for
the big battle, that's all. Get off my case.
Let's hurry up and get there
so we can retrieve that stone.
Then we're gonna need some sort
of plan for the fight with Wamuu.
We'll wait for that until we cross.
What the hell?
Knock it off!
If you want to go on, just quit honking, and pass us.
German soldiers.
What the hell are they doing in a
car on the swiss‐italian border?
Well, well, you're looking rather spry.
My, you have grown so much, Joestar.
Huh? W‐what did you say, mister?
What was that about?
G‐get back here!
Who the hell are you?! What's going
on? I don't know any German soldiers.
Hey, look at the train.
So many soldiers.
Hey, major, we found the package!
The crest. Look. They've got the package.
Yeah, and we all know what's inside.
The Red Stone of Aja!
I don't understand. Why do the Germans want it?
We have decided to take the stone as a
specimen for our scientific research program.
For the past three weeks,
we have been watching your every
move while you were operating in venice.
We began the surveillance when we lost our team in Rome.
We saw your training, we saw Esidisi,
and we knew you were chasing the stone.
Now, our base is set up at a lodge up ahead.
Follow us.
We want to ask a few questions
about the stone und about Kars.
Why not work together, eh?
After all, we are not complete strangers, JoJo.
Hey! What are you blabbering about?
Don't think you know anything about me, you bastard!
If the Germans are here, that means...
What do we do, coach?
We have to follow them.
At least we know Kars doesn't have the red stone either.
At that time, the German army was marching
across Europe, taking country after country.
They wanted to ensure their rule across
the continent would last indefinitely.
The power of the mask and red stone
would solve their problem perfectly
by giving them everything they would need to prevail.
The Germans were planning to use
the ultimate power of immortality
to conquer the world.
I'll read the heat inside.
The fireplace is lit.
Four lights on the wall, two on the ceiling,
two on the desk. No, three.
Four humans standing by the wall.
Their heights are 178, 174, 181, and 178 centimeters.
One human is by the fireplace, 183 centimeters tall.
There are five humans, all male.
One, two...
That's four
and five.
So you must be Kars. You're fast.
In just a few hours, you heard about your friend's defeat,
learned that we had obtained the stone,
found our location, and have come for it.
Very impressive.
And then this brutal, perfectly calculated assault.
Not one of my men made even the
slightest sound before they died.
I was sure there were only five men in this room.
Now tell me, why can't I sense your body heat?
Hey, rifle heads,
what's a guy gotta do to get a little food in here?
Kars!
Huh?
This man's mechanical.
Wait a minute.
You're Von Stroheim!
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
We should attack now.
The building on top of that hill is the address.
That was pretty mean.
German science is the finest in the world!
No machine can stop me.