JoJo...
I've heard so much about you.
Listen, and listen good.
Santviento here, the so‐called pillar man,
uses a mask to turn men into vampires.
He does this to make them
stronger, und then he devours them.
Destroy him! Take him out while there's still time!
Don't do it, JoJo! He's dangerous!
You're it.
Oh, I get it.
You're one of those strong, silent types, right?
Ever thought about modeling? You've got a nice look there.
Come on. Let's see what you got. Give me a smile.
I know you can do it.
Show me some vulnerability.
Work with me here.
Make some love to the camera.
Ready? Set?
Give me happy. Now be silly.
Show us those pearly whites.
Heh.
Come on, big guy. Smile at the birdie.
JoJo, stop this nonsense immediately!
Don't provoke him.
Please, JoJo, Santviento is dangerous.
Yeah, I know you think he's dangerous, but
I have a theory that maybe he's not so bad.
Let me test something out here.
I don't want to assume he's evil just
because he killed a bunch of brainless...
What are you, insane?!
If he's not evil, why did he kill all my men?!
Don't know. Some would say you're
responsible for what's happened.
Weren't you the one experimenting on him and
trying to blast him away in the first place?
Not that I really care about that.
The only reason I'm here to make sure that
Speedwagon makes it back to New York safe and sound.
Anyway, I'm not here to fight, and I'm feeling generous.
Come on. Loosen up, big guy.
How 'bout that smile?
That was rude.
He just walked through me like I wasn't even there.
Who the hell does this guy think he is?
Maybe I should teach him a quick lesson.
Have a nice trip.
Wh... what the hell was that?
That was the weirdest feeling, and it hurt.
What is this, this tool?
Cold and long... with many different pieces.
He does understand!
He's not simply mimicking.
It took him practically no time at
all to completely master our language.
How... how is he doing that?
He took it apart.
He dismantled that entire
weapon like some expert gunsmith.
It takes a soldier dozens of hours to
learn how to field strip his weapon that fast.
He's... he's using his advanced
intellect to learn everything.
So bright.
This light is new to me.
What is it?
Don't you see?
We weren't the ones observing all this time.
He was actually watching us!
Hey, big guy, you wanna learn a new joke?
Just stop me if you've heard this one before.
Knock, knock. Knock, knock.
JoJo! Get away!
You are playing games, primitive.
I do not want to play games.
What the...
Rib blades, sometimes known as fighting ribs.
They are capable of being manipulated in any direction.
JoJo!
Sparks. Energy.
This human seems...
Different from the others.
I was not able to absorb his body into mine.
He just flew away.
And somehow his leg, it remains... it still seems fine.
This one is something new.
I have yet to see such a human.
Is he a unique specimen,
or do all humans of his particular
class possess the same properties?
Could it be related to age?
Ah, now I see.
My instinct was right.
That human is unique.
Agh. JoJo, please.
Make it stop, please!
Speedwagon.
That bastard.
Let the old man go, Santviento!
Now I'm in the mood.
Come on, big guy. You wanna try and take me on?
It would seem
that humans have evolved their confidence.
Hope you're hungry!
One hamon sandwich coming up!
Huh? What the devil?
My hamon is making that blood float.
Something's wrong here.
My hamon is running off him like rain off a raincoat.
He's somehow repelling it and
pushing it into all of this blood.
I don't understand it.
His skin is acting like a ground.
Somehow, it's behaving just like Straizo's scarf.
My body and his body seem to
be repelling against one other.
What... what have you done to my hand?!
Wait. It's...
Still there.
But check it out. I can completely remove my thumb.
Doesn't anyone have a sense of humor left?
Come on, guys. This is funny stuff here.
But seriously, folks.
Lucky thing I rolled my wrist just in time.
The beast's immune to hamon.
That's not true, JoJo.
Don't you see?
It was hamon that was protecting you.
It kept your body from being
completely absorbed into that thing.
Idiot! It's like eating a blowfish for him.
He's knows he must kill it first
und then remove the poison parts.
That is how Santviento plans on absorbing JoJo's body.
Well, too bad for him I'm not a blowfish.
Regardless, I need to think of something fast here.
Maybe it's time to make my emergency escape.
You can't do that!
The danger of Santviento escaping is
too high, no one leaves until he's dead!
Ah, shut up!
You released this monster, and now you're
saying you need someone else to clean up the mess?
I don't need anything else on my plate, Von Stroheim.
Let's see if I can inject some hamon
into his system with something sharp.
His skin is malleable like rubber.
See if you can dodge this one, big guy!
How about a dose of hamon right in the eye?!
I hope you're ready for your can't... miss close‐up.
What? That's impossible.
Even his eyes feel like they're some kind of rubber.
JoJo, get out of there right now!
JoJo!
That hit to the solar plexus
completely knocked the wind out of him.
Hmm.
He seems to create his own energy.
He controls it with his breathing.
But lying there now unconscious, he
is as vulnerable as any other human.
JoJo! You've got to use your hamon breathing!
You've got to breathe! Ohh!
Use your hamon breathing! Breathe, damn it! Breathe!
No, there's no stopping him.
I've got to initiate the self‐destruct sequence.
For the fatherland und for eternal glo...
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Everyone just calm down here.
Looks like my gamble paid off.
Figuring that attacks from outside are no good,
I'm going to send some hamon into
him while he tries to enjoy his meal.
JoJo!
I waited for you to start devouring me.
This is gonna be fun.
Enjoy your hamon blast!
I... I think I get it.
Now that I've seen him from the inside, I understand.
His whole body is one big digestive system.
Every one of his cells,
they'reall filled with aggressive digestive
enzymes, making it possible to dissolve his prey.
It looks like he's absorbing them,
when actually he's digesting them whole.
Hamon. That was what kept me from being digested.
I sent it inside him when he tried to eat me.
JoJo, your hamon wasn't enough.
You have to find a way to completely destroy Santviento.
The separated parts of Santviento
are trying to connect to one another.
That's pretty much exactly what happened with Straizo.
Lucky me, I figured you would
try to go and do the same thing.
Von Stroheim!
Aah!
Come on! Get ahold of yourself!
Does this thing have any weaknesses?
Uh, sunlight! Ja, that's it.
It was there on the walls of the cave.
Sunlight is his natural enemy.
The very reason he made the masks in
the first place was to conquer the sun.
Hmm.
Are you insane?! What are you doing?!
You can't let Santviento escape into the outside world!
On the contrary, I think he
needs to go on a nice sunlit stroll.
He's running out of breath.
He won't be able to control his hamon.
He hasn't had enough training with it.
This fight has completely exhausted him.
Cease this foolishness now,
you lowly primitive.
Remember, you must control your hamon breathing!
If I could breathe, I probably
wouldn't be so tired in the first place.
Come on, big guy.
I think we've all had just about enough of you.
But fortunately for me, we're just a few steps
away from the two of us catching some nice rays.
What the hell?
I can't move.
I feel so heavy.
What... what's happening to me?
Meat invade, also known as foul flesh.
They're pieces of his flesh.
They're... they're feeding on me.
You... you son of a...
Got to stay focused.
I never once imagined a human such
as you would be born during my slumber.
What?
Joestar, leave the rest to me, colonel Rudol Von Stroheim.
Opening the door will end all this.
Allow me to help you destroy this vile creature.
Wow, Von Stroheim.
I would have never thought...
Humph. Well attempted, primitives.
I can almost reach the door.
A meaningless struggle. Humph.
This is bad.
Joestar, get up.
Don't just lie there like a baby.
I'm trying to think here.
If you hadn't noticed, we're both in deep trouble.
Silence!
Do you see those axes on the wall next to you?
Reach up, und grab one.
Take one, und chop off my leg!
I... I can't do that!
You coward, cut off my leg. It's the
only way we're getting that door open.
Maybe you're right, but are you sure about
this? I mean, there has got to be some other way.
Do as I say!
He's recovering, Joestar.
But I'm no doctor. I've no idea how to do this right.
I am a proud servant of the Wehrmacht! I am
prepared to do whatever is required to fulfill my duty!
I proudly give up my leg for the
fatherland! Now hurry up before it's too late!
Damn it! Do it now, Joestar!
Okay, I'll do it.
If you really want me to chop it off, then off it goes.
I demand that you chop it off now!
I figured this guy was just some bloated powermonger,
but I gotta hand it to him. He's got guts.
I wish there were some other way.
But if he's courageous enough, then...
Forgive me!
Tell me, big guy, how does
that sunshine feel on your skin?
We did it.
What's he doing?
Help me! That monster is trying to crawl inside my leg!
Get outta there, you!
Whoa. This is a shock.
Von Stroheim's basically okay, and he's free of any hamon.
Huh?
Damn it, you get out of me, Santviento!
I... I can't believe this thing's willpower.
I've never seen anything like it.
If he stays inside Von Stroheim, he'll be
totally fine even here in broad daylight.
I can feel him.
This can't be real.
Do you want to know what the worst part about this is?
My leg doesn't even hurt anymore.
It feels pleasant. You believe that?
My god.
Von Stroheim!
Wait. What are you doing?
Put it down, Von Stroheim.
Stay back!
You've seen what horrible things Santviento is capable of!
There is no hope!
My destiny has been determined!
So now all I can do is destroy the both of us!
But I have one more thing to
say to you before my time is done.
If you know what's good for
you, you listen close, Englishman.
Our Wehrmacht, we... we did not awaken Santviento
simply for scientific research or military gain.
Then why?
Why did you risk it? Tell me!
Silence! It's your destiny to hear
these words from my lips, Joestar!
Santviento is just the tip of the iceberg.
The Wehrmacht has discovered
another pillar in Europe. Agh!
We now know that Santviento is
not the only one of his kind around.
Wait. So there's more of them?!
Where are they? Tell me, Von Stroheim! Where?
I'm sorry, but I don't have that answer for you, Joestar.
There are more pillar men out there, und they
have powers that are beyond our wildest imagination.
For millennia, those powers have remained dormant,
but that won't last, und soon they will awaken.
You must find another weakness other
than just sunlight, or else hope is lost.
That's why we were experimenting on Santviento.
We were looking for that weakness.
There's a battle against the pillar men yet to be fought.
The events of 50 years ago call upon you for that battle.
Listen to me.
You will need more than just your hamon to overcome them.
You must go to Rome!
There you will find someone who can help you!
It is someone that your Speedwagon knows very well.
Santviento is trying to move my body
into that well so he can hide again.
But he can't stop me from opening up my
body completely to let the sun shine in.
Von Stroheim...
Don't you dare.
"Human greatness lies in having
the courage to face down one's fears."
Do you know who said that?
The Greek historian Plutarch.
Farewell...
You annoying Englishman!
Don't do it! I still have questions for you! Von Stroheim!
Damn that crazy German and all his honor.
I'm sure that we could have found another way.
Santviento!
You annoy me, primitive.
I will destroy you!
Steady your breathing.
Use your hamon technique.
Primitive, why oppose me?
You were doomed here from the start.
Hah!
I know just what you're going to say next.
You'll say, "I've seen right
through you all this time, Joestar."
I've seen right through you all this time, Joestar.
It's high noon over this well.
The sun reflecting off of the water should cook
you nicely, although I doubt you even thought of that.
You were thinking about jumping under the
nice cool water and getting out of the sun, right?
Well, screw that idea.
I'm not letting you touch the water!
I'm alive, thanks to the sun.
He's a statue now.
But we finally got that smile.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound and
in and out the valley in and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
My grandfather died tragically.
You couldn't even beat one of those pigeons.
Quickly! Bring out more U. V. Lamps!
Now is the time. Awaken, my masters!