This... this can't be!
I didn't see him with the mask.
I didn't know that he had it anywhere near him.
I didn't see him put in the red stone.
No, it can't be.
Dear god.
Kars.
He stood up again, major.
Ehh. You're the fatherland's cream of the crop.
You will stand on your ground no matter what.
He has become the ubermensch.
Can it be?
I thought no creature could attain perfection, but now...
Damn you.
See that, how his arm is burning?
Maybe we don't have to fight perfection after all.
Hamon melts his accursed flesh even now.
In another minute, there will be nothing left of him.
He has lusted after the red stone for millennia,
but when it is all said and done,
his quest for immortality has failed!
You will perish knowing that you are a failure!
Ready the U. V. Amplifier for another shot.
One direct hit should be enough to finish him off.
Hurry it up, soldier.
Jawohl.
What's he doing?
Looks like he's thinking.
Staring at a damn squirrel.
What the hell?
Look! Mr. Speedwagon!
His hand, it's changing.
I've seen some crazy stuff, but this?
Gets his hands on the red stone,
first thing he does is make a squirrel?
Oh, hey. Well, look at that. I think it found a friend.
Hey, squirrel, get away from that thing!
You don't know the guy it's made of.
Squirrel incoming!
Soldiers, full retreat!
My god.
He has complete mastery over organic life.
Huh.
All right.
The sun is rising.
Not a one of 'em left alive.
Kars is about to get what's coming to him.
Thank goodness.
How...
Think again. He's feeling fine.
He's standing in the morning sun,
and he couldn't care less about it.
JoJo, this is a horrible nightmare.
We're doomed.
This is the day all of us die.
Humanity's done for.
Alpha and omega both,
I am the pinnacle of all life
that has ever trod the earth.
All of their forms are mine to take,
and you, my old nemesis, I see how entrancing you are.
Yours is a beauty the likes of which I have never seen.
I once feared you,
but now I fear you no more.
Kars, he's become invincible. He has no weaknesses now.
He even shrugs off hamon like it's nothing.
He's won, and he knows it. You can see it in his eyes.
Kars the pillar man is no more.
He's become Kars, the ultimate creation!
This is all my fault.
I'm the one who hit him with u. V
after he put on the completed mask.
Is... is there really no way to stop him, Mr. Speedwagon?
He's so strong now.
We're all gonna be food for this walking museum piece.
No. I've got a plan.
Did I hear you right, JoJo?
Hold her. Uh‐huh.
One last all‐or‐nothing gambit.
"All‐or‐nothing gambit," you say?
Yeah. It's my final move.
What does it involve?
JoJo, when you say, "final move," you're
not referring to that final move, are you?
Listen up. This is something you're
going to have to do for yourself.
Just tell me what to do, and I'll follow your lead, JoJo.
Humph.
Run for your life!
Aww, man! I knew you were gonna do that!
Hamon users mean nothing to me now,
but you are a special case.
This is a historic moment, and
Wamuu and Esidisi must be avenged.
I shall celebrate my rebirth
with the utter eradication of Joseph Joestar.
He's gaining on us!
Not helping!
Really, how am I gonna think of
something with you carrying on?
We've still got our dignity, Smokey.
JoJo's out there risking life
and limb to lead Kars away from us.
Good on ya.
But still, it is only a matter of time.
This foe ain't one you can beat.
He's coming.
If you're gonna think of something, do it now!
Why are you running with me, anyway?
Maybe you haven't noticed this yet, Smokey, but i'm
the one who's got Kars really bent out of shape, you know.
You and I are good friends, so I'll take it
really badly if you die because of me today.
For the moment, at least, Kars is after my blood alone.
He thinks that killing me is a
good way to ring in his new life,
which means that monster's not gonna stop
chasing me until I've drawn my final breath.
JoJo...
There's something you really need to know.
Lisa Lisa, she's more than just some hamon master.
She's your...
That was fast.
Quit flapping, you son of a bitch!
Speedwagon, tell me,
has that pillar man really become the perfect being?
Yes. Our greatest fear has been
realized right in front of us.
Kars has become an unstoppable force of nature.
A perfect being is, above all, invincible.
That means it does not grow old.
It will never succumb to death in any form.
Additionally, it has the abilities of all other
life‐forms at its disposal and outperforms them.
And finally, its predominant form is the
standard by which physical perfection is judged.
Uhh. We have no way to stop him now.
We've already lost.
He has no weaknesses at all.
Humans can't kill him.
Not even hamon or the sun itself
will do a lick of good against him.
JoJo!
Sorry, but you're gonna have to tell me later.
Huh?
I'm kinda short on time.
JoJo!
That won't save you.
Hah hah!
You're not the only one with wings.
I'm coming for ya!
Up there. That's...
One of our German warplanes.
JoJo!
Kars mutates his feathers into plated
projectiles as hard as armadillo shells
and coats them with a bullet‐deflecting oil.
Therefore, their toughness makes
them ideal not only as shielding,
but as weapons in their own right.
Shooting those feathers at me is dirty pool.
This doesn't look good.
Oh, no, you don't.
Touching down is not an option.
I've got to make my getaway!
JoJo!
Aw, man, how long can he last
when all he can do is run for it?
Fly, boy, and don't look back.
That's all we humans can do now,
just try to save our skins.
240 kilometers an hour.
I don't care how perfect that bastard may be.
This plane has got more horsepower.
I'm safe for now.
If he has any morning plans, he'd better
cancel 'em, because I'm in this for the long haul.
Or am I?
Two hours left.
Guess I can't give him the
slip for as long as I had thought.
You cretin.
That metal coffin of yours
will only protect you for so long.
If your plan involves landing
somewhere, I've got news for you.
The only way you'll return to
terra firma is in bloody chunks.
JoJo. JoJo, do you read me?
This is Speedwagon. Over.
Hey. You guys missing me down there yet?
Thank goodness.
Listen, you were smart to grab that plane.
I know it's not much, but the Germans
and I will do what we can to help from here.
Do you have a map?
Yeah. Found it.
Good. Maintain radio contact,
and I'll guide you to safety.
Jackpot.
All right.
First give us your current position.
Huh?
JoJo, you're breaking up.
What's going on? Hey.
If you can hear me, for the love of god, pipe up.
Yeah. Clear as a bell.
How do you think this is gonna go?
I mean, we don't have a weapon or fighting
technique that'll work on Kars worth a damn.
You were yelling about him being immortal, remember?
Don't I know it? You running away isn't ideal,
but it's all you can really do.
Heh.
Maybe not.
Looking over this map gave me an idea.
What idea?
Hey, JoJo, don't face Kars alone!
This is no time to act the hero!
He'll be too strong later. This is the only time.
Don't do it! I forbid you to get
yourself killed out there. Do you hear me?!
Just listen for a second.
I know Kars is the most powerful
creature on earth at the moment,
but he was born here.
Thousands of years ago, this planet gave him life,
and if we're lucky, it'll take that life right back.
Take it?
But how?
What in the world do you think will be a threat to Kars?
Magma.
After all, magma's the hottest substance on earth.
I'll drive him into the lava at isola di vulcano.
Even he can't survive that.
No! You can't!
You've risked your neck for
humanity more than enough, boy!
Let me and the Germans do the heavy lifting for once!
Listen to him, JoJo. Don't be stupid!
Kars is gonna kill you!
Maybe, but I'm at the volcano, so it's too late.
Carpe diem, as they say.
Mr. Speedwagon.
No, god. Not again.
Lord Joestar, his son Jonathan, and his son George.
The men of the Joestar family
were all cut down far too soon.
Not again!
Why do they always have their lives taken?!
Don't fly into that volcano.
Survive, for Lisa Lisa's sake.
Huh?
Listen to me.
Lisa Lisa is your mother.
What did you say?
You're breaking up.
Huh?
That sounds like chewing.
Are you kidding me?! Yaah!
Piranhas, huh? That's logical.
They'll eat the plane right out from under me.
But how'd they get here?
Those feathers Kars shot before,
they turned into these damn things.
Bugger all.
No, don't eat the parachute!
You devilfish!
Eh?
Huh?
Oh, this is bad.
Yaah!
JoJo!
What's going on?
Can you even hear me?!
JoJo!
Please, say something.
What a moron.
You think that parachute is your
salvation, but all it does is seal your fate.
You're just a butterfly caught in a spider's web.
Now, JoJo,
time to split you asunder!
Huh? What the...
But if this is a decoy...
Hey, Kars,
I'm a Joestar.
We don't go down without a fight!
You and I have got a date with
that volcano! Don't try to weasel out!
JoJo!
Damn you!
You're a lunatic.
Granny Erina, a long time ago,
you told me about my grandfather.
You said he died on the Atlantic
to save you and father from his greatest foe.
Trust me.
I don't mean to be a copycat.
Maybe this is the hand my blood dealt me.
Really now.
Do you think I can't pry myself from this foul contraption
before you try to smash it into
the ground, you gibbering primate?
You coward!
Know that your death won't accomplish anything!
Is... is that a hand?
What a shame.
All of your scheming, und still you die here.
Damn you.
Von Stroheim.
How did you get into the plane?
When did you have time?
I wasn't sure you could handle this battle all alone.
Next time, I should stow away in the cabin proper.
Next time, huh?
When I give the word, jump out, JoJo!
Not on your life. No way.
Believe it or not, piranhas ate my damn parachute.
Unless you want to die, jump out of there this instant!
Please respond. I don't care what you say!
Tell a bad joke, or call me an old man.
Let me hear your voice one more time.
JoJo.
Stroheim, you're crazy.
I'm crazy, too, but
I admit when someone's got me beat.
That was a pretty courageous move.
You seem to be all right,
but what about... where'd he go?
Please tell me Kars fell into the lava.
Eh?
I'm...
Still alive...
Worms!
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
you spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound and
in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
Did you say, "Hamon Overdrive"?
Who's laughing now, huh?
To purge your fears and reign forever as gods!
JoJo!
Everyone, goodbye.