This gothic structure began its
life as a 14th‐century castle.
Converted into a hotel in the early 1900s,
it closed 10 years ago when the owner died.
Now Kars is using the ancient
building as a shelter from the sun.
He lurks within waiting.
Alas, JoJo and Lisa Lisa know
nothing of the hotel's layout.
Disgusting.
Come on. Cobwebby halls, really?
Would it kill you to sweep a bit?
Okay, I get it. Scary monsters
don't do much housecleaning,
but that does leave evidence.
See this blood trail?
It seems as though Wamuu took a good hamon thrashing.
Caesar didn't go down without
giving a good account of himself.
We mustn't let Wamuu heal any more.
Coach Lisa Lisa, it's time for some action.
Yuck.
What is it?
Eh, it's just,
well, when I took a hold of
this doorknob, it wasn't pleasant.
It felt like I was grabbing the
hand of something cold and dead.
I'm not a door.
Where's that...
Why are you looking around?
I'm not a door, but I am here.
What?
That's... it's a...
A vampire.
Careful, JoJo!
JoJo!
If it weren't for your little yo‐yo there,
I would have peeled your face right off your head.
Hi. I'm Wired Beck, and I'll be slaying you now.
I killed my sweetheart, but then I busted out of prison.
In no time, lord Kars took me in
and made me part of his little gang.
He's got my loyalty,
and I am not going to let you go in there and disturb
lord Kars when he's enjoying a well‐deserved rest.
So they've done it. It's begun.
They've started unleashing their
demon hounds on the weak and innocent.
Stop that noise.
You're just another vampire who's
bound for hell and leaving now.
Well, then, let me help you plan your
trip so you don't have to wait any longer.
Huh? Lisa Lisa?
Mmm.
You're beautiful, magnificent.
Your skin is so soft, heavenly, and clear.
Let me hold you, and then I'll drink
your life right through that skin.
You're really not impressing me.
I refuse to waste my time listening to
your weak flirtations and shallow threats,
but if you want to hold me, go ahead, and give it a try.
I guarantee it'll be the last thing that you do.
Spikes!
He's covered top to bottom.
They're popping out of him
like hundreds of pointed fingers.
They're metallic and razor
sharp like an iron‐maiden jacket.
I don't appreciate it when stuck‐up
females are insulting like that.
They need to be punished. Wouldn't you agree?
I'll give you a nice squeeze.
I'm going to hug you to death!
Oh, no. He's a lot faster than I thought he was.
Wait. I see. Her scarf becomes a
hamon‐filled weapon with incredibly long reach.
Huh?
Gosh, thanks for the thought.
Yah hah! You can't catch me like that.
Don't make me laugh. Hee hee hee!
See? I'm free.
Hmm? That's all? Where do you think you're going?
Come, JoJo. Let's go.
Uh, okay.
Lisa Lisa's movements, they're
effortless and flow like silk, efficient.
She doesn't waste any energy.
Come back! You can't just walk away.
Hey, you, wouldn't you agree that a woman
who behaves like that needs to be punished?
Oh, no. You are the one being punished.
You see, you've just run out of time.
Hamon is now running all through your body.
Huh?
Don't be ridiculous. I'm not...
No!
Lisa Lisa has really got what it takes.
I thought she might be out of her depth in a fight,
but it's plainly obvious she's even better than me.
I am so impressed.
I'm lucky to have her training me.
By the way, JoJo,
have you taken it? You really shouldn't delay any longer.
You must use the antidote.
Huh? Oh, you mean this?
Yes, of course.
I'm going to drink it only after I defeat Wamuu.
Heh.
See this ring, it no longer signifies
a promise between me and Wamuu.
It's now a promise I make to Caesar
that I will go on living and stay in the fight.
Would you please hold it for me
until I actually need it, Lisa Lisa?
No.
It would be better if it stayed with you.
Who knows what might happen to me?
Huh?
As they ventured further into the depths,
the trail of blood grew ever thinner.
Both JoJo and Lisa Lisa knew well what
meaning could be drawn from that fact.
Wamuu's hamon wounds were healing.
So you're here.
I've been waiting.
I see your powers have grown greatly.
Bastard! You're the one who killed Caesar. Now I...
Cool your head, JoJo.
Now look at the floor.
I'm very calm.
Don't worry. I'm in control here.
You mean the footprints, right?
I noticed it, too.
There are two sets.
That means Kars is here!
Tell me where I can find him!
Show your cowardly self now!
Indeed. There are two sets of footprints.
He's here, but I feel dozens of
lungs moving the air around as well.
Eh?
So it's you.
Fascinating. You are extremely composed
and perceptive though you are a woman.
I can see how JoJo and Caesar were
able to learn so much so quickly.
And you can feel even the lightest respiration.
You rank among the finest hamon warriors.
Damn. Look at that.
There's so many. I'd guess
you're all vampires. Is that right?
No response? That's creepy, too.
Kars!
Lord Kars saw fit to give us, his chosen
ones, the gift of eternal life. We number 100.
On our master's order, we'll tear you
both to shreds, 100 against two, JoJo!
You fiends.
This really is not good.
It's 100 of them against the two of us. We can't win.
Lord Kars, a moment.
Back in Rome, JoJo and I
promised to fight one another again.
I want revenge for Esidisi.
Please allow me the chance to fight him.
No.
Remember that my goal is only
to obtain the Red Stone of Aja.
Don't forget that, Wamuu.
Yes, lord.
Oh, darn, no fight.
Well, I'm not in the mood anyway.
Of course we both know I would beat you.
But to what end? All these vampires are here.
What sort of motivation is that, I ask you?
Win or lose, I would still come out of it dead, right?
With odds like that, giving
up is the only rational choice,
so I'm throwing in the towel.
Damn. Had to try.
I thought it was worth a shot, even
if you were watching all the time.
A hamon net was a good idea.
Kill them without any further delay.
Your choice, but if you kill
us, you'll never get the stone.
Hmm? Hold it.
What are you saying now, woman?
You don't think I'd have the stone here with me?
That wouldn't be wise, now, would it?
We're headed to our destination.
If we're not there in time to set the device, the
red stone will be destroyed, and you will have nothing.
Huh?
Look, woman, don't try to fool me.
Are you confident that you and your
minions will be able to find it in time?
The bomb I set is a very small one,
but enough to damage the stone and prevent its use.
Could this really be true?
She never said anything.
Whatever. I'll follow her lead.
Were you fellows listening?
If we don't stop it, the bomb will go boom.
Even if true, we cannot let you leave here alive.
Therefore, I have a suggestion.
JoJo and Wamuu can have their fight one‐on‐one,
and, Kars, you and I will also fight one‐on‐one,
and those who are left standing will possess the stone!
What?!
The winners of this fight will have
the red stone and all of its power.
It'll be made very clear.
Which one of us will prove strong
enough to wield the stone's power?
Who is fit to survive?
The pillar men or humankind?
How dare you say?
Wamuu.
Lord Kars, this is most absurd.
She is good.
She's just proven herself to be a better
gambler than I could ever dream of being.
No doubt, you do have pluck.
Very well. Then we will battle for the stone.
But don't get cocky.
You have no tomorrow.
Using only words, she just turned a dire
situation into more‐or‐less even odds.
Then so be it. Let's do this.
And so now we need to arrange
a time and place for our battle.
Wamuu, what are your thoughts?
We fight tonight under the gaze of the full moon,
the arena at the base of piz
bernina, 15 kilometers to the southeast.
We will meet at the skeleton's heel stone circle there.
Many warriors have found death, glory, or
both throughout the history of that place.
In a stone circle?
Hey, you can't just choose a
place because it happens to suit you.
Yes, Wamuu, I believe that to be a fine choice.
Now let's speak of the red stone.
JoJo, you will bring the Red Stone of Aja
to the skeleton's heel at midnight tonight.
And don't forget to remove the bomb.
The woman will remain here with us as insurance.
Well, Lisa Lisa?
They want to make sure that we
don't run away from the fight.
It is a reasonable request.
JoJo, go and fetch us the red stone.
You mustn't worry about me.
Would I?
I'll see you back at the arena.
Trust me, all right?
I assure you I do.
Caesar.
Until yesterday,
I lived my life thinking only about myself,
but now there's a new intense
feeling burning up inside of me.
Is this compassion?
I swear...
I just want to destroy those bastards and all their line.
I have to do it for Caesar and for Meshina, too,
Lisa Lisa, and for everyone else I know.
I'll fight for you all.
Obviously there's no bomb here
or anywhere else for that matter.
Lisa Lisa, even when you're under
pressure you are one deceptive young woman.
Hmm.
Well, now, maybe I should bring you a
change of panties in case you get scared.
Wait a minute what are these photos?
What? It's granny Erina.
What would Lisa Lisa be doing with this?
Huh?
Who are these people?
"May 22, 1889"?
50 years ago.
Then that young guy there is...
Speedwagon!
And granny Erina!
And that's Straizo holding a baby.
Lisa Lisa, I don't know anything about your
past or the life you have led or who you've known.
What could you possibly be doing with these photos?
It's genuine.
We accept your proposal.
We honor you by fighting one‐on‐one.
I suppose this means you saw the photos,
and you'd like to talk about it, right?
Actually I had intended to discuss this with you anyway.
Start with who you are.
50 years ago now,
Erina lost her husband on a ship sailing the Atlantic.
He was Jonathan Joestar,
your grandfather.
That horrible day,
your grandmother saved the life of a baby girl.
That was me.
I am the baby in that photograph.
W... wait a moment here. That was 50 years ago.
So if you were a baby 50 years ago...
Ho... hold on now. Just how old are you, anyway?
Y... you're 50?!
Oh... oh... oh... oh... oh, man.
If you're 50,
that means then... you're really old!
Is that right? Normally...
Y... you look like you're in your late 20s. Hmm.
They say that hamon energy is
life energy and keeps you young.
I guess that explains why you really don't
act like a young woman would behave at all.
Ah. I think I see a little wrinkle back there. Yup.
Hey, I'm just kidding, all right?
Vampires, prepare the arena.
Light the fires!
There is not enough time for us to talk now,
but we really do need to find the time,
because our roots are deeply connected.
Our roots?
The stone mask killed my parents.
Erina was pregnant when she
rescued the little girl on the ship.
She couldn't raise two children,
so Straizo became a father to me.
Straizo as a father?
Are you serious?
Everything I know about hamon, Straizo taught me.
He even gave me the Red Stone of Aja.
He did that? Wow.
This is all just so unbelievable and hard to accept.
It's tragic beyond words that the fear of
growing old drove him to commit such acts of madness.
JoJo, my feelings about you
defeating him are extremely complicated,
but I believe that it was destiny.
What is there to say?
Everything, all of it, is so complicated.
What a bizarre relationship.
Lisa Lisa, she carries with her a past painted by sadness.
It's time.
The rest of it will have to wait.
W... what's that rumbling noise?
They have come. It was worth
the wait. The battle can begin now.
Huh? What's that?
Out of the way!
I don't care how many of you get crushed!
What... what is that thing, a dinosaur?
No, I think a horse. That's a horse.
Lord Kars, lord Wamuu, please move!
They've gone berserk! I can't control them!
Lord Wamuu, please!
Ah, these are fine steeds.
The stone masks worked extremely well.
They're now strong vampires.
Wha... vampire horses?
On that track, JoJo and Wamuu will face each other
one‐on‐one in a fierce ancient‐style chariot duel.
What do you mean?
An ancient roman‐style death match.
You will battle, racing around
the arena, trying to kill each other.
Lord Wamuu or JoJo,
who will be the first one to fall under
the wheels or get beaten down by his opponent?
The loser dies!
Those are the rules, JoJo.
The beasts have a hundred times normal strength.
Even lord Wamuu can barely control them.
Hold it just a minute.
I will fight you on any field or in any cage,
but vampires are your minions,
even horses, so how is that fair?
Don't fret, human.
The reins you use will conduct hamon.
Wamuu will use his superior strength,
and you can use your hamon to control them.
Are you sure about that? They look pretty vicious.
Be careful. They're mean.
That's true, but a little hamon does help.
Ah.
Wamuu! Wamuu! Wamuu!
Raah!
See Wamuu?
He has chosen an ancient form for this battle.
That's a sign he means to win.
It's not for fun.
He's not going into this for the sport of it.
He wants to take your life.
Just beat him, JoJo.
We have no choice but to win this.
There are no draws.
Wamuu, hey!
Did you notice that I haven't taken this antidote yet?
I made a promise to Caesar
that I wouldn't drink this until after I took you down.
That promise is going to provide me
with a power I've never experienced before.
We'll face this fight together, Caesar.
Let's ride into battle!
Along the drifting cloud the
eagle searching down on the land
catching the swirling wind the
sailor sees the rim of the land
the eagle's dancing wings create
as weather spins out of hand
Go closer hold the land feel
partly no more than grains of sand
we stand to lose all time a
thousand answers by in our hand
next to your deeper fears we
stand surrounded by a million years
I'll be the roundabout the
words will make you out and out
Wamuu! Wamuu! Wamuu! Wamuu!
Wamuu! Wamuu! Wamuu!
Begin now!