Eh?
Huh?
Hmm?
Ohh.
Heh.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Agh!
JoJo!
JoJo.
Hamon!
Now...
Person?
In hell!
Lick it.
Not that!
Whoa! No!
Yes, sir.
A mirror?!
Batter up.
Take this!
Am I right?
Straiz‐oaf!
Not at all.
Gently now.
Speedwagon?
That's im...
No, you did.
Child's play.
You son of...
And if he was,
but I don't...
Is that hamon?
A truth serum?
Guns will fail.
Make way! Move!
Out of the way!
Run, JoJo! Run!
It was ghastly.
JoJo, let's run.
Just despicable.
Your mouth okay?
That's outta here!
No, really, it is.
You demonic freak.
That's impossible.
No. No, you can't.
JoJo, what'd you...
I'm also very fast!
This guy is insane!
Hey, wait up! JoJo!
I want answers now!
We can do anything!
He... he's unharmed.
Please just save me!
He followed us here.
You'll pay for that!
Help us! Let us out!
You are quite brave.
Here comes the pitch.
He... he's a monster.
Sure. Of course I do.
Run as fast as I can!
Do I hear what, JoJo?
Release her, Straizo!
Hah! You mean Straizo?
Why, isn't it obvious?
No, not that. Look up!
Farewell to you, JoJo.
Don't cut your tongue.
How are you feeling...
You just shot a person!
What else would he be?!
Let's have a look here.
I'll be the roundabout
I'll be there with you
someone call the police.
Great. I knew you would.
That's our ticket there.
This is a perfect scoop.
Are you all right, miss?
What? I never said that.
All right, here's a hint.
Look at his legs, Smokey.
It's behind me, isn't it?
I'll kill her regardless.
Fight me, or run. Decide!
That... that was a tooth.
As the German army grows,
Good. Slowly now. Slowly.
Give me a history lesson.
I'll do anything! Please!
Let the experiment begin!
I spend the day your way
The music dance and sing
he's going to kill us all!
Wh... what the hell is he?
Shall we interrogate, sir?
Can you tell me your name?
Why did you make me live?!
You are stubborn, old man.
I have a proposal for you.
That was a little too easy.
Look who finally noticed...
Well, that was a close one.
It's too late for that now.
My legs are in great shape.
What are you talking about?
You drew blood from me, no?
I can't wait to see Mexico.
Me. I volunteer for it. Eh?
Smokey, get out of here now.
I know what you'll say next.
Come on. Follow me, Straizo.
What sort of threat is that?
Be careful now. Careful now.
Allow me to escort you home.
Why, god? Why do this to me?
Und don't screw anything up.
Wow, that's quite impressive.
Give my best to Speedwagon...
I'd like to see you try that.
I want some answers, Straizo.
Did you lose your mind?
Just look at what you've done.
Can we please stop the crying?
I'm trying to think here.
Hmm. Next thing you'll say is,
Bah. Go ahead and do what you
think you need to do, Straizo.
Really? Wow, I didn't mean it.
They've been completely warped.
There will be no mercy for you.
Here's a secret before you die.
Sure, but I was still able to
pull one over on you, wasn't I?
So what are you gonna do, then?
This bastard has no conscience.
Fool me once, then shame on me.
24 before my love you'll see
we should be safe by now, right?
Consider that your last warning.
So I dragged the bodies outside.
If I didn't have to kill you now.
I am a master of its strengths
and flaws in all forms of combat.
You know what to do, right? JoJo?
I'll just pummel you into
fertilizer with my remaining arm.
Tell me, why did you throw
Speedwagon's body into the river?
Why in the hell did you do that?!
Make the necessary preparations
for the blood feeding experiment,
but I have a different philosophy.
So I hear that hamon does a pretty
good job of melting vampire faces.
And you should take a look at
the grenade you just knocked away.
No stealing, no lying, I swear it!
I would not do that if I were you.
Are you certain that this is
the type of game you wish to play?
Your act of playing it calm belied
the fire that we see in you now.
There is nothing I regret, Joseph.
I cannot tell you the ecstasy that
I have felt in being young again.
Yeah, I'm sure it "just happens"
every time you talk about a woman.
You were nearly dead in the desert
Everything! I want to know it all.
You're a vile, inhuman abomination!
Something here just doesn't add up.
Joseph, your grandfather
Jonathan's blood flows through you.
They make the children really ring
but... but how could he possibly
be alive with that hole in his head?
Just as much as you are to sunlight!
There is an insect deep in southeast
Asia called the satiporoja beetle.
Smokey, I thought I told you to run.
I will make him pay dearly for that.
Whether you know this woman or not
is inconsequential. If you flee now,
Now you'll say, "that's impossible."
The pillar sucked deeply of the
blood from those bodies in the cave.
So that means... you must have been
creating hamon inside your own body.
Mmm. I think the pain is going away.
The words will make you out and out
Call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
You've no idea what he's capable of!
Or I could just smash in your brains.
How would you feel about that?!
It's similar to an electrical ground.
Unlike Dio, I have studied the craft.
Pressure applied by fingertips,
235 kilograms per centimeter squared.
But I threw the bodies into the river
because of him. Don't you see, fool?
Now it's time to find out about this
pillar man Straizo was talking about.
You have a secret, a secret that is
very dangerous and could kill us all.
Only thing I got to hear is the river.
However, if you were to come up
here after a girl you don't even know,
But unfortunately for you, Straizo,
you'll never be able to fool me twice.
Your destiny has already been written.
However, they also research astrology,
sorcery, alchemy, and psychic powers.
It wasn't god. At least, not your god.
I also know that you were
penniless when you first got to Texas.
Once you have all agreed on who
will be the one to sacrifice his life,
Courage like yours is a thing that
must be cultivated like a lush garden.
Straizo! I'm going to give you a choice
on how you want to meet your demise.
Will it be plain old sunlight or hamon?
Now the only one left is Erina Joestar,
and that should be...
Too much time meditating out in the
Tibetan boonies has dulled your senses.
Run away, and I'll kill her right here,
"The village in which the elderly kill
each other is not long for this world."
He's powerful enough to destroy us all.
Hmm. Yeah, I know. It'll take a small
fortune to fix everything in this place.
But did you think I'd completely rely
on a gimmick like hamon all of the time?
You probably kill monsters all the time.
I basically blew them to smithereens,
and they still haven't fully healed yet.
I'll know just what sort of man you are.
But I have no doubts now that he will
soon awaken from his 2,000‐year slumber.
Not as some withered, desiccated corpse.
If I do your experiment, you promise
that you'll let everyone else go, right?
30,000 of their tiny stomachs have been
dried out and then woven into this scarf.
I have inherited 4,000 years worth of
history and research in the art of hamon.
I'm afraid not, Smokey. Do you hear that?
He just ripped it right out of her mouth.
The wehrmacht would like some information
from you before anything drastic happens.
About as easy as taking candy from a baby.
You wouldn't be so confused right now
if you had just been a bit more observant.
Which means you'll present a real threat
and continue to pursue me into the future,
Such gratuitous cruelty would be unseemly.
Why would you try to save me from falling?
I know you wouldn't want to hurt me again.
The old man found on the bank of the Rio
dada, he is now awake, major Von Stroheim.
Get ready! German medicine is the greatest
thing in the world, don't you think?!
Could it be possible that granny was wrong?
Their bodies conduct hamon far better than
the human body, thus dispersing the charge.
Even though I'm immortal, it'll take some
time to regenerate after what he did to me.
Predictability can be quite the fatal flaw.
All this time, I planned on entering hell
while still vibrant and filled with energy,
Pardon my interruption, major Von Stroheim.
Just who do you think you are, anyway, huh?
I'm smart enough to know that torture alone
would not give us what we want out of you.
Your granny was not wrong, because I can see
that you would grow into quite a worthy foe
Straizo, wait! Not yet! I need to know more!
I knew the man was crazy,
but not that crazy!
A secret weapon? Really? What kind of weapon?
What do his legs have to do with your weapon?
Tell me about Straizo und about this Joestar.
Set the boy aside, und execute everyone else.
Just as I feared, Straizo is indeed a vampire.
Aren't you frightened that I still possess
enough power in me to blow your arm clean off?
From the outside, you appear to be
opposites, but you're both insatiably curious.
You don't know the forces you're playing with.
Here, we will allow only the most fit to live.
I figure I'll have plenty of time to reflect on
the extent of my powers after you're destroyed.
That's why I like the city. It keeps you sharp.
It's as though I never even touched him at all.
The papers will be falling all over themselves.
But come up and meet me, and I will let her go.
I don't even know who that woman is, you moron!
And when that time comes, you shall learn
his identity and the true meaning of evolution.
Don't make me order you to lick my wound clean.
There is a saying in Europe that comes to mind.
You wouldn't happen to have the time, would you?
Let's skip the pretty speeches. Now you're mine!
When you found the oil fields that would soon
cause a massive overhaul of the world's economy.
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
I was pretty sure you'd go for my forehead again.
They seek to gain advantages through every manner
imaginable in their quest for global domination.
I'm... I'm so terribly sorry, major Von Stroheim.
Why couldn't you just have let me die back there?
I thought it would be appropriate to open up
with the technique that Dio used to kill Jonathan.
We extracted it from the location we got from you.
Go ahead und choose someone from among yourselves.
Call it morning driving through the sound
and in and out the valley in and around the lake
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
He's squeezing himself into the ventilation ducts!
It would be so easy to tear through her neck
and open up her chest cavity with just two fingers.
Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
this is my chance to break into big‐time journalism.
It was like a plant ravenously drawing in nutrients.
For what? What more could you possibly want from me?
Look deeply into my space‐ripper stingy eyes, Joseph.
What the... how did you pin that grenade on my scarf?
I deflected your shot with a little hamon shot glass.
Granny should be able to sleep well tonight, finally.
Oh, shut up. I'm done decoding your rubbish, Straizo.
My hand, it just slipped. I don't know what happened.
There appears to be a man trapped inside this pillar.
Tell us so that we can finally awaken the pillar man.
All I've got under my skirt is more Tequila, big boy.
And now it is my pleasure to warn you that your nature
has trapped you in a fate you cannot hope to escape.
Soon you shall learn of him, of the pillar man,
and then you shall finally come face to face with him.
I'm really sorry about that. It just happened kinda...
Looks like the adrenaline from her fear just wore off.
However, I can fire high‐pressure essence from my eyes.
I heard the story about Dio taking down my
grandfather by firing some sort of blast from his eyes.
Leaping ability, currently four meters, 22 centimeters.
1938. The second world war rages, threatening to engulf
more nations around the globe with each passing day.
It seeks to conquer the world with technology and
weapons that stand at the very cutting edge of science.
I was the one who made you live, but I can change that.
We will grant the rest of you your freedom immediately.
Which one of you was fool enough to disturb my slumber?
That thing I shot, I can only hope that he was a person.
I'll happily go to jail without thinking twice about it.
If you don't calm down, I may have to make out with you.
Dio's failure was in his infatuation with his own power.
I also heard that you may be severely allergic to hamon,
Yep. I have a secret weapon for situations such as this.
For a true coward would not seek revenge for Speedwagon.
Then I'll see that you are both courageous and powerful,
And it was through this tenacity that one of their
spy networks in Mexico caught wind of Straizo's actions.
We need blood for a very important, historic experiment.
And I would therefore have to eliminate you here and now.
You've got some nerve calling me a floozy, you big brute!
He just couldn't resist constantly pushing his own limits.
Please, god, I promise I won't ever do anything bad again!
You said that you would never fight for a floozy like her.
He stretched himself thin,
allowing Jonathan to strike him.
A true master of Tibetan hamon
would never do such a thing.
These bullets I fired at him
all have strange dents in them.
"How could he possibly be alive
with that hole in his head?"
Not to worry. It is fated that
you shall meet him very soon,
rather than pursue you, I could
use this time to heal myself,
I wouldn't fight for that floozy
even if I was married to her.