The spines that this mask uses can pierce a human brain.
However, they don't yet have the
strength to probe our immortal brains.
The solution is finding more power.
Ooh. What's that now?
The mortals call it the Red Stone of Aja.
Its power is of a particular interest for our kind.
This little stone can refract
light at least a billion times.
The end result is light of incredible purity and strength.
This amplified light holds power untold.
But this one won't do.
This little red pebble isn't large enough.
We need more capacity and strength in it.
To complete our mask, we need a red
stone that is large and utterly flawless.
We need a super aja.
Once we have that, we will conquer the sun
and then become the final, perfect step in evolution.
The masks were invented by the oldest
pillar man among them, and his name is Kars.
Eh?
Kars, Esidisi, and Wamuu crossed the Atlantic
in their search for a suitable super aja.
There you are, Suzie Q.
Signora, here. Just like you wanted.
Thank you.
You see this?
What I have in my hand here is a
natural, perfectly flawless stone,
a super aja.
Whoa!
You've been carrying the Red Stone of Aja around?
The warriors of hamon were wiped out by the pillar men.
This stone narrowly avoided being taken, and
now I have been given the honor to be its guardian.
Caesar, I know exactly how you feel.
The stone masks not only killed our grandfathers,
but they took the lives of countless others as well,
and now we've met its creator, Kars.
Just break it.
Yeah, crush the damn thing.
Smash it to pieces, and they'll cry like babies.
No, I can't do that.
Why? What's stopping you?
Legend says the pillar men can't be defeated
unless the stone is somehow a part of the process.
What? That's crazy. Why would that be?
I don't know,
but I will perform my duty as guardian as best I can.
JoJo, Caesar,
I'm afraid it's necessary for a final examination.
What? A final exam?
Caesar, take on Meshina, and defeat him.
JoJo, you have the same assignment,
but with Loggs. Are you two ready?
Are you ready, Caesar?
I was born ready.
It's almost dawn.
It's always darkest then.
Now, where could I expect Loggs to be hiding?
Stay sharp, Joseph. Eyes open.
You've got a score to settle with him.
Huh?
Is that instructor Loggs?
Horrible. Unnatural.
Instructor Loggs...
H‐he's dead!
Esidisi.
So you came to venice, came here to this island.
Hmm.
To think that the woman guarding the stone
is merely an island or two over that way.
His lungs were pulled out.
Lungs are vital for hamon users.
It had to have been a kick of incredible power.
The tyrant Loggs.
You yelled at me for three weeks.
You were relentless with your instructions.
To be honest, I hated you.
I was sure that this would be my chance to
get you back for everything you did to me.
You'll have to watch me from
where you are now, instructor.
See what I've learned from you.
Hey, Esidisi, I know it's six days early,
but I'll take it now.
That antidote in your nose ring is mine!
Hmm.
Out of my way, boy.
I don't have the time to deal with you.
You don't have the time? What do you mean?
You have a lot more time than I do.
That was pretty sharp.
You may have a little more to offer.
But when someone looks at me with
an obvious challenge like that one,
they are asking for their death.
I'll tell you this one more time.
Back away.
You know that with one touch of my hand,
you'll soon be missing half of your body.
Just try to move me.
Ooh. What's this now?
Oh, look. I'm still here.
I only move for important things,
like dog poo in my path.
Using his hamon, he's able to break
right through the flesh of my hand.
He's learned a great deal of
control in a very short period of time.
However...
You've developed new skills.
I have to say I'm rather surprised.
But you're still far from ready to fight someone like me!
I've met and devoured countless hamon
users like you thousands of years ago!
If I twist your finger completely off,
you'll never use it for hamon ever again.
Like this!
Hmm? Eh?
Oh, you finally noticed?
Your arm is wrapped up in a loop of fine silk thread.
It's soaked in vegetable oil,
so it really conducts hamon quite well.
I admit I was aiming for your neck,
but you didn't give me the chance.
How could a mortal have done this to me?
But‐but that's...
Actually a little morbid for my taste,
but still, first blood goes to me and my instructor!
2,500 years ago in China, a man wrote "the art of war."
He said this...
"Victory is decided before the battle is fought."
That means if you plan to win,
you need to lay out strategies
while your opponent is unaware.
It's true that I skipped school a lot,
but granny Erina made darn sure I studied my history.
So while you may have a lot of years under your belt,
you didn't leave any room in your head for strategy.
Take this!
How dare you?
Aww. Are you angry?
Are you upset that I disintegrated your widdle arm?
Well, then, get upset!
I'm far more furious than you.
Because of that little ring
you saw fit to put inside my neck,
I haven't slept right for weeks.
Huh?
I just can't take it!
What the hell is this?
He's bawling his eyes out,
and I thought he'd go on a bloody rampage.
This is more than weird.
This is embarrassing.
He's throwing a tantrum like some three‐year‐old.
My poor arm!
Ehh.
Some things are creepier than mindless anger.
I should finish him off quickly.
Eh?
I feel better now.
Sometimes my emotions overwhelm me,
and when I'm about to lose it,
I try to calm myself down by venting with a crying jag.
Earlier you referred to sun tzu, didn't you?
I knew him personally.
Long ago, I journeyed to China to study.
To fight is to delude.
All war is deception.
One tries to make their enemies angry
in order to lure them into committing costly mistakes.
That is precisely what you're planning on. Am I right?
Well, it's not going to work.
But I must say, JoJo,
I really am shocked at your improvement.
I admire your hamon ability.
I've been longing for a worthy opponent.
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Huh.
Well, it is a bit thin at the moment, but
it'll grow thicker with the passage of time.
He's too much.
Just a minute ago, he was crying.
Oh, JoJo, did I just frighten you there?
Come on. Admit it. You're frightened a lot, aren't you?
I can't read him.
I've always been able to read my opponents
and then use their own feelings against them,
but this guy's personality is beyond me.
Am I the one who's being read here?
W‐what's happening to Loggs's body?
Gah!
That burns.
His body, it's boiling.
What's going on?
An animal's core temperature will increase when
it's fighting disease or greatly exerting itself.
I can raise my blood up to 500
degrees and then shoot it out at will.
At the same time I took off his arm,
I also sent in some of my boiling blood to show you.
With his Divine Sandstorm, Wamuu can control the wind.
My domain is that of heat.
I control the inferno.
I'll grant that your power to destroy
a defenseless dead body is amazing,
but I can also see that the reason you did it
was to try and scare me.
Now try a clacker volley!
My hamon isn't like it was a month ago.
I really did frighten you.
You see, JoJo, your uncontrolled emotions
caused you to attack me recklessly and too soon.
My veins will inject boiling blood into your skull
and then turn your brain into a nice red stew.
This is the reason that I am called the burning king.
JoJo.
Caesar, take this!
Bubble launcher!
Caesar, stop. Hold your attack.
If we continue this contest, one or both of us will die.
And much as my ego doesn't want
to admit it, I'd be the loser.
For nearly 10 years more than
you, I have been in preparation here,
but today your hamon attack was so focused
you were able to burn the hair off of my arm.
What else can I do after being shamed like this?
You have passed your final exam with flying colors.
You should feel a sense of pride for this.
Or are you more interested in how your
good‐for‐nothing friend is doing in his exam, Caesar?
The only reason I had the power I did in this training
is that I wanted to match JoJo's talents.
In the end, we're both going to
survive the trials being presented to us.
I can't deny it. JoJo seems lazy and impudent,
but deep down, he's worth having as a friend.
Heh. You're not so good at making
friends for yourself, are you?
But when you do, it's true love, isn't it?
Wha?! Look there!
Esidisi!
Humph. And there's another of
those clever dodges of yours.
All right. The mask gave me
some protection that time, but...
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Ah, damn him and his blood.
Man, oh, man, I finally have the chance for these
sexy lips to come out from under that rotten mask,
and the first thing you do, you bastard, is burn 'em off.
JoJo. Hmm. Let's see.
On the surface, you make witty banter,
but inside your head, you're
making all sorts of plans, aren't you?
Ooh, you went pale, JoJo.
Did I hit the mark?
Was I anywhere close to the bull's‐eye?!
Heh. My next plan.
Right. Yes.
I'll use the string.
I'll act like I'm dodging to get away from him,
but all the time, I'll be running a string
along these spikes with each move I make.
I can't let him catch on.
Once he steps inside the string,
I'll wrap him up in it, then
use my hamon to finish him off.
That laugh means trouble.
Could‐could he be reading my plan, my intentions?
No, it's impossible.
Whoa!
Here is the burning king's prison!
How long can you possibly keep avoiding my attacks, JoJo?
Humph.
Huh?
So I guess you finally noticed.
Now, what possible reason would my hat be shrinking?
You appear to be caught in my web.
My hat is made of 100% wool.
It conducts hamon very well.
And?
You're smiling again. I don't like it.
What are you laughing about this time?
The next words from your mouth are,
"I'm going to knock that smirk
right off of your face." Watch.
I'm going to knock that smirk right off your face.
What a second. You can't do that. That's my trick.
You said you had a web?
Look around.
I am the one with the web.
I knew exactly what you had in mind
with your little plan even before you did.
So, JoJo, what was that phrase you said earlier?
Something like, "victory is decided before
the battle is fought." Was that what it was?
It's true, true,
very true, very true, very true!
How incredibly true were the words you spoke.
But my plans were the ones to go deeper.
My plans were the ones to decide victory!
It looks like my veins have created
some little holes on your body.
So now I'll fill every one of them with a
generous portion of my boiling, burning blood.
You'll look like a lovely birthday cake covered in
candles flickering with their merry little red flames.
He's on a knife's edge.
He's not going to make it.
Caesar!
Judging from what I can see,
we have to assume that Loggs has been killed.
If JoJo is not the one to survive,
we will be the ones Esidisi will come after next.
JoJo is too far away for us to be able to help him now.
I know it's painful, but right now we have to
think about protecting Lisa Lisa and the red stone,
so come. Let's make our preparations.
JoJo.
Let me hear your screams as you
twitch and writhe in despair and agony,
knowing that you lost today, JoJo.
Are you really laughing as I'm about
to deal you an excruciating death?
Have you been driven completely insane by the fear?
Well, let's see here.
You'll notice my arms are folded and my eyes are closed,
so this laugh would be one of victory, Esidisi.
You're the loser here today,
because for the last 2,000 years,
you have been asleep at the wheel.
I lost?
What do you mean by that?!
Oh, really? You don't get it?
You can't read me as clearly as you thought you could?
Let me help you understand just
how badly you've underestimated me.
You said that your plans went deep.
Well, they didn't go nearly as deep as mine.
While you were snoozing for the past 2,000 years,
humans have progressed.
During the 18th and 19th centuries,
legerdemain, or sleight of hand, became
a very popular form of entertainment.
I'm a really big fan of it myself.
Illusion is my thing!
But I cut all those strings.
I cut them! It can't be!
I'd say the rope magic worked.
I laid my trap carefully, so that even if
the string was cut, it would still function.
A simple trick.
What you're going to say next is,
"my veins will move faster than your
pathetic hamon can possibly go." Now.
My veins will move faster than
your pathetic hamon could possibly go!
Now feel the beat of my Hamon Overdrive!
I can't. I can't.
You're only a human.
I am the evolved one, the highest life‐form!
I will not be beaten!
Know that you've pushed me too far!
Esidisi's body is shooting some kind of strange energy.
That must come from living for millennia.
Die already.
Die with the power of life you stole
from thousands of innocent human beings.
My instructor, I thank you for torturing me.
Mille grazie to you, Loggs.
Hmm. When we defeated Santviento in the
well, his entire body turned into stone,
but even Esidisi's bones were completely destroyed.
Why is he so different?
Well, maybe it's because my hamon is
so much stronger than it was before.
Well, he's dead now,
and I have one of the antidotes I've been chasing down.
Ugh.
Oh, man, this reminds me of snot.
Hopefully it's just because it's dripping
from a ring that came out of his nose.
But I need to knock it back.
Yes. I do think it worked.
The ring around my windpipe is
gone, and I can breathe free again.
So then, I'll go see Lisa Lisa and Caesar.
I think maybe I was using my head too much in that fight.
My shoulders are really kinda stiff.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
I think the white one is pretty.
We'll wait for that until we cross.
But I really like the lovely design on this one.
I'll eradicate every one of them.
Which do I choose?
Damn it all. I just can't hit her.