Battle for the Red Stone of Aja,
JoJo versus Wamuu
in a one‐on‐one chariot duel.
The time is upon us.
When the full moon once again
emerges from behind that cloud,
the battle will begin!
Wamuu! Wamuu! Wamuu...
I wish they wouldn't make all that noise.
Why is it that the bad guys get all the fans?
One lap is 960 meters.
It takes approximately one minute
for these beasts to complete a lap.
Do you see that column over there?
On each lap, a different weapon will be hanging from it.
Weapons?
No.
One weapon at a time.
Whichever of us can capture that column before the
other will then have the opportunity to wield the weapon.
Do you see the first one up there?
It's a giant sledgehammer.
That thing could smash right
through a chariot in one blow.
If Wamuu is able to get his hands on it,
my situation isn't just going to be bad,
it could be terminal.
But if I can get to it first,
cover it with oil, and fill it with hamon,
then victory will be mine.
I am looking forward to an excellent,
fulfilling fight from you, JoJo.
Get ready.
The moon approaches the cloud's edge.
When its light falls upon us, the contest begins.
JoJo, what are you doing there?
The race is about to start.
Heh. I'm well aware of that.
The start will be the key, and I
sure don't want to mess that up.
That's why I'm checking the rubble under my wheels.
Look at that, Wamuu.
You've got quite a big pile under your buggy.
Are you going to take care of it?
Hurry! Come on! Get up there!
JoJo!
Begin now!
Hyah!
What's this now?
Lord Wamuu is having trouble.
His chariot is just standing there.
Look at that. His wheels are blocked.
JoJo, he did this.
That cheeky little devil.
You bastard. You piled them there while we
turned our attention to watching the moon.
You're nothing but a cheater. A rotten human cheater.
Show me in the handbook where it
says I can't do something like that.
All you told me was to lose means to die,
and that was the only rule in this fight.
When it comes to my survival, I don't care who I offend.
Beep beep!
Hyah!
The human's getting close to the column!
Yeah! Get him!
Don't let him get it!
JoJo will be the first one to the hammer.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I can't wait to have you in my grasp.
I've got ya. You're mine.
Damn, I'm going a lot faster than I thought I was.
No, stay there.
JoJo!
Eh? It snagged my ring.
Couldn't have predicted that.
Great. That was lucky.
Now the fight is in the bag. I've got this.
You can have the hammer.
That was my plan from the very beginning.
I see Wamuu has a plan in mind.
Let me see it now, your fighting genius.
A little oil up here. Add some hamon.
I've got a little medicine for you right here, Wamuu.
Wamuu's starting to lose speed.
It's not a race.
They are in a fight to the death.
The keys to winning are tactics and strategy,
the right weaponry, control of the environment.
All right then. I'll just slow down and
introduce him to my little friend here, the hammer.
JoJo, listen! You mustn't slow down any more!
Since you're the one with the
hammer, I'll just get something else.
So, Wamuu, are you ready to see
exactly what this thing can do?
Then here we go! Hah...
Look there.
He was so happy with his hammer at first, but not anymore.
He sure plans ahead...
Better than I do.
Hurry up! Go faster, and get away from him, JoJo.
Too late.
So now you will no longer have your chariot.
Down already? Things seem to be over a bit early.
He might want to rethink his plan. Heh.
JoJo!
The probability of him being
trampled by my vampire horses is 90%,
the chance of him attempting to break left is 5%
and breaking to the right is 5%.
So, now then,
what is our little human warrior going to do?
M... my hammer.
Where is my hammer?
He wants his hammer?
Did he hit his head too hard?
That hammer's not going to save you now.
JoJo must not dodge.
If he does, Wamuu will stop and
finish him with his Divine Sandstorm.
But what JoJo did was grab the hammer
and head straight for Wamuu's chariot.
Well done, JoJo. Great thinking.
That's exactly right.
What?
He struck the yoke midway between the horses!
As the horses ran on,
JoJo used the hammer's force
to launch himself into the sky.
Hmm?
That move was unbelievable.
The hammer's length kept him from being
trampled under the hooves of the horses.
How was that?!
And now for that big hammer
whack you've worked so hard to earn.
Huh? Wh...
He's gone. W... where'd he go?
Heh heh. You can clearly see that
Wamuu is a step ahead of his quarry.
Wait. That's right.
These fellas can hide themselves inside other creatures.
That was close.
His boot came off his foot.
That boot saved him.
If he only had on some other kind of footwear.
I've got luck on my side,
for example, the way the handle of
that hammer got caught on my ring.
Luck helps with effectiveness.
Now let's take a look at your situation.
Wamuu, your own power has trapped you
inside of that horse. That's not very lucky.
And here we go!
A little hamon for you and the horse you rode in on!
You fool. You don't see the trap.
Careful, JoJo.
You need to keep at arm's length from him!
Now that Wamuu has merged with
that horse, he's free to use his hands
without worrying about vibration
or speed, which means that...
No one has survived a direct hit by that attack!
Caesar couldn't.
And now you will taste Divine Sandstorm!
Even if it lasted only the distance of half a lap,
it was a battle filled with many twists and surprises.
But in the end, Wamuu proved the superiority
of both his thinking and his fighting prowess.
I think the next battle is
going to be quite a test of will.
Truly, it is not my preference to fight a woman.
Wamuu dislikes it even more.
Notwithstanding, all users of
hamon must be done away with.
Drink that.
It will provide a painless death.
Thanks. That's quite considerate of you,
but JoJo seems to be a little less dead than you thought.
Huh?
Uh, lord Kars,
look out there in the arena.
It can't be!
Lord Wamuu's arms, they look
like they're about to fall off.
Madness.
How could this have possibly happened to me?
What's wrong?
What is happening to Wamuu out there?
Look! There, it's JoJo.
He's alive. He's moving.
He's not even hurt.
Well, I apparently managed to survive once again.
But Wamuu hit him directly
with his Divine Sandstorm attack.
How could he...
Directly? Heh.
JoJo was cunning enough to make
it look like it was a direct hit.
He is an absolute genius at trickery and misdirection,
but I'm not sure I should be giving him praise for that.
Hmm?
Take a close look at Wamuu's arms.
Oh. Wait. Now I see.
He wrapped the reins around Wamuu's
arms after filling them with hamon.
Wamuu's Divine Sandstorm was short‐circuited.
Wamuu was already sticking one hand out of the horse.
He was going to try to use his Divine Sandstorm.
However, in order to do so, I knew he'd
have to stick his other hand out, too,
and I had the perfect counter for that move.
Lord Wamuu's face, look at him.
He's in agony. See that?
He doesn't seem to know where
he's going. His eyes are vacant.
What should we do?
It's the second lap.
But what's going to happen?
Lord Wamuu can't hold a weapon like that.
Is it even possible for him to fight?
It's not a surprise.
Right in midattack,
Wamuu was struck with a lethal dose of hamon.
The confidence built up over
millennia of triumph has crumbled.
The quiet, calm intensity his
victories gave him has vanished.
A tragic shock for him.
But it matters not at all!
Put out the next set of weapons, and do it now!
Lord Kars has given the order.
When he speaks, we must obey.
For the second lap, both warriors will receive crossbows.
Each comes with ammunition for two shots.
The first warrior there has the
choice of the small or large bow.
What's this now? There's two weapons.
There's a large one and another that's smaller.
Lisa Lisa, this is what's going through your thoughts now.
"Wamuu's mind is in no condition to entertain a fight.
"So why then would Kars be deploying these
new weapons and with such apparent confidence?"
It's very unsettling, is it not?
Well, the reason is that, at his core,
Wamuu is a warrior of legendary mental power.
The very best athletes use a psychological
technique called the switch comeback.
When these champions are brought low by
the pressure of shock, failure, or fear,
they can flip a mental switch and bring out
their fighting spirit for one last herculean effort.
Desperate times call for desperate measures,
and Wamuu will win at any cost.
No, I don't believe it.
Did he really just do that?
What? No, lord Wamuu.
Look! His eyes are gone.
He poked out his eyes!
I foolishly relied on my eyes, because I was
able to see, and JoJo exploited my weakness.
Now I will use this horn to see
things outlined in wind instead of light.
Hyah!
He flipped the switch by
removing his eyes from the equation.
Now he is once again psychologically invincible.
He senses the wind with that horn on his forehead.
He sees air better than he did light.
Huh? What is that supposed to be?
That's not going to have any effect on me.
Because of you, I lost my friend Caesar.
Try any trick you want.
I'll do whatever it takes to finish the fight.
JoJo, which crossbow will you take?
Yeah, which one?
You need to ask? You know the answer to that.
The large one, you stupid morons.
Power is what I want.
You gotta admit that one does have power.
Yeah, lots of power.
Oh, come on. I can't even draw this thing.
It's so tight. I can't get the
string to go anywhere at all.
You like it?
You got greedy, didn't ya?
Even a normal crossbow takes a huge
amount of strength to draw back. Ha ha.
You had to have the big one, huh?
That's what greed gets you!
I will use the first ball to paint a picture of the wind.
Whoa!
Now that I know what the range
is, the next shot will not miss.
How am I supposed to defend
myself if I can't shoot this thing?
Lord Wamuu, shoot him!
Blow him to smithereens.
Let us snack on whatever small pieces remain.
Hyah!
Right. Just as I thought.
The wind stirred up by these fires makes
it hard for him to figure out where I am.
This is the spot.
That's an error, underestimating Wamuu.
What? Lord Wamuu's pointing away from JoJo.
He's turned this way. He's aiming at us!
JoJo is staying on the opposite side from
Wamuu, thinking to shelter behind the flame.
Actually he has only served to point out his position.
I see what Wamuu is doing.
He's banking it like it's a billiard shot.
What?!
He hit me from behind!
I was examining the terrain while we were circling.
I had to find the proper wall
placement to use as a weapon.
Can't breathe.
The ball lost some of its momentum,
so it did not pierce JoJo's skin.
But he's spitting up a lot of blood,
which would then betoken some injury.
Finish him now, Wamuu!
But remember how wily and full of tricks JoJo is.
Be on your guard!
Has he set another trap?
When I hit the ground,
the impact cocked my crossbow.
I can't let him know that.
I can't kill him from this distance.
Closer. A little closer.
That's it.
He did.
Hmm?
Huh. Almost made it.
His aim was off, though, unfortunately for him.
But I really must commend him for
staying in the fight until the very last.
It's over, JoJo.
No. Stay away.
Ohh. Don't come any closer.
Go away. Leave me alone.
Please, I just can't take any more!
You've gotta spare me!
Shameful.
Look at him. The sniveling coward's throwing rocks.
He's just a pathetic loser.
Try to go down like a man, you disgusting little worm!
Listen, Wamuu.
Here is the very next thing
that will come out of your mouth.
"Don't you dare dishonor our battle here, JoJo."
Don't you dare dishonor our battle here, JoJo.
Want some more?
That bother you?
You know that a bat could simply fly right
between all those rocks and avoid every little piece.
Why can't you avoid them like that, Wamuu?
An iron ball!
It showed up out of nowhere!
You bastard.
I guess the human just took you down again.
You see, I banked the shot just like you did earlier.
The arena went silent.
Not one individual made a sound.
There wasn't even a moan.
Wamuu's injury peered out like the
sneering face of a jack‐o'‐lantern.
The iron ball carried with it a small amount of hamon.
The wound began to fester.
Wamuu's damaged arms grew even worse.
No more divine sandstorms now or ever.
I... I've got to try to breathe
again, get my hamon in balance.
You're trying a kick after faking a fall?
All right. If you still think you can do this.
Rebuff overdrive!
It's over! Wamuu won't be getting up again.
How can this be?
What has become of the great Wamuu?
The mighty warrior is no more.
12,000 years of victory reduced to this.
His arms.
His arms are gone.
It is not Wamuu's way to give up an easy win.
My wounds are only to flesh.
My losses are a path to ability.
I will use all of these things for victory!
His arms,
he threw them using his chest wound.
They grabbed JoJo and are choking him.
What's this? I can't breathe.
I can't gather my hamon.
What's going on?
That wind, it's flowing towards Wamuu.
The wind obeys me. This is my ultimate mastery!
Ultimate mastery?
No, you shouldn't!
Stop it, Wamuu! It must not be done!
The wind is going into those pipes.
Ultimate mastery,
atmospheric rift!
I will remember you
your silhouette will charge the view
of distant atmosphere
call it morning driving through
the sound and even in the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over, we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
doo doo doo yeah
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
Along the drifting cloud the
eagle searching down on the land
catching the swirling wind the
sailor sees the rim of the land
the eagle's dancing wings
create as weather spins out of...
You cowardly animals!
No matter the method utilized...
Remarkable.
You crossed a line.
No honor earns you no consideration.
This world and all in it belong to me.