You monsters!
Don't turn your backs on me!
Hmm?
Fine then.
I'll savor this one!
Hamon bubble launcher!
Could... could this be... is this what I think?
Nice work. Caesar may be a narcissist,
but his hamon skills are solid.
These bubbles may look harmless,
but prepare for a bombardment!
He... he popped them all.
How on earth did he do that?
That's not his hair.
Those are wires attached to his head he's manipulating.
He popped my bubbles with the wind that they created.
But then that means
they were designed to be anti‐hamon weapons.
Somehow they're already familiar
with the principles of hamon.
They must have faced hamon at
some point over 2,000 years ago.
What is that?
What's happening to the air around them?
Caesar, look out!
Get down!
Wh... what the...
Cover your eyes! That wasn't just wind! It was the
aftermath of a powerful vortex that's still active!
Caesar!
These humans know hamon.
I thought we destroyed all the members
of the hamon tribe 2,000 years ago.
And yet here they are, ready to
welcome us at our own awakening.
Damn... you.
You killed him.
You killed my friend.
Do you think losing an eye will stop me?!
Stop.
Why are you laughing? What's so funny?!
You all have memorized your hamon handbook very well.
You always say the same thing.
It was that way when we crossed from the
western continent, and it is that way now still.
"You think losing an arm or an eye or a leg will stop me?
"How dare you take my friend's life?
Don't you know how much I loved him?"
That's why we laugh, human.
You... you bastards!
Ignore him.
We're on a quest to find the stone.
What? Where are you going?!
Face me, cowards!
You're most vulnerable in your throat and your lungs.
We know that if you can't breathe,
then your hamon is rendered useless.
But because I cannot resist a worthy opponent, hear me.
I shall spare you, because I long for the
opportunity to meet you again when you are stronger.
The next time we meet, I want to admire your strength.
I want you to become worthy of my time
so that I might destroy you with great honor.
It appears that he was the only hamon user.
Hmm. Let's move.
Sorry. I just can't seem to shake this cough.
Maybe it's the hamon training that's making me ill.
What do you think?
Hmm.
He only sliced your eyelid.
The actual eyeball itself is just fine.
Perhaps you should sit this one out.
I think we've all seen enough of
the bubble launcher for one day.
Watch and learn as I take care of this one myself.
JoJo!
Just calm down, Speedwagon.
This guy is asking for it.
It's time for me to show off the
brand‐new technique I've been working on.
What?
Please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Joseph Joestar, and these are the
hands known for defeating your mate, Santviento.
I call this move my hamon clacker volley.
I start off by filling these little
clacker balls here with a bit of hamon.
Wuh... whah!
Oh, no!
JoJo, what the hell do you think you're doing?
This is no time for games.
What are you doing? Are you trying to
disrespect my friend by playing the fool?
Not intentionally.
I'm trying to be serious.
Caesar, I am truly sorry for the loss of your friend.
I understand both your pain and your anger.
Additionally, these guys may be the biggest group
of egotistical jackasses I've ever seen in my life.
I may not be a master of this yet,
but I'll still knock you into
next Tuesday with my clacker volley!
I hate to admit it, but I know
that my hamon is relatively weak.
I'm pretty sure I can make up for what I'm lacking
with these steel clackers.
If I can just break open your skin
even a little and fill you with hamon,
that should even up my handicap, don't you think?
I can tell you're nervous.
Take that!
Well, that was fun.
Let us keep moving.
Apparently the human race has
regressed rather than evolved.
Quite an understatement.
Amusing, though.
JoJo, what are you doing?
Your childish little games are going to get us all killed.
He's playing coy,
but this may actually be the best JoJo's got.
He'd be fine if he was facing some common street punk,
but I don't think he realizes that these
opponents are on a completely different level.
It would be comical if it weren't so tragic.
Why isn't anyone taking my little metal balls seriously?
That's far enough. Don't make
me clack you into the ground.
Stop.
Don't you feel that human lives are short enough?
There's no need to sprint to your death.
Silence. If you've ever had spaghetti al nero di
seppia, you know it looks bad, but it's delicious.
You should taste my clacker volley before you judge it.
The clackers, they vanished.
I've been training on my hamon all the live-long day.
He's insane.
Hmm?
Well, look it, ma. No hands.
Where are the clackers?
A true magician...
Never reveals his secret! Eat this!
How can anything move like that?
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
He's faster than Santviento.
I don't think those idiotic
clackers did so much as graze him.
I admire your weapon, your
courage, and your creativity, human.
I'm actually enjoying your company.
You deserve time.
One minute, but only one,
that is how much time I will
allow you to fight the mighty Wamuu.
JoJo!
I shall use your wound as a timer.
Your wrist will work well as a timekeeping device,
and you will lose consciousness due to
a loss of blood in exactly one minute.
Show me what you can do, human.
This is what I often told the members of the hamon tribe,
"your life is now my hourglass measured in blood."
Wamuu, we'll be waiting outside.
Now, boy, go ahead, and retrieve your weapon quickly.
What? I'm sorry. I'm growing deaf in this ear.
It almost sounded like you said, "go ahead, and
retrieve your weapon," which would be ridiculous.
I mean, why would you retrieve
something that comes right back to you?
Hmm?
Looks like my clacker boomerang worked pretty well.
I shouldn't even need the full minute to destroy you now.
That's for killing Caesar's friend,
that's for not taking me seriously,
and that's because I'm sick of looking at your ugly face!
Do what you must.
I deserve as much.
No opponent has ever struck my face,
and this is the price for my carelessness.
I shall take this beating in order to
properly honor you before I destroy you.
You say that no one has ever
hit you in that ugly mug of yours?
What an honor.
You didn't even stop to blink when you killed
Caesar's friend mark, did you? You monster!
Do you not value life at all?!
JoJo, watch yourself!
His arm isn't broken! He's getting ready to use it!
Whoa. I have a feeling this isn't good for me.
A charming observation, human.
I'm now scarred due to my carelessness.
It was my duty to allow you to pummel me
as punishment for my own lack of judgment.
That has now ended, however.
JoJo, finish him now while you still can!
My ultimate technique,
the Divine Sandstorm!
Guhh! I don't like the sound of that.
He starts by spinning his left arm clockwise
and then his right arm counterclockwise.
JoJo is unprepared to counter a technique like
this, as Wamuu's fists seem to grow before his eyes.
The air between Wamuu's arms transforms
into a powerful vortex of destruction.
This vacuum creates a highly
pressurized, deadly maelstrom.
Great, if he can tear through marble pillars,
I don't see myself having much of a
chance against a windstorm like this.
I don't think I've ever seen anything this powerful!
Uhh. JoJo.
I call that Divine Sandstorm.
No! JoJo!
Don't be a damn fool.
Run, Speedwagon. Get out of here before it's too late.
I'll try and distract him somehow.
Curse this blood in my eye. Threw off my aim.
But it proved enough when you made
the choice to hide behind a pillar.
Hmm. You died quickly.
Normally I would ignore human
onlookers such as yourselves.
However, you witnessed my shame,
so unfortunately I must take the time to destroy you both.
You may pray now if you wish.
Eh?
Hmm. Must be the light.
What does he think he's doing?
I don't believe it.
He's actually trying to escape.
Huh?
Hmm.
That coward has no shame playing dead like that.
I understand leaving me, but what about Speedwagon?
I knew he was spineless.
This guy is the most powerful foe I've ever faced.
My breathing is out of control.
I can't control my hamon.
I don't really have any other option left.
Luckily, my specialty is running away.
Behold our now‐broken hero,
JoJo, forced to play dead, crawling for his life,
and now leaving Speedwagon behind to face certain death.
Even with all of this, JoJo remains
dedicated, a hero worthy of this tale.
How is that, you ask?
Nice try there, human.
You coward.
No true warrior would ever
feign death just to save himself.
Hmm?
That may be true, though my intention
was not to escape, but to distract.
Truth be told, I was just trying
to get you onto this mine cart.
You are clever indeed.
So you were only playing the part of the coward
to lure me away from your friends. Is that right?
I'm surprised you fell for it.
That trick is probably older than you.
Get out now, Speedwagon. Run!
Caesar, go! What are you guys doing?
JoJo.
That bastard. What a noble move.
Now that I've painted myself into a corner here,
I need to come up with a second part to my plan,
which would be...
The unflappable hero.
He calmly searches for options, not knowing
what to do next, but his will remains unbroken.
JoJo!
Damn you, JoJo.
He's in far worse shape than I am.
I should have been the one to lure Wamuu away.
I see now that JoJo only acts
foolishly to confound his opponent.
He must actually have a good plan to beat those monsters.
Although you are quite confident for
someone who is knocking on death's door,
I must tell you that your plan is a poor one.
You're quite tough. I'll give you that.
Softheaded, but tough nonetheless.
Tell me, how do you remain unyielding
in the moments before your death?
Is it because you have bricks for brains,
or do you still have another trick for me?
Do you really want to know?
Actually, no. Let me guess.
Because you're so obviously clever,
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt
that you wouldn't be stupid enough to be
holding a stick of dynamite behind your back.
Damn. He's onto me.
And I know you wouldn't insult my intelligence
by thinking you could quickly throw the brake
and send the mine cart flying off the tracks,
maybe like this!
Damn. He got me there, too.
Hmm?
The time on your hourglass wrist is just about up.
There is absolutely no chance that
you will survive this any longer.
I found your tricks to be very quaint.
Before you die, tell me, why do I
still not see defeat in your eyes?
I'll tell you if you want, but you're
gonna have to say, "please," first.
More games. You've tested me long enough. Prepare to die.
Such a shame, because a month from now, I can
guarantee that I would be able to destroy you.
What was that?
With just one more month of
training, I would annihilate you.
I was the first person to hit, as
well as the first to scar your face.
When I put my mind to something, I
can accomplish pretty much anything.
Oh, well. I guess none of that really matters now.
So can we just get this over with?
It will be an honor to be killed by
a warrior like you, blah, blah, blah.
What do you mean by this?
Oh, I'm sick and tired of all this talking.
Just hurry up, and make it painless, Wamuu.
Explain yourself. What are you trying to get at?
I don't know how, but he's still alive.
Is it true that you pillar men often live for millennia?
That's a long time to be walking around with the
shame of having your face rearranged by a lowly human.
It seems to me that the only way you could
regain your honor would be by defeating me in a fight
after I've undergone proper hamon training.
I do not have to defeat you in order to maintain my honor.
His entire body is shaking with rage.
I have a chance if I can make
him think his integrity is at stake.
He gave himself away as the proud warrior
type the moment he called me a coward.
Pride is his Achilles heel.
I don't know if you noticed, but I'm still new at this.
However, if I trained with my hamon for a month, I know I
could give you the fair fight a warrior like you deserves.
The first person who ever hit you
in the face gave you a nasty scar.
It would be a shame if you killed
that person before he's worthy.
But if you feel the need to kill me before
I have a chance to battle you as an equal,
then go ahead and do whatever you need to do.
You bastard!
Wamuu.
Master Esidisi.
You gave this human one minute.
Why must you insist on letting him toy with you? Eh?
Just go away. I almost had him.
Hmm.
Master Esidisi, I have grown fond of
this particular member of the hamon tribe.
I got him.
JoJo, you will be happy to know that I
have decided to accept your proposition.
If you swear that you will train
your hardest to fulfill your potential,
then I will give you exactly one month to do so.
So you're not going to kill me now?
That's right.
But we're going to fight again?
We are.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I'll give you a chance to take it back.
Yes. I can't believe it's working.
However...
I will need assurances that you will
not try to run away again, of course.
Heh heh. Nice, Wamuu.
I was wondering when you would finally propose.
Say hello to the wedding ring of death.
Guess where it goes.
A hint, not on your finger.
W... what are you doing with that?!
This ring will start to dissolve in 33 days.
It's impossible to remove, and once
dissolved, it will release a virulent poison.
Any attempt to remove or damage it
will also release the lethal poison.
However, there is one certain way
to dissolve the ring without harm.
Simply battle and defeat me within 33 days,
and I shall give you the antidote that
I keep inside the hollow of my lip ring.
JoJo!
The vow on that wedding ring
states, "till death do us part," JoJo.
Be at the Colosseum in 33 days.
Meet me there at midnight, and
we shall battle as equals, JoJo.
I hope you didn't think your paltry
tricks would help you escape, human.
I don't imagine the two of us will fight,
but just in case, here's a gift for you...
One that fits perfectly around your windpipe!
Agh!
My heart and my throat!
My poison is quite different from Wamuu's,
and I keep the antidote for that poison in my nose ring.
Kars? Would you like to go next?
I don't think so.
Immortality can be boring at times.
To encounter a worthy opponent, that is
both such a rare and tantalizing thought,
a gift that would give our lives meaning.
I can see why you do this.
However, do not forget that our
goal is to obtain the Red Stone of AJA.
We must stay focused. Let's go.
Train long and hard, JoJo,
so you can challenge my Divine Sandstorm.
I... I can't believe that.
Two wedding rings with poison?
Is that supposed to be some
kind of sick joke or something?
I've got one around my throat and one around my heart.
Do these guys think I'm some kind of bigamist, or maybe...
Well, at least Speedwagon and Caesar are safe.
That's what's important.
No sense in feeling sorry for myself.
JoJo.
You fool.
That was one hell of a bluff you just pulled there.
The best con man couldn't have done it better than you.
You acted bravely, but now you'll need to back it up.
We don't have much time to work,
and we have serious hamon training ahead.
In and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky
they stand there
24 before my love and I'll be there
When I said I needed a month, I only meant it as a bluff!
Well, from up here, it's really more deep than tall.
Coach, wait! Please don't do this!
Because you're a girl, doesn't mean
that I won't give you what you deserve.
Welcome to Venice.