JoJo won his battle against that demon.
Poor sod.
He lost everything in the process.
That's why I brought him here three days ago.
And now, bereft of father and home alike,
how's he gonna muster up the will to live?
Don't give up on the world yet, JoJo!
Spirit...
That's what he needs, so I'm gonna give it to him.
Huh?
It's the dead of night,
but there's a lamp burning in his room.
What do we have here?
How long's she been at it?
Don't tell me she's been watching over him all this time.
Her fingers,
cracked from the damp, I'd wager.
She must have been cooling his burns round
the clock for them to get like that.
Thank goodness.
He's awake.
You're through the worst of it.
You should be fine.
So you've been tending to my injuries?
But how can... how can you be standing here?
You're the image of...
But no. I'm sorry.
Your face reminds me of a girl I used to know.
Her name wouldn't happen to be Erina Pendleton, would it?
It's you.
It's been a long time, Jonathan Joestar...
JoJo.
Erina, you've really grown up.
Me? But you've grown a fair sight more.
Yet...
You're still the boy you were.
Yeah.
She makes a better Florence nightingale than I do anyhow.
You rest up, JoJo.
Time for Speedwagon to make his exit.
I... I must have fainted for a moment.
But your arm, it's broken. You shouldn't have caught me.
You caught me long ago.
I daresay oi' JoJo won't be lacking
a reason to live after this reunion.
You should have made an early night of it, you harlot.
Big mistake.
Most men shackle themselves to petty morality.
Huh?
They fear the consequences of their evil.
But some are unfettered by
man's laws in all their tyranny.
They are the vanguard.
Become my servant, Jack the Ripper.
You've no further need for free will.
I will make you an instrument of death,
the likes of which you can't begin to imagine.
Do it.
As for what I shall take in return...
Only Speedwagon and I know what
truly took place here that night.
Dio was consumed in the inferno,
but what of the accursed mask?
No sign of it in the rubble.
Smashed by falling masonry?
I hope so. I want to put this nightmare behind me.
JoJo.
Erina.
Hmm?
That man, he haunts our steps.
Is something wrong?
No. All is well.
Ah, signore Joestar.
And the lass at your side is signorina Pendleton.
Who are you?!
You survived against the mask.
Not many men can claim that.
JoJo!
That's right.
Let the shock of that impact
push all the air from your body.
JoJo!
Why? He was already hurt, you cad!
It's true I knocked the air out
of him, but he'll thank me for it.
My arm!
What is this? My broken bones...
Feel like they're mending!
Baron Zeppeli, at your service.
Courage alone will not be enough to beat the mask.
My arm was shattered, but now...
The pain has subsided.
Lifting this rock is nothing.
That's incredible.
Sir, why are you here?
And what is happening to me?
Please, try to limit yourself to one question at a time.
You healed yourself, JoJo.
How you breathed after I poked you was the key.
But why did you go to the trouble in the first place?
And how do you know who I...
He's gone.
What part of "one question at a time" eluded you?
You'll get the answers you desire, amico. Follow me.
This day, I will show you things the likes
of which will change your destiny forever.
It was with good reason that
I struck you in the diaphragm.
The shock of the impact altered your breathing.
But how did that heal my arm?
With the energy I am about to demonstrate for you.
Wait. What mischief is he planning?
Look at him, Erina.
His legs. Those ripples.
I've never seen water do that.
What you see is the force that eased your pain
and healed your broken bones, signore Joestar.
Don't do it!
That frog seems none the worse.
That was sendo you saw.
Wait. "Sendo"?
It's ripple energy created by hamon.
I sent my hamon coursing harmlessly through
froggy to split my real target, the rock below.
JoJo, I know for a fact,
the stone mask was not destroyed.
Dio Brando keeps it close to him even now.
No, it can't be.
Baron, is Dio still alive?
Indeed, and he holds the mask
I have sought for decades now.
That mask must be destroyed,
and its master must be reduced to ash.
It is your destiny to fight for this righteous cause.
You will learn to wield sendo, or you will die.
The future of humanity is at stake!
My destiny?
What is he talking about?
None of it makes any sense.
Erina.
She's already suffered enough at Dio's hands.
I can't drag her into this.
Incredible.
It's blossoming!
He's passing the spare hamon energy from his
healed arm into the branch and sending it into bloom.
And amazingly he doesn't even realize he's doing it.
This boy, he is a natural.
Of what might he be capable, with
the proper refinement of his abilities?
Rejoice, mankind.
This day, I may have found your champion.
Mmm.
With every meal, I feel my strength returning.
What a simple thing, the food chain.
As pigs feed on grass, so does man feed upon them,
and I, at the top of it all, feed upon the humans.
They exist to serve me and quell my thirst.
Go, Jack. It's suppertime.
Now to swell the ranks of my
diabolical army and send it hence.
I will stand astride this world.
Humanity will kneel at Dio Brando's feet.
And so I began to study hamon under
the tutelage of the mysterious Zeppeli.
The training was spartan, but I had no choice.
Here's how it came about.
JoJo, my history with the
stone mask has been a long one.
I was your age.
Hard to believe that was ever the case now.
I harbored a great thirst for
adventure, as the young so often do.
It was my good fortune to travel the world
as a member of my father's archaeological team.
Would that we had never lain
eyes on those aztec ruins that day.
You're saying...
Yes.
The hands that pulled that evil artifact
into the light of day belonged to me.
One ill‐fated night during the voyage home,
a man of our number succumbed to his curiosity
and donned the mask.
The change in him was immediate.
Rampaging through the ship, he ripped his
companions' heads off in a bacchanalia of blood.
58 crewmen butchered in a matter of minutes.
I dove into the sea to escape, but the fiend gave chase.
Suddenly dawn broke.
As he crumbled to dust in the sunlight,
I saw his face...
And to my utter horror,
the demon was my father.
The crewless ship drifted away with the mask still aboard.
I had survived, but it was cold comfort,
knowing the mask's dreadful
power could be unleashed again.
I dedicated my life to finding a way to stop its evil.
That pledge led to my discovery of hamon.
The energy we call hamon is
created by the flow of one's blood.
Those who wear the mask feed on the
blood of others to consume that energy.
Hamon and the mask, they are two sides of the same coin.
Of course.
We can overload Dio with that which animates him.
Correct.
If we can hit Dio with enough hamon
energy, that devil will burst asunder.
Hamon's ripples are the same form as the
waves of light sent out by the sun itself,
the bane of all vampires.
Baron Zeppeli, I beg of you,
teach me how to wield it.
I promise I'll give it my all.
You don't get a choice in the matter, amico.
Given your contentious history with Dio,
I'm sure he will be coming for you.
There is a poetry to this, JoJo.
Breathing oxygenates your blood.
Your blood carries the oxygen throughout your body.
It enriches the cells, giving
them the power to keep on living.
Those cells combine to form you.
Like ripples in the water, your body thrums
with the hamon created by proper breathing.
All that is left is to use it!
There's no way he could have reached me from there.
How did he do that?
Zoom punch is a useful one.
I merely dislocated my shoulder.
Hamon dulls the pain, and the
surprise is well worth the effort.
You must maintain the rhythm of
your breath, even when taking a hit.
If your mind or heart are tempestuous,
the caliber of your hamon will suffer.
Yes, sir.
Oi!
I found something!
Eh? Speedwagon.
So the village is called wind knights lot?
Right.
They've had a string of disappearances
lately, people vanishing after dark,
and folks have caught glimpses
of a fella who looks like Dio.
We're out of time now.
Your final test will be one of life or death, my pupil.
Yes, sir. I'll meet him in combat and lay him low.
Give him hell.
Look, gents.
The entrance to wind knights lot.
We'll attack Dio while there's
still plenty of light left in the sky.
Erina. I left without giving you a proper farewell.
I swear I will return to her.
Huh?
Why did we stop?
Oi, mate! Hurry it up!
Keep an eye out.
Sunlight can't protect us in here.
Well? What's wrong?
Is it Dio?
It has to be him.
Listen, both of you.
Step away from the horses.
What in the blue hell?!
That crazy blighter's inside our horse!
Good god, this one's mad as a hatter!
Dio's evil, yeah,
but I ain't seen him jump out of any animals so far.
He must be gathering minions, and
who knows how many he might have?
Stand aside, my young friends.
I will do the fighting.
He is a zombie.
They must feed on living flesh to survive.
However, they are in constant thrall to their master,
not unlike marionettes.
Oh, you lads is both as white as a sheet.
All the blood is drained from your faces.
Maybe I should cut off those useless heads of yours,
and watch it spray outta your necks.
Now, you mewling corpses‐to‐be, prepare for the carnage!
Tell me, what's his next move?
You must think as he does.
JoJo, this strategy will serve you in good stead.
Ask yourself, "what would be the most
advantageous thing for my foe to do next?"
Him, for example.
If he blocks off the tunnel entrance,
we can't retreat to the sunlight.
Just as I predicted, he's blocked our retreat!
Speedwagon, jump!
Try harder.
Knives are coming out of him.
Baron Zeppeli,
you didn't say nothing about fighting a pincushion.
Hamon cutter!
Hah hah hah hah!
Eh?
I'm afraid your blades are rather
dull compared to my hamon cutter.
JoJo, this creature illustrates a principle.
Imagine a minuscule flea,
so small that it's barely visible.
Why is it they bite humans who tower over
them without a single thought to their own safety?
Would you call their behavior courageous?
Of course not. It's hunger compelling them.
I will tell you what courage is, JoJo.
Courage is to look your fear in the eye
and know that it has no dominion over you!
Fear scatters your breathing.
When you toss your fear into the dust,
breathing is the sword ever at your hip.
Breathe with courage, and you will never want for hamon.
Bravery is our birthright, lads!
And for all the abilities they may bring into a battle,
courage is something a zombie
relinquished when he took this form!
They're no better than fleas!
Sendo wave kick!
A knee full of hamon to the head seems
to have cured this one's braggadocio.
I don't believe it. He didn't even spill any wine.
JoJo, you finish the creature off.
Destroy the brain. It's the only way.
Anything else, and you risk it coming back.
Time for the slaughter, naughty little pigs.
I'll cut you to shreds one by one.
Don't tell me we're following him into that passageway.
It has to be destroyed,
but we will be doing no such thing.
JoJo...
I expect you to finish off this
abomination without spilling a single drop.
All right, one last bit of advice before you go.
There were no vikings in the land of Norway,
until the north wind blew in and created them.
If even one drop of that vino goes to waste,
I don't care how utterly you defeat the zombie.
I will abandon you here and now.
Oi!
Listen to yourself. Have you gone insane?
I know what I'm doing!
I will do my best.
Like the vikings, I will be strengthened by hardship.
It's a labyrinth.
Even with this torch, all it's
doing is casting shadows to bedevil me.
The torch!
I'm bright as day to him!
All this does is illuminating my position,
but without it, I haven't a clue where
he's lurking, or from where he'll strike.
Even in the dark, I can smell the blood from his arm.
I must think like my foe, just as the baron commanded.
I'm sure he's close.
Next, I must master my fear, lest it sap my hamon.
Breathing is the sword at my hip.
That's it. A little closer,
and I'll be picking my teeth with your bones, boy.
The harsh wind blowing down off of the
arctic ocean birthed the fearsome vikings.
Only when we are tossed headlong into the
crucible of adversity do we rise to the challenge.
What will a glass of vino create this night?
If he should fail, Dio has already won.
What? The wine is rippling.
Of course. Just like when we were training in the stream.
It's conducting the hamon.
It passes through the glass, my arm,
my body, the ground itself!
I can feel his vibrations in the wine.
With hamon, all is made clear to me now.
My spirit trembles!
My heart is ablaze!
I've found you, zombie!
These stones offer no protection!
Sendo Hamon Overdrive!
Turn the corner so I can feast on you.
Sounds like you passed the test
with flying colors, JoJo.
Excellent.
Adversity has made the lad a viking.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound
and in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
this time, I break you.
Curses on you, queen!
Can he overcome this delusion?!
A duel between heroes.
I'm ending your reign of terror here and now!