All the air, it seems to be flowing over to Wamuu.
My ultimate mastery, atmospheric rift!
That's only wind?
I know you're near the flame.
I sense it, though I can't see exactly where that is,
but I am going to find you eventually.
Now that I've prevented you
from gathering your hamon energy,
I'm going to cut you in half.
Atmospheric rift is Wamuu's supreme final weapon.
The pipes he uses to cloak
himself take in huge amounts of air
and then unbelievably compress it.
The air is then blasted from
an orifice thinner than paper.
It is a razor made of wind.
But it creates heat and friction
at levels terrible even for Wamuu.
His body cannot handle it.
He is falling apart.
But he is certainly a breathtaking
figure, tragic and heroic.
Victory is yours, Wamuu!
Take his life as a balm for your wounds.
JoJo!
It's getting close.
Time to pull off one of my famous tricks now.
This one's called the hamon oil trick.
His lungs are literally high‐pressure oxygen tanks.
Those pipes, if I can only hit them,
he'd inhale the flaming oil, which in
turn would create an internal explosion.
But this is the very last ace up my sleeve.
If I mess it up...
Got you now.
Your life is mine.
Damn it!
Take this, Wamuu!
Hmm?
That's your choice?
Fool.
I can sense anything that is
far enough away from the fire.
You're out of tricks,
and that cry of yours gave away your position.
And now...
Atmospheric rift!
Caesar!
Lend me your strength!
Another fire attack?
I told you I can sense these things.
And now I will cut you in half to claim my victory.
JoJo, no!
Now he has finally won.
Wamuu...
Let me tell you exactly when you lost.
It was when I threw Caesar's scarf.
Eh?
Don't you get it? I meant for you to
cut the bottle in half the entire time.
Your ability to do it so quickly and
easily is what led to your downfall.
The oil inside of it is now vaporizing.
And look. You see the bandana,
all the pieces flying around?
Every little fragment is still on fire,
and they're entering my body.
Wamuu, you have been a worthy and admirable fighter,
but a powerful ally named Caesar
was with me throughout this contest.
He was defeated.
Lord Wamuu. How could he have lost?
JoJo, be careful. He can regenerate,
even like that, after being blown to bits.
You have to use your strongest
hamon to destroy him completely.
So it is finally over now, JoJo.
It is.
You took revenge for Caesar.
Yes, I did.
Then go ahead.
Finish it.
I will!
What is going on?
That smoke isn't from the flaming oil.
It's coming from your wounds.
The hamon from your arms spread through you.
Every part of you is infected now.
You are dissolving.
I can only imagine the agony you feel.
I can't prevent you from dying now,
but there's this.
My blood can at least ease your pain.
Why do you want to shame me?
I have made peace with myself.
Stop. I don't need pity from you.
Is that what you think?
That this is done out of pity for you? No.
Why didn't you destroy Caesar's bubble
of blood that carried his bandana and ring,
knowing full well that they posed a serious threat to you?
Was that pity?
It was because the man was a worthy and noble warrior.
He deserved to be honored for that.
What you'll say next is, "JoJo, you can't mean..."
JoJo, you can't mean...
Yes, I do, Wamuu.
The honor you showed my friend, Caesar's
warrior spirit, had earned your respect.
So in return, I wanted to find a
way to honor your warrior spirit.
My blood is a tribute to you.
You beat me, JoJo.
And as a warrior,
it would now appear that you stand taller than I do.
Kill the bastard!
Hold!
What betrayal is this?
Huh?
You cowardly animals!
Wamuu!
Why do that?
I am Wamuu.
Although sworn to lord Kars, I will
not allow the vampires to attack you.
It's not because of sentiment.
I told Caesar this as well.
To me, only the strong truly existed.
Victory was the single quality to be admired.
I existed only according to my own code of honor.
JoJo, please understand,
to me, immortality was something
utterly unimportant and trivial.
All that has ever mattered to me was living up to my code.
And now...
I desire that you should drink the antidote.
You must do it before I dissolve completely away.
You won't see it, though.
I don't need eyes, words, or a horn.
I will know it. What matters is that you do it.
I have no regrets.
I am glad I was able to witness your growth as a warrior.
Perhaps
the reason I lived these thousands of
years was so that I could meet you at the end.
Farewell to you,
warrior JoJo.
Wamuu became one with the wind.
JoJo gave his opponent one final salute.
Though no tears fell, they had shared a silent song.
They had shared a warrior's affinity.
Wamuu...
You must kill him.
But, my lord Kars,
with utmost respect, he is only an innocent young boy.
That's true, just a boy.
That is the reason he must die.
If these hamon users are allowed to live,
they're likely to become our mortal enemies,
and humans grow very quickly indeed.
Hmm.
Is it beyond you?
It would seem I must demonstrate how it is done.
Now, resolving the problem is handled like this, Wamuu!
Wamuu, he was too pure in his warrior philosophy,
and he became weak as a result.
Well, that's the end of Wamuu.
Indeed it is. What a disappointment.
You're right. He's only a poser.
Your followers are such base creatures.
Makes me want to vomit.
No, don't. Lord Kars, we...
He's draining us dry.
I alone am the only one to remain...
Because...
This world and all in it belong to me.
Look at him! Look!
Lord Kars is amazing!
Our lord is ready to fight!
Listen, lord Kars, there's no reason for
you to waste time on any one‐on‐one battles.
Forget the rules. Let us kill these two for you.
For you, lord, we'll turn them into sprays of blood!
Just what I thought you would do.
I told you.
The red stone! Look!
It's me against Kars one‐on‐one,
but if those terms aren't to your liking,
why don't I just smash this thing right here and now?
I will honor my word.
A one‐on‐one fight, count on it.
My promise stands.
That is why I chose to reveal my horn to you.
As for my underlings' behavior,
as you can clearly see, they are already dead.
Why, lord Kars?
All I want is that red stone.
However, though, Esidisi and Wamuu
were my comrades for 10,000 years.
I have no choice but to honor both their
warrior deaths and their warrior pride.
I will fight you hamon users fairly,
and then I will finish this with my own two hands.
For you, Lisa Lisa, seeing the fighter you are,
I will not think of you as merely a woman.
I will fight you with all the
strength I have at my command.
Come with me.
That is where we shall fight...
The temple at Piz Bernina.
Champions of battle would come here to drink the
blood of those they had felled mixed with liquor.
They thanked the gods for the gift of life.
It's not an arena, but it will serve for our fight.
Coach Lisa Lisa, you may be extremely
skilled, but you are still a woman.
He doesn't look as strong as Wamuu was.
Let me take him for you.
I will not.
I didn't live my life as I did and train all
those years to be replaced by some stripling.
Oh, that's right. You have lived a lot of years.
I shall use my brilliant bone blades.
It would offend Wamuu's memory if I
didn't offer you the weapon of your choice.
Feel free to pick anything you like.
My scarf will be more than sufficient.
As you will.
And now let's fight.
Remarkable. There is no violence in his stance.
How can he fight without violence?
What's the matter? Are you not ready?
Apparently the first move is mine!
He disappeared completely in that sudden white light.
Where'd he go?
Kars is here.
I... I can feel him.
But he seems to be coming from above as well as below.
Attack of the brilliant bone blade!
Look! In the pillar, there's a crack!
Snake muffler.
Eh?
What you don't know is this satiporoja beetle scarf
is able to conduct hamon energy perfectly.
It's both a deadly weapon and a life detector,
and it protects against being attacked from behind!
All right. A knockout.
My wonderful coach really got him good.
He didn't really compare to
Wamuu, but dogs who bark rarely bite.
Coach, I have to say that you really are better than me.
Help me. Help me, lord Kars.
Kars is behind her.
Then who's that? Who's at her feet?
It can't be.
What the hell is going on?!
Kars wasn't the one fighting with her. He used a double!
What stupidity.
Why would I ever choose to fight one‐on‐one?
The only thing I wanted out of this was the red stone,
because I plan to become the ultimate life‐form.
I am not a warrior‐philosopher like Wamuu was,
nor am I a romantic.
No matter the method utilized, in the end...
Victory is the only thing that matters!
So that's why I sensed no violence.
He never had any intention of fighting me.
It's over!
Jo... Jo.
I have the red stone.
The only thing that's left is for all
of you to make me happy by killing JoJo!
Kars. Kars!
You are going to pay!
Kars!
Out of the way! Move back!
I'll split your damned skulls and kill you!
Zoom punch!
Eh?
Your hamon,
I don't think it's working anymore.
You're weak now, so we're...
Rebuff overdrive!
JoJo, you look completely worn out.
Your breathing is ragged, your hamon level is weak,
and you're the only one left out of all
of the hamon users that Lisa Lisa trained.
Can you last?
Will you last?
JoJo...
Think you can beat me?
Mmm.
What? It can't be gone.
Let's rip off his skin!
Ah, crap. You can try!
Eh?
Th... that light.
And that face.
This is your warning, vampires.
You are now facing major Von
Stroheim und the German elite.
And we represent the special
forces of the Speedwagon foundation!
JoJo.
Damn. Speedwagon, you look great.
And, Smokey, too.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
My right leg might be stiff now,
but my body is better than it ever was before.
Now all you vampires will see what German science can do!
Taste our ultraviolet floodlights!
It was the Speedwagon foundation
that made them small enough to carry,
but our boy does like to brag.
Hmm.
Crafty creatures, no question.
Hmm?
I don't see JoJo down there.
Gone again.
Eh?
Oh, you're just as quick as ever, aren't you?
Take eyes off you for a second,
and there you are putting another little scheme in play.
You crossed a line.
No honor earns you no consideration.
You said it would be a fair fight,
but attacked Lisa Lisa in a cowardly ambush,
thereby showing what you're made of.
And you have betrayed the honor
and memory of your friend Wamuu.
Save your indignation.
Your outrage means nothing.
Any action is a means to an end for what I desire.
The thing that matters to me is the red stone.
Battling over thousands of years means minimizing danger,
not taking any risk, and moving
your pawns very carefully indeed.
This is what the battle has been about.
And to show you how good I am at this,
I'm going to maneuver you effortlessly to your death.
Listen to me.
For your information, Kars,
I've never hated anyone before this day, but you, I hate!
You really hate me?
Then show me, JoJo.
Let's go one‐on‐one.
We'll have that fair fight you wanted to have.
Lisa Lisa is almost dead,
but not completely yet.
I left her alive.
My plan is to let her live for a while.
And why would I do that?
She's just another pawn,
a worthless little pawn I can use against you.
You utter bastard.
Hah!
Now I've tied her feet together with this rope.
And do you know why?
Why would I do such a thing as this?
This is why!
Lisa Lisa, no!
Off you go.
If she hits the ground, she'll be dead.
If you don't save her in a few seconds,
she'll be a lisa‐lisa‐shaped splatter.
Huh?
What?! JoJo!
Lisa Lisa!
Hmm? Lisa Lisa?
That Lisa Lisa?
Do you mean to say she's the baby
on the ship granny Erina told us about?
Then that means she is JoJo's...
Now that you can't move from that spot,
here's how efficient battle can be, JoJo.
I'll very calmly walk right up to you
and slice you to pieces while you can't move!
Kars, you bastard!
There's a place waiting for you in hell!
JoJo doesn't know.
He doesn't know the woman he's trying to save
is his mother.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound and
in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
Have you finished disposing of those vampires yet?
I'm taking your life at the moment of my choice.
The scarf is a gamble.
Poor little child.
Von Stroheim, you must stop!
This can't be!