Down here,
my hamon will hit you all the harder.
Underwater turquoise blue overdrive!
He did it!
Bravo.
That was amazing.
It's not over yet!
I can't believe Blueford was able to dodge
that blast of hamon. He moves so fast underwater.
He was all a blur.
My overdrive barely glanced off his forehead.
Now I know anything less than a solid punch
won't be enough to send the hamon into him.
My good lord Dio, I thank thee for this life anew
that I may duel with this stouthearted lad.
My heart would swell to bursting if still it beat.
In blood and deed, he is the stuff of heroes.
Now we will fight in our native element.
It is by mastery of our arts and strength
of our spirits that we wage this duel.
Bare your soul. Hold nothing back,
lest you not survive beyond this moment!
Even as Dio's puppet, his pride
is a force to be reckoned with,
but his knightly valor has been
twisted into a wanton love of violence.
When I best you, I'll take your head as my trophy!
It's easy to let your hair do the work.
Come. Withstand my hamon face to face like a man!
Overdrive barrage!
JoJo!
This is terrible.
Hamon can only be projected through the arms and the legs.
With his arms bound in front of him
like that, he has no way of blasting
through that infernal hair of Blueford's.
I‐i wanna help him out, but you
and me have got things even worse.
I think of Tarukus fancies a dust‐up.
His hair, it's tearing through my clothes.
Through my skin.
The more I struggle, the tighter it winds,
and it's sucking my blood away.
Bid your petty life adieu.
Behold, the coup de grâce!
I'll take your head and bathe in
a fountain of life‐giving blood!
Take this!
Water's not all that conducts hamon.
Metal silver overdrive!
What a brain.
Using the sword to hoist Blueford by his
own bleeding petard. Who thinks of that?
How my heart resonates.
I'm pulsing with heat and life.
My very blood is a symphony within me!
Sunlight yellow overdrive!
There we go. That's it. About time
we heard the welcome crackle of hamon.
When I pummeled Blueford a moment ago,
something felt different. Knowing his past
makes his present corruption all the worse.
Take heart, JoJo. He is that man no longer.
He's nothing but a zombie eager to spread his evil.
You must be the one to end him.
I am the black knight Blueford.
Strike me as thou wilt.
This pain is nothing!
He's still dangerous, mate! Look out!
Even missing an arm and scorched all to hell,
he's laying into JoJo every bit as ferociously.
What the?!
Don't just stand there! Do something!
If you don't get outta there now, it's curtains for you!
Have they both gone mad?
What are they doin', eh?
A moment ago,
you said, "this pain is nothing."
That means pain is something you can feel again.
The flowers,
they're blooming all around him.
Even now, the hamon ravages the evil
that animates Blueford's long‐dead corpse.
You see? The long‐forgotten pain came back.
Only humans know that sort of ache.
Observe, my dear Speedwagon.
His zombie body succumbs to the hamon,
but his noble soul is redeemed in the process.
I could sense the good in you.
That's why I didn't try to dodge.
You could have killed me just now,
but you stayed your hand.
Look at his face.
It's like all the rage and hatred he
had when Dio brought him back are gone.
His features are so gentle, he could be
a bloke catching up with his oldest mate.
You stood there like a statue,
ready to take the fatal blow.
Oblivion beckoned, but you put your trust in me.
Your faith in human goodness is rare.
Once I'd have railed against the pain I feel.
Now, going to my rightful end,
I cherish all that proves me human.
It gives me joy.
The embers dull within me,
but I am tranquil.
There is no bitterness left.
What irony to live yet again,
dying with thanks on my lips
for the very man who slaughters me anew.
I shall return to my one true master.
I would know the name of the warrior who bested me.
Would you kindly do me that honor?
It's Jonathan Joestar.
Sir Jonathan, I leave you this
sword, given to me by my precious queen,
and the word engraved upon it.
Luck.
But first. Let me affix my own benediction.
Pluck.
Sir Blueford.
Heh.
Go you to your rest.
Let no one doubt you have earned it, Blueford.
Why? Why did I have to strike him down to redeem his soul?
He died once before with hate in his
heart, but his spirit was still pure.
He returned not out of choice,
but dragged above by Dio's evil,
his evil and the mask's power.
I will send them both to hell before the dawn!
JoJo, he's right behind you!
Tarukus!
You villain!
That was the armor of a steadfast friend and comrade.
He died with honor and dignity.
He died like a spineless dog!
He was too clever by half,
liked winning his fights with thinking.
I just hit 'em until they fall to pieces!
What use have I got for clever?
I carry a sword as tall as a man.
None of you will get an easy death.
JoJo, nice catch.
The cliff is crumbling!
Hmm.
These dead leaves.
JoJo!
Yes, sir.
Life magnetism overdrive!
Hurry, Poco, Speedwagon! Grab on!
All human beings, whether adept at hamon or not,
constantly exude a weak magnetic field.
An overdrive can increase the power of that field.
JoJo and Zeppeli sent it into the leaves,
drawing them together into a solid sheet.
W‐wow.
Bye.
We're flying. I can't believe it.
I bet you're magicians, huh?
You'd have to be, right? How did you learn to
do all of these neat spells in the first place?
Damn good question.
I've been watching 'em do it, and I still pinch myself.
Oi, baron, what's the story?
We're not going anywhere.
How on earth did you pick up all this mumbo jumbo?
Many years ago, my travels took me to India,
where I discovered a mysterious man.
He called himself a doctor, though he was
very young and lacked all the tools of the trade.
Little did I know
he was more potent of a medic than I'd ever encountered.
He took a gangrenous limb in his hands
and healed it with light from within.
That was the day I learned of hamon.
I'd been looking for something with
which to fight the stone mask's evil,
and in hamon, I had found it.
Eager to learn, I crossed into
Tibet and up the salween river
in search of he who had taught the young healer.
His name was tonpetty.
Stranger, these eyes of mine have seen your future.
If you pursue the mysteries of hamon as my pupil,
your fate is sealed.
The day will come when this will be the death of you.
I understand.
If I must die to end this quest, so be it.
Master tonpetty's prophecy is never far from my mind,
but I cannot tell them, not even JoJo.
Baron...
So that sound, that's part of hamon doing its thing, yeah?
Hardly.
Look out! It's Tarukus!
He's insane,
leaping from that height just to give chase to his foes.
There's a goodly amount of hamon
holding these leaves together, you brute,
painful to the touch for the undead.
What's that?
That's where the knights used to train in the olden days.
Leap to safety, everyone, before
we get swatted out of the sky!
Crazy blighter.
He just slammed himself straight into the tower.
Yes, and thank your lucky stars that he did, Speedwagon.
Unlike their master, Dio's minions can't regenerate,
so that should be the last we see of that beast.
How did... he should be mincemeat.
Even in death, he has a will of iron.
How does his body endure under such punishment?
He's climbing up.
We can't destroy Dio while this monster dogs our steps.
It seems we have no other choice.
Tarukus meets his doom here and now.
JoJo, this will be perilous. Get the lad to safety within.
This door...
Something's odd about it.
Be careful.
This is where they used to train
the knights how to kill people.
They say it's full of booby traps.
Duck, JoJo! Something's coming at ya!
Oh, no!
JoJo!
Who ensnared me?
Tarukus.
Yes. Caught you good.
You're fleet of foot, little man, but
now you and me are chained to each other.
You got nowhere to run.
JoJo had wandered into the lair of the two‐headed dragon,
an ancient sparring ground and
home of the chain death‐match.
I killed 48 men here.
Taking a life's an art form, and I'm a master.
That's enough. You can't punch through it.
That door is solid iron.
Goodness. He's battered his knuckles bloody against it.
Hamon is very versatile,
but it's meant to be used as a
rapier, not as a sledgehammer.
Bricks I could beat to a powder,
but this door is too strong.
JoJo faces a darker dilemma.
That chain about his neck is more
than ripple energy can overcome.
Breaking out of that collar is impossible,
and you'll need the key to unlock it.
Too bad it's right here.
During a death match, the door to
the outside is fashioned to lock tight.
Just as I have the key to your collar,
you have the one that goes to mine.
Therefore, the only way that either
of us is going to get out of here...
Is by taking the other's head!
Overdrive!
The chain is touching the stone ceiling,
so the hamon lacks a direct path into Tarukus.
He's broken the bone in my forearm.
It's a simple thing to fix. A
little hamon, and I'm good as new.
But in order to use hamon,
I need to be free of this damnable collar.
I can't breathe.
JoJo!
Oh, no.
This is all so frightening, I think I wet myself.
This village was safe until these men arrived.
I'm in danger here. You need to get away
from all this fighting on the double, Poco.
I see a lever, baron Zeppeli.
No telling for certain, but I think
pulling on it will open this door.
Fighting Tarukus is a daunting enough task as it is,
never mind doing it fresh out of a battle with Blueford.
Come hell or high water,
we must find a way to get in there and help him.
Uhh! It's locked up tighter than a nunnery.
It's so narrow.
Try as they might, they could never squeeze through,
but...
Maybe I could.
Blast it!
We could batter this door 'til judgment day to no avail.
We'll have to use the cliffside entrance Tarukus used.
But that'll take too much time,
time that he don't got.
I know, but we've no other choice.
Always on the bleedin' sidelines.
I'm powerless.
There's nothing I can do to help.
Look at me, brat. I'm talking to you.
I said look at me.
Are you stupid or what?
He's such a little scaredy‐cat.
What a baby. He's shaking like a leaf.
Look, fellas. Look at him.
Aw, is the baby gonna cry?
Hey. Look.
Hmm?
Come on! Let's get outta here.
Sis, it's you.
Poco, really?
You're letting those boys bully you again?
They do this all the time.
Why not try standing up to them for once?
I'll bloody their noses! I will!
When? Tomorrow? In a year?
Uh, I don't know.
Poco...
What frightens you more than anything else?
I know that hurt, but you're still in one piece.
Pain's not the worst thing.
There's something far worse.
Huh?
It's growing up being too afraid to do anything.
What kind of a life would that be?
I'm sorry, sis.
It's all right, Poco.
Let's get you home and into some clean clothes.
Poco!
A window.
Oi, lad! That's brave, but goin'
in there is gonna be the end of ya!
Speedwagon, get the boy down!
A butcher like Tarukus doesn't care who he kills!
He'll crush Poco underfoot like a bug!
Come on, now! Enough of this nonsense, Poco!
Just think of what's gonna happen to
wind knights lot if these monsters win.
If that JoJo guy gets killed
in here, they'll attack us next.
What if they hurt sis?
I have to keep her safe, no matter what.
Hey, sis!
I'm standing up to them now!
Stay back! He'll kill you.
Do not interfere, you brat!
Poco!
It hurt a lot,
but I'm still in one piece, so it's fine.
I was brave, huh?
Brave as a bear, my lad.
Take heart. It's nothing that won't heal.
Get him, baron! Go!
Give that hulking bastard the what‐for.
Zeppeli?
The day will come when this will be the death of you.
Infine.
Is tonight the night that I go to my grave?
Fate is a fickle mistress,
but I cannot deny her.
Zeppeli...
Why do you sound so dire?
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound and
in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
This bloody savagery is unbelievable!
Oh, no! Tarakus!
Pathetic waste of flesh!
JoJo, take it!
Make it yours!