What the heck is this supposed to be?
You think you're funny, putting black
ink all over my spaghetti, is that right?
N... n... no, sir, not at all.
This is called al nero di seppia.
It is a classic pasta dish made
with fresh squid ink, hence the color.
Really?
It's quite delicious.
Hmm.
Say, this is delicious!
Mmm.
Mm... mm... mm.
This hotel used to be a place of class and refinement.
Now they let just anyone in here.
Signorina, accept this, a token of your beauty.
It's beautiful.
Not as much as you.
When you remove this at night, please think of me,
and we shall be together in your dreams.
Come on!
Did that mozzarella cheese‐ball
just say what I think he said?!
I didn't know eavesdropping could rot your teeth.
I shall cast an enchantment upon it,
just a little love spell,
and then you will have no
choice but to fall to my passion.
You've got to be kidding. This guy is making me sick.
And I shall spread my charm's magic
to those delicious lips of yours.
That's just ridiculous.
How could any modern woman fall for such an obvious act?
Disgusting.
I have an idea.
Hamon di seppia.
This should stick to that little
Casanova's enchanting face for a bit.
How... how did he just do that?
That... that was hamon.
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Your pardon the intrusion.
But there is a phone call from a
Mr. Speedwagon, Mr. Caesar Zeppeli.
Mamma Mia. I will be right there.
What? What the...
That spaghetti‐brained womanizer is the
Caesar Zeppeli we came all the way here to find?!
This is the Speedwagon foundation.
This complex was built 28 years ago with
funds from the ample Speedwagon fortune.
Here, all manners of science, medicine, archaeology,
and more are generously funded and exhaustively researched
for the benefit of all humankind.
But the foundation also houses a darker purpose...
One to unlock the secret of the stone masks.
The U. V. Lights are very powerful.
Please, if you don't mind.
Introduce the snake.
It was absorbed into the stone!
Santviento still isn't dead.
His body is defending itself somehow.
What if he finds some way to awaken in there?
This can't be.
We must find a way to destroy him.
The monster feeds on masked vampires.
He's immortal for all we know. What are we supposed to do?
Don't worry, Mr. Speedwagon. He can't do anything.
As long as he's under those U. V. Lights, he
will remain petrified and can pose no threat to us.
That's right.
Well, I suppose that's a relief.
There is still more research to be
done if we are to understand him fully.
See those? These pictures were taken in
the cave where we originally found Santviento.
Inspect them carefully.
The horns.
They all have different types of horns.
So if the one on the bottom is supposed
to be Santviento, then who are the others?
According to Von Stroheim,
the Germans have uncovered another pillar at an
undisclosed location somewhere on the European continent.
Is that true?
Their faces are stacked vertically in this picture.
Speaking historically,
I would theorize that this indicates
status or rank among the three pillar men.
JoJo and I are headed to Rome.
Von Stroheim told him that we must go there
in order to find the person who can help us.
And it turns out that person...
Is none other than the grandson of Will A. Zeppeli,
Caesar Zeppeli.
Tell me, where might you be from?
Would you like me to take a picture?
Perhaps one of you in the fountain?
Huh?
Boy, the birds in this country sure are friendly.
They seem much smarter than the
men here, too. Don't you think?
Knock it off, JoJo.
We didn't come all this way for nothing.
The two of you better start talking.
Mr. Speedwagon, I'm sorry, but not a chance.
My grandfather died tragically 50 years ago.
My father then took up his torch
and spent his life hunting the mask.
We Italians have the strongest familial
bonds of any culture in the world.
We are very proud of that tradition.
It is everything to us.
That's something he'll never understand.
In fact, you told me he didn't know about
his own grandfather until just recently.
A true man knows his history.
Tell me this, true man. Is your whole family this dumb?
That's not fair, Caesar.
JoJo didn't know anything, because
I kept it all a secret from him.
I don't think that's any excuse.
I heard about Straizo, and I was impressed to
find out that he fought one of the pillar men.
But I wanted to see for myself how
tough he was, so I waited at the hotel.
And I'm disappointed to say that his
hamon skills leave much to be desired.
His hamon is weak.
It's worthless.
His defeat of the pillar man was nothing but blind luck!
I won't be forced to work with this imbecile!
Caesar, just relax for a moment.
JoJo is still training with...
We're done with the niceties here.
I'm going to have to settle this with a good thrashing.
Hamon as weak as yours couldn't pluck
the petals off this delicate flower.
Oh, yeah? Well, you couldn't
even beat one of those pigeons.
Are you gonna fight me or not?
If there's any mocking to be done here,
I'll take care of it, thank you kindly.
You... bastard.
You gave this woman a hamon kiss!
Like I just said,
your weak hamon couldn't even defeat a woman. Sad.
I must not intervene here.
This will be a good lesson for JoJo.
Overcoming this will only make him stronger.
What did I tell you?
My grandfather might still be alive if
your grandfather hadn't got in his way!
I refuse to accept your kind, your pathetic blood.
That's enough. You've crossed the line now.
Stop. I've got this.
Someone as arrogant as you just couldn't
resist insulting my entire family, could you?
Like to see my maneuver sure to eliminate the pillar men?
It's a clean technique.
Behold! My hamon bubble launcher.
It's important to keep oneself clean.
I, myself, have a thin layer of
soap on my clothes at all times.
You're looking a little dirty yourself there, Joestar!
Ohh!
Well, I am impressed that you're still conscious,
but your weak little hamon couldn't even pop a bubble.
Just look at you. Your breath
is already all over the place.
Enjoy your stay, Joestar.
And next you'll say, "now I'll lift
my hamon spell, signorina. Thank you."
And now I'll lift my hamon spell, signorina. Thank you.
While that woman was throttling me,
I filled the pigeon with as much hamon
as I could and hid it away in her mouth.
Mm?
I knew you'd kiss her,
either because you had to withdraw
your hamon or just to show off.
So I was right.
Turns out that you couldn't even beat a pigeon.
What a day.
Honestly, just who does this jerk think he is?
Grandstanding like that just to sit down in a chair.
I really can't stand people like him.
If only I had a technique like his bubble launcher.
I'd be able to teach him some humility then.
I have to get stronger with my hamon,
but training is always such a hassle.
Hmm. Let's see how our little
friend handles a game of chance.
I saw that, JoJo. Deal the
cards right. Only cowards cheat.
Huh? Whatever do you...
Deal the cards properly, Joestar, or play elsewhere.
Fancy that.
Well, that didn't work.
Pathetic.
You should be ashamed that you have to
resort to cheating and gimmicks to beat me.
You really are serious about cleanliness.
This mirror is spotless.
Stop provoking me, Joestar!
Oh, I haven't even started!
Calm down!
It's been eight hours, Caesar.
Do you mind telling us what we're waiting for?
What are we waiting for?
Here's your answer.
What the hell is a German soldier doing here?
It looks like we're clear.
Just who do you think guards the pillar men?
He'll get us in there. Behave yourself.
Again with the Germans?
Germany and Italy have an alliance,
and the Germans are interested in
researching the nuances of my hamon, see?
You Englishmen are very lucky that you are
being granted access to view the pillar men.
No need to thank me. Your
appreciation's written on your face, JoJo.
Mr. Speedwagon...
Huh?
We have so many questions for you.
I hope that we can all work together
to stop the pillar men before they awake.
How is the beauty?
Huh?
Now don't be embarrassed you have a girlfriend back home.
Well. She's...
uh, actually, the truth is I'll be going
home next week so we can finally get married.
Really?
Mamma Mia! Congratulations, Mark.
I was his wingman when he picked
her up, you know. He was so nervous.
Heartwarming.
Please don't get us all killed here.
And please stop cuddling with
the wheel, if you don't mind.
I wanted to ask you, JoJo,
do you have a girlfriend back home?
I'll take that as a no.
But you're such a great catch.
Why doesn't anyone want to date you?
Perhaps they're all too busy washing their hair, eh?
Where does this pompous ass
get off talking to me like that?
Once I develop my own killer technique,
I'll show him a thing or two or three.
Look! There's something on his head.
I don't think that was there before.
Calm down. They're just rocks as long
as they're under those U. V. Lights.
No need to worry.
Now get a closer look!
Yes, sir.
The death of Von Stroheim's team
is an important lesson to us all.
Once we cut this pillar out, we'll have to seal
it so that it will never see the light of day again.
I can't tell what that dark spot is. It
looks like a hole, but it might just be a shadow.
Get a closer look.
Eh?
D... do you hear that?
His horn!
He's supposed to be petrified!
He's waking up!
Quickly! Bring out more U. V. Lamps!
Yes, sir!
Schnell!
This can't be happening!
He's blocking out the lights with the blood of my own men!
I see the world has undergone
significant changes during my slumber.
These insignificant inventions must be quite popular here.
What'd he say?!
I said your pitiful illuminations
are no match against my power.
My hands!
We're stuck together!
Wamuu!
Now is the time.
Awaken, my masters!
Somehow, this doesn't surprise me.
The famous mouth of truth
was a secret entrance all this time.
You can really feel the chill of the dead here.
Caesar, what sort of effects has your
hamon had on the sleeping pillar men?
Hamon is only useful on the living.
No reason to waste my powers on stone.
We can't learn anything if they're not alive.
Hmm.
I'm surprised you Germans don't have
more than, uh, zero guards down here.
It's a little quiet. Hello?!
Stop being foolish, JoJo.
Wait. Something's wrong.
Hmm?
He's right. There should be
guards posted all around this place.
Huh? Really?
Yaah!
Why didn't anyone tell me there were bats in here?
Gross. I stepped in bat dung!
And I just cleaned these.
Wait. Those are...
They're husks of dead soldiers.
What... what the hell happened to them?
They're all dead!
Stop where you are! Whoever did this could still be here!
We don't know what's out there!
What... what is that?
I can't believe it. They're... they're alive!
Run away, Mark!
Get out of there now!
No!
Mark!
Mark, no.
Caesar. Caesar.
What have they done?!
They just walked right through
your friend like he wasn't even there.
The pillar men have awoken with such
massive power that we barely even exist to them.
We may as well be nothing more than
a colony of ants beneath their feet.
It appears to be night outside, Wamuu.
That is correct, lord Kars.
And what shall be your bidding?
Easy.
We will be searching for the
whereabouts of the Red Stone of AJA.
The stone is the last piece we
need in order to complete the mask.
Then we will unleash its power.
Of course, master Esidisi.
However, the human world has changed
much over the years that we slumbered.
Long ago, it was the Emperor
of Rome who possessed the stone.
Unfortunately, I am certain that age has ended.
Well, then, we simply need to find
where it is the stone currently calls home.
They say the emperor cherished the stone above all things.
I believe that the humans of
today still tell stories of it.
I shall retrieve the stone for you, my master.
There's time, Wamuu.
For the moment then,
let us go outside and observe the changes
that have occurred in the human world.
Hmm.
Wamuu!
Explain your insolence.
Stay your hand, Esidisi.
I apologize, lord Kars.
Of course. It had slipped my mind
that you possess a reflexive attack against anyone
who dares to walk across the depths of your shadow.
It has been 2,000 years, after all.
I have offended you, my lord.
I will accept whatever punishment you see fit.
I simply cannot accept your apology.
Your innate fighting spirit is what makes you
a great warrior, and that is why I trust you.
The fault is my own for treading upon your darkness.
Please forgive my transgression.
You are too kind.
Rise, Wamuu.
Yes, master.
Caesar!
Kill me, please. Do it. You've got to kill me now.
I can't.
It's... it's getting so cold. Please, Caesar.
I'm... I'm so scared.
I couldn't feel anything at first,
but now, the pain.
Please, Caesar, you've got to kill me now.
Mark.
There's nothing we can do.
I can't do anything to help this poor bastard.
I feel so powerless.
I must control myself.
I feel like I'm going to explode.
Goodbye, friend.
Caesar.
Give her my love, Caesar.
I promise.
He was so young, his whole life ahead of him.
He worked hard for a living.
He loved his family dearly.
He loved his girl and his country.
He was a good person, clean‐cut, the boy next door.
And they killed him.
Now they die!
Caesar!
Don't you dare get in my way, JoJo.
I'm going to enjoy every second of this!
This is personal. I'll destroy these fiends myself!
Along the drifting cloud the
eagle searching down on the land
Catching the swirling wind, the
sailor sees the rim of the land
The eagle's dancing wings create
as weather spins out of hand
Go closer hold the land feel
partly no more than grains of sand
We stand to lose all time a
thousand answers by in our hand
Next to your deeper fears we
stand surrounded by a million years
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out and out
Oh, I'm sick and tired of all this talking.
Explain yourself. What are you trying to get at?
I knew he was spineless.
These humans know hamon.
I call that divine sandstorm.