All right, enough.
Something's going on here.
I've felt like someone's eyes have been
on me all morning watching my every move.
Why? Clearly I'm alone.
Nobody could have followed me all the way out here.
I'm out in the middle of nowhere.
But I can't shake the feeling that someone's here!
Damn my imagination.
Must be the heat playing tricks with my mind.
Well, aren't you a sharp one?
You somehow sensed my presence although I was
engaging my skills of stealth this entire time.
Even wild bats can't do that.
Why the hell are you following
me? I've got no business with you.
Oh, I'm not following.
I'm in the business of capturing, see?
Our army would like to ask you some
questions about Straizo, Joseph Joestar!
Straizo? Why would you be interested in him?
And who is "our army"?
By your accent, the cut of your face,
and your smell, I'd guess you're German.
I want to know what business a thug like
you has with either Straizo or Speedwagon.
But if you're not gonna say anything,
I don't mind having to beat some answers out of you.
You think you can take on the blade of s. S.
Commander Donovan with just your bare hands, little boy?
I'm almost insulted.
But since you insist, I'm happy to oblige!
Great, but how 'bout I give you
back your flea‐ridden magic rag?
Cactus needles.
Victory.
I really thought that you were going to give me
more of a challenge there. What happened, little boy?
Repeat after me. "I never should have challenged
your superior power, herr Donovan."
I... I never should have
challenged your... superior power.
What's that? I can't hear you.
I underestimated your etiquette.
Huh?
You really are quite the gentleman for letting me rest
right here and giving me these moments to recover safely.
What are you talking about? Recover safely?
Have you lost your mind, little boy?
Wait a sec. What's this?
What's up with this cactus?
You should take a closer look.
That cactus was my goal all along, herr Donovan.
Cacti are made up of nearly 95% water, and
they're known to be fabulous conductors of hamon.
Now then, repeat after me, herr Donovan.
"I promise to tell Joseph Joestar everything."
Okay, then.
When Speedwagon's body disappeared,
I swore to myself that I would
never give up hope, no matter what.
Turns out he was safe all along.
Man, it's nice to hear some good news for a change.
I can't wait to tell granny Erina.
She'll be so happy to hear about this.
Although, there's no way of telling how
the Germans have actually been treating him.
Regardless, I'll bring him home, and granny
Erina's smile will shine like the midday sun.
Hey, don't leave!
Look, major Von Stroheim! The
pillar's shell is starting to crack.
It's currently holding the blood of five prisoners.
We still don't know what its full capabilities are.
Feeding it any more could push it
beyond our established safety zone.
Hmm.
I'm curious how the blood was
extracted in the first place.
No, wait! I don't want to know. I can
imagine what sort of things you came up with.
Oh, Speedwagon.
No need to look so pale.
I told you from the start there was nothing to fear.
Stop being so arrogant! You've
no idea what he's capable of!
Relax, old man.
That test chamber is impenetrable.
It has iron walls nearly 20 inches thick.
It's equipped with flamethrowers, machine
guns, und explosives if we need them.
I shouldn't be surprised that all of your courage
doesn't even add up to what I have in my little finger.
You coward!
Want to know what I think, Speedwagon?
I think that thing is simply a statue of
petrified caveman bones that's wasting my time!
Major! He's erupting!
Hmm?
It's blood!
That blood it took in is spraying out everywhere!
I can't see a thing!
Activate the sprinkler system!
His outer layer is transforming.
It looks like it's morphing into flesh.
He's trying to move.
I... I think he's alive!
Then, he'll need a name,
something better than "the pillar man."
As his new godfather, I suppose this task falls onto me.
Let me see.
I'll name him after the Mexican
winds. He shall be known as Santviento.
Look. He's trying to stand.
Rise before us.
Rise up, und show us what you are made of...
Santviento!
Hmm?
You see that?
Santviento might have a future
doing comedy in the cabaret.
The ultimate organism? More like the ultimate idiot.
What do you think there, Speedwagon?
He's got the brains of a feral animal.
He's trying to smell his way around.
He's really just a primitive man.
This is a farce.
Regardless, let's just move
on und assume he made the masks.
You there, start the experiment.
Somebody open the door to the next chamber.
Yes, sir!
What... what's that supposed to be?
A prisoner.
Well, a prisoner with a mask, actually.
Is... is that a vampire?
Only a few days ago, that thing was a feeble,
toothless old man knocking on death's door.
We still haven't fed him today, so he must be thirsty.
I think he'll go straight for the attack.
Who will win?
I can hardly wait.
What? That's all? He didn't even put up a fight.
He's an ordinary man after all.
We don't have any other subjects
for this test, major Von Stroheim.
We planted explosives in the
prisoner's head for this exact situation.
Just give us the word, and
we'll activate them immediately.
Major?
Fine.
Wait! Stop!
I rescind the order!
His jaw, look.
What's happening there with his jaw?
His hands, his arms.
What's going on with his arms?
I'd given him up for dead in the beginning, but
look, Santviento is somehow absorbing the prisoner.
He's pulling him straight into his body.
He's devouring him!
What a marvelous creature.
The masked man was no more than fodder for him.
Santviento feeds with his entire
body, so... so nothing is lost.
He can absorb every bit of his
prey's life force down to the last drop.
He ate him!
He actually ate the masked man.
How is that even possible?!
Und now look! He's... he's grown something.
Get a grip.
As long as he's still in that chamber, he can't hurt you.
He just gained a little weight
after his feeding. That's all it is.
His... his intelligence?
And what about his intelligence?
What level of thought is he capable of?
Huh?
Ma... major Von stro... Stroheim.
What?!
But how did he...
He said... how did he know my name?
He's not even supposed to be
able to hear anything from in there!
There it is.
According to my dangling cactus pal Donovan,
the underground facility I'm looking
for is hidden down there somewhere.
If he was telling the truth, Speedwagon should be inside.
So now how am I supposed to get in there?
Vegetables, canned goods, meat, ham, eggs.
Looks like you've got a nice
basket of food there, all right.
Now then, it's time for the frisking.
Aw, come on now. Stop making that
face. You can give me a little smile.
Lift up your skirts, and smile.
Hmm.
You're cleared to go. Next!
All I've got under my skirt is more Tequila, big boy.
Is it all right to bring that through, too?
Hmm?
Hands up in the air!
Any funny moves, and we shoot you dead!
What? Put your guns down. I haven't done anything.
That's a funny move there.
Fire.
No! Please don't shoot! I'm not
moving, and I've got my hands in the air!
All right. Damn. You Germans are so smart.
You saw through my disguise almost immediately.
Are you crazy?
Of course we saw through that thing.
You're disgusting.
Even my big sister isn't as ugly as you, and
we used her to plow the fields. She was an ox.
You should've spent more time in front
of the mirror this morning, big sissy!
What was that?
Hamon!
Oh, jeez.
Well, that was disappointingly easy.
If I can get this thing to fit,
this uniform should work nicely.
What... what's going on?
I... I don't know.
You don't know? Weren't you watching?
Major Von Stroheim, I only looked away for a moment.
Surely you understand.
I mean, you were here as well, right?
Everybody here was watching.
It just happens that nobody saw anything.
Put that coffee down!
It... it was only for a moment.
I took my eyes off him for just a few seconds.
That's all. I swear.
It makes no sense. I mean, my vision is perfect, we
all have a clear view, but we don't know what happened!
This is unbelievable!
The chamber is completely sealed,
und still the subject managed to escape!
None of the walls show any sign of damage.
I don't care what you saw. I want him found.
Keep in mind that he may have concealed
himself somewhere inside the chamber.
Simply cut off the oxygen supply in there.
He'll turn up when he finds out he can't breathe.
The recorded film is now ready
for your viewing, major Von Stroheim.
What are you waiting for? Set it up.
Yes, sir.
Roll the film.
See that? He's running towards the wall.
Ja, but why?
Was ist los?
He's squeezing himself into the ventilation ducts!
Those slats are less than two inches tall.
How the hell could anyone possibly stuff
an entire body through a gap that small?!
Incredible.
He didn't simply dislocate his joints.
He somehow disassembled his entire skeleton so
that he could completely alter his shape at will.
You know what this means.
He is now wandering around freely
somewhere in your base's ventilation system.
Santviento already knew your name somehow,
major Von Stroheim, and I think I might know how.
The only way that would be possible is
if he heard your name through the vents.
The vents lead directly into this room?
You, soldier, turn around, and
move away from that vent immediately.
Go, you idiot!
Uh...
It's him, it's Santviento!
What's happening to me?
Major Von Stroheim!
What's happening?! Where did everybody go?!
And why is it so dark in here?! Why can't I see anything?!
Somebody, please help me! I
can't see! What's he doing to me?!
Santviento is trying to take
control of that soldier's body.
Someone, anyone, please don't leave me alone!
You can't abandon me. Don't
leave me here with him inside...
Well, well,
I don't fully understand what's happening here, but
I feel like I'm practically bursting with new life.
What a catastrophe.
If this thing escapes, I'll be known for
creating the fatherland's most powerful enemy.
We must destroy him.
At this point, it's either him or us.
Very well! Take him out! Open fire,
and shred that monster to pieces!
Ooh. Heh.
Stop. That tickles.
He's still alive!
Impossible!
The bullets, they have no effect on him.
He's an abomination.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Why is he pointing at us?
Nobody move.
Don't you see he's imitating one of your machine guns?
Look. He's just copying what he's seeing.
So when he spoke earlier, he only said my name,
but did not understand it,
which means he's not intelligent.
He just apes what he sees,
und that gives me a great idea.
If he's only capable of acting like a monkey, we
should start preparations for using him like one.
You...
Which one of you...
Was fool enough to disturb my slumber?
He... he spoke.
He's clearly capable of higher thought.
I'd bet he possesses a great intelligence.
He just learned our language.
Don't you understand that he did that in almost no time?
Die.
What the...
That must have been one of our bullets.
He's shooting at us. He's gonna kill us all!
Let's go, old man.
We better get you to safety.
There's no telling how many more bullets
that monster might have inside of him.
Just leave me. The last thing I need
right now is help from a German flunky.
What a pain.
You never change.
I'm glad to see that you're
still just as stubborn as ever.
S... somebody do something! Open fire!
No! Stay away!
Pardon me. I'll need a bit of your hair.
Just a small handful or two.
What do you think you're doing?! Let me go!
The more you fight, the more it'll hurt.
You're assaulting a superior officer! Ow!
Who are you?
I know that demeanor, but it couldn't be.
I call this one, the old hamon hair attack!
But that means... that means you're...
Joseph Joestar!
Barrier up!
You're gonna lose your hair if
you're not careful, Mr. German army man.
That felt like sandpaper.
You should consider investing in a decent moisturizer.
But how long have you been here, Joseph?
Eh, just got here.
H... hair.
Sorry I took so long.
I'd have been here sooner if i'd
known what kind of party was going on.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound and
in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
he's using his advanced intellect to learn everything.
Work with me here. Make some love to the camera.
You lowly primitive.