This senior gentleman seems familiar.
We definitely know that upright bearing and that scar.
It's good to see you again, Speedwagon.
I understand you're an American oil tycoon now.
That's a bit exaggerated.
You look as young as ever, Straizo.
Hard to believe we're the same age.
Hamon energy is life energy, right? I envy you.
It has been half a century since
Jonathan Joestar made his sacrifice.
Straizo has succeeded master tonpetty,
while Speedwagon has had success building a fortune.
Together, they're headed for Mexico to see something.
This something was discovered by a
speedwagon‐funded exploration team.
What's more is that it's a secret
known only to these select few.
I tell you, Straizo, once you lay eyes on this,
I believe no, I am certain you'll feel a chill.
It's frightful enough to make even
your disciplined hair stand on end.
I find it even worse than the terror we
faced 50 years ago when we all battled with Dio.
I can't believe how large this space is.
And this is the reason we came here.
What? It can't be!
A stone mask!
And there are so many of them!
It was in the fall of 1938.
I was doing my job, just like I
always did, eyes peeled for a mark.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Huh?
You really never heard of this fine beverage?
All right. By your accent, I'd say you're in from England.
Tourist, huh?
No kiddin'?
You're gonna make the big city your home?
Well, if you want a drink, you're
gonna have to lay down some shekels.
Cash is the king around here.
The nerve of him!
You're not gonna let that mook steal your wallet.
Get after him.
Hah!
What a patsy. That was easy as pie.
Hey‐a, Smokey.
Looks like I finally caught you red‐handed, ya punk.
What are ya doin' on my beat, you trash?
I'm gonna make sure they lock you up for 20 years.
Take it easy. Please, sir.
I only pinched a wallet.
I hate bottom feeders like you preyin' on the public.
But see, I'm nice. I'll do you a solid.
I'm gonna let you bring me $20 every week,
also half of everything you glom.
Hello.
Hmm?
Hey, it's the pigeon what got his wallet lifted.
This is evidence, so I'm gonna be keepin' it.
Well, now, how shall I put this?
Here is what happened.
There actually is no crime since
that wallet was a gift, constable.
Hmm?
Eh?
For some reason, this six‐and‐a‐half‐foot
giant of an Englishman was covering for me.
So then, sir,
would you please return both wallet and boy?
What'd you just say?
As I said, it was a gift.
He and I are good friends.
Let him go, please.
Uh‐huh.
A good friend, eh?
Why don't you tell me what your good friend's name is?
Hmm...
What's the matter, limey?
You want to see what a New York pokey is like? Huh?
Here's a present for you.
That's curious.
Help me understand. Why would you do something like that?
It's just such an unsavory thing to do.
There is no reason!
I do what I like whenever I feel like it, you fool!
But if someone wipes a booger on
your face, it probably means that...
You've made the wrong move, you stupid pig!
You were shot resisting arrest!
Please, try to shoot me,
but I am warning you right now,
before you can pull the trigger,
I will have broken your finger like a rotten matchstick.
Not from over there!
I'll blow your damn brains out!
Suddenly his body started to give off some sort of glow.
It was just incredible.
The soda cap blew off and flew as fast as a bullet
straight over to snap the cop's finger.
I gave in to my temper again.
Crap. I'm in for it.
Oh, granny Erina's going to be furious.
He beat down two cops, but is scared of his grandma?
I'll just explain.
Granny Erina will understand if I explain, won't she?
All right. Mr. Pickpocket, what
say we high‐tail it on out of here?
He didn't know exactly how he had
launched the bottle cap with such force.
He said he could always do things like that.
Apparently his grandpa could do the same kind of things,
but he died at a young age.
His dad, who died in the war,
didn't have any talents like that.
His mom was gone, too.
I really owe you big time.
Everyone calls me Smokey, and i'd
sure like it if you'd tell me your name.
It's Joestar,
Joseph Joestar.
My friends call me JoJo.
What is this?
Who is that a carving of on that pillar?
That's not a carving.
He has amino acids, proteins, and cells,
and though it's faint, he has body heat and a pulse.
We are looking at a living man!
Straizo, understand,
who he is, how long he has been there,
how he got there in the first place,
what the masks are for, none of that matters.
We are here for one purpose only.
I brought you because of your hamon ability,
so you can use it to utterly destroy him
while he slumbers in this stone.
And Joseph Joestar?
What?
Joseph Joestar, how is he doing?
I hear he has hamon ability and saved your life once.
Wh‐why bring up JoJo now?
As I recall, he was but 13 years of age at the time.
Yes, quite young.
Your plane was hijacked by criminals
who wanted to hold you for ransom.
Hey, kid, you can't stay back here, you know.
Get up front!
You're hijacking the plane and
kidnapping Speedwagon, correct?
I am only a bystander.
This is his problem.
I'm just going to read my story.
Do your business, and just leave me out of it.
Wrong answer, punk!
Now move!
JoJo.
Not good.
That suit was a gift from Erina.
This'll set him off for sure.
He's got no sense of self‐restraint.
Control yourself, JoJo!
You fellows did know there was the possibility
of a crash if you hijacked this plane, did you not?
Is that hamon? Oh, no.
What did that crazy kid do?!
We're gonna crash!
Grab the controls!
I can't fly, idiot.
Here. Get the pilot ready. We're going to jump.
Why can't you ever just think things through, JoJo?
I do in fact, a great deal,
mostly about how to best keep you and granny Erina safe.
You two are the only family that I've got.
He may have his grandfather's face,
but he's far from being a gentleman.
That was the day I discovered
that Joseph was able to use hamon.
So young Joseph inherited the ability to
control hamon from his grandfather Jonathan?
Yes, but why are you speaking of him now?
What the hell?!
I just took the lives of all these men,
and when you lose your life,
Jonathan's grandson will know grief and anger and hate.
He will develop a tremendous hatred for me.
No! Straizo!
Straizo...
Have you lost your senses?
I haven't.
In fact, my thinking is extremely clear.
I chose hamon to forge my body
into something pure and strong,
but as I trained, the aging of my
flesh became painfully clear to me.
Hamon provides only a small
advantage over ordinary people.
It cannot guard against the process of aging.
In the battle we fought so many
years ago, I secretly admired Dio.
He was powerful.
He was beautiful.
He was immortal.
I coveted the power granted by the stone
mask. I didn't care who got in the way.
You're a twisted traitor, Straizo.
Your blood will now bring me immortality.
With you gone, the only ones to know of
the mask will be Erina and Joseph Joestar,
and once I have disposed of them,
I shall learn more of the mask than Dio ever could.
No, don't do it.
The knowledge you're seeking
could have terrible consequences.
Jo...jo.
Erina...
Hey, you! Why don't ya get a
clue what you're doin', dumb‐ass?
Pull your head out of your butt, and see where you are!
Now get the hell out of my way!
Hello there.
What? Didn't hear that. I can't make it out.
Would you mind repeating all that?
I'd like to know what it was you meant to say,
in case I have to pound you.
JoJo.
What is it you're doing there?
Uh, granny Erina.
I asked what you're doing with that man.
Uh, well, you see...
This man is...
A taxi!
This way, you don't have to walk so far.
Thank you, JoJo. You're such a thoughtful boy.
Climb in, Smokey. We're going for a ride.
The Joestar family,
reduced to a grandmother and her grandson.
Over time, I would hear bits of their past.
Granny, really.
Speedwagon sent for us, and we came all
the way to New York simply because he asked,
but now we find he's not even here?
I think his behavior is quite rude.
I'm sure that the oil business requires much of his time.
Hmm.
Say, granny...
Hmm?
I'm curious.
Was Speedwagon really grandpa's best friend?
Is that all it was? Come on now.
What are you implying?
Well, let's see. He was never married, was he?
And you yourself are a widow.
Well, it leads me to wonder if simple friendship
was the only relationship that was going on there.
You rogue, you!
Sorry. Ow! I was wrong.
Ow! Forgive me. Aah!
I know Speedwagon is loyal. Ow!
Agh! Ow!
The Joestars tended to be short‐lived.
Granny Erina lost her husband in an accident at sea.
She was pregnant with a son at the time.
When he grew up,
he married a girl who had also survived the wreck.
They were JoJo's parents,
later claimed by war and disease.
Granny Erina was a gentle and giving woman,
even to punks like me or anybody else.
Maybe it was because she lived with loneliness.
JoJo was the same.
This time, however, his basic
kindness got him into trouble...
...thanks to me.
Hey, waiter. Waiter!
Yes, sir?
Who decided that stinkin' animal
could be allowed in here, huh?
Huh?!
His smell is ruinin' my appetite.
That kind shouldn't be allowed in a place like this.
I understand, sir,
but there is a policy handed down by management.
As long as the check is paid in full,
we happily serve anyone.
What was that?
You'll happily let beasts like
that do their grazing in here? Huh?
Uh, guess I'll just be on my way.
JoJo.
You heard him. Come on.
You're not going to tell me to stop, are you?
No. People are entitled to their opinions.
But this misbegotten oaf has
given public insult to our friend.
Be mindful of the other guests
now, but teach him a lesson.
Hmm.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Well, now, boy, lookin' to fight?
Let me help.
If the brass knuckles are what you're looking for,
you are not going to find them inside of your coat.
You might want to check your back pocket instead.
Wha?
What?
Eh? No way.
Eh?
Next you'll say, "you bastard, how could
you have possibly known where they were?"
You bastard, how could you
possibly have known where they were?
Huh?!
By the visible abrasions that are on your right hand,
it's obvious that you do your
fighting using brass knuckles.
You've no wounds, so the the
blood on your shirt is not from you.
Therefore,
you've just come from a fight.
Since the blood is on your shirt
and not that pink horror of a coat,
it was taken off prior to the fight.
And then after you had completed your assault,
the knuckles came off, and that's when you proceeded
to stow them away in your back pocket.
For my next glimpse into the future,
you will now say, "so what, you little punk?"
Yeah, so what, you little punk?
And now you're gonna get it.
I got ya!
You like that, huh?
That'll teach you a lesson.
Sorry. You missed.
What have you been punching?
I wasn't the one you were pummeling so happily.
Oh, my god!
I can predict and counter anything
your tiny brain is able to come up with.
Do you understand that now, you simpleton?
Please, forgive the behavior of my underling, madam.
You're Erina Joestar, aren't you?
I've worked on a lot of business
deals with your Mr. Speedwagon, you see.
He told me some stories about you when
him and me were in London a while back.
I'm glad to meet you.
I heard a little something through the grapevine.
It hasn't made it into the
papers yet, but you should know.
It seems that Mr. Speedwagon has been murdered.
Are you sure?
Rumor is the cat who did it was some sort of Tibetan monk.
Some sort of monk? Could it be Straizo?
All they're saying is that the bodies of Speedwagon
and his team washed up along a
riverbank somewhere down in Mexico.
It's a genuine mystery.
Nobody has any idea why they were killed
or where the monk might have gone to afterward.
Actually, I think I might know.
Perhaps.
Speedwagon said something a long time ago.
It involved Dio
and the horrible stone mask that changed him.
JoJo, that guy is a mafia man.
You can't trust what he tells you.
He's trying to pull something!
Believe whatever you want to, kid.
Hold on.
Try your breast pocket if you're after your lighter.
Eh?
Anyway, thanks for the warning, Smokey.
But I think I believe what this man is telling us.
These fellows are only motivated by money.
Clearly information like that is valuable to
his organization, so I'm inclined to listen to him.
However...
As true as that may be, you don't simply waltz over here
and then just blurt out awful news to granny Erina.
Don't you see how badly upset
you've made her with this news?
You are very thoughtless!
It was 50 years ago,
and still those events haunt us.
Don't be frightened. I'm here,
and I'll protect you.
You mustn't, Joseph.
I'm concerned for you.
I don't want you snared by evil from a half‐century ago.
I'll be fine, granny.
If this is my fate, I accept it fully.
At the time,
I didn't understand what was going on,
but these two had an unimaginable history.
Hey, Smokey.
Hmm? What's going on, JoJo?
Look at this here.
See what they're saying?
What is it?
Do you think this is true?
Can girls really make them bigger? Whoo‐hoo.
Let's see. "Go from an aa cup to a c cup."
Hah! Right. Just a bunch of snake oil.
Don't buy into it.
Come again?
I think $1.25 a pair is too much.
Hmm.
Uh, no.
Yes, but
I say...
You look rather familiar to me, yet somehow different.
Please tell me, have we possibly met somewhere before?
And why isn't your breath visible? It's so cold tonight.
And if my eyes aren't deceiving me,
I think I caught a glimpse of
fangs in your mouth just now.
Was I seeing things?
Don't trifle with me. I warn you.
Heh.
Even if it is in plain sight on this city street, JoJo,
I'll take your life long before you ever become a danger.
Or perhaps not.
I knew the man was crazy,
but not that crazy!
Right out in public? Incredible!
Where did he even get the Tommy gun?!
Why shoot up the whole city?!
Yes, I was awaiting you, Straizo.
That was on behalf of Speedwagon,
but I don't think you'll go down so easily.
Our war has begun.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound
and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over, we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see I'll be there with you
Straizo is indeed a vampire.
Now you're mine!
German medicine is the greatest
thing in the world, don't you think?
You don't know the forces you're playing with!
Give my best to Speedwagon in hell!