Seven years later, in 1888...
Jack the Ripper stalked the streets
of London, murdering women in the night
and holding the entire city in his thrall.
However, he was nothing compared to the horror
that the feud between JoJo and Dio
would unleash upon the world.
Interception!
The ball is plucked out of the air
by our hero, Jonathan Joestar!
Joestar, a gentle giant at 195 centimeters,
sprints for the try zone with a spirited roar!
Can he win this, the last game of his university career?
He's tackled from behind!
Wait! He's still standing tall.
Two more fly in.
It's three on one out there!
Huh?
Eh?
Incredible!
He's still making for the try line,
undaunted by the men who dog his steps.
What power. What determination. He's Hercules reborn.
Another tackle!
Oh, the weight's too much for him!
He flings it away, and...
Yes! There's the catch.
The ball lands safe in the hands of Dio Brando.
It's still anyone's game!
Can he make it?
He dodges one and another!
He's done it!
There's nothing left between Dio and the
try line, and still he gives it his all.
Yes!
They did it!
On the last play, they snatched
victory out of the jaws of defeat.
What teamwork. When JoJo and Dio work together,
there's nothing they can't do.
Hell of a pass, JoJo.
All for naught if you hadn't run it in like you did.
Watching you drag those defenders,
I couldn't just let you down.
Having finished his studies, Dio is
set to graduate with top marks in law.
JoJo, meanwhile, has set the faculty
afire with his bold thesis on archeology.
On and off the field, these two young men are giants.
They're the pride of our school.
JoJo, I think we should tell our
father about this victory of ours at once.
It's been seven years now since my
father welcomed Dio into our home,
seven long years.
I smile and treat him as a brother,
but in my heart, nothing could be further from the truth.
He's nothing if not affable and smart as a whip...
But I just can't forgive him for his early villainies.
Dio, mightn't you give us a quote
about your friendship with JoJo?
You seem quite close.
Write about the team, all of us.
Come on. Tell us how close you are.
Hmm. Should I?
Heh.
Friendship, huh?
The truth is I despise this grinning imbecile.
I've spent seven years making
nice to that Joestar brat.
But now that I am of age,
I shall bring my plans to fruition.
At long last, the Joestar fortune will be mine,
and devil take anyone who tries to stop me.
Father, how are you feeling today?
But for this cough, much improved over yesterday.
The doctors say I should be in the hospital.
Why? I fear it would do you no good.
Hospitals only care about profit.
They'd measure you for a shroud ere they saw you cured.
Hmm. Then here I shall remain.
The comforts of home are curative, like as not.
My chest doesn't pain me so,
and the swelling has gone down.
I'm on the mend.
It was just a cold.
Why has it worsened so?
I heard tell of your victory.
Stunning bit of teamwork.
Someone told you about it?
I got word straightaway from an old college chum.
Whoever he is, he's fast.
I'm glad he wasn't on our
opponents' team, or we could have lost.
I'm proud of you, lads.
You both turned out so well.
Providence is too kind.
Dio, I'm so glad you've thrived.
Pursue your ambitions, whatever they may be.
I will lend you aid in any way I can, my son.
You rescued me from calamity.
Already my debt is more than I can ever repay.
You do me too much honor.
This secret is mine alone.
I can't imagine for what purpose this
mask may have been fashioned or by whom.
But it belonged to my mother,
and so having it near is a
comfort, strange as that may seem.
When I finally outwit this sphinx of a mask,
it will be the talk of the archeological world.
My goodness!
Many thanks to you, master Dio.
The years betray me.
Climbing the stairs is much harder than it was before.
This letter, having read it, all has been made clear.
Dio...
I think he's...
Dio!
Wait. That's...
That's father's medicine.
He's due for his next dosage.
All this time, you're the one
who's been bringing it to him.
Yes. What of it?
This letter, your father sent it to mine.
Guess what it says.
"Your lordship, sickness has laid me right low.
"It's the end of me, whatever it is.
"My chest hurts, "my fingers're all swollen up,
and I can't breathe, but for all this coughing."
Those are the same symptoms as father's, blow for blow!
No way is this mere coincidence.
Dio!
What are you trying to say, JoJo?
I'm having a doctor look at this powder.
JoJo, if you think I would poison father,
then from this day forward, you and I...
Are friends no more!
Try as I might, I can't look Dio in the eye.
It's because I lack proof.
All I have to go on are my suspicions.
Now, then, if you put that medicine back on the tray,
I'll be willing to forget about your lapse in judgment.
Dio, there's only one way
you're going to convince me.
Swear to me that the contents of this are safe.
Do it in Dario's name.
Swear to me on Dario's honor as a gentleman.
Do that, and I'll never bring up this moment again.
If my hunch proves true, his father's honor
is the one lie that will catch in his throat.
Say it! What are you waiting for?
I s‐swear...
How can I swear on the honor
of a man who didn't have any?!
He deserved to die!
How's that for the truth, JoJo?!
You just gave me all the proof I needed, Dio.
At hearing his name, you lashed out.
I don't know what he could have done that moved you
to such murderous rage, but murder him, you surely did.
You hurt father. Never again, Dio.
Damn your eyes.
Of course. You've been planning
to murder him for years now.
I knew it. I knew that you were playing false with us.
But now your villainy is over.
Once I've learned what this is, i'm
taking it to the police straightaway.
Damn it.
Their fortune was within my grasp.
Was it fate that JoJo found out when he did?
No. It was that letter.
He vexes me even now.
You're weak, just like your mother!
He drove her to an early grave.
Knowing that cur's blood flows through my veins,
it's enough to drive me mad!
Sir Joestar lives for now.
I'll be back from London in a few days, father.
'Til then, accept medicine only from
the hands of these doctors and no one else.
Master JoJo said he doesn't want me to bring it up?
Yes. We will do as JoJo has instructed us.
His reasons are a mystery to me,
but I trust the boy with my life.
Thank you, father.
His illness is getting worse.
If it is a poison, he may need an antidote.
Whatever you may learn in London about the poison,
I'll see you take the truth of it to your grave.
Your death will be the perfect crime.
Seven years ago, this mask reacted to my blood.
The spikes hidden within will
make short work of JoJo's brain.
His injuries will be so unique,
there'll be nothing at all to tie it back to me.
JoJo, your curiosity will lead to your destruction.
Whoa. Whoa.
The university couldn't identify the so‐called medicine,
though they did speculate that
it was a compound from the orient.
Therefore...
Young master, that stretch of road there is ogre street,
the most dangerous alleyway in all of London.
Yes, I know, but this is the one place
I will be able to find what I came for.
You're more than welcome to leave.
Hmm?
Dio grew up in London.
Where else in England could he have acquired such a toxin?
I shall have my evidence... and father's antidote.
Another dead end.
That cat... it was eating a puppy.
You do the honors, tattoo.
Right!
Use that shiv of yours to slice him open.
I want his guts for garters!
Ogre street. It is aptly named.
Check out this idiot! He grabbed my blade!
In all my days, I've never seen the like.
Ha ha ha! Stuck, ain't ya?
One quick yank of the knife, and they'll be
picking your fingers out of the snow for a fortnight.
Try it, then.
The moment you pull, my foot will kick out at
your groin with all the force of a sledgehammer.
I'm willing to see our transaction through.
Are you, sirrah?
I'm fighting to protect my
family from those who wish it harm.
I doubt very much that your resolve is equal to mine.
That's quite enough.
Now tell me, one of you, where
can I find an Asian apothecary?
Tough talk.
If you're looking to lose body parts, do stick around.
Observe.
I'll mince ya right finely with a tip of the hat.
And now, we dance.
I have to find that apothecary, no matter the cost.
Don't tell me this here's your first proper dust‐up.
If you mean to block like that,
it'll be your last one, too.
Ha ha!
Cut ya straight to the bone, looks like.
Granted, I didn't think you'd hoof the shiv at
me like that, but my chapeau still hit its mark.
Now I know why he weren't defending himself better.
Fingers, hands, legs, he don't
care one whit what he loses.
It's as if his resolve runs deeper than pain or fear.
I took the lad for an easy mark.
Guess I've been right disabused of that notion.
What? JoJo went to ogre street on his own?
I told him it was perilous.
Keep this to yourself. Sir Joestar is still unwell.
Yes, sir.
I guess I won't need to use the mask after all.
There, alone? His fate is sealed.
That's enough, lads!
I won't let a single one of ya
lay a finger on that gentleman there.
But why?
Tell me something.
Strong as a bull, you are. It's plain to see.
You coulda stove my head in with that foot of yours,
but you went easy on me, didn't you?
I came here for the sake of my father.
You have a family, people who expect
you to return from this dark business.
It is not my place to cause them grief.
He means it, don't he?
How'd this fella survive so long?
Wait.
He spared my mates' lives, just like he did mine.
I like the cut of his jib. Sure, he's naive,
but he's a gentleman through an' through, this one.
I wanna know the name of him who spared me.
Jonathan Joestar.
Well, pleased to make your acquaintance.
If it's Asian concoctions
you're looking for, mind your back.
That druggist is one sly customer.
Sir Joestar, JoJo's been gone three days.
Whatever his errand, he'll accomplish it.
Heh. Where have the years gone, I wonder?
He's grown into a fine man.
I cannot help but wonder if I
was too hard on the boy growing up.
I'm sure JoJo's laying dead in some alley by now.
Did he find the apothecary?
Look at me. Swilling it down.
Nothing but a drunken fool, just like my bastard father.
Damn it!
Watch yourself!
Or have you no respect for your elders, boy?
Look at the baby toddling around past bedtime,
sucking on a bottle like it was his mother's teat.
Look at the man when he's talking.
Didn't your old man teach you right?
My god.
Just for that, I'm gonna take your face clean off ya.
Oh. Your threat has me quaking
in my boots, you old guttersnipe.
How will I escape this moment of mortal peril?
How about... we use this?
It's meant for JoJo, but
you'll make a fine guinea pig.
Just die already!
Eh?
Let's see what you can do!
W‐what is that light?
All of that spectacle for nothing?
Useless.
That was boring.
I expected more from you, mask.
Impossible.
He's alive.
That face. Those teeth.
No!
What incredible strength.
Even now, he advances.
But his hand... does the pain mean nothing?
He shattered my shoulder with but a glancing blow.
The river. I must jump in.
It's odd.
I was drinking through the night,
but suddenly I got such a brutal thirst.
My blood, he's draining it.
What the...
So this is the secret of the mask.
I'm dying.
No! I had such plans!
Must my last sight on earth be this damnable sunrise?!
The sun destroyed him.
What's the meaning of this?
Why's it so bloody dark?
JoJo.
You're a poisoner, Dio Brando.
I have all the proof I require and then some.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
The music dance and sing
they make the children really ring
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through the sound
and in and out the valley in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over, we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before, my love, you'll see
I'll be there with you
JoJo, I've been a devil, but grant me this one wish.
This fellow reeks of brimstone and blood.
You see, I am about to become so much more!
Dio!