With the help of Caesar's bandana,
JoJo barely managed to defeat Wamuu.
Then it was Kars's turn to face
Lisa Lisa in their one‐on‐one combat.
Suddenly Von Stroheim showed up to battle the vampires,
along with Speedwagon and Smokey.
In a cowardly turn, Kars used
a double to deceive Lisa Lisa.
Then he literally stabbed her in
the back to use as a pawn against JoJo.
JoJo and Lisa Lisa are in the
greatest peril of their lives.
Kars, you bastard!
There's a place waiting for you in hell!
JoJo doesn't know.
He doesn't know the woman he's trying to save
is his mother.
You don't want to let go of that, JoJo.
It's a forest of crystal spikes
down there. She would die horribly.
Kars!
You have lived for far too long.
Your soul's decayed.
It's like a pumpkin left to rot out in a dead field.
Even flies avoid it.
Yes, grumble at me.
Shout your lungs out. Heave your insults at me,
for as long as you're holding on to that
rope, my friend, that's about all you can do.
JoJo! Lisa Lisa!
He can't follow what's really going on.
He doesn't realize that's his mother he's holding.
Mr. Speedwagon, we need to tell JoJo.
Not yet.
But why not?!
It's not the proper time.
Von Stroheim!
Have you finished disposing of those vampires yet?!
We must help JoJo.
Ja, right.
You think I just have to wave my
magic flashlight und then it's all done?!
Out of sight und out of mind!
Von Stroheim has got his hands full right now.
JoJo.
Careful now.
That rope looks like it's starting to slip a little.
Hmm?
As long as you're holding on so tightly to that rope,
your clumsy feet have limited reach.
Oh, no. His kick did make it
to Kars, but there was no hamon.
We're in real trouble.
You poor boy, it looks like you're running out of hamon.
But it is possible you might have enough left
to make one last‐ditch attack on me.
I'll walk up there,
and then I'm going to take your life as easily as if
I were plucking a little flower along a garden pathway.
Kars.
Mmm?
Maybe there is enough left in me,
enough hamon for one last desperate attack.
To be honest, even I don't know.
Hmm?
But either way, I've devised a cunning plan.
I guarantee it's something to make you choke.
How badly do you want to know what it is?
'Cause I'm not telling!
Hey.
I can see that you've stopped
tying those ropes together now.
Hmm?
You see this match?
What do you think I'm going to be doing with this fire?
Humph.
Huh? What on earth is JoJo thinking?
He set his scarf on fire.
Before this flame has a chance to burn me,
I'm going to find a way to use whatever
I can to send you straight to hell.
The scarf is a gamble,
something to motivate me,
a little pain to help me find a way.
JoJo, come on now.
You can't fool me.
That's just an act of desperation!
Don't toy with me.
You're just dodging around for
a chance to catch your breath.
It's no matter.
I'm taking your life at the moment of my choice,
I'm tired of dealing with your silly antics.
Oh, come on. I need to breathe.
So what if I look silly doing it?
JoJo, look.
Clearly I can sever Lisa Lisa's
rope with just a flick of my wrist,
and if you dodge me again, that is exactly what I will do.
What do you think?
Should I press just a little harder?
It's so easy.
Is that what you want?
Don't do it!
You ran away before.
Now come toward me slowly.
Heh. Or you could stay where you are
and watch as I cut through the line.
The coward.
So, what then?
Is your life more precious than
that of the woman dangling down there?
Hah!
Here's my choice!
I don't know what you think you're
doing, but when I cut this line,
you will both be impaled on the crystal spikes below.
You fool!
JoJo!
Lisa Lisa!
Heh. Idiot.
Two birds with one cut.
Huh?
What?!
But he...
This rope, it's connected to JoJo.
When did he make this happen?
He didn't have enough time to...
Oh.
When he first kicked at me,
he allowed himself to be cut along with the rope.
And then when he ignited that damned match,
he secretly tied his leg to the rope on Lisa Lisa.
I see it now.
He needed some kind of distraction.
That's when he set his scarf on fire.
And then to tie the lines together, he maneuvered me
into doing his work for him by cutting Lisa Lisa's rope.
That manipulating cheat.
Now you're the one saving both me and Lisa Lisa.
You deceived me, JoJo!
How odd that I should hear you complaining about trickery.
You enjoy deceiving others, but
now the shoe's on the other foot.
You may have lived for over 10,000 years,
but if you're going up against
my skills, you need another decade!
You're through!
Hamon Overdrive!
Did it work?
That was the last of my hamon.
I'm burned out.
I don't have an ounce of strength left.
Yes. It was enough.
Oh, yes!
He did it.
He hit Kars with his hamon.
Off you go.
I'll get you.
Ohh! Look at that.
Kars fell right onto his own crystal spikes.
Bwa ha ha ha!
The pillar man is done!
See?! The hamon will travel
right up his arm und do the job!
You're weak! Your time on earth is up!
A mere human could finish you off now!
Ohh. Trying to spook us, eh?
Now let's eliminate him forever.
Bring out the ultraviolet amplifier.
Jawohl!
Lisa Lisa.
Kars said that he wasn't actually
planning to kill you with his blade,
so I don't think that your wounds are fatal.
We need to get you taken care of quickly,
but I don't think this is the day you're going to die.
It's finally done.
Looks like it, and I'm glad.
Say, Mr. Speedwagon, um...
Huh?
Can I please ask you something?
Of course.
Well, why did granny Erina lie to JoJo?
Why'd she tell him that his mother
had died when he was little boy?
Why does Lisa Lisa hide her past
and not tell him who she really is?
Smokey, that's, uh...
I know granny Erina told me not to ask you,
but I've gotta figure this out.
I mean, she is his mother.
Keeping that information from him is just awful.
Smokey.
JoJo and granny Erina,
they're my friends.
Back in New York, they both saved me.
I was just a lowly pickpocket,
but they helped me out anyway.
That's the reason I'm here.
I'm going to do anything I can to help.
All right then, Smokey.
Let me tell you.
In New York, you proved what a good friend you were.
You took excellent care of Erina while I was gone.
But this, you can never reveal to JoJo.
This is the business of the Joestar family.
Friends or not, we don't have the right to talk about it.
The name Lisa Lisa is made up, an alias.
Her real given name is Elizabeth.
Raised and trained by the hamon‐user Straizo you met...
She and Erina's son,
George Joestar, fell in love.
They got married.
Soon George and Elizabeth had a son.
You know him as JoJo.
JoJo's father, George, enlisted as a
member of britain’s royal flying corps.
Aviation developed rapidly during the first world war,
and George was among the brave
pilots to fly into battle in the skies.
He stood out as a hero, even among
the members of the royal flying corps.
It was then...
That a gut‐wrenching horror from the past came
back to haunt the members of the Joestar family.
50 years earlier,
Dio Brando created bloodsucking zombies.
Straizo, myself, and the others
believed that we had exterminated them.
But one of them had escaped.
He hid himself within society
and lived for decades undiscovered.
He was cunning, intelligent, supremely dangerous.
He created no spawn.
He devoured the bones and hair of his victims,
leaving behind no evidence of his existence.
And by some wretched, wicked twist of fate...
He had placed himself in position as
a commander in the royal flying corps.
The royal flying corps? With JoJo's father?
The very same.
George was observant and figured this out.
He had listened well to Straizo and myself.
But ultimately, George was only an ordinary man.
He had character and talent,
but he had no training in the ways of hamon.
Before he was able to unmask the commander,
he was discovered by his monstrous quarry.
His message to Straizo was too late.
George's death was covered up as
an unfortunate nighttime plane crash.
Straizo and I found this suspicious,
so we investigated and eventually learned the truth.
That night, Elizabeth held an infant JoJo
as I told her what we had discovered.
Instead of showing grief,
she ran out intent on bloody revenge.
She was a genius with hamon,
but she let her emotions consume her.
She was careless.
There was a witness to the commander's death.
The military knew nothing about zombies or hamon.
They concluded that for some unknown reason,
Elizabeth had attacked their beloved commander,
killed him, then burned his body to hide the crime.
Word spread as only bad news can,
and soon she was known around the world
as a murderer and traitor to the war effort.
We used all the resources of the
Speedwagon foundation to cover her trail.
Elizabeth had to leave England behind
without even a word of goodbye to her son.
Erina knew what had occurred,
and she gave me this specific request.
When the child grows up and asks about his parents,
please tell him they both died in the war.
This child,
poor little child.
And so it was that Elizabeth became Lisa Lisa.
Why?
Why is it that way?
At least let him know his mother's not dead somewhere!
I know painfully well why.
Erina lost her husband and her son
in the battle between hamon and the stone masks.
But thinking of her grandson,
her Joseph, her JoJo,
she didn't want hamon to create
yet another hole in her life!
Lisa Lisa feels the same.
What tragedy for this family.
Such a miserable fortune.
But now...
It's better.
JoJo used hamon positively to save his mother's life.
Mr. Speedwagon.
Hmm?
There's no reason for Lisa Lisa to
hide the truth from JoJo any longer.
Eh?
He already knows about hamon,
and he used it to save his mother's life.
That's true.
But still it's not my decision to make.
It's a question of how Erina and Lisa Lisa feel.
I guess.
Major!
We're ready to fire, sir.
Excellent.
Everyone focus on him.
Und now we will share the honor of executing Kars.
Jawohl!
Now, Kars, die!
I can't begin to tell you how good
it feels to give this order myself!
Von Stroheim, you must stop!
He's got the red stone attached right there on his mask!
U.V. light will help him!
No, damn it.
Stop now!
Don't fire the U. V. Amplifier!
This can't be!
I didn't see him with the mask.
I didn't know that he had it anywhere near him.
I didn't see him put in the red stone.
No, it can't be.
Dear god.
Kars.
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
you spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
24 before my love you'll see
I'll be there with you
He has become the ubermensch.
He has complete mastery over organic life.
Is there really no way to stop him, Mr. Speedwagon?
Kars the pillar man is no more.
He's become Kars, the ultimate creation!