Caesar was the son of Mario Zeppeli,
considered the best furniture maker in all of Naples.
Mario was a proper Italian man of his day,
thoroughly dedicated to his family.
To Caesar, he was the ideal man.
When Caesar was 10,
Mario suddenly left without so much as a word.
Having lost their mother years before, they were alone.
Distant relatives stole what little they had.
Caesar became a delinquent,
growing to hate his father and what he had done to them.
I bet he's living carefree with some hot young woman!
I'll gonna find him and then kill him!
He threw away his youth and his future.
He committed theft, arson, assault,
anything short of outright murder.
Even the local mafiosos feared him.
Hey, you're that guy named Caesar, aren't you?
So what's your last name?
I don't have one.
Well, that means there's no way you're italiano.
Italianos are proud of their family names.
Never holding back, he often
started fights by using a wrench
to suddenly bash his opponent's head,
before calmly finishing them off.
Though he didn't know it yet,
he was already beginning to use hamon.
Then, at age 16 in Rome...
There's no mistake. It's really him.
At that moment,
Caesar felt he might murder his own father.
But then...
W‐what is all that?
Huh?
That's a massive diamond.
No! Boy, don't touch that stone!
It's you!
W‐what the hell is the wall doing?
Stay back.
This is all a trap.
Events had occurred 50 years ago
that were completely unknown to Caesar.
His grandfather will had died
tragically while on an expedition.
Mario took up his father's torch
and trained with hamon to prepare,
discovering the ruins soon after.
He began a worldwide search for
a way to defeat the monsters within,
and unlock the treasure they hide,
but Caesar knew none of this.
Young man, I beg from you a favor.
Make your way to venice, and speak
with a woman named Lisa Lisa.
It's a matter of life and death.
She is the only one who has any chance of stopping them.
Perhaps because so many years had passed
and Caesar had grown, Mario did not recognize his son.
Fa...
Caesar's father hadn't abandoned
his family for selfish reasons.
He'd left in order to keep his children
safe from the nightmare of the pillar men.
Father!
I see.
Caesar's misunderstanding
led to a deep hatred, but then that changed.
It became pride in his father and his family.
So Caesar sought me out
and picked up where his father had left off.
He's going, because he needs to avenge his father.
Forgive me, Caesar.
I didn't mean to speak ill of your brave family.
If you still want to
go charging in there
even though you know damn well
it's going to be a trap,
then you must have figured out
some way to beat Kars.
Changed my mind.
Since you're going in that derelict hellhole,
then I'm right behind you, Caesar Zeppeli.
A set of footprints leads into the mansion.
Who was that?
I swear I saw someone there.
Am I hallucinating?
There it is!
It's not an illusion!
What the hell is that?!
Caesar!
He vanished.
But I know he's here, close.
He's within a few steps of me.
Does Kars have some kind of new trick?
No, the sun is shining too strong for him.
He can't be out here and survive.
The cat stance,
a fundamental element of kung fu.
Caesar has never heard of kung fu,
but instinctively balances his stance
as he relaxes his limbs,
ready for attack from any direction.
For him, it is not a technique, but a reflex.
Caesar.
What do you think you're doing?
Going in there all alone is madness.
Just stay back, instructor!
I can't move at all, let alone go rushing in.
Something is hiding just inside
the entrance of the building.
What do you mean? I can't see a thing in there.
Huh?
A...a single footprint just appeared.
He must have jumped.
He's coming at us from above! There!
What the...
Wamuu!
Instructor, no!
What the hell is this?
That guy was Wamuu.
Are he and Kars inside that mansion together?
But wait a minute. How can Wamuu
come outside during the day?
He did look kind of ghostlike.
Where is he,
that infuriating smart‐talking upstart?
I hear tell that JoJo has learned quite a bit.
Where is the man who killed master Esidisi?
Wind.
Wamuu can control the wind.
That's why he's difficult to see.
Air's coming from pipes in his chest.
He's only slightly visible
because of water vapor swirling
in the flow around his body.
I've got it!
He's cloaking himself in vapor
that he's generating from the air,
and then he's pumping it out of those pipes.
It's refracting light like a million tiny prisms.
It's a suit that bends light around him,
protecting him from the sun's rays,
thus allowing him to be outside.
That's why he seems to be transparent.
Too bad JoJo isn't here.
You are the bubble user named Caesar, are you not?
Simply by looking into your eyes,
I can see that you've also learned
much though your ordeals.
Very well!
You are worthy of death at my hands, bubble user!
We'll see who dies!
I feel like I did back then,
when I was naive and poor,
back when you viciously took the life of my father.
And now I'll use my viciousness to destroy you!
Very impressive, but don't think your wind
will be able to just blow my bubbles away.
Some bubbles go right through wind.
I've significantly updated my grandfather's hamon cutter.
Bubble cutter!
High‐speed rotation turns the
bubbles into a salvo of deadly disks.
Hamon ensures they won't pop along the way.
Hmm?
The wind protecting you is nothing
more than a pocket of empty air to them.
Instead of defending you, it'll suck them in.
I underestimated his skill with hamon.
It is far more than I bargained for.
Heh.
Now, hamon‐user...
Hold it. I won't let you go inside.
Gliding bubble cutter!
Now, while you're standing there stunned
and helplessly off balance, I'll give you a hamon kick.
But Caesar was in for an extremely big shock.
If you are tripped, you try your best not to fall,
especially if you need to avoid sunlight
in order to survive.
But Wamuu was different.
He bent over backwards and attacked.
I've never seen anything like that before.
He's not just an immortal with incredible strength.
With senses like that, he's a fighting genius.
But my bubble cutter must have
inflicted severe damage on him.
The advantage here is mine!
I have a way to take you down, even indoors.
My nerves are honed to a razor's edge.
I can feel differences in the air.
I have the itch like when I was poor.
My breathing is relaxed and normal.
I'm not sweating.
Perfect hamon conditions.
Instructor Meshina!
I see you've taken off your coat and
made yourself ready, Wamuu.
Damn it. Caesar and Meshina aren't here.
Do you think they might have already gone inside?
No. That's his... that's Meshina's arm.
Now take this! Bubble launcher!
That's nothing.
Bubble cutter!
Running? Hah!
I won't run or hide from you!
Huh?
Bubble cutter!
You're dead, Wamuu!
Gliding bubble cutter!
Wamuu!
I'm finished with these games.
You're through.
Divine sand...
Wait a minute, Wamuu.
Stop, and look around.
Huh?
My bubble cutters are now bubble lenses,
and they're floating in the air all around you.
And that enormous hole you knocked in the wall earlier
is just like the open shutter of a
camera on a bright summer day.
Those lenses, they focus the sunlight...
Into the hotel.
What?!
You can't move.
You're like film, a frozen image.
You're totally exposed, Wamuu.
Trying your vapor barrier again?
Not this time.
Now, Wamuu, I'm going to finish
you off with a direct hamon blast.
One point at one moment,
a tiny blind spot.
Caesar's body created the briefest of
shadows amid the blazing wall of sunlight.
Wamuu didn't waste his chance.
He showed Caesar once again
that he was a fighting genius and a genius of strategy.
Wind power, Divine Sandstorm!
Huh? S‐such destruction.
It couldn't be.
It's Wamuu's Divine Sandstorm. I'm sure of it.
So that means Caesar is....
You had grown so much in so little time.
I'm satisfied.
I haven't had a fight like that in ages
now, warrior of hamon.
And it was a close one as well.
If the wind of my Divine Sandstorm
hadn't had the strength to blow your
bubble senses to oblivion,
I have no idea how I would have stopped
the light before it destroyed me.
And even if the mighty lord Kars,
who cannot use wind,
had been the one to first
note your presence
and confront you as I did
and faced your power...
If he had prevailed,
he most certainly would have been in far worse shape
than I find myself in now. Huh?
Enough. You will not fight again,
for you have nothing left with which to fight.
My Divine Sandstorm has shredded your body
beyond any chance of survival.
Stop.
The battle is over.
You have no more hamon with which to continue. See?
You've almost completely bled out.
That means you have no hope.
Stop, Caesar.
Goodbye. Your life and all you once were has ended.
What?
My lip ring with the antidote,
why did you take it?
I‐I'm not afraid to die here...
But I am a proud member of the Zeppeli family,
so you see, it's in my blood.
Something like this might mean absolutely nothing
to a demented, inhuman monster like you.
My father didn't recognize me,
but he sacrificed his life to save mine anyway.
My grandfather gave his hamon energy to
save JoJo's grandfather right before he died.
It's tradition.
I have to do something.
I‐i can't let my life's flame just
sputter out to darkness.
This is the Zeppeli family spirit,
handed down from the past to ensure the family's future.
It's the human spirit!
JoJo, this is the last of my hamon!
Take it from me!
Did you hear that?
It sounded like Caesar screaming.
Yes, I heard it. Oh, no. Caesar can't....
Caesar!
He made a bubble from his blood.
He must have used every last bit of his hamon to make it.
Before he died, he saved it for his friends
rather than using it to try and destroy me.
I'll let it go,
but not because I'm sentimental about him.
His talent as a fighter was undeniable.
He has my deep respect as a fellow warrior.
I will hold you and the last moments we spent together
forever in my memory, Caesar...
A man as splendid and as fleeting
as the bubbles he conjured.
The place is a wreck.
A Divine Sandstorm did all this,
and Caesar was caught right inside the heart of it.
A bubble.
C‐could it be?
Look at that.
Inside is Caesar's bandana.
Also a ring,
Wamuu's lip ring.
This hamon energy feels really strange.
W‐whoa!
You know, I haven't been able to bring myself
to call Caesar's name since we
made our way into this place.
It's because I'm afraid there'll be no answer.
If I came in here and cried out his name,
there might not be any response in return.
There might be nothing but a lifeless silence.
That is what scares me.
I couldn't accept it, so I didn't call his name.
But now I know he's gone.
The hamon contained in that bubble
told me everything I needed to know.
Right here,
just a few moments ago, Caesar died.
Guh! Caesar, you bastard.
You had to be a damn showoff right up until the very end,
and then you leave
a precious gift like this for me.
Caesar, where are you?!
Where the hell are you sleeping?
I'll find you, Caesar.
I'll dig you up.
Caesar!
JoJo.
This isn't the time to search or grieve.
We have work to do.
What?
There are two of them and two of us.
The numbers are balanced. They're even.
That trail of blood leading up the stairs
tells me that Caesar significantly wounded Wamuu.
We're in the middle of enemy territory.
Let's go finish this fight.
JoJo, come on.
Take the antidote. Then we'll go hunt
those bastards down.
That heartless...
She can't even manage to shed
a single tear for Caesar.
Coach Lisa Lisa,
your cigarette, it's backwards.
Lisa Lisa is our coach,
so she always has to keep a cool exterior.
I know she wants to cry much more than I do.
He treated her like a goddess
and knew her longer than I've known her.
I have to try and hold my feelings back.
Caesar, I know you always thought
I was impulsive and self‐centered,
but sometimes I do understand
the feelings of those around me.
I might finally be learning.
I swear I will fight them both like the devil
until there's nothing left of them.
I'll avenge you, Caesar.
Your spirit is with me.
Blood. His blood.
This is where he fell.
Caesar.
Caesar!
They were deep in enemy territory.
Kars and Wamuu were very nearby,
but the two simply couldn't help themselves.
JoJo called out Caesar's name.
Lisa Lisa's tears flowed freely.
But their heartbroken cries of grief
were answered only by a cold silence.
Caesar was gone.
As they mourned him,
they took solace in one simple fact.
Though his body had died,
his soul would live on through them.
Rest in peace, Caesar Zeppeli.
In and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky
they stand there
24 before my love and I'll be there
You're really not impressing me.
I'm going to hug you to death!
We fight tonight under the full moon.
You have no tomorrow.
We'll face this fight together, Caesar.