Long ago, an already extraordinary
man wished for further power.
This man could soar like a bird, swim like a fish,
breathe like a tree, and move like a winding stream.
But sunlight spelled his doom,
so he created a stone mask.
One day, he would face the sun without fear,
and then the world would be his.
Hmm.
Where'd he go?
Please tell me Kars fell into the lava.
I'm... still alive.
All right.
Must create armor...
Something like a clam...
Or a crab...
A bony shell.
Yes. Make me impervious.
It's not enough!
You dummy, that's lava!
It's a thousand degrees in there!
Now burn to a crisp, you cocky bastard!
Ouch.
Yes. That did it.
Finally.
Kars was the last of them.
The pillar men are defeated!
The shock of his demise triggered an eruption.
Let's get to safety before we celebrate further.
Good call.
Hang on tight, all right?
Guhh!
Music to my ears.
You perform that aria perfectly.
I've so longed to hear you sing it, JoJo.
Kars, you're alive.
A bit of his shell.
Inorganic. But of course.
Kars first covered himself in a
substance not unlike a crab shell.
However, it was still organic.
It wasn't up to the task.
Faced with the heat of the lava, it burned away instantly.
Luckily for Kars,
he had the idea to create a second layer of armor
made of an unlikely substance,
mere air bubbles.
The bubbles maintained a pocket of air
between Kars's body and the lethal heat.
As the outer layer burned away with each passing second,
more bubbles worked their way outward to replace them,
maintaining a perfect equilibrium.
Kars had the moments he needed to escape.
The earth gave birth to life,
but now, horror of horrors,
Kars, a creature of the earth,
has conquered the planet itself.
Eons ago, long before man first
thought to chronicle his deeds,
a group of creatures, like us, but not,
evolved alongside humanity.
The sun was lethal to them, so they lived
out their lives under the cool glow of the moon
and in their subterranean cities.
Even without the sun's sustaining rays,
they endured far longer than their human rivals
by feeding on other living things.
To humans that knew of their existence,
they were revered as gods or demons.
Their numbers were small,
as few died and children were rare.
In all things, they maintained a vital balance.
They knew no strife and lived in peace with one another.
But then...
A man of great pride and ambition was born among them.
Strength is hidden within this body,
talents we can naught but dream of.
I shall be the one to unlock them.
To that end, he created a stone mask.
The mask granted him unheralded power,
but at a terrible, ravenous cost.
To survive, he had to consume life at a dizzying rate.
If left unchecked,
he would eventually devour every living thing on earth.
His brethren began to fear the mask,
as well as the gifted soul who created it.
Hmm?
His very existence is a threat!
There is no place for one such as him in this world.
Ahh! We have to wipe out his evil.
Look at you fools.
Don't you want to have dominion over the sun?
To stand in ascendance over all life?
To purge your fears and reign forever as gods?
If not, then die.
The iconoclast brazenly slaughtered his brethren,
even killing the parents who had given him life.
He and his sole ally took the two surviving infants
and left the scene of the carnage.
They set off in search of ultimate power,
a journey of continents and centuries alike.
And now, ten thousand years later,
that power was in his hands at last.
He's a god.
This tyrant has become a deity,
and against such a foe, there is nothing that we can do.
We must submit or perish!
Hmm?
Hear that?
I think JoJo is trying to tell me something.
Hamon Overdrive!
What? Hamon?
Did you say, "Hamon Overdrive"?!
JoJo!
No. How?
My leg, it's melting away.
This is impossible!
Melting? You don't mean to say...
It can't be!
Denial will get you nowhere, my friend.
Hamon did that.
I conquered the sun itself.
What makes you think that something
like hamon was somehow beyond my reach?
Huh? I just...
Not only is hamon at my disposal,
but it seems that mine is hundreds of times more potent.
Mein gott. That much stronger than JoJo's?
It's as though he brushed his knee against the sun.
His flesh is liquefying und
vaporizing before his very eyes.
I wonder, how do you like the taste of your own medicine?
Hmm. A very articulate reply.
I suppose it's time to put you out of your misery.
JoJo!
This is it. I'm going to die here.
This is the end.
JoJo accepted his impending demise calmly.
He felt no fear, no pain, no regret at his plight.
"I did all I could," he told himself.
As the epitome of evil loomed over JoJo in triumph,
he watched his dying self with perfect clarity.
Stroheim felt much the same.
Unable to move, he knew what snake prey fells like
as it stares into oblivion's maw.
The power in a breath.
To think I will annihilate a practitioner
of hamon with his own discipline.
Surely you can appreciate the irony in that.
Ha... mon...
Stronger than mine has ever been.
Let me be the first to welcome you into oblivion!
Wait. Hamon.
What the...
The red stone!
The Red Stone of AJA.
But why did JoJo brandish it at Kars in
that final moment? Even he had no idea.
As if by instinct,
he'd lunged the stone towards the
approaching hamon to which it gravitated.
Now in a moment devoid of hope,
JoJo's body did the one thing that could save his life.
Having survived Kar's coup de grace,
his will to live sprang into action.
Yes. The red stone amplifies hamon.
Huh?
Fueled by the magnified blast of hamon,
the volcano's fury reaches the breaking point.
It erupts!
What? They blasted into the sky!
The force, it's strong,
like nothing I've ever known.
Do you really think a little eruption
will be enough to conquer the likes of me?!
I'll just fly my way to safety.
Enjoy the fruits of your folly, JoJo.
Who's laughing now, huh?
Let me guess.
You're gonna say, "Did you plan this, too, JoJo? Tell me."
How do you always know?
For a moment, Kars was distracted
by JoJo's arm and his cocky attitude.
That moment was all it took.
Scalding rocks he didn't see coming
launched him even higher into the stratosphere.
Did you plan this, too, JoJo!
Tell me!
Why are you even asking?!
I set the trap, and you walked right into it!
All of this went down like clockwork.
I just got lucky, but thinking I
outsmarted him will drive Kars nuts.
At that moment, the rocks launched by the
volcano's eruption reached escape velocity.
Kars was the perfect being.
Nothing on earth could kill him,
but just then...
He was blasted into the vacuum of space.
No! Damn you!
It's over.
Granny and Stroheim,
old Speedwagon, Smokey...
And Lisa Lisa.
Everyone, goodbye.
No.
JoJo!
Von Stroheim made it back to the others eight
hours later, whereupon he told them the sad news.
No!
The earth! No!
Don't panic.
Just find the earth.
I'll use air to change my trajectory.
Once I'm back on solid ground, I will tear that boy apart.
No! It's not working!
I'm freezing.
The air is freezing around me.
The moment it comes out of the jets, it turns to ice.
I can't change my path.
I can't move.
So ended Kars,
last and greatest of the pillar men.
His body turned hard as rock,
and he floated through space for the rest of time,
never to return.
He wished for death,
but there was nothing out there to kill him.
The spark of thought within him went dim and then silent.
We commend his soul unto the heavenly father.
Though his life on earth has ended far too soon,
he lives in grace with you.
Comfort those he leaves behind, o god,
and let them know your peace.
Goodbye, JoJo.
I didn't know you for too long.
Couldn't have been more than six months.
Don't matter.
Even though you're gone,
I'm your friend...
Forever.
Come, Erina. It won't do to catch cold.
Let's get you home.
Just a bit longer.
Guess who.
What gives, fellas?
I finally make it to New York,
and nobody was there to pick me up.
Then I got word you were all at a funeral,
so I decided to crash it.
Hey, Lisa Lisa.
Guess you healed up pretty well, huh?
Meshina, good to see you, too.
New hand works well,
though I've been meaning to ask Stroheim if he can
jazz it up with a few gadgets or tools or whatnot.
I guess that's right out, with us fighting Germany.
Hey, now. You leave these mourners alone.
This is a funeral. Show some respect, you oaf.
Oh, so I'm an oaf, am I?
You need a lesson in manners, and I'm glad to oblige.
All right. Calm down. Let's not be hasty.
But how?
No way.
Hey, I'm talking to you, big guy. You'd better...
Back off, man!
I'm just trying to catch up with my family and friends.
JoJo!
You're telling me JoJo's alive?!
Huh? Yeah, of course.
Wait. What's this about?
You're all staring as though you've seen a ghost.
I know it's a funeral and a...
Huh?
What the?!
What's my name doing on there? I'm alive and well!
Wait. This funeral was for me?
JoJo!
You're still recovering, you big silly.
Don't run off in the rain like that.
Here. Take this.
Hey, that girl is Suzie Q,
and that... that ring looks like a...
Are you telling me you don't know that we got married?
You got married?
Isn't it crazy? Just think about it.
I'm officially Mrs. Joseph Joestar. Goodness.
It makes me blush.
Wait a second here.
Suzie Q, something about this doesn't
feel right, and I wanna know what.
The rock I was on fell into
the ocean, and me along with it.
A fishing boat picked me up.
So far, so good.
You nursed me back to health in Venice for two weeks,
and we tied the knot.
So why did they all think I was dead?
You never sent that telegram like I asked, did you?!
Uh,
I don't really know.
To me, that sounds like no!
Uh...
Now, now. Let's not get all clicky‐fingers.
I never sent it! I'm sorry, JoJo!
Suzie Q, what the hell?!
You had one job, woman, one job!
JoJo came back to us all!
Stop it! I said I was sorry!
Sorry?! They thought I was dead!
JoJo.
Soon after, Lisa Lisa, A. K. A. Elizabeth Joestar,
told JoJo that she was his mother.
They moved to America.
In 1948, she found love again
and married a Hollywood screenwriter.
Erina Joestar continued her work as a teacher.
In 1950, she died peacefully at the age of 81,
surrounded by family and friends who loved her.
Robert E. O. Speedwagon continued to
pour his energy into philanthropic research,
helping to further science and medicine in countless ways.
He died in 1952 of a heart attack at 89 years of age.
A lifelong bachelor, he left no family behind.
Smokey Brown went on to work his way
through college, majoring in political science.
Later, he became the first black mayor
of a city in his home state of Georgia.
Major Rudol Von Stroheim would never see JoJo again.
He died in 1943 at the battle of Stalingrad,
a fearsome example of the German
science he'd always championed.
Our technology is the greatest!
And so the years flowed by...
To a new generation.
And as for JoJo...
Oh. Right in the leg, huh? Sorry about that.
You should watch where you're going.
You wouldn't want a broken bone at your age.
You're right. How careless of me.
I guess this is a case of live and learn.
Hmm? Hey, wait a sec.
You're Japanese, aren't you?
I am. Why do you ask?
In that case, watch your damn bag!
Yow!
Alitalia flight 285 for Tokyo
is now boarding out of gate c‐17.
My only daughter has been married
to a Japanese man for over 20 years,
fell in love on the other side of
the world, and never came home again.
Her son rarely gets to see his own grandfather!
That's why I'll never forgive the Japanese!
Then again...
They make some rather nifty gadgets.
All right. It's finally time to haul it up.
Oh, man. What do you think's inside it, you guys?
A hundred‐year‐old chest like that?
It could be anything.
Come on. Let's open that bad boy.