Poco, where you been?
How dare you leave the house like this?
But please, papa.
Papa, I'm sorry I left the house,
but wh‐where's my sister?
Well, where do you think? She's out lookin' for you.
Wha?!
No, papa. Don't say that. Tell me she didn't go out.
Poco, what's ailin' you?
You're not behavin' right.
My sister!
Consider this, dear.
Examine this rose in bloom for but a moment,
vibrant, fresh, and young.
What you see is a mirror of your youth.
Consider this fact carefully, mademoiselle.
From the first moment this flower
fully blooms, it begins to wither.
A shame, don't you think?
Only 16, so sweet, so innocent and pure now,
so full of delicious life energy.
Wonderful, lord Dio.
Those lacking in manners are not fit to exist.
Now, mademoiselle,
I offer unto you a choice.
Would you not care to enjoy your
youth and beauty for all eternity?
Fret not, my dear.
I shall not force my friendship
upon you, like others might do.
You control your life.
You hold your destiny in your own hands.
You fiend.
Eh? How's that again?
You wear the flesh, but you're not a man. Devil, go away!
Alas, although your acquaintance will
be brief, let me introduce my companion.
I present unto you doobie.
As regrettably I am not to your
taste, enjoy your time with him.
Au revoir, mademoiselle.
Oi! Who hit me?!
Who's there?!
Doesn't matter, does it?
You're a zombie.
Your kind don't deserve any introductions.
Sister!
Poco!
Bit you. Bit you on your pretty little face!
What did that?
What's he got under there?
His mask. Look at it.
Look out!
Run, run, run.
That zombie, he's chock‐a‐block with serpents, all
sorts, venomous cobras, flesh‐eating asps and vipers.
Bit surprised, are you?
They sank their fangs in his face,
and more than just once.
How wearisome.
I haven't the time to deal with
any more of Dio's foolish games.
Damn. Very well done.
He squeezed out the poison. Good control.
He's learned a great deal about blood
flow in a very short amount of time.
Baron Zeppeli, he's helpin' our boy after
giving Jonathan his life energy when he died.
I'll use a bit of the great hamon I possess
to turn these serpents back on their master.
Sister!
Poco!
Guess who survived his time in hell, Dio.
You are alive, JoJo.
Curious.
I suppose logically that would then
indicate you have killed my two knights.
Lord Dio, we await your order to
reduce him to a pile of bloody flesh.
Lord, let my fangs make an impression on him.
Dio!
No.
This one is for me.
He falls by my hand alone.
Don't misunderstand me, JoJo.
Honestly this is something in
which I will take no pleasure.
We were raised in the same house, and the
prospect of turning you into an undead thing
is not a happy one for me.
That's why I wanted you to be
quickly dispatched by my knights.
But it would seem, in the end,
I underestimated you.
Seeing you here alive brings me to the realization
that, as an emperor, I was being far too soft.
But now, now I'll put you to death
without a moment's thought or compunction.
I could say the same.
I will feel no hint of guilt for your death.
But first I have a question, JoJo.
Whatever happened to that mustachioed charlatan of yours?
You seem to have lost him.
Hear me, Dio.
It shames me as a gentleman to say this,
but I can no longer hold back the truth. I,
Jonathan Joestar, have such hatred for you,
vengeance consumes me.
I swear I will kill you!
Come, JoJo!
What are you doing?
JoJo, please step aside.
I have a prior claim.
It is my right to avenge my friend's killing.
Zeppeli was a brave man and boon companion
through two decades of harsh training.
Dio, for his life,
I shall now send you to the bowels of hell itself.
No. Wait, Dire. Listen to me.
Dio has hidden abilities for which you are not prepared.
Hmm? Ah.
There's an interesting walk.
Apparently with decades of the proper training,
mere humans can enable themselves
to float through the air.
But in only a single night,
I attained power far surpassing that of any human guru.
You truly think you can defeat me in this manner,
like you were sleepwalking?
Fell for it, didn't you, fool?
Thunder cross split attack!
Uncanny. In crossing his arms, he can mount an attack
while still keeping his guard up for protection,
an incredible strategy.
No fighter has ever been able to escape this move.
Oh, no!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
I can't, I can't move.
He froze Dire.
Dio must have somehow chilled all
the moisture in his body at once,
turning him to ice in an instant.
Dire can't control his hamon.
He can't send it into Dio unless his blood is flowing.
'Strewth, that Dio's a fearsome creature right enough.
He froze Dire's whole body at once.
How did you do this?
Oh, we are feeble, aren't we?
You imbecile, you dare think
you could lay a finger on me?!
You're the one who's going to
give up your life like some mongrel.
Let's endeavor to give them a good show, shall we?
No. Dire, no!
Dio, stop it now!
It's time, JoJo.
You're the next I shall dispatch to oblivion.
Dire!
Those hamon‐filled rose's thorns do sting a bit.
Insect. How dare,,,
how dare you wound me,
wound my face?!
Dire, no.
Speedwagon, my sword.
Catch!
Dio!
I know exactly how to deal with you.
Dire gave up his life,
which showed me just how vulnerable you are.
It will be very easy for me now.
You won't be able to stop it.
All I need to do is fill Blueford's
sword of luck and pluck with hamon
and slice you with it.
You dare to touch me, filthy human?
You dare to touch me with your hamon,
more disgusting than frog urine?!
Your string of luck's run out.
Now shall you be fodder for my zombies.
They will gnaw the faces right off your skulls.
Now we see. He shows his true colors as
someone fit only to rule over a dung heap.
His cool toff's sophistication, nothing but a cheap mask.
Now that he's had himself a
nice humiliating taste of hamon,
he reveals his true filthy self.
Straizo's my name.
No mercy.
Page would be my name.
Jones.
Plant.
Bonham.
Needle vein strike!
Roses are alive and vital,
so hamon will remain inside them,
flowing along with their life force,
but the same thing can not be said for steel.
It's necessary to make contact.
A great many of them are coming.
If you wish, I shall handle them for you.
From all the indications I've seen,
that bloke Dio's more swift than any leopard.
But with Zeppeli's hamon,
Jonathan just might keep up.
Though Dio is strong enough to pulverize
flesh and bone with a flick of his wrist.
For the both of them, it could be up
to what happens in the very first moment.
I will squeeze the life out of you with my own hands.
I will cleanse the world of your evil influence!
What?
He snatched up some roses when I wasn't looking.
Come now!
Wait. That's good.
He circled around to the right.
Dio is blind on that side.
Take this, Dio!
No! Damn it all!
He knows exactly what he's doing!
Yes! Kill him!
He finally defeated Dio!
Defeated?
You fools.
Oh, no.
I‐i can't move.
I'm frozen.
You're so feeble, JoJo.
Now, weakling, you shall join
my other children of the night.
I've got your rubbery little carotid between my fingers.
So warm and springy.
A strangely pleasant feeling.
A kick.
My legs have been frozen, too.
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Enjoying this anguish, JoJo?
One tiny little move,
and this delicate blood vessel
snaps in two like a wet ribbon.
With your carotid open, all your blood will be mine.
Then I shall fill the vacancy with my own
vampiric essence, and you will be my thrall.
We have to help him.
Zombies, to me!
Keep those peasants back.
I'm rather busy.
Nothing seems to stem this tide of zombies.
We cannot provide any help.
Now, JoJo, in your last moment of free will,
realize that the victory was mine.
No, Dio. You've not won yet.
You've made a fatal mistake.
How so?
You see, Dio, if you freeze me completely,
you'll not be able to continue feeding on my life energy.
This means, however, that my hamon is unaffected.
You can't block it as long as I remain partially unfrozen.
Your tactics, to say the least, are somewhat flawed.
How long has the sword been in those flames?
The metal blade is conducting heat from the fire
faster than I can freeze it.
Hamon is flowing up the blade.
Sunlight yellow overdrive!
Now!
He's done it!
Huh?
Not exactly correct.
It's quite evident the hamon did not make it through.
My arm.
My arm is frozen solid again!
I only briefly touched his face.
This isn't over, JoJo.
I have to admit I must admire your tenaciousness.
Really, I do.
And your ingenious use of the flame,
truly marvelous example of quick thinking.
Hmm.
But really, JoJo,
an emperor's reach should exceed his grasp.
Just a touch on the arm is all it takes.
I can turn your whole body to ice in two seconds.
The vampire essence, he squeezed it out.
He's not done.
Jonathan won't give up.
Really? The "let's do battle" stance?
You're not serious.
No matter how you prepare,
human ability is extremely limited and finite.
Your hamon training avails you nothing.
It's useless, useless, useless, useless, useless, useless!
A mere monkey can never defeat a lion.
In comparison to my power,
you are but a mere monkey, JoJo!
You're wrong! With true conviction,
the human race can overcome anything!
Let me demonstrate to just what
heights a human being can rise.
Don't waste your time.
A zombie is all you'll ever be!
'Strewth! His hand is burning!
Flame's coming from his glove.
That might just have the power to get through Dio's ice.
When this business is done,
which one of us will have fallen?!
We'll find out, Dio!
Dio's blocking JoJo.
But, no...
It's breaking through.
I'm disintegrating.
It can't be!
The pain. The burning.
I can't...
My reign was to have lasted forever,
for centuries uncounted by man.
You had to be destroyed, Dio.
I will not die!
How did...
He shot energy from out of his eye.
He came to within only mere
inches of incinerating my brain!
Far too close.
The last act.
The demon refuses to acknowledge his death.
Dio has fallen from the parapet.
Dio.
Look! He fainted!
He's worn out.
Too right. He's been in more fatal fights
tonight than a man should have in a lifetime.
But why would he shed tears
for an evil creature like that?
He weeps because they spent their youth together.
Dio was like a brother to him.
But as for me, I could sing a song of joy.
Baron Zeppeli, were you watching?!
He did it!
Jonathan Joestar did it.
Dio is dead.
It may sound an exaggeration,
but JoJo saved the world tonight!
I'll be the roundabout
the words will make you out and out
I spend the day your way
call it morning driving through
the sound and in and out the valley
in and around the lake
mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
one mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
10 true summers we'll be there and laughing too
with you
24 before my love you'll see I'll be there with you
What a beautiful sight.
These tears that I'm crying are from joy,
you must leave, Erina.
I want to stay like this.
Where is my body?