[KIKYO]
This isn't my fault.
Why is everybody so mad at me?
They're the ones with
the problems, not me.
All I did was tell
everybody the truth.
They have only themselves
to blame for rejecting me.
[KIKYO]
It was inevitable!
[HIRATA]
Okay!
So is everyone on board
with holding study
sessions to prepare?
I need the help for sure!
Yeah!
[HIRATA]
We'll split into groups.
Kushida, Horikita, and I will
serve as our class's tutors.
Group one will meet after class,
and group two after club's end.
Each will get two hours.
Let's decide on the groups now.
'Scuse me!
I'd love to help both
groups as much as I can!
Thank you for volunteering!
We can do this, guys!
[giggles]
[HIRATA]
I'll be overseeing group two.
[SUZUNE]
Then I'll take group one.
[GIRLS chuckling]
[HIRATA]
As for Kushida,
she'll be assisting both groups
whenever she can.
--[phone dings]
--[KIKYO] Uh?
Well, bye!
[MIYAKE]
Hey, can we talk?
[HIRATA] Oh, Miyake and
Hasabe? What's up?
We got paired up together,
but the problem is that
both of us struggle
in the same subjects.
I see.
Which means you might not hit
the minimum score to pass.
That's right.
But both the study groups have
too many people already.
Adding you might do
more harm than good.
Agreed.
Things would be
a whole lot easier
if we had another
potential tutor.
[YUKIMURA] How about me?
I could look after them.
[HIRATA]
Yukimura? Are you sure?
I want to help our class
get through this exam.
During the sports festival,
I was basically useless.
[HIRATA]
That's not true.
It's a miracle that
our whole class
managed to pass the last exam.
I doubt we're going to
get that lucky again.
We can't just focus
on our strengths.
At this school, if we want
our class to move up,
all of us have to
be well-rounded.
Yes. That's true.
Smarts. Creativity. Instinct.
This Paper Shuffle will put all
those qualities to the test.
None of us can do
all of it alone.
What we need now is for our
class to come together.
That makes sense.
Favor. I want you to help out
Yukimura with his study group.
He's fine on his own.
Just observe and make
sure things run smoothly.
Shouldn't be too hard.
Plus, on the cruise ship test,
seemed like you two
made a pretty good team.
Having you work together
again would be good.
[YUKIMURA]
All right, let's begin.
Our study group's first
official session.
Just us four, huh?
I guess. Should we jump
right into it, then?
Sounds good to me.
Whoa, so you can
talk, Ayanokoji.
Hey! You're being rude!
Am I wrong? I hardly ever
notice when he's in class.
He takes being "a fly on the
wall" to a whole 'nother level.
Still, though. Besides,
he did great in the festival.
Yeah, people keep saying that,
but I was in the bathroom,
so I didn't get to
see him in action.
You raced the former student
council president, right?
[YUKIMURA]
Since we're on that topic,
no more holding back on us
like you did in the festival.
I asked Horikita about it,
and she says that you're good
when it comes to academics.
I've just got a decent
memory, that's all.
[YUKIMURA]
Miyake, Hasebe,
I've already gone over
your weakest subjects,
and I've come up
with a lesson plan...
I'm terribly sorry,
but specialty cakes have to be
reserved a week in advance.
[ISHIZAKI]
I heard you,
but you've gotta make
an exception this time!
What's his deal?
I recognize him.
He's from Class C.
Come on, guys, stay
focused on the questions.
A cake, huh?
[AYANOKOJI]
That reminds me.
My birthday is coming
up soon. Right.
It's actually impressive.
[YUKIMURA] They made almost
the exact same mistakes.
So this'll just be
like we're teaching
a single person, then, huh?
Class C's gonna be coming up
with our questions, aren't they?
Yeah, they are.
As long as we get
you two up to speed,
it shouldn't be a problem.
Even if they throw
us some curveballs.
It's not like they're gonna
stick to the textbook.
You honestly think this study
group thing is gonna help?
You have a point.
Teachers will be
reviewing the questions
and deciding if
they're appropriate.
Yeah?
If we can figure out where
the school draws the line
when it comes to questions,
it'll be a big help.
[MIYAKE] Yeah, but that's
easier said than done.
How do we find that out?
[AYANOKOJI]
I think I've got a way.
For the next step,
we should only turn in questions
that have a good chance
of getting rejected.
Stuff that could be considered
too hard or tricky.
Whether or not they
accept our questions
will tell us where
they draw the line.
Yes, I see.
That would be valuable.
[AYANOKOJI] How's the question
writing coming along?
Hirata and I are
making some progress.
And on the other front,
we're sharing study
group information, too.
Good. How are things
with Kushida?
Pretty much the same.
Any changes in her behavior?
No, and she helped out
as much as she could, too.
I know this is something
that goes without saying,
but don't let her know
about the questions.
Right. Hirata and I are
keeping everything secret.
Although it still
doesn't resolve
our main issue with Kushida.
Agreed.
Don't worry, I think I've
got a way to deal with her.
Ayanokoji, I actually
have another favor
I'd like to ask of you.
Which is?
On days when Yukimura's
group isn't meeting,
could you stop by and help tutor
the members of our group?
[AYANOKOJI]
This again?
[SUZUNE]
There are just too many people.
It's hard to keep
track of everyone.
[AYANOKOJI grunts]
Are you all right?
[SATO] Whoa! I haven't been
to the school's library before!
Have you, Ayanokoji?
[AYANOKOJI]
I've been many times.
[SATO] Oh, really?
You must love studying, huh?
[AYANOKOJI]
I do it to kill time.
Don't you have any hobbies
or anything better to do?
Hey, so... am I a problem?
[AYANOKOJI]
What do you mean?
I was wondering
if it was all right
for me to work my way into
the study group like I did.
I don't mind at all.
It's good that you came along.
And if you ask Horikita,
I'm sure she'll say the same.
That's not exactly what I meant.
[SUZUNE] I need for everyone
to stop the side chatter
and focus on studying.
Right! You won't hear a peep!
Yeah, for sure!
Hey, so what should I be doing
to get ready for this exam?
You lucked out.
Your partner is here,
so why don't you just
go along with Ayanokoji?
[AYANOKOJI]
Are you sure about that?
My test scores aren't that
much better than Sato's are.
That's a great idea!
It'll be fun!
[AYANOKOJI groans]
I like how, no matter what,
you're always so
calm and collected.
It makes me wonder what you
were like in middle school!
Wait a second, when did
those two get so cozy?
Almost like they're
dating or something!
Yeah, right!
[SUZUNE]
Hey, Ike, Yamauchi.
Quit goofing around and
get your notes out,
we're starting soon.
Everyone ready?
[ALL]
Fine.
[alarm beeping]
[SUZUNE]
That's enough for today.
[YAMAUCHI]
Ah, it's finally over!
Well, thanks for
coming, everybody!
Bye, Horikita!
Sure.
Wanna walk back to
the dorms with me?
Sorry, but I still have a few
things I need to take care of.
Aw, that's too bad.
Yeah.
Well, I'll see you
tomorrow, then.
What did you have in mind
for dealing with Kushida?
[SUZUNE]
I've been thinking it over.
If I hadn't come to this school,
none of this would've happened.
Kushida would've gotten
along with the whole class.
Not only that, she
would've whole heartedly
helped the class to move up.
Thing is, that possibility
was stolen from her
because I'm here.
And I know it's not
my fault, of course.
But it does involve me.
What will you do?
I've got a plan for
how to deal with her.
[AYANOKOJI]
Mhm.
[SUZUNE] Kushida,
sorry for making you wait.
[KIKYO] So, what were you
talking to Ayanokoji about?
That is none of your business.
You know how much
I love secrets.
The reason you're trying
to have me expelled
is because I know
about your past
since we went to
the same school.
Have I understood
things correctly?
Yup! That's exactly it!
It's really too bad, Horikita,
and I'm sorry that it's
had to come to this.
It doesn't matter
what I have to do,
I'll make sure what happened
stays buried in the past.
I only heard rumors,
nothing more.
But you know I can't take
that risk, don't you?
[SUZUNE sighs]
How about we place a bet?
Sounds interesting!
We'll use the Paper Shuffle.
If I manage to get a higher
score than you on the exam,
then I want you to promise
that you'll stop
trying to sabotage me.
I see!
What happens if I get a
higher score than you?
In that case, I'll voluntarily
drop out of school.
Ooo!
And we'll only be comparing our
individual scores, correct?
[SUZUNE]
Yes.
I'll have to pass!
That's not very fair!
I don't think I've ever
beaten you head-to-head
when it comes to overall
test scores before!
I've already considered that.
Which is why I'm proposing
that we compete
in just one subject
from our finals.
And I'll even let you
choose the subject.
Huh?
So it'll be fair.
Sounds good, but how are
we going to make sure
that both sides follow through
with their end of the bet?
What if afterwards,
the loser pretends
the bet never happened
in the first place?
That won't be a problem.
I've gotten someone to act
as a witness for us.
[KIKYO]
A witness?
Sorry for the delay.
It's been some time, Kushida.
[gasps]
Well, that's surprising.
I can't believe you remember me.
Don't read into it.
I just never forget a face.
Does this ease your concern?
I trust that he'll be impartial.
Plus, you know his reputation.
I'm sure that you also place
some degree of trust in him.
[KIKYO gasps]
Are you okay with this bet?
It's not my business.
I'm only here to serve as
a witness, nothing more.
[KIKYO] But it's your sister
we're talking about!
If I score higher than her,
then she'll have to
leave the school!
[MANABU] She's the one who first
proposed the terms of the bet.
She'll have to deal
with the consequences.
You want to play for
keeps. I like it.
I'd rather get this
over with already.
Okay. Let's see who can
get a higher score.
The subject I choose is math.
You said I could pick, right?
[MANABU]
Then it's done.
There will be severe
consequences
for going back on your word.
No exceptions.
I'll be looking forward to the
finals, so good luck to you!
Let's both give these
exams our best efforts.
Good luck to you,
too, Ayanokoji!
Come on, you don't think
I'm that stupid, do you?
He's been listening from your
cell phone the whole time!
Don't be shy!
Why don't you join us?
[KIKYO]
So, if it's okay with you two,
I'd like to propose another
condition onto our little bet.
What do you mean?
It's just a suggestion,
but if I beat your score
on the math final...
...I'd like for Ayanokoji to
withdraw from school as well!
I can't agree to that.
That's too bad! Oh, well!
Fine by me.
I accept. I'll throw in
my lot with Horikita.
I don't need you to step in.
This has nothing to do with you!
[AYANOKOJI]
Tell her that.
[KIKYO laughs]
I'm so glad you
agreed to join in!
I'm sure.
[KIKYO laughs]
Just one thing. I have
a request of my own.
I'd like for you to
tell me everything.
What did you do
in middle school?
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] Don't you think
that I have a right to know?
After all, I'm putting
myself at risk
over a secret I'm
not even privy to.
Furthermore, you've been acting
under the assumption
that Horikita already
knows everything.
So that's why.
Telling us what really happened
doesn't actually
change anything.
I'm not interested in digging
around in Kushida's past!
I get that you don't
care, but I do.
How 'bout it?
It's fine.
If you'd rather
keep it to yourself,
we can just call
the whole thing off.
[KIKYO] You want to know
that badly, huh?
[KIKYO sighs]
[KIKYO] So tell me, Ayanokoji.
Do you know what it feels like?
To realize that you're better
than everyone else around you?
It's an incredible feeling.
[KIKYO]
In elementary school,
people would always
lavish me with praise,
even over the littlest
accomplishments.
If I got the best
grade on a test,
or finished first
in a sports event,
I'd instantly become
the center of attention.
They'd call me amazing,
incredible, and cute!
I loved those moments of
being in the spotlight,
of being seen.
I wanted everyone to notice me.
I needed everyone to praise me.
It was only when I
got that attention
that I felt like I
was worth something.
I think they call it a
"desire for recognition."
For some reason,
I felt it more strongly
than those around me.
I began to crave it.
Eventually, I started to get
less and less recognition.
No matter how hard I worked,
whether it was in
academics or sports,
everyone stopped paying
attention to me.
[KIKYO]
Then I came to the realization:
I just had to do the things
nobody else wanted to do.
"It's okay, I'll tutor you!"
"I'll help you with that!"
"I'll be there for you!"
I'd do whatever I could to be
nice and friendly to others.
I made sure I was
everyone's best friend.
The most popular
person in class!
I was needed and trusted!
I felt that wonderful
feeling again!
Ah! It was pure ecstasy!
It didn't last.
You see, always putting
everyone else's needs
before my own... was painful.
[KIKYO]
And that pain only got worse.
[scraping]
[KIKYO]
It hurt, but I couldn't stop.
I had to suck it up.
[KIKYO]
If I wanted to stay popular,
I couldn't throw away
what I had built.
So I endured it,
day in and day out.
But it had become
unbearable. I snapped.
[snap]
[KIKYO] I needed an outlet to
release all the pain inside me.
So I created a blog!
It was the one place
I could let everything out.
I didn't have to
pretend anymore!
It was like magic; I could
finally breathe again.
It was the perfect answer.
Until one day, a classmate
happened to stumble across it.
Even though I didn't
use any names,
they could tell exactly
who the posts were about.
[KIKYO] Eventually,
everyone in class figured out
that I was the one who wrote
all those awful
things about them.
Then, the attention
became negative.
They wouldn't listen.
After everything I
had done for them,
the entire class turned on me
without a second thought!
Even the boys who
said they liked me!
And the girls who cried on my
shoulder after they got dumped!
I mean, those boys were gross
and there were so many times
I wished they would just die.
And if those girls wanted
to know why they got dumped,
all they had to do
was look in a mirror!
The entire class was against me.
My back was against the wall.
I had no other choice!
I did what I had to do;
I used my weapon.
I told them everything.
I held nothing back.
I even revealed things I hadn't
written about in my blog.
[KIKYO] That he had been
cheating with someone
from another class.
And that she had been
badmouthing her friends
behind their backs!
I brought all those dark secrets
that lurked inside
them to the light.
Then, naturally...
Did you think I
wouldn't find out
that you're messing
around behind my back?
[BOTH shouting]
[KIKYO]
Just like that,
all the anger they had
pointed in my direction
suddenly turned
in on themselves.
That's the way it had to be!
Since there's no way they'd
go back to praising me.
I hope that answers
your question!
[AYANOKOJI]
So she used the "truth."
It's certainly effective,
but it's a double-edged sword.
[KIKYO]
To be perfectly honest with you,
I don't know Class D
all that well.
But I've gathered enough secrets
to really shake things up.
If I felt like it.
Looking back on it,
my only real mistake
was venting online.
You never know
who's looking at it
and they could get a screenshot
of it even if you delete it.
Things are better now!
Anytime I'm feeling angry
or stressed out,
I just use my words instead!
[KIKYO] I swear to god, I hate
you, I hate you, I hate you!
I wish you would just
drop dead, Horikita!
[giggles]
All that for attention?
What's wrong with you?
[KIKYO] Of course!
It's my purpose in life!
There's nothing I love more
than being noticed and praised
by everyone around me!
And whenever somebody
tells me a secret
that they've never shared
with anyone else,
I get this feeling inside me
that's simply indescribable!
[AYANOKOJI] A monster consumed
by her "desire for recognition."
Since you know about my past,
I'm sure you can see why
I want to keep it to myself!
Don't forget your promise!
If I beat Horikita,
the both of you will have
to drop out of school.
I'm looking forward to it!