[RYUEN]
So...
I hear you've been pretty
busy lately, Kushida.
Something about a bet with
Horikita and Ayanokoji?
I couldn't pass up
the opportunity!
And as long as you
give me the answers
to your class's questions,
there's no chance
I'll lose to them!
Sure. Although,
you know I can't just
hand them over
for free, don't you?
Yeah, of course!
But you see, you are
getting something for them!
I'll make sure Class C
wins the Paper Shuffle.
[RYUEN]
That's quite the promise.
Just trust me on this!
By the way, any progress
on tracking down this
"shadowy mastermind" of yours?
It's only a matter of time
before they're exposed.
And I know just
the person for it.
[HASEBE]
Jeez. Is it just me,
or are today's
questions extra hard?
Yukimoo!
I told you to stop
calling me that.
It's demeaning.
Aw. C'mon, let me have this.
Stop messing around, Hasebe!
Let's just get this over with.
Oh, wow, you're raring
to go! How studious!
[MIYAKE] I'm already giving up
club time for this.
I'd like to get out of here
sometime today, please.
Stop distracting them.
It's good to see you're so
motivated to study at least.
Fine. But first, I'm
getting another drink!
[HASEBE yelps]
[HASEBE]
Whoops!
Oh, sorry.
Really? I said sorry!
Well, well, what do
we have here?
Ryuen!
I never got a
response from you.
What are you talking about?
[AYANOKOJI]
That email.
What do you think?
Anything in particular
standing out? Hiyori?
[HIYORI]
I'm not sure.
Both of these guys have
really boring faces.
Completely forgettable.
People should be,
at the very least,
somewhat memorable.
Don't be like that.
After all, there's a good
chance you'll be spending
a lot of time with them later.
Why don't you just
leave us alone? Okay?
Don't worry,
I'm heading out now.
I'll be seeing
you all again soon.
[HIYORI]
Here. To apologize for earlier.
Once finals are done with,
I hope we can talk again!
[HASEBE] So, that was,
like, super weird, right?
[MIYAKE] I mean, all they
did was come over
and waste a bunch of our time.
[HASEBE] Mm! Man,
that really hits the spot!
There's nothing like ice cream
after a study session!
It's filled with preservatives
and artificial ingredients.
If you let stuff
like that stop you,
then how do you eat anything?
There's nothing wrong with
being health conscious.
Though I shouldn't expect
too much from junk food.
You always such a killjoy?
[HASEBE chuckles]
To be honest,
I do kinda like this.
What's so fun about this?
You know, Miyacchi and
I have always sort of
done things on our own.
But these study
sessions have been
actually way comfier
than I was first expecting.
So, I was thinking...
Instead of being
a bunch of leftovers,
the four of us should
become an official group.
Sounds good. Yeah, I'm on board.
So, we agree!
What do you guys think?
I'm really only here
to help improve your grades
for the Paper Shuffle.
Although, if you want
to create a real study group,
I'm not opposed.
Yeah, right!
Just say you want in!
[YUKIMURA sighs]
That's what I thought!
You've got a point.
You all have been surprisingly
easy to get along with.
Yeah! Then it's settled!
[YUKIMURA] If we do this, no
more of those silly nicknames.
[HASEBE] We'll use our
given names, then.
Just call me Haruka!
I'm Akito.
Kiyotaka for me.
I guess that makes
you Teruhiko, right?
It doesn't! Seriously,
don't use that name.
[MIYAKE]
You don't like your own name?
[YUKIMURA] My mother
came up with Teruhiko.
But she abandoned my father
and I when I was little.
I'll never forgive her.
Oh, sorry. I wasn't
trying to vent.
[HASEBE]
It's fine! I brought it up.
It's not like you knew.
How about instead, just call
me "Keisei" from now on?
Sure thing.
It's the name my dad
wanted to give me.
No problem! I like it!
It's fine with me, too.
A pleasure, Keisei.
Right!
Kiyotaka, Akito and,
of course, Haruka.
Yeah!
And with that, this new
group is official!
[SAKURA]
Excuse me! Hold on!
Um. Wait!
Sakura?
Well, you see...
I was wondering if
maybe it'd be all right
for me to join your group, too!
[YUKIMURA] To be honest,
Horikita would probably
be a better teacher
than either of us.
Oh. that's fine!
She's got her hands full as is,
and if I'm being honest,
I'd rather be in a group
with all of you.
No objections here.
What do you think?
Should we let her join us?
Well... I don't have
a problem with it.
Sakura's pretty quiet anyway.
Hold on a sec!
I'm sorry, but it's
not that simple,
there's something
you gotta do first.
Sorry, I'm not following you.
If you really wanna be
a part of this group,
then you have to call us by
our given names or a nickname!
Here's Keisei,
Akito, and Haruka.
Right. Hello, Keisei.
Uh, Akito... and Haruka!
Also, um, Kiyo...
...tio... kaka... I mean, K--
Kiyotaka!
Good! 'Kay, you're in!
Now, call him "Kiyo- pon "!
[AYANOKOJI]
Excuse me? "Kiyo- pon "?
It's, uh, Airi?
[gasps] Yeah!
Now that Airi's here,
I'm pleased to announce we're
officially the Ayanokoji group!
Hold on. I think we
should revisit the name.
Hey, why not?
You are the one who
brought us all together.
It'd be better than
the "Yukimura Group."
How embarrassing.
--[HASEBE] It's settled, then!
--[SAKURA] Thanks for having me!
[YUKIMURA laughs]
[KARUIZAWA]
A movie?
[AYANOKOJI]
Uh-huh. Sometime tomorrow.
[KARUIZAWA]
Thanks for the short notice.
Whatever, it's fine. So,
what movie are we seeing?
There are some good ones
that just came out!
[AYANOKOJI]
Wait a minute.
Why are you acting like
you're coming along with us?
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
It'll just be my group.
We're going to the movie theater
after we're done with
our study session.
[KARUIZAWA]
I see.
When did you all
become so friendly?
[AYANOKOJI]
Anyways, I was calling you about
the test strategy meeting
with everyone tomorrow.
I need you to do me
another favor.
What do you need?
[AYANOKOJI]
Do you understand the plan?
Look, what you're asking for
is a lot easier said than done!
What's the point of it, anyway?
[AYANOKOJI]
I'll explain everything later.
Yeah, you better!
Well, see you tomorrow.
[phone chimes]
[KARUIZAWA] Look at this!
They've got a ton of songs!
Hey, Karuizawa.
We came here to work,
not to have fun!
[KARUIZAWA]
Aw, come on!
The whole point of this meeting
is to discuss our strategy
for the Paper Shuffle.
Fine, whatever!
But if you ask me, not singing
at a karaoke is just dumb.
It's okay, we can sing
after we're done!
Good enough for me!
Back to what I was saying
about the study groups.
It looks like the entire class
is making good progress.
Yeah! I told you my
flash-card game was on point!
Yes!
I wouldn't be so fast
to celebrate if I were you.
All that studying and
you're barely doing better
than a middle schooler.
Uh-- Come on, can't you
just let me have one win?
[SUZUNE] How are Hasebe
and Miyake doing?
I have no complaints.
That's good to hear!
It would be terrible if
anyone was left behind!
Let's get through this together!
I know we can do it!
[KARUIZAWA] As if.
That's easy for you to say.
[KIKYO]
Is something wrong?
The teacher said that every
year someone gets expelled.
You say we're all gonna pass,
but you can't guarantee
me or Sudo won't fail.
I'm gonna pass!
I'm really sorry, I wasn't
trying to offend you!
You're always talking about
looking on the
bright side, Kushida.
Must be easy when
you're smart, huh?
Calm down, Karuizawa!
I've wanted to say
this for a while.
You way overdo it with
that "good girl" act.
Um, I don't know what
you're talking about!
The two of you can
settle this later!
We should be focusing on
the upcoming test--
[KARUIZAWA]
You stay out of this, Horikita!
Look. You may act nice,
but I know you think
you're better than us!
That's not true at all!
[KARUIZAWA] Then stop pretending
like everything's just fine!
I promise you, I'm not!
What are you gonna do if
I fail and get expelled, huh?
[KIKYO]
But you won't fail!
[KIKYO gasps]
Whoa!
You can't do that!
Come on, we've talked
about this already!
[gasps]
[KIKYO]
Wait! Please don't blame her!
She's under a lot
of stress right now!
[YUKIMURA]
Even so, that was unacceptable!
Uh... I just...
You have to calm down.
If you storm out of here,
you'll only end up
regretting it down the road.
I think you should
start by apologizing.
[KARUIZAWA]
Sorry.
It's okay, I forgive you.
To be honest, I should've been
more sensitive to your situation
and how you were feeling.
Thank you.
[sighs]
I don't think I've ever
seen her freak out like that.
Wow, as if you're in
any position to talk.
I know this doesn't come
close to making it right,
but would you let me
clean your uniform for you?
[KIKYO]
You don't have to do that!
[KARUIZAWA]
Unless I do something,
it'll just keep eating at me!
I won't be able
to sleep at night!
I'm begging you, please!
[KIKYO]
Don't cry, Karuizawa!
It's okay! You can
clean my uniform!
[CHABASHIRA] So, then these
are the questions your class
has decided to submit
for the Paper Shuffle.
I see.
Although, I wasn't expecting you
to be the one to turn them in.
I couldn't say no
when Horikita asked!
[CHABASHIRA]
I understand. Thank you.
Actually, can I ask you
a favor, Ms. Chabashira?
I'm afraid someone
might come by later
and try to replace all the
questions at the last minute.
It's possible.
I was thinking.
If someone comes by and
tries to turn in a different
question sheet, you could
pretend to take it,
but then throw it away
once they're gone.
Very well then.
I suppose I could go along
with what you're asking.
Yay!
Thank you so much
for all of your help!
Going behind everyone's
backs and swapping out
your class's question
sheet, are you?
How very cold-blooded.
I already told you,
I'll do whatever it takes
to get Suzune Horikita
kicked out of school!
Anyway, don't you have
something to give to me, now?
[RYUEN]
But of course.
A copy of Class C's
question sheet.
[KIKYO] I can't wait to see
how everything turns out!
Good luck. I'm counting on you.
[SATO] Hey, good morning!
Guess it's finally test time.
[AYANOKOJI]
Did you sleep okay last night?
Kind of.
I was just feeling
a little nervous, y'know?
You're gonna do fine.
I've seen first-hand
how much effort
you've been putting
into your studies lately.
[gasps]
G'morning, Sato!
Hey, morning to you, too.
[KARUIZAWA]
It's funny, I thought I saw
you two back there!
So, what's up?
You guys having a
last-minute study session?
Oh, no! Just talking.
If you say so!
Hey, do you wanna grab
something to drink real quick?
Okay! See you later, Ayanokoji!
[KARUIZAWA]
Let's go!
[AYANOKOJI]
Hm?
[HIRATA] Wow, I've never seen
Karuizawa get jealous like that.
What does that mean?
I've gotten to know her
pretty well at this point.
It'd explain why she's been
so hung up on you lately.
Think someone's got a crush.
No way, you're reading
too much into it.
[HIRATA]
I don't know about that.
Maybe I am, but it'd be good
to see you two together.
Me and Karuizawa, huh?
[HIRATA] She deserves better
than some pretend relationship.
Well, anyway.
It's none of my business.
[AYANOKOJI]
Hm.
I barely recognize
our class like this.
Yeah, it's a good sign.
[AYANOKOJI]
Agatha Christie, huh?
That's ominous.
Nobody is getting expelled.
Of course, that
includes us, too.
[CHABASHIRA]
You may begin.
[AYANOKOJI]
Looks like Yukimura was right.
These questions aren't so bad
if you understand the material.
But I'm curious how she's doing.
No.
[KIKYO]
What's this?
[YAMAUCHI]
Kill me!
[IKE]
My brain hurts so bad.
How was it for you, Miyacchi?
[gibberish]
Sorry, Suzune! I gave
it everything I had,
but I think I maybe got
a 40 at best!
That's plenty. Based on
the questions we were given,
I'd be surprised if I ended up
with less than a 90,
so we should be fine.
[KEN]
That's awesome!
[bang]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[KEN]
What's her problem?
[KIKYO]
What the hell was that?
Why was the exam
completely different
from the question
sheet you gave me?
Thanks to you,
Horikita's gonna win!
How could you
betray me like that?
Heh. You still haven't
figured it out yet?
Huh?
You were so sure you
had outmaneuvered Suzune.
In the end, you're the
one who got played.
What?
[AYANOKOJI]
It's all very simple.
Kushida thought that
handing in a question sheet
before anyone else did was all
she would have to do to win.
But Horikita had
already planned for that.
How'd she do it?
The same day we found out
about the Paper Shuffle,
she went to talk to the teacher.
During the meeting
with Ms. Chabashira,
Horikita got her to agree
to two things.
Number one, she would only
accept a question sheet
turned in by Horikita
personally, as the class rep.
And two, if anyone else
submitted a question sheet,
she would pretend to accept it.
Then, without letting them know,
she'd get rid of the
new set of questions.
I see. Then that
means Horikita knew
exactly what Kushida
was gonna try to do!
That's right.
Which also means we didn't need
to do your little plan at all!
After everything I did
to make a scene
and plant that
cheat sheet on her.
I get that it was in case
things went wrong,
but now everyone
thinks I'm crazy!
I had my doubts.
But Horikita managed
to pull through.
In the end, I didn't even
have to lift a finger.
[KIKYO]
I hate that stupid bitch!
[RYUEN] You didn't hold up
your end of the agreement.
So why would you
expect me to just
hand over the real
question sheet?
[KIKYO] I was so close
to getting rid of her!
Yeah, right. You lost
before the game even began.
[KIKYO gasps]
Don't touch me!
Don't flatter yourself.
Look at this.
[gasps]
I thought so.
It's a little cheat sheet.
[KIKYO] That's not mine!
What was it doing in my jacket?
[RYUEN]
If I had to take a guess,
somebody in Class D was about
to throw you under the bus.
[gasps] Hold on!
Something about this
doesn't make any sense.
All the answers on this
piece of paper.
They're for the
questions you gave me!
But if you and I were the only
ones who saw the questions,
then how did the
mastermind know?
[laughs] You're finally
catching on.
[growls] You handed it
over to them? You did this!
[RYUEN]
Don't be ridiculous, Kikyo.
I've never thought of you as
anything but a tool to use.
[gasps]
It really shouldn't come
as any surprise to you.
I'll admit, you beat me
this time. Are you happy?
Will you stop trying
to sabotage me, now?
Just remember, you agreed
to it as part of the bet.
You don't have to
worry about that.
I'll be sure to keep the promise
I made to you and your brother.
I'll even sign a contract.
[SUZUNE]
There's no need. It's fine.
I trust that you won't
go back on your word.
Yeah, no. I hate you.
Yes, I'm sure you do.
But still, I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to get you to like me.
You can try, but it won't work!
Oh, and by the way.
As far as my promise goes,
I only said that I'd
stop sabotaging you.
What?
Is she gonna go after him next?
[AYANOKOJI]
Just as expected.
Ryuen decided to agree
to the trade.
"Give me the question sheet
that Class C submitted
for the Paper Shuffle,
as well as the answers for it.
Or significantly alter
the question sheet
you give to Kikyo Kushida
without telling her."
In exchange, I told him
that Horikita had already
figured out and come up with
counter to Kushida's plan.
I kinda wish I could've seen
the surprise on his face.
In the end, he chose
the second option,
changing the question sheet
he handed over to Kushida.
[RYUEN]
Incredible.
This mastermind knows
me all too well.
In a single move, he protected
Suzune from expulsion
and drove a wedge between
Kikyo and Class C.
It's only a matter of time
before he's forced
into a corner.
And if he still doesn't
wanna come out of hiding,
I'll break his toys, and I won't
stop until he reveals himself.
[RYUEN] You'll pay
the price for using me.
That I promise.
[AYANOKOJI] I gave you
the chance to back off.
But go ahead and throw
everything you have at me.
I'm more than happy to entertain
you anytime, anywhere.