Please, stop it. L-Let me go!
Hah! You really think we'll
just let you off the hook
if you shed a couple tears?
You're the worst kind of
person, you know?
Always looking for some
guy to hide behind!
For real, I hate girls like you!
What happened to all that
attitude you had before?
--Come on, I'm talking to you!
--[KARUIZAWA yelps] Ow!
That's hilarious!
Hold her still for a sec!
If we're getting pictures,
we should clean
her up a little bit!
[YAMASHITA]
That's a great idea!
[YABU]
Yeah, let's do it.
Leave me alone! I'm sorry!
[YUKIMURA]
We have to do something!
Not yet.
I can't watch this anymore!
What are you doing?
Leave her alone!
[MANABE]
Leave her alone?
We're just having a little chat!
[YAMASHITA]
Yeah! That's right!
Don't think for even
a second that this is over.
One way or another,
you're gonna apologize to Rika.
[YUKIMURA]
You okay?
[KARUIZAWA]
Leave me alone.
I-I was trying to help!
Shut up! I never asked
for you to help me!
What the hell is her problem?
[AYANOKOJI] I see,
maybe I'll give it a try.
[AYANOKOJI]
So, Venus Group's test
has ended early as well.
Which means someone
in that group sent in a guess
about the VIP's identity.
Too bad this only helps Class C.
[AYANOKOJI] Ryuen is trying
to figure out the criteria
for the VIP selections.
I guess I should start
assembling my pieces
while I can.
[AYANOKOJI]
Okay.
Let's see what they
decide to do now.
[sighs] There's no
signal down here.
If Hirata wanted to talk,
we could have met up
somewhere else!
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
What? Why are you here?
We're glad you could make it!
This is the "Karuizawa begs
for mercy" photoshoot!
[YAMASHITA laughs]
Make sure you get
everything, Yamashita!
Sure thing!
Stop this!
I haven't done
anything wrong, okay?
[MANABE] If that's true,
why is your voice shaking?
[YABU]
Look at her! She's scared!
[YAMASHITA]
That's hilarious!
Her knees are trembling!
[MANABE]
What's the matter, little piggy?
[YAMASHITA]
Are you gonna cry again?
Please. Yeah, right!
It just occurred to me.
You've been bullied before.
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
[MANABE]
I called it!
[YAMASHITA]
Oh, my gosh, she totally has!
Well, you already
know how this goes!
So, start begging already!
--[gasps]
--[MANABE] On your knees!
[GIRLS chanting]
On your knees!
On your knees! On your
knees! On your knees!
What are you talking about?
I've had enough of this!
[screams] Let me go! Now!
You don't leave until
we say you can leave!
[yelps]
[KARUIZAWA grunts]
[YABU]
Nice one!
[MANABE] Why don't you
take a shot, Rika?
[RIKA]
No thanks, I'm fine.
[MANABE]
We're doing this for you!
That slap was sad!
Do it like this!
[KARUIZAWA grunts]
Your turn!
[GIRLS laugh]
--[RIKA grunting]
--[slapping]
[grunting]
This is kinda fun!
[AYANOKOJI]
Stanley Milgram conducted
a series of experiments and
found that external pressure
can enhance a person's
natural cruelty.
Yes! That's the kind of
expression I like to see!
[AYANOKOJI]
Well done, Manabe.
All I did was set the scene,
and you've run with it.
[MANABE] If you just
begged from the start...
[KARUIZAWA]
Please, forgive me.
[AYANOKOJI] Getting Karuizawa to
rock bottom will save me time.
This is necessary.
[KARUIZAWA]
How did you find me?
It seems no matter
how you try to change,
you'll always be a victim.
[gasps] You were
watching all that?
I wouldn't bother
reaching out to Hirata.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] I know he's not
really your boyfriend.
And I know about your past.
You have no secrets from me.
What that means for you is
I can expose you
any time I want.
Let go!
You were terrified
of being bullied again.
So, you hid your past and became
a parasite that used others.
Where did that get you?
What--What are you
planning to do with me?
[AYANOKOJI] Let's see how
far you're willing to go.
Spread your legs.
[gasps]
[KARUIZAWA]
I don't know what I expected.
You're just another bully, no
better than those other girls.
Trying to make me do
something ridiculous,
and using blackmail
to get your way.
And yet, you don't
seem to be resisting.
You don't understand anything.
What do you think people do
when they're stuck in a reality
that they have no control over?
They simply accept it.
When placed in
a hopeless situation,
they give up, and stop
resisting the abuse.
That mentality invades
every part of their lives.
They can't run away,
or fight back.
It becomes automatic.
There's more to it than that.
There's something you're
trying to escape.
[gasps]
Something so dreadful
that you'd be willing
to surrender your body.
What is this trauma
that you're hiding?
I want to see it for myself.
No! Don't touch me!
[AYANOKOJI] Is this it?
Is this your darkness?
I understand.
There are many kinds
of despair that exist.
What you've been through
definitely qualifies,
and you're not alone
in that misery.
Those with darkness in their
hearts are drawn together.
And then the stronger
one between them
inevitably engulfs the other.
What? I'm confused.
What do you mean?
[AYANOKOJI] This world of ours
contains more darkness
than you could ever imagine.
I'll release you from
the shackles of your past.
Karuizawa, I promise you.
From now on,
I will protect you.
And in a far more reliable way
than Hirata or Machida.
[YAMASHITA]
Oh, my gosh, she totally has!
[MANABE laughing]
The next time
they come after you,
tell them you'll
release this video,
and they'll leave you alone.
I want you to help me.
I have a problem that
only you can solve.
Huh? Why would you need my help?
As it is now, Class D will
never be able to move up.
But if you can use
your popularity
to lead the other girls,
we'll make it so our
class works together.
[AYANOKOJI] Right. This is
something Horikita can't do.
Seriously? But why?
I'll keep the promise
I made to you.
And all you need to do
is help me out.
That's the kind of exchange
that you've been
looking for, isn't it?
All right, then.
What's the next step
in this plan of yours?
First thing's first.
I'd like for us
to win this test.
And to do that...
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[CHABASHIRA]
Sorry to make you wait.
What did you need?
There's something that I'd
like to purchase with points.
[AYANOKOJI]
Already here, huh?
[phone beeping]
Ayanokoji! I'm sorry!
I was hogging the sofa!
Whoops!
No, it's fine.
Can we chat for a bit?
Before everyone else gets here?
To be honest, there's
something I've been dying
to ask you about, Ayanokoji!
[AYANOKOJI]
Really?
Yup! Is it true
that you're trying
to get to Class A
before graduation?
It would be nice, yeah.
What a diplomatic answer!
It's the same for me!
It's a dream of mine to
graduate as a part of Class A.
Too bad, though, huh?
That we're in different classes.
I guess that means
only one of us
can make our dream
come true, right?
I suppose. Although,
there's another way for you to
get into Class A, isn't there?
Ah, that's right!
You could just buy your way in
with 20,000,000 points!
Uh-huh.
But from the rumors
that I've heard about it,
nobody's ever done it before.
Hey, Ayanokoji.
Remember that time
you borrowed my phone?
You saw my point
total, didn't you?
Sorry, I wasn't trying
to pry or anything.
[AYANOKOJI]
Right.
It was during the end
of the first term.
She had amassed a
huge number of points.
[laughs] I wasn't
accusing you of that!
It's fine that you saw.
But please don't
spread it around!
Of course. It's none
of my business.
I didn't expect you'd be here
this early, Ayanokoji.
Looks like Ichinose's
here as well!
Wait a sec.
Have we interrupted
a romantic rendezvous?
[ICHINOSE]
What are you imagining?
That's not the case at all!
[ICHINOSE] Let's start
the final discussion!
Oh, Hamaguchi!
I believe you wanted
to say something?
Please correct me if I'm wrong.
But I think everyone here
wants to earn points.
And the best way to do that is
to aim for a case one result.
[IBUKI]
Thanks for stating the obvious.
[SOTOMURA]
Of course!
That is the very motive for
these discussions, is it not?
At the rate we've been going,
we aren't going to find the VIP.
That's why I have a proposal.
We need to make a drastic
change in our strategy.
[YUKIMURA]
And what are you suggesting?
[HAMAGUCHI] A way to remove
the possibility of falsehoods!
We should show each other the
email we got from the school.
Everyone received an email
on the first day
telling them if they
were the VIP or not.
Since they're
impossible to fake,
they'll be definitive proof.
This is ridiculous.
Aren't you forgetting about
the case three result?
Someone could betray the
group and steal the points.
If there's even
one traitor, it's over.
I'm well aware of
the risks in my plan.
However, if we keep playing
it safe, only the VIP will win.
So, you'd rather our
group take a gamble.
Yes. But my proposal
evens the playing field
for those of us who aren't
the VIP or their friends.
What do you guys think?
[HAMAGUCHI]
If you think about it,
they'd be the only
ones who'd object.
Do you seriously think
we're all going to agree
to such a risky plan?
[ICHINOSE] You seemed awfully
quick to reject it, Machida.
[MACHIDA]
What's that?
Just thinking out loud.
If this ends in a deadlock and
no one earns class points,
wouldn't that work out
in Class A's favor?
But, on the other hand,
that means the rest of us
from the other classes
have an incentive
to take a risk, doesn't it?
[AYANOKOJI]
Ichinose has to be behind this.
Hamaguchi may be speaking,
but I'll bet anything
those are her words.
I can't force anyone
to show their email
if they don't want to.
But since it was my idea,
I'll show you my phone!
Hamaguchi!
I'll show mine, too!
Look, I'm not the VIP.
Oh, my! What a twist!
[AYANOKOJI]
The longer we take to agree,
the more suspicious we look.
Might as well.
All right.
I'll go along
with your proposal.
What are you doing?
Ayanokoji? You sure?
[AYANOKOJI]
Yes.
I see, so you weren't
picked to be the VIP either.
Huh.
Uh, whatever, I'll join.
Are you serious?
If we wait out
the clock like this,
the entire test will just
have been a waste of time.
It's better to risk it.
Unless, one of you is the VIP?
Obviously not!
[KARUIZAWA]
I'll show my email, too!
Any chance is better than none!
Fine, here it is. You happy now?
A wise man said, "If you
can't beat 'em, join 'em!"
It's not me, either!
Other than Class A,
all that's left is you.
Come on! Show us your email!
I need everyone to promise,
right now, that you won't
betray the group by turning
in your answer early.
Does that mean it's you?
[YUKIMURA]
Ayanokoji.
Please forgive me
for lying to you.
I'm our group's VIP.
What? You're kidding!
I see.
[AYANOKOJI]
Good job, Yukimura.
With that, our victory
is all but guaranteed.
Everyone!
Let's all agree not
to expose Yukimura!
We can win this test together!
I guess that's fine.
I appreciate that.
I want to believe.
No, I choose to believe!
[HAMAGUCHI]
Right!
[BEPPU]
Let's win this!
[SOTOMURA]
We shan't betray your trust!
[AYANOKOJI] Of course,
that's not gonna happen.
Blinded by greed, someone
will betray the group.
But that's exactly what we want.
Yukimura isn't the VIP.
Earlier, I told him that
the school chose me.
So, we swapped our cell
phones with each other.
I wasn't expecting
Ichinose to make a move.
But it still worked out.
--[phone rings]
--[YUKIMURA gasps]
Yukimura, would you care
to explain why you were
in possession of
Ayanokoji's phone?
Oh? It's his? Who knew?
You see, I just called
Ayanokoji's number,
but the phone in your hand rang!
And it couldn't have been your
number, because I don't know it!
Does that mean that
the real VIP is Ayanokoji?
What the heck is going on?
They switched phones?
Hah. That was pretty sneaky!
So, everything you
said before was a lie?
You better explain
yourselves, Class D!
Hold on! I didn't know
anything about this!
[ANNOUNCER 201A] The discussion
period is now over.
All groups must disperse...
[YUKIMURA]
Damn it!
Finally showing everyone your
true colors, Class D scum.
Nice job.
We got to see exactly how
little your "trust" is worth.
Well, here's hoping
that no one else
breaks their promise, huh?
[YUKIMURA]
This is awful!
It all went according to plan.
[AYANOKOJI] Yup. This was
the perfect outcome for us.
I need you because
you're the VIP, Karuizawa.
[gasps] How did you know?
[AYANOKOJI]
Hirata mentioned it to me.
It's good that you're the VIP.
We can use that to set a trap.
First off, you and I need
to exchange our cellphones.
Then, I'll pretend
to be the VIP.
I'll convince Yukimura
to trade cellphones,
but I'll keep him in the dark
about your involvement.
For part two of our plan,
we'll steer the conversation
to make him admit
to being the VIP.
So, it doesn't matter if
someone sees through our plan.
Because even if they figure out
that you two swapped phones,
if they guess you, we still win!
[AYANOKOJI] But there's a
critical flaw with this plan.
It doesn't matter how many times
we switch. If we can't change
our phone number,
we'd be exposed
the second someone called us.
What are we supposed
to do, then?
When we swap phones,
I'll keep my SIM card.
Aren't the SIM cards locked
to their original phones?
The ones from the school
don't let you take them out.
There's nothing you
can't buy with points.
That's one of the fundamental
rules of this school.
I'm certain I can
get Ms. Chabashira
to sell me the key.
[KARUIZAWA]
It worked out,
but I still feel kinda
bad for Yukimura.
[ICHINOSE]
Yeah, me, too!
Oh, Ichinose?
[ICHINOSE] After uncovering
a lie, people have a tendency
to accept the next answer
they hear as true.
Someone from our
group is definitely
going to fall into your trap.
I see, that explains why
you tried to call my phone.
I'm guessing Class B has
something similar planned.
Great minds think alike!
Although, if you knew our plan,
then why didn't you just
call us out during
the discussion?
We didn't have to! We
weren't gonna risk guessing.
So, we decided we should let
someone from Class A
or Class C take the fall.
Was that the reason why you let
all the discussions drag on?
Just so you could
orchestrate this situation?
Yeah, something like that.
My turn!
I'm curious, did Horikita
come up with this plan?
If not her, who else could?
[ICHINOSE]
Huh... Well, if you say so!
[phone chimes]
Huh? Results?
[SUZUNE]
How could this have happened?
Class C got so many points.
Somehow, Class A totally
dropped the ball!
An acceptable result. But still.
[RYUEN]
That's a nice expression.
Suzune.
Do you believe me now?
I did tell you that I'd
find out the identities
of all the VIPs, didn't I?
Believe you?
You wouldn't hesitate for a
second to betray the group
if that meant that you won.
Our group made it to the end,
so there's no way you knew.
[RYUEN]
Kikyo Kushida.
What's wrong?
Did you really think you could
hide the VIP's identity?
I figured out it was
Kushida by day two.
How'd you know?
It was painfully obvious.
I can read you
like an open book.
That look on your face--
it gets me going.
I think I'll make you
my next target.
How's that sound?
I'm going to tear you into
pieces, body and soul.
Our second term is
shaping up to be a fun one.
[AYANOKOJI]
With how things are panning out,
Class D could be put
in a difficult spot.