[sighs]
[SUZUNE]
So, you're saying...
...she's a traitor?
Just think: there's no way
anyone could've figured out
your group's VIP
with how careful you were.
I seriously doubt you or Hirata
would let that information slip.
Of course not.
[AYANOKOJI]
The only other answer
is that Kushida
revealed it herself.
But why would she do that?
She has no reason
to betray the group.
We can't say that for sure.
It's possible that another
class paid her off
with private points.
Wait, seriously?
You think she'd just
sell out Class D like that?
[AYANOKOJI] All I'm saying is
it's a possibility.
The only one who knows
the real reason is her.
And that's why you invited
her to come along?
To find out her real motive?
You and Kushida appear
to have some sort of history.
Not really.
Any class that allows
a traitor in their midst
is doomed to fail.
What?
[AYANOKOJI] If you want to
lead the class to victory,
it's something to consider.
[sighs]
[STUDENT 5A]
Keep up the hustle!
[STUDENT 5B]
Come on, I can't hear you!
This was a surprise!
I mean, getting asked to tag
along by you of all people!
I suppose so.
Watching everybody else is fun!
So, thanks again
for inviting me!
Yeah, sure thing.
Although, you kinda
brought the mood down
by inviting her along.
For some reason,
Horikita doesn't like me
all that much, but you
invited her, too!
To tell you the truth,
she's the one
who planned this whole outing.
[KIKYO]
Oh, wow, really?
I didn't expect that!
[SUZUNE]
Kushida.
To be clear, I don't care
about you in the slightest.
[gasps] How could you say
something so mean to me?
Who cares?
I just wanted to know,
during the special exam,
someone told Ryuen
our VIP's identity.
Was it you?
What's that?
[AYANOKOJI] I knew that she
wasn't gonna sugar coat it,
but I didn't expect
her to be so upfront.
You don't have to confess.
I'm not looking for that.
But it wasn't me.
All the same,
as a member of Class D,
I need some kind of assurance
that you can be trusted.
I still don't get why you
think it's me betraying you.
All I want is for everyone
to make it to Class A together!
I promise, it wasn't me!
If you say so.
[KIKYO] I can't wait
for the sports festival!
[STUDENT 5AA] Don't worry,
I'll beat you next year!
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
Attention, students!
The third-year girls 100-meter
dash is about to begin.
Competitors, please assemble
at the designated location.
We got off to a strong start!
And now all we gotta do
is win this thing!
You guys have been
training for this!
We're gonna take first place
in every single event!
That'll show 'em!
He's expecting a
little much from us.
He does know we can't
win every event, right?
[KEN] Fight like your life
depends on it! Got it?
Come on, people!
I wanna see some excitement
in your eyes, okay?
You just need to follow my lead
and give it
everything you've got!
What's with him?
He's like a little kid trying
to show off to his crush.
[AYANOKOJI]
Is that...?
That's Sakayanagi.
She's one of the central
figures of Class A.
Class A is on Team Red with us.
We lucked out.
[SAKAYANAGI]
How are things coming along?
[HASHIMOTO]
Well enough, I suppose.
And how has Class D
been fairing?
On the whole, their students
are below average.
Ken Sudo is their only standout.
Seems he's desperately trying
to raise his class's morale.
Excellent. Just as anticipated.
[KEN]
All right!
Let's keep up the good work
and win this thing!
Who's with me?
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[SUZUNE]
It's a promising start.
[AYANOKOJI] Yeah. It's all
thanks to you and Sudo.
Your wins let our team take an
early lead in the competition.
[STUDENTS cheer]
[STUDENT 5AB gasps]
And there's him,
impressive as always.
My brother wins
at everything he does.
He's the embodiment
of perfection.
Damn it, get moving, Koenji!
Your event's next and you're
still just sittin' here?
Quit screwin' around!
First, she talks my
ear off, and now you.
It's ridiculous how you can't
do anything without my help.
What's that supposed to mean?
That cool girl you've been
working so hard to impress.
She was practically begging me
to compete in this festival.
[AYANOKOJI]
That's surprising.
I would've been more
than happy to participate.
But I'm feeling a little
under the weather today.
You son of a--
[HIRATA] It's almost time
for the next event!
If you're not there, it'll be
bad for the whole team!
Yeah, yeah, I know that.
--Asshole!
--[bang]
[KEN]
Hey! Anyone skips out,
you'll have to deal with me!
He's a little too into this.
He's scary!
[SOTOMURA] If you need me,
I'll be in the bathroom.
[airhorn blows]
[KEN]
Go!
All right! It's time
to show these losers
exactly what we're made of!
Don't let Sudo get past!
[gasps] Why are they
focused on me?
This is really bad, Ken!
--What?
--[BOYS grunting]
[ALBERT]
Back off!
What the hell?
What are those class A punks
trying to do, anyway?
Bastards. Just wait
till I get up.
Damn it!
Ryuen.
[ALBERT]
Too easy.
You buncha cheaters.
That's against the rules!
You know what?
That's a good look for you.
Class D belongs in the dirt.
[AYANOKOJI]
Are you all right?
I'm not gonna stand for this!
I'm gonna kick his ass!
Don't do it, you'll get
yourself disqualified.
So, it's only okay if
they break the rules?
They were careful to make it
all look like an accident.
Gonna be pretty hard
to prove otherwise.
[sighs] So much for
winning every event.
My apologies,
our class didn't keep
our part of the arrangement.
It's fine. We kinda
messed up, too.
Nah, he's right! Those guys
totally let us down!
What were you idiots even doing?
[STUDENT 5AC]
Look over there!
[STUDENT 5AD]
Is she okay?
No, Horikita!
I'll go back to the tent
for a first aid kit!
Right, and I'll find a teacher!
[AYANOKOJI]
Does it hurt?
If you're wondering if
I can still compete today,
don't worry about it.
[SUZUNE] Don't touch me!
What's wrong with you--
You shouldn't be walking
on this, let alone running.
We've got way bigger
things to worry about
than a bruised ankle.
That Class C girl
you collided with?
I've got a strong feeling
that she did it on purpose.
But still, focus on yourself.
I can take care of
my problems just fine.
I heard that you had
a talk with Koenji.
Big help that was.
He still flaked.
Maybe if I was
more like Kushida,
I might've been able
to convince him
to help out the class for once.
Well, that's surprising.
Never thought you'd say
you wish you were
more like Kushida.
I don't wanna hear it.
It's not like I always
hated her, you know.
Just don't tell
anyone what I said.
If you say so.
Try not to push
yourself too hard.
[SUZUNE] I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
[STUDENT chattering]
It looks like all the Class C
girls are targeting Horikita!
Aw, man! This is Ryuen's doing!
[STUDENT 5AF shouts]
I got it!
[gasps]
[IKE]
Ken! Your event's up next!
Got it!
Are you okay? Your leg.
I'll be fine, thanks.
What do you want?
Oh. That's good.
I just wanted to say that you
can leave everything to me!
I'll fight hard enough
for the both of us!
I'm very glad to hear that.
[KEN]
Yeah! Come on, you guys!
We'll knock that jerkass
Ryuen's head right off!
[AYANOKOJI]
It started well.
Our strategy was
to work in tandem
with the Class A students.
[groaning]
[AYANOKOJI] But Sudo let
Ryuen get under his skin
--and lost his cool.
--[airhorn blows]
Meaning, we lost the match.
I'm gonna teach that
son of a bitch a lesson!
Just try to ignore it.
Yeah, that's real easy
for you to say!
[AYANOKOJI]
Looks like the early lead we had
is completely gone, now.
Hey, Kiyotaka, you think
we can still win?
[AYANOKOJI]
Maybe.
Wait. Did you just
use my given name?
Well, I've been calling Hirata,
"Yosuke" for a little while now.
So, I thought I'd give it a try.
Oh, yeah. Horikita's
in bad shape, huh?
It's because Class C
is targeting her.
Is that the reason she
keeps getting matched up
against tough opponents?
It's not just a coincidence?
That's right, and
it's not just her.
From what it looks like,
our class's event
selections were leaked.
Seriously?
Yeah. There's a traitor
in our class
and they gave the list to him.
It seems that Ryuen
has two goals in mind.
The first is to put
their weakest students
up against our
powerhouses, like Sudo.
Then strategically assign
the rest of their class
to beat ours, accumulating
more points overall.
His second goal is to completely
crush Horikita's spirit.
No way.
With how far our class has
fallen behind at this point,
do we still even
have a chance to win?
[AYANOKOJI]
Win?
I've never had any
intention of winning.
Huh?
[AYANOKOJI] Our best course
of action in this moment
is to let this play out.
It's part of my plan.
The worse we lose
in the sports festival,
the better our position
will be later.
[KARUIZAWA]
I don't understand this at all.
[KEN grunts]
That smug bastard Ryuen
thinks he can get
away with cheating.
I'm gonna beat
the shit out of him!
You gotta calm down!
If you get disqualified
for fighting,
we're definitely
gonna lose it all!
Shut the hell up! Out of my way!
Don't forget, I'm the leader
as far as this is concerned!
Yeah, I know, but look
at how you're acting!
Would you follow someone
who lashes out like that?
'Cause I sure wouldn't.
What's with you guys?
Can't you see me bustin' my ass
to win this for our team?
[YUKIMURA]
Is that really the case?
What the--?
You keep saying you're
doing this for the class.
But it looks to me like
you're just trying show off
how great you are.
Shut your mouth!
[HIRATA] You're an irreplaceable
member of the team, Sudo!
Calm down.
You gotta look at
the bigger picture!
Don't tell me to calm down!
Everyone here
is counting on you.
Please, stop it!
[KEN]
I told you to shut up!
[YUKIMURA]
Hirata!
[MIT]
Is he okay?
Wow, Ken.
What's this?
What happened to you?
Oh. I tripped and fell,
clumsy me!
I'm all good now, thank you!
That's not what
it looks like to me.
But if that's your story,
then I won't pry any further.
[sighs]
[KEN growls] I'm outa here!
Screw this sports festival!
[IKE]
But, Ken!
What are we supposed
to do without you?
If he wants to leave, let him.
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
Attention, students.
We will continue with
the afternoon's events
after a 50-minute break.
Oh, right.
You're about to tell me it's my
job to get Sudo to come back.
Well, at least
you already know.
If he doesn't come back
before the break is over,
we'll have no hope of winning.
[SUZUNE]
What's the point?
It's not like
he'll listen to me.
I have enough to worry about,
I'm not gonna waste
my time coddling him.
[AYANOKOJI] How long are you
going to be utterly useless?
What do you mean by that?
What do you think?
I'm just calling it as I see it,
and you're useless.
[SUZUNE]
You're joking.
I know I'm much more useful than
all those idiots in our class!
If it wasn't for
all these accidents...
Yeah, so, does everything
that's happened to you,
and the whole class,
really strike you
as coincidental?
No, of course not!
Even I can tell that it
all leads back to Ryuen.
But there's nothing I can do!
My hands are tied
and I don't know
what my next step should be.
If you ask me, this is
the perfect chance
for you to acquire a weapon.
Weapon?
Moving forward,
you'll find there are limits to
what you can accomplish alone.
Even now, you're nearly
helpless by yourself.
That's not--
You need something that you
can use in these situations.
Ken Sudo can be that weapon.
In the right hands,
he'd find his worth.
Use him, in the same
way I use you.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] Tell me, what else
do you think you'd be doing?
Praying that your
ankle somehow recovers?
Good luck with that.
I'm not sure.
I'll leave you to
think it over yourself.
[KARUIZAWA]
Come on.
How long are you gonna
keep it a secret?
Can't you just tell us
who the traitor is?
Sorry, now's not the time.
Huh? But why is that?
Wait. If you knew
there would be a traitor,
we could've stopped them from
leaking out our class's list.
That's true.
But that's something you'd
have to ask Horikita about.
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
Where is Horikita right now?
I haven't seen her
in a little while.
She's busy, taking care of
something only she can do.
[KIKYO]
There you are! Hey, Horikita!
Oh, it's you.
Is something wrong?
Yeah! It's bad!
You know, Kinoshita,
the girl you ran into before?
They had to take her
to the nurse!
[gasps]
And now, they said they want you
to come to the
nurse's office, too!
All right, I'll go.
[gasps]
Hey there, Suzune.
[SUZUNE]
Wait. What are you doing here?
Poor Kinoshita was just
telling me what you did to her.
I can hardly believe that
you would stoop so low.
What are you trying to say?
Don't play dumb.
Kinoshita said that you
knocked her over on purpose!
That's just absurd!
Why would I do that?
When I fell,
you looked over at me
and then said,
"As if I'd ever let you
take first place."
[gasps] That isn't true!
You know I never said
anything like that!
[RYUEN]
Oh, come on.
Is this the kind of injury
that happens by accident?
It's shocking.
How cold-blooded does someone
have to be to do that?
[MINORI grunts]
I've had enough of this!
You're just trying to set me up!
And now it seems
you're trying to blame me
to cover up your own wrongdoing.
How sad can you get?
[SUZUNE] It's nearly
impossible for me to prove
that I didn't
intend to hurt her.
In other words,
it's The Devil's Proof.
I think it'll be best if
Kinoshita reports this incident
to the school, don't you?
The school?
You could try to
prove your innocence
and bring it up to
the Student Council.
Don't bother.
[SUZUNE] No matter what, I can't
make trouble for my brother.
Wait! Please, Ryuen!
I know Horikita, and she
isn't the kind of person
who'd try to injure
someone on purpose.
Kushida.
There's no way she
meant to hurt Kinoshita!
So, couldn't she just
say that she's sorry?
You know that could work.
Depending on how sorry she is.
I want a million points.
How's that sound?
All you have to do is pay up,
and this goes away.
It's only fair that Kinoshita
gets compensated for her injury.
Don't be ridiculous.
Is this what you were after?
Why you orchestrated
this whole thing?
Too bad. It looks like
we're gonna have to
bother the student
council, after all.
Hold on!
If I give you 1,000,000 points,
do you promise that you'll
never bring this up again?
Yeah. But, I'm afraid
you're too late.
That offer was only available
for a limited time.
[SUZUNE]
What?
[RYUEN] You really shouldn't
have turned it down.
[RYUEN]
Let me think.
Now, on top of the points.
I want you to grovel.
You're truly a
disgusting person.
Well, I'm not gonna force you
to make a decision right now.
Why don't I give you till
the end of the festival?
[SUZUNE]
I should've seen it coming.
I was careless and fell
right into his trap.
Right, I'll check
on that now, sir.
[gasps]
[SUZUNE]
I'm keenly aware that Class D
isn't pulling their weight.
And the effect that's having
on the entire team's score.
I know that the fault
lies in my leadership.
But I promise
I'll turn it around.
No matter what, I won't
bring you down with me.
I couldn't sense a shred
of sympathy from him,
but he stopped
and listened to me.
I'll have to be
satisfied with that.
[SUZUNE]
All right, then.
For Class D to have any
chance of coming back,
there's one more thing
I need to take care of.