[RYUEN] You can make this easier
on yourself, Karuizawa.
Why do you insist on putting
yourself through all this pain?
You're holding out
hope for someone
to come and save you.
Now that you're no longer
useful, you've been abandoned.
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
[RYUEN]
Come on.
Just tell me the name of
the mastermind, already!
Let's get this over with.
I'm curious, Karuizawa.
Back during the
cruise ship exam,
you agreed to
meet up with Hirata,
but were ambushed
by Manabe and her friends.
Any guesses why that happened?
Your precious mastermind
set you up.
He orchestrated it so he
could turn you into his pawn,
and you fell right
into his trap.
You're wrong.
[RYUEN] Do you get it now?
You have no value to him.
He won't be coming.
[KARUIZAWA] That can't be.
Ryuen's lying to me.
There's no way.
Was I just deluding myself?
He promised that
he'd protect me.
There's only one way you're
getting out of this situation.
So, tell me.
His name. Right?
Exactly.
All you have to do
is tell me who he is.
If you do that,
I promise I won't touch
another hair on your head.
But, if you refuse,
I'll keep going.
I'll drive you to
the brink of insanity,
and plunge you into hell.
And I'll see to it that
you drop out of school.
Now. Give me the
mastermind's name.
[KARUIZAWA] If I tell him...
will all of this really go away?
Ah, will I go back
to the way I was then?
His... name.
[RYUEN]
That's a good girl.
[KARUIZAWA]
I won't.
Even if it means that
I'll be losing my safe place
at this school, and that this
nightmare keeps on going.
No matter what.
I'll never tell.
Do your worst. I don't care.
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
Why go to such lengths
to protect someone who
made you their pawn?
Who knows? I wish
I could tell you.
I guess, even after
everything, somehow I...
I just can't bring
myself to betray him.
[RYUEN] Stubborn to the
very end. Huh, Karuizawa?
Yes. I don't care if
I end up regretting it.
I won't give in.
Your loyalty is admirable
in its own pathetic way.
But face it, he doesn't
care about you.
Too bad.
This is the end of
the road, Karuizawa.
Because I am going
to destroy you now.
[KARUIZAWA] I accept this.
I don't mind it at all.
As long as I can still help him.
That's enough for me.
I'm sorry, this is the
only thing I can do.
For as long as I can
remember, my entire life's
been nothing but
a pointless marathon.
But teaming up with Kiyotaka
to do all that stuff,
it was actually kind of fun.
That's why I don't
regret anything.
[KARUIZAWA]
Although,
if I'm being honest, a part of
me believed that he would
really keep his promise and
come running here to rescue me.
[KARUIZAWA] It's true that
you reap what you sow.
I deserve this.
Farewell to my fake self.
[HASEBE]
If we're gonna do karaoke.
I say we make it interesting
and compete for points!
Uh. No thanks, I'm good.
[SAKURA] You've been quiet.
Is something wrong?
Sorry. I'm gonna have to pass.
--[HASEBE] Really?
--[MIYAKE] You okay, dude?
I didn't sleep well last night
and it's catching up with me.
That sucks.
Go on without me,
I'll join next time.
[SAKURA]
Oh. Sure.
So what's this
"emergency" of yours?
I'm waiting.
A warning. There's
something going on
that I believe you
ought to know about.
If you do nothing,
then, after today,
Class D will lose any chance
it had of ever advancing.
Well, I'm listening.
You see, Ryuen is
targeting Karuizawa.
He wants to put on one of
his little plays, no doubt.
Your point?
If Ryuen manages
to break her spirit,
she'll likely drop
out of school.
And Class D won't be able
to recover from that loss.
You can stop
with the theatrics.
I know what you want.
To force me to save Karuizawa.
If I ask for your assistance,
would you help me?
[CHABASHIRA] You're expecting
too much. It's school policy.
Teachers can't meddle
in students' affairs,
not without a
damn good reason.
I wouldn't say that.
[CHABASHIRA]
What do you mean?
Well, I haven't asked you
to do anything yet. Right?
Correct.
[AYANOKOJI] Aren't you curious?
How this situation turns out?
[AYANOKOJI]
Sorry to make you wait.
[CHABASHIRA]
Manabu Horikita? Is this a joke?
What is he doing here?
Don't tell me he's
going to stop them.
Of course I'm not.
My only purpose here is
to deal with the aftermath.
Also, if the school has to
get involved in the matter,
he's agreed to testify
that Ryuen and Class C
started it all.
Consider it done. Don't
forget your promise to me.
Right. I'll do whatever I can
to help your sister get
onto the student council.
[MANABU]
So, we understand each other.
[AYANOKOJI] In that case,
whatever comes next
is up to you.
What do you plan on doing?
Tell me, how exactly do you
intend to resolve all this?
I see.
It seems his aim is to end
this conflict by himself.
No way.
I don't understand.
Is he planning to thwart
Ryuen's group all alone?
[AYANOKOJI]
Just relax.
I'm the one you're waiting for.
[RYUEN] Too bad. This is the
end of the road, Karuizawa.
Because I am going
to destroy you now.
[KARUIZAWA] I deserve this.
Farewell to my fake self.
Why are you here?
[KARUIZAWA]
You came.
Ayanokoji?
Forgive me, Karuizawa.
For being late.
But why are you...?
What are you doing here?
I promised you
if anything happened,
I'd be there to protect you.
Karuizawa sent me a message.
Asking me for my assistance.
Which means,
I'm the "mastermind"
who you've been looking
for this entire time.
You've gotta be kidding!
There's no way that you're
the person we're after!
Back on the island,
you didn't even think
twice before accepting.
During that test,
the camera you hid away
stopped working.
What? How'd you know?
[AYANOKOJI] Because I'm
the one who broke it.
I'm sure you just thought
it was caused by the rain.
[gasps]
The fear in her eyes has
completely disappeared.
So, it really is you.
The person controlling
Class D behind the scenes.
But, Ayanokoji,
I have to say, I expected
so much more from you.
I'm honestly
kind of disappointed.
Surely, you must know
that your best move
at this stage of the game is to
sacrifice your little pawn here.
But instead, you've decided
to throw yourself
into the lion's den.
I'm dying to know.
What plan have you cooked up
to get out of this?
Sorry. I don't have a plan.
There's no need. I just
came to get Karuizawa.
[RYUEN]
Hold your horses!
Why don't we play
a little first?
You must not think
very highly of us.
You see, that hurts
our feelings.
Wait! Don't do this!
In this world, there's
nothing more effective
than the power of violence.
No matter what clever
tricks you try to pull.
They'll be crushed before
the might of absolute violence.
[RYUEN] It looks like you still
have some fight left in you.
Don't worry, though,
I'll break that soon enough,
and that'll be
the end of Class D.
I don't suppose you'd
be willing to negotiate?
[RYUEN] Heh. You should've
thought about that
before you came alone.
Too late now.
I think there's been
some confusion.
I'm not the one in trouble here.
What?
There are only four of you.
You'll need more than that.
[RYUEN laughs]
Ishizaki.
[ISHIZAKI]
It's nothing personal.
I'm sure you understand.
[gasps] Ishizaki!
[ISHIZAKI grunts]
Impossible!
Hey, you better
take this seriously!
No way.
[ISHIZAKI] I'm gonna make
you pay for that!
[AYANOKOJI] You shouldn't
shout before you attack.
[ISHIZAKI yells]
[ALBERT groans]
Not bad!
You're much better than
I imagined you'd be.
[IBUKI]
Wait, was he always this strong?
So, have you
figured it out yet?
A situation where violence
is the only way to resolve it.
That's what I've wanted
from the beginning.
Huh?
[AYANOKOJI]
If my goal really was
to keep my identity a secret,
I never would've used
Manabe in the first place.
This whole time you've
been operating under
the assumption that I was
afraid of being discovered.
But that was all just an act
to draw me into a trap, right?
Took you long enough.
I'm surprised you didn't
figure it out sooner.
Is that so?
You're telling me that
we've just been dancing
in the palm of your hand?
What do you think
of that, Ibuki?
[gasps]
You are messed up.
Both you and Ayanokoji!
Just shut up!
I don't get what's going on.
But you're annoying!
[RYUEN]
I underestimated you.
I see that now.
And yet you've managed
to remain relatively calm.
Impressive.
Yeah, I wouldn't act like
I've already won, if I were you.
There's more to fighting
than fancy moves.
[coughs]
Not bad. Really.
You having as much fun as I am?
Let's keep on going.
I could do this all day!
Do you get it now?
This is all a game to me!
Everything, from crushing
the other classes,
and even luring out
Class D's mastermind.
Don't tell me this is
everything you've got!
Come on, entertain me!
[AYANOKOJI] He hasn't had
any formal training.
He's using his own unique style,
developed from actual fights.
Tell me, if you're as
good as you claim to be.
Why won't you fight out in the
open where others can see you?
I simply don't
wish to, that's all.
[RYUEN]
Then I'll have to make you!
[gasps]
[RYUEN]
No matter what it takes,
I'll drag you out and
force you into the light!
[RYUEN grunts]
Do you honestly think
you can still win?
[RYUEN]
Of course!
Losing was never an option!
Forgive me.
But I just don't
see that happening.
[RYUEN] You may beat me
today, that much is true.
But what about tomorrow?
Or the day after that?
So, you plan on
continuing this farce?
Sure do.
I'll be there 24/7,
waiting to strike
when you least expect it.
It seems you're not
afraid of failure.
[RYUEN] 'Course not!
What is there to be afraid of?
I've never felt fear
once in my life!
[RYUEN] Fear and pleasure are
just two sides of the same coin.
Emotions separated
by a hair's breadth.
[RYUEN]
Although people try to deny it,
this world runs on violence.
And a person's
strength is determined
by their capacity for it.
The truth is, there's only
one thing that can overturn
that law of nature,
and that is the power of death.
Fear is the natural
response of the weak!
It's simple: if you subject
a person to pain,
it's only a matter of time
before it turns to fear.
Interesting.
In that case, why don't you let
me test out your little theory?
[laughs] If that's
what you want.
I'm more than happy to oblige!
No! Kiyotaka!
Do you feel it now?
If I'm being completely
honest with you,
I've been trying to
experience this "fear"
you keep talking about.
Unfortunately,
I haven't felt it.
Don't lie to me!
[RYUEN groans]
[RYUEN]
Truly. You're something special.
Given all the power you
have at your disposal,
I don't understand
why you waste your time
with the garbage in Class D.
I can't say I've ever
thought about it that way.
I don't believe
that for a second.
[AYANOKOJI]
That's enough. Don't you think?
I believe you told me
earlier that you've
never once felt fear before.
[panting] You're damned right!
Sure, it hurts a little,
but that's it.
So, you're gonna have to do
a lot better than that.
Even if you beat me this time,
I'll never give up.
Ma-Mark my words!
No matter the time or place.
I'll be watching.
Waiting for my moment.
Of course, in the end, I'll be
the one who comes out on top!
All that's left is for you
to savor this moment.
Victory is just
within your grasp,
however fleeting it may be!
So, go on, Ayanokoji!
Show me exactly what
you're feeling right now!
Is it joy? Or anger?
Maybe even annoyance?
I want to see all the emotions
you're experiencing!
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
Why would a mundane task
like this make me feel anything?
[AYANOKOJI] There's no
emotion for me to show you.
[sputtering]
Yeah. I suspected
that this might happen.
[RYUEN sputters]
By now I'd think you'd realize
that even you have the
capacity to feel fear.
Kiyotaka.
I'm sorry for letting
you suffer for so long.
I'll be okay.
It's just that my legs are
still numb from the cold.
You must be disappointed.
Well, who wouldn't be?
You were using me
from the beginning.
That makes sense.
But then why didn't
you sell me out?
For myself.
That's it, no one else.
[KARUIZAWA]
I was so scared!
I really thought you
weren't coming!
You're okay. It's all over now.
I want you to know,
as of this moment,
the chains of your past that
once bound you are gone.
It's my fault that you got hurt.
I won't ask for
your forgiveness.
I just want you
to remember one thing.
Like today,
if anything happens,
I'll be there to save you,
no matter what.
You better. Okay?
[AYANOKOJI]
This will do.