[KARUIZAWA] I don't get it.
What are you talking about?
What did the names of the groups
have to do with the VIPs?
Were they supposed to be a hint?
We already explained it to you.
Now, now.
Remember how the groups
were named after planets?
That, along with
the student's names,
was how the VIP was
chosen for each group.
You following so far?
[KARUIZAWA]
Mm.
[HIRATA] Mars is the fourth
planet from the sun.
If we sort that group into
Japanese alphabetical order,
it goes Ayanokoji, Ichinose,
Ibuki, and Karuizawa.
So that's why I was
picked to be the VIP.
In the Earth group,
Kushida was chosen.
Third name listed for the
third planet from the sun.
I get it now,
but doesn't that method
seem a little...
Simplistic.
Exactly!
It's only "simple"
once you know it.
Yeah.
It's a lot harder to figure
it out during the test.
Even if you saw the
pattern in your class,
there's no way you'd
be able to prove it.
That's right.
But Ryuen did, somehow.
Based on their scores, Class C
must have found out the rule.
He still made a mistake.
I suspect that someone
sabotaged him.
From what it looks like,
he has all of Class C
under his control.
Who'd betray him?
It's just speculation, dictators
foster an unhappy populace.
What if the miscalculation
was because of
someone from another class?
[AYANOKOJI]
I wonder that, too.
[SUZUNE] Maybe, but I have
a hard time believing
that no one would
stand up to that bully.
[HIRATA]
You've got a good point.
I gotta say, I'm glad you
decided to come join us.
I mean it.
What choice did I have?
It's becoming apparent that
these exams require teamwork
to successfully clear.
That does seem like the trend.
So even if I don't like it,
it's important to
form connections
with the people
I need to rely on.
[AYANOKOJI]
Yes.
There are limits to what
a single person can do.
[CHABASHIRA] Today marks the
beginning of your second term.
Starting September
and continuing through
early October, you'll have
more gym classes than usual,
to prepare you for
the sports festival.
I've handed out your new
schedules along with
the rules for the festival.
You can find
the same information
posted on the school's website.
You may compare them
if you must.
'Scuse me!
Is the sports festival going to
be considered a special exam?
You're certainly free to think
of it as one, if it helps you.
Regardless of what you call it,
this will have a major influence
on your class's standing.
[SOTOMURA] This is cruel
and unusual punishment!
[KEN]
Yeah! My time to shine!
A sports festival.
[CHABASHIRA]
This year, the entire school
will be split into two teams.
Competing as either
Team Red or Team White.
All of you will be working
together with Class A
to make up Team Red.
We're teaming up with Class A?
With the second
and third years, too.
This sounds annoying.
Just leave it up to me,
I'll carry us to victory!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Hold on, guys!
Let's try to speak
one at a time.
Everyone! We can
discuss it later!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[AYANOKOJI]
You okay?
You're thinking about
how you'll finally
get a chance to see
him again, huh?
I don't have a clue
what you're talking about.
So, I'd drop it if I were you.
Right.
Make sure that you fully
understand the rules.
It says all events are
classified as either
"mandatory" or "voluntary."
[AYANOKOJI] Generally
speaking, voluntary events
award more points
for participating
than the mandatory ones.
As a word of advice,
you should try your hardest
to place well in every event.
The penalty for
losing is severe.
[IKE]
Question!
What's this about bonuses
for the top three places?
[YAMAUCHI] There's something
else about adding points
to written exams?
Think of it as an incentive
to win your events.
[YAMAUCHI]
Oh!
Those who do well enough
will be awarded bonus points
that can be added to
their next written exam.
I'm sure a number
of you could use them.
Seriously?
[STUDENTS gasp, chatter]
[AYANOKOJI]
Sounds too good to be true.
There has to be a catch.
Those who place
in the bottom ten
will be penalized.
Uh. Wait. Hold on a second.
It says there'll be a penalty?
The ten first-year students
in each event who perform
the worst will have ten points
deducted from their
total score on their
next written exam.
[STUDENTS]
Say what?!
So we can lose
exam points, too?
Dude, this sucks!
Why did they crush my dream?
Does that mean we can fail
even with a good score?
The handout I gave you
includes a list
of all the events.
It'll be up to you to pick
the ones you compete in.
[AYANOKOJI]
There are 13 events total.
This feels like a lot of events.
They expect us to do
all of this in one day?
Yes, of course.
The sports festival
will be the only thing
happening on that day.
Prepare yourselves.
Each event will be a test of
your strength and athleticism.
It'll be up to you to decide who
will participate in each event.
Once you've made
your selections,
mark them down and
turn it in to me.
How much of the planning
are we expected to do?
It's all up to you.
Absolutely everything.
From how many voluntary
events you enter
to which heat each
person will be in.
[STUDENTS murmur]
[AYANOKOJI]
Hm...
[SUZUNE] In both of the
previous special exams,
there were multiple
ways to pass.
The school likes
to give us options.
That's why there has
to be more at play.
I dunno.
I've got a feeling
this sports festival
is going to be different
from the other tests.
You sure?
It seems like any other
special exam to me.
It's structured
just like the last two.
Each class can earn
or lose points.
You're not wrong.
On paper, it is similar.
But the principle behind it
is very different.
Think of it this way.
The first two special exams
had different premises,
but at their core, they were
testing our intelligence.
And you're saying the
sports festival isn't?
[AYANOKOJI] Exactly,
Ms. Chabashira even told us
that our strength
and athletic abilities
were the only things
that mattered
for the sports festival.
We can't trick
our way through it.
[AYANOKOJI]
If we want to win this,
we'll need to make sure
our class is fully prepared.
It's the only option.
I was talking about that!
How we should prepare!
You were looking for loopholes,
a shortcut to victory.
Like having the other team's
students miss their events
or by finding a way
to make them drop out.
--That's--
--[AYANOKOJI] I know.
You want, more than
anything, to win.
I see. So, you're
saying we'll have to
beat the other classes through
more traditional means?
If that's how you wanna
take it, be my guest.
I'm tellin' you, you guys are
way overthinking this thing!
I know I can easily win
all those events, trust me!
Plus, if I win, the class wins!
It benefits everybody here!
I guess so?
Well, if he says he can do it.
Honestly, I don't see a problem
with Sudo competing
in all the voluntary events.
Then it's settled!
You won't regret it--
I'm gonna win every single
one of those events!
Now that that's decided, let's
go back to the main question.
How will we determine who gets--
[SUZUNE] Hold on.
I have an alternate proposal.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Between those two options,
I do prefer the skill method.
But still, there's no
guarantee it'll be enough
for us to beat
the other classes.
[HIRATA]
I guess that's true.
The idea itself is sound,
though it could be better.
We should still put
our athletic students
in the events they're good at.
But for the mandatory events,
we need to be more strategic
with whoever we select.
If we do it right, we can
easily gather points.
Just think, instead of
putting two fast people
in the same race together,
we should pair them
with someone slow, to
guarantee better placements.
[SHINOHARA]
Wait a minute. That sounds good.
But doesn't that put
the non-athletic students
in our class
at a disadvantage?
We wouldn't stand a chance
at earning those bonus points.
Sacrificial pawns
who's fate is to lose!
Coming in last place would cost
them their private points.
It's hard to believe
they'd agree to this plan.
The benefits of our class
winning far outweigh that loss.
What's the problem here?
But you're telling us
to throw away our chance
to earn extra exam points!
You can't just use
people like that!
I understand your concerns
about this strategy.
It's unfair!
But your priorities
are misplaced.
Instead of trying
to earn exam points,
focus on your studies so you
don't have to rely on them!
--[STUDENTS murmur]
--[KEN] No!
Only the top three places
get those points,
earning them was
never a sure thing.
You need to face reality.
What event do you think you
can place third or better in?
[SHINOHARA]
It... could happen.
[KARUIZAWA]
Um. I have some thoughts!
Horikita's suggestion.
I'm sorry, but I can't
go along with it.
And what's your
issue with my idea?
Well, your proposal just
doesn't sit right with me.
Your objection to it is
based on your feelings?
[KARUIZAWA]
Fine. I don't understand it!
[SUZUNE]
I thought I was being clear.
What are you not understanding?
[KARUIZAWA]
Um, all of it?
Why don't you dumb it down
so even I get it?
[sighs]
Oh, yeah. That's
right, I forgot.
You don't like
dealing with idiots.
Stop putting words in my mouth!
But it's the truth, isn't it?
I agree with Shinohara!
How could you say that you
want your classmates to fail?
It's for the greater good.
Then you berated the people
who wanted extra exam points!
How do you expect our
class to work together
with that attitude?
It's not like we
have another choice.
[sighs] I guess I should've
expected that from you.
Well, what do you
think, Kushida?
Huh? My thoughts?
Yeah.
This is kind of
a tricky situation.
Because I feel like
I can understand
where both sides
are coming from.
In a perfect world, we'd find
a way to combine both ideas!
So, everyone, regardless
of how they place
in their events, can be happy!
That would be the best solution!
True.
Yeah, something like
that would be nice.
Well, I had already
considered that.
There's a way we
can satisfy everyone.
While coming in last place
results in a penalty,
placing in the top three
awards you private points.
The points that our
top placers earn
can offset any
points we'll lose.
As long as we work together,
no one loses out.
Yeah! That's a great idea!
Ugh. But it only helps
for private points!
Your proposal is still unfair!
What do you think
about it, Sato?
If Karuizawa is against
the idea, then I am, too.
Same with me.
I'll go with whatever
Karuizawa thinks we should do!
Did you not listen
to a word I said?
You're against it
only because she is?
That's irrational!
My idea is the most efficient
way for our class to win
as many points as
possible in this test!
[KARUIZAWA] You act like
you know everything.
But at the end of the day,
I, along with plenty
of other people in
the class, don't agree!
You're a cruel person, Horikita.
[SATO]
She really is.
[MATSUSHITA]
Yeah.
[MIT] It's no wonder that she
doesn't have any friends.
Hey!
[HIRATA]
Both of you, calm down!
This argument isn't going
anywhere, and since neither side
is budging, let's settle
this with a vote.
Yup! That's exactly
what we need!
[HIRATA] Horikita's suggestion
is to focus entirely
on optimizing our picks.
While Karuizawa's suggestion
is to let people
choose their own events.
Let's have a show of hands.
First up, who here
agrees with Horikita?
[HIRATA]
All right, ten votes.
Hey, Ayanokoji!
I'm abstaining.
Don't look at me like that.
[HIRATA] And next, if you
agree with Karuizawa's plan
for how we'll pick events,
then rase your hands now.
[HIRATA]
Thank you all.
It looks like we have a winner.
With ten votes for Horikita,
and eight votes for Karuizawa.
Everyone else abstaining.
[KEN]
Heck yeah!
[HIRATA]
All right.
Now that we've
decided our approach,
let's hammer out the
rest of the details!
Sure!
Put me down for every event!
Maybe we can just have Sudo
win the whole festival!
Oh, yeah!
You can leave
everything to the Ken!
Don't you think
it's super cute?
Yeah, it totally is!
[laughs] Thanks!
[KARUIZAWA]
Wait a sec!
I did what you asked me to do.
Mind telling me what
the point of it was?
Only the top three places
get those points--
earning them was
never a sure thing.
You need to face reality.
What event do you think you
can place third or better in?
[SHINOHARA]
It... could happen.
That was a good argument
you came up with on the spot.
I still don't get why you
told me to argue with Horikita.
I actually agreed with her idea.
And what was the point of
asking Kushida for her opinion?
Come on, don't you think
I deserve to know?
If I had to explain myself
for every little thing,
it'd be a pain.
Anyway, I have secrets
I'd like to keep.
There's something that I've
been meaning to ask you about.
What's your reason
for doing this?
[AYANOKOJI] I'd like to raise
Class D's standing.
If you asked Horikita,
she'd say the same.
That isn't what I meant!
I wanna know what
you're actually after.
[AYANOKOJI]
I wonder.
Currently, my goal is to
put Class D in a position
where they could
take Class A's spot.
Are you satisfied with that now?
And you really think
you can make that happen
by pulling everyone's strings?
It's understandable that you
wouldn't just believe me.
Especially without any proof.
That's why I'll
create a situation
that'll show you what I mean.
During this sports festival,
one of our classmates
will betray our class.
[gasps]
That's right.
The traitor will likely
share information
amongst the other classes.
Wait-- Really?
Well, if that's the case, we
should do something about it!
We will, when the time comes.
But what are we waiting for?
Wouldn't it be safer to expose
the traitor right away?
Just trust me.
Now, go. We don't want
to draw attention.
[KARUIZAWA] All right,
what did you get again?
[KARUIZAWA laughs]
Looks like 11.5!
[KEN yells]
Look at that! 82.4!
[STUDENTS gasp]
Dude, you're some
kind of monster!
That's some nice
grip strength!
I've been working out
a lot lately!
So, you know.
Hey, Koenji, why don't
you give it a try?
No thanks, think I'll pass.
Tch. Whatever.
Here, your turn.
[KEN]
Something wrong?
What do you think the
average grip strength is?
Huh? I dunno, like 60?
Sixty, huh?
[AYANOKOJI]
When it comes to grip strength,
It's not necessarily
proportional
to the size of your arms.
It mainly relies on
two different muscles
in the forearm which are
called the brachioradialis
and flexor carpi radialis.
If you can focus on building
up those two muscles,
you can increase your strength.
In other words, with enough
exercise and muscle training,
a person's grip strength can
reach over 100 kilograms.
That should be enough.
This is the best I got.
What was it?
[AYANOKOJI]
60.6.
Oh, wow, you're a lot stronger
than you look, Ayanokoji!
Oh really? Isn't that
just kinda average?
[HIRATA] I'd say that you're
far above average!
It's like 45.
Or maybe even 50
on the high end.
Just 42.6? Can we fudge
the number to like 50?
Sorry! You got a 42.6!
[IKE groans]
[AYANOKOJI]
I see. So, 60 is a bit too high.
[HIRATA]
All done!
All right! The results!
Yeah! I'm in all
the voluntary events!
Everyone, remember,
these assignments
are highly sensitive,
so only write down
the events you're in!
Please make sure this
information doesn't get out.
[ONODERA]
Okay.
[KEN]
Keep pulling!
Don't you dare
think about giving up!
Good! Keep your
center of gravity low!
Yeah. Okay!
[KEN]
Put your backs into it!
Pull like your lives
depend on it!
We have to win!
[YAMAUCHI]
We're trying!
[KEN]
I can't hear you!
Hey, slow down a little.
You're running way too fast.
So that's why our
rhythm was off.
Because you can't keep pace.
[gasps]
Why should I have to hold back
to match your mediocrity?
Instead of asking me to slow
down, you need to speed up.
[AYANOKOJI]
Can we talk?
Talk about what?
Listen, I know you
may not like it,
but you're gonna need to learn
to compromise with the others.
If I don't push them,
we won't place high enough
during the sports festival.
For the three-legged race,
it's more logical to make
the slower runners go faster,
than the other way around.
[AYANOKOJI] You're not
budging on that position?
[SUZUNE]
No.
If that's the way
that you think,
then you might have a hard
time finding a partner.
If they can't match my rhythm,
I don't want them as a partner.
So, that works out for me.
Why don't we make an attempt?
What do you mean by that?
Let's run a three-legged race.
And what good would that do?
The sports festival
has a co-ed event.
I would like to see for myself
if we'd make a good team or not.
You seriously think you
can keep up with me?
Quit dreaming.
Come on, just this once.
I promise that I'll keep up
with your rhythm.
Whatever. Okay.
Let's get this over with.
Hey, hold on!
It shouldn't be hard
for you to match my pacing.
Well, duh. I've already got it!
[AYANOKOJI] It's not about
how fast you can run.
Your problem is that you aren't
paying attention
to your partner.
You need to look at them and
get a feel for their rhythm.
Focusing only on your own pace
is what's holding you back.
Oh, right.
You'll be coming
with me tomorrow.
What for?
We'll be gathering
intel on Team White.
It'll be you, me,
and someone else.
[SUZUNE]
Who is it?
[AYANOKOJI]
Kushida.
What? But why?
During the last test,
there was somebody
who betrayed the Earth group.
It was her.
[gasps]
[HIRATA] Well, I appreciate you
helping everyone out, too!
Of course!