To tell you the truth,
the real reason I called you
was so that I could apologize.
[KARUIZAWA]
Apologize?
Yes.
It's my fault that you've
now a potential target.
[KARUIZAWA] Huh? Where's
all this coming from?
[AYANOKOJI]
Things have changed.
There's no need for me
to try to bring up
Class D's standing anymore.
What was motivating me
before is gone.
[KARUIZAWA]
I see.
So you're gonna go back
to laying low from now on?
Yeah. I'll leave it
up to Horikita and Hirata
to take care of everything.
[KARUIZAWA]
Makes sense.
Well, this means you're
free now, doesn't it?
[AYANOKOJI]
I guess it does.
Although, there's something
you should know.
I won't be contacting
you again.
[gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
Good morning.
Hey.
[MIYAKE] Yeah, but I got
club stuff to do.
[MIYAKE]
Sup, Kiyotaka!
[AYANOKOJI]
Morning.
[MIYAKE]
As chipper as ever, I see.
[AYANOKOJI]
Sorry. Not a morning person.
[SUZUNE] So, what was it that
you wanted to propose?
I was thinking, what if we make
the study groups
an ongoing thing--
[slam]
[IKE]
Guys, look!
You assholes lost?
Get the hell outa here!
Hey, Ryuen. What are
you doing here?
Since when do I need
any special reason
to pay a little visit to
my neighbors in Class D?
You all can relax now.
I don't bite often!
Wouldn't be a
big deal elsewhere,
but this school is different.
Since we have to compete
against the other classes.
And here I was thinking
we could start being friends.
It's time.
Y'see that?
Is it just me, or does it look
like they're up to something?
--Wanna check it out?
--[YAMAUCHI] No way!
You don't think they're gonna
try to mess with Koenji, do you?
Class C's gone crazy!
This is bad.
Agreed.
Hey, so...
Do you think we should
go after them?
Like, with as many
people as possible.
You know, just in case they
try something nefarious?
Probably.
Having cameras around wouldn't
be enough to stop Ryuen.
[YUKIMURA]
I'll go, too!
You're right, a few of us
won't be enough.
[AYANOKOJI] I think it might
be best if you stay here
to hold down the fort.
If Ike and Yamauchi
come along,
they'll only escalate
the situation.
You can keep them here
and make sure
they don't do something stupid.
That's a good point.
All right, then.
If anything happens,
safety first.
Hey! What are you doing?
What's this? We've got
ourselves an audience.
Well, it doesn't matter.
As you can all plainly see,
we haven't done anything.
I'm curious what you're after.
Forgive me, but I don't
recall ever conducting
any business with Class C.
Well, I wanted to talk to you.
The "weirdo."
'Scuse me?
You're not referring
to me, are you?
[RYUEN] Who else would
I be talking about?
You don't have high
opinion of me, it seems.
I'll pretend I didn't
hear your slander!
A sign of my magnanimity.
In case you didn't know,
I've got a big date
I've gotta get ready for!
So, I'd appreciate it
if you kept this brief.
[whistle]
It's too bad, but you're
gonna have to delay
those plans of yours.
[KOENJI]
Huh?
[KOENJI] How terribly lowbrow!
What've you done?
Do you know how much
this mirror cost me?
Sorry. But accidents happen.
That's enough! Stop this!
Just pipe down, there, Suzune.
Right now, I'm playing
a game with Koenji.
I thought I heard
something brewing.
But I certainly
did not anticipate
seeing all of you here!
Hey, Sakayangi.
Seems to me that you came here
right in the nick of time.
Just a coincidence.
I happened to be passing by.
As if I'd believe that.
But now that I'm here,
I'm curious what
you were discussing.
Christmas plans, perhaps?
That's enough from you.
Your turn will come, just wait.
[SAKAYANAGI] Oh, come on,
after I came all this way?
There's no harm in letting me
join in on the fun, is there?
[RYUEN]
Fine, you can stay if you want.
Just don't interrupt.
[KOENJI] Not that I mind
having a larger audience.
But you still haven't said
why you've stopped me.
I'm a very busy man.
Please, don't waste my time.
Sorry about that.
Let's get down to brass tacks.
Though, I can already
guess what it is.
It seems that
somebody from Class D
has been interfering
with your plans of late.
And you're trying
to find out the identity
of this mysterious mastermind.
That's exactly right.
[KOENJI]
In that case, I can assure you
I'm not the person you're after.
Truth be told,
I couldn't care less
where any of the classes
ultimately end up.
Up to this point,
I haven't put any effort
into clearing these
so-called special exams.
Nor do I ever intend to.
So, what could you possibly
gain from confronting me?
Thing is, your story
doesn't quite add up.
What about the VIP
test on the ship?
Doesn't fit your narrative.
I know what you did back there.
I was just killing time.
Plus, turning in the answer
early had the added benefit
of freeing me from those
insufferable get-togethers.
[RYUEN] Well, sure, you say
that, but how can I be sure
you haven't participated
in any of the other exams?
What's more, that little stunt
you pulled on the cruise ship
only proves that you're
more than qualified
to take control of Class D.
Correct?
I'd be inclined to agree!
Although, if that's all
it took to convince you
that I'm who you're looking for,
I must say, you're only
demonstrating the limits
of your mental capacity.
Moronic.
That's how I would describe
your thought process.
I suppose that's fair.
And if everything you've
just told me is the truth,
that would make you
entirely irrelevant
to my investigation, then.
Exactly! I do
appreciate the fact
that you're quick on the
uptake, my dear Dragon Boy.
[SAKAYANAGI giggles]
Hold on, a thought
just occurred to me.
What if I decided to just
force the truth out of you?
There you go again with
your nonsensical ideas.
You wouldn't do that, not with
all these witnesses nearby.
That's where you're wrong.
You see, I'm capable
of doing anything,
even if you have witnesses.
I truly couldn't care less.
All right, then.
Since you're so insistent,
let's say, for the
sake of argument,
you decided to use brute force.
I'd have no choice but
to defend not only myself,
but my pride as well.
Suffice it to say, I can't
guarantee the safety
of anyone who comes after me.
[RYUEN] You really think
you can beat me all alone?
[KOENJI]
But of course, I can't imagine
any reason why I couldn't.
[RYUEN]
I see.
The way that brain of yours
thinks is completely insane!
But I'll believe your story.
I'm glad to have this
misunderstanding sorted out.
[RYUEN]
Just tell me one thing, Koenji.
If it's not you, then who is it?
You'd tell me if your
class's mastermind was among
the crowd here, wouldn't you?
[KOENJI] I wouldn't dare dream
of depriving you of your fun.
[SAKAYANAGI]
So that was what this was about?
A little birdie told me that
our dear Dragon Boy here
was tearing his hair out
looking for a particularly
clever member of Class D.
I guess it was true af--
I already told you to keep
out of this, Sakayanagi.
And another thing. If you ever
try to call me that again,
I'll kill you.
Don't tell me you're
embarrassed by it!
If you ask me, I think it's
a lovely nickname for you.
Dear Dragon Boy.
Oh, my goodness,
did that upset you?
I tried to tell you
what would happen.
Seems you need to get
your ears checked.
What are you doing?
You just attacked someone!
Are you insane?
Hashimoto, did someone
attack you? Tell us!
Oh. No. I just accidentally
tripped and fell.
[SAKAYANAGI]
And there you have it!
Everything's okay!
You're just as crazy as he is!
What's wrong with you?
[SAKAYANAGI]
I'm terribly sorry, Ryuen.
It's just a harmless joke.
[KOENJI humming]
There he goes.
You sure about this?
Trust me, if he was
the one I was looking for,
he wouldn't be going anywhere.
If you ask me, he's
acting pretty suspicious.
On top of that, he's almost
impossible to read.
How can you be sure
he wasn't lying
about not being the mastermind?
His thought process
is completely
incompatible with mine.
And from how he
treats his classmates,
do you really think he
would scheme with Suzune?
I agree, he doesn't seem
like that kind of person.
But then what was the
point of going after him
in the first place?
Hey.
I'm curious what you
think about Koenji.
Why the hell would we tell
you anything, you jerk wad?
Just get lost already!
Control your dog, Suzune.
What was that?
I'm warning you.
I have half a mind to
report this to the school.
Leave our class alone.
You can try.
But it's pointless since
I haven't broken any rules.
And after today, I can
take yet another name
off my list of suspects.
It's only a matter of time
before I find who's behind you.
I don't really care why you're
harassing Class D's students.
But it's time for you to stop.
From now on, I want you to stay
away from me and my classmates.
[RYUEN] What are you
gonna do if I say no?
Find some way to
make me back off?
I'd love to see you try.
But don't you worry,
we're already in the endgame.
I can't wait for you
to see the finale.
[AYANOKOJI] It looks like both
Ichinose and Sakayangi
have started to show
an interest in me.
As long as I'm careful, I should
be able to fade out of view.
But there's still
one obstacle left.
Ryuen.
After all that, he still
never tipped his hand.
My first little fox hunt ended
as a complete failure.
What's the point of this?
Let's just drop it.
[RYUEN] I refuse.
Not until I destroy him.
He managed to stay hidden today,
but he won't be able
to avoid me forever.
The hunt continues.
After the Paper Shuffle,
I assigned watchdogs
to keep tabs on specific
Class D students
who I deemed worthy.
Even though they just
watched, their presence
sowed unease and tension
through Class D.
After only two weeks,
I'm sure he's starting
to feel the pressure.
There're no signs
of cracking yet.
But I wonder how much longer
he can hide behind Suzune.
Why are you doing this?
I'm just enjoying myself.
The truth is,
it makes my heart race.
This burning feeling in my chest
is like finding my first love.
So, are you gonna share
why you had us come
all the way out here?
[RYUEN]
You worried?
I like to know
what I'm getting into.
[RYUEN]
You'll find out soon enough.
I've called the bait here.
I've also sent an email
to the mastermind.
[IBUKI]
Do you really think he'll come?
Who's to say?
Worst-case scenario,
neither of them shows up.
Which would be entertaining
in its own way.
So, what's a "good scenario"?
[RYUEN]
To catch the mastermind.
Or...
...crush the bait if
he doesn't play along.
[IBUKI] Right, good luck
getting away with it
with all these security
cameras around.
[RYUEN]
That won't be a problem.
[spray can rattling]
[spray can hissing]
[IBUKI]
It's freezing!
Now we can conduct
our business in private.
But wait, won't you
get in trouble?
I'm just pulling
a harmless prank.
I'll get a slap on
the wrist at most.
Albert.
[RYUEN]
Take your position.
If the bait comes,
let it through.
If anyone unexpected shows up,
call me immediately.
[ISHIZAKI grunts]
That's heavy!
Hope you're right about this.
It'd suck if the bait no showed.
[RYUEN]
Or, she'll show.
The card I hold is far too
important for her to ignore.
Now, all that's left is to wait.
[RYUEN]
Are you alone?
[KARUIZAWA] Well, that's what
it said in your message, right?
Yeah, I came by myself,
just like you asked.
And what the heck
was that email about?
It didn't make any sense!
[RYUEN] Do I really need
to spell it out for you?
I don't know what Manabe and
those other girls said to you.
I have no clue what
you're talking about!
Then why didn't you
ignore my message?
Well, because...
...I just didn't want you to go
spreading a bunch of lies
and rumors about me.
[RYUEN]
Why should I believe you?
I'm telling you the truth!
Quit playing dumb.
Everyone here knows that,
before you reinvented
yourself for high school,
you were the victim
of constant bullying.
[KARUIZAWA]
No, you're wrong!
What are you doing?
Cut it out!
Stop--I said stop!
Let me go! Right now!
Hey, that hurts! Ow!
[KARUIZAWA]
What do you want from me?
I don't know anything,
so there's no point
in threatening me!
I'm just killing time.
If you don't let me
go this instant,
I'm reporting you all
to the school!
Sure. Go for it.
[gasps]
[RYUEN] But I don't think
you can afford to do that.
You wouldn't want everyone
to know the truth about you.
[RYUEN]
Karuizawa.
I'd like for you to tell me
the name of the person
who's pulling you
and Suzune's strings.
If you do that,
you can leave and I'll never
bring up your past again.
I still don't know where
this is coming from.
Class D's mastermind stopped
Manabe from bullying you.
He went out of his way
to save you.
What are you talking about?
I've never been bullied!
And I don't know anything
about this "mastermind"!
[RYUEN]
I have the video.
I had Manabe show it to me.
And according to her,
the mastermind used it
to make her leave you alone.
That's a lie!
[RYUEN]
Of course.
All that means you know
the mastermind's identity.
Who is it?
[RYUEN] All I want from you
is a name, Karuizawa.
I'm not really interested in
airing out your dirty laundry.
You can make this
easy on yourself.
No, I told you! But you're
not listening to me!
I don't know what
you're talking about!
I see, he must be someone
important to you.
Go ahead and keep asking me
the same questions!
My answer isn't gonna change!
Untie me already!
I'm freezing to death in here!
Well then, you've left me
with no other choice.
I'm going to tell every
single friend you've made
at this school the truth
about your past.
Is he worth losing all of that?
You're just bluffing.
Don't treat me like I'm stupid!
You think there's someone out
there pulling my strings, right?
And the only reason
you're coming after me
is because you can't figure out
who they are by yourself!
Which means I'm your only chance
of uncovering this
mastermind of yours!
You think I'm bluffing?
I see. If I expose your past,
I lose my leverage.
Exactly! Get it now?
I'm never gonna
tell you anything,
so you're better off
just letting me go!
We'll see. I'll get
that name from you.
Don't worry about that.
[RYUEN]
No matter what it takes.
[gasps]
Ishizaki.
[ISHIZAKI]
Right!
[KARUIZAWA]
Wait! What are you doing now?
Hey! Hold on a second!
You don't have to do this!
Just let me go!
[KARUIZAWA]
Please, stop it.
[RYUEN] On the surface, this
school appears to be governed
by strict rules.
But in reality, it's not.
We're allowed to use violence,
to a certain degree.
Tamper with the cameras.
Bribe upperclassmen.
And make deals
with other classes.
The school prohibits
these things outwardly,
while at the same time,
implicitly encourages them.
It's obvious to
anyone with a brain.
And it's up to us to find the
boundaries of what's permitted
through trial and error.
Let's see where
that boundary lies.
That's enough. We'll move on.
--[water splashing]
--[KARUIZAWA grunting]
[RYUEN] Trauma, by its
very nature, is something
that triggers faster
through experience,
rather than just words.
I will break you down until
there's nothing of you left.
[door chiming]
[MIYAKE]
Kiyotaka!
I was thinking we
could go do something!
Oh! You mean like karaoke?
That's a great idea!
Well, we managed to
pass our second term!
I think we all deserve a break!
You in, Kiyo- pon ?
Sounds like fun.
[KARUIZAWA coughs]
Stop it. Please, no more.
[RYUEN] I love seeing you
this way, Karuizawa.
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
No, please. Stop it.
Ishizaki.
[KARUIZAWA]
No.
I'll ask you one more time.
Who's Class D's mastermind?
There's no one!
They're not real.
I promise! Please, no more!
That is some resolve
you've got.
Oh, that's right!
I understand now.
Since you've been
bullied your whole life,
your tolerance for pain
must be a lot higher, huh?
[IBUKI]
Hey.
The second we get her
to tell us his name,
I'm leaving.
[RYUEN] This turned out to be
more fun than I thought.
I've decided.
I'll destroy Kei Karuizawa.