I have news.
The special exam results.
After spending an entire week
on a deserted island,
--the winners were...
--[MANABU] Class D.
[AKANE]
Yes.
[MANABU] How will you overcome
this next challenge,
Ayanokoji?
That man who called me.
Who, I am sure you've figured
out by now, is your father,
said "Someday, Kiyotaka will
choose to leave the school
of his own accord."
[AYANOKOJI]
"Everything humans do
is in service towards
some goal." Indeed.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENTS chattering, laughing]
[GIRL 201A laughing]
[GIRLS laughing]
Now this is what I call
a summer break!
Heck yeah!
[YAMAUCHI laughs]
[yelps]
Watch where you're splashin'!
Damn it, knock it off!
[KIKYO] Hey, Horikita!
What are you up to?
[SUZUNE]
I thought it'd be obvious.
Is the book good?
It's not a romance novel, is it?
Of course not.
Must be nice.
[HIRATA]
Ayanokoji! You busy?
I was wondering.
A couple of us are gonna get
lunch, if you wanted to join us.
I'm good, thanks.
All right, what if it
was just you and me?
I'll pass.
I get the feeling Karuizawa
wouldn't be too happy with that.
[KARUIZAWA]
Hirata! There you are!
Ready to go?
Karuizawa.
Hey, so, mind if
Ayanokoji comes along?
Huh? Do we have to?
He's always so gloomy. He'll
just bring the whole mood down!
[ANNOUNCER 201A]
Attention, students.
We have an important
announcement.
The second special examination
will begin shortly.
All first-year students on board
will receive an email
from the school administration.
Please ensure that you read it
carefully and follow
the instructions.
[SUZUNE]
"Regarding the special exam:
Make sure you arrive
at your assigned room
at the time indicated below."
[AYANOKOJI] "Students who are
more than ten minutes late
may be subject to penalties."
Looks like I have no choice.
"Come to room 504
by 6PM today."
[doorbell rings]
[MASHIMA]
The door's unlocked.
[AYANOKOJI]
Yukimura and Sotomura?
I was wondering who else
was gonna show up!
After Ayanokoji,
there's one spot left!
Something doesn't feel right.
--Yeah.
--[MASHIMA clears throat]
We're waiting on the
last person to get here.
Please refrain from talking.
[KARUIZAWA]
Sorry, I'm late!
Ew, seriously?
Don't tell me I'm stuck
in a group with you guys.
Enough chatter.
Hurry up and take your seat!
[KARUIZAWA]
Whatever.
[AYANOKOJI]
What's got her so upset?
[MASHIMA]
Now that everyone's here,
I'll explain the rules
of this special exam.
All first-year students
will be split
into eight different groups,
each named after a planet
in the solar system.
You all will be part of "Mars."
Look here. Every group
will include students
from each of the classes.
[AYANOKOJI] There're 14
people in each group.
[KARUIZAWA]
We have to work with Class C?
Plus, three from
Class A and Class B!
But aren't we supposed
to be competing with them?
[AYANOKOJI] For this test, we're
no longer students of Class D,
and instead, we'll be acting
as members of the "Mars" group.
Our test results will go towards
the group's overall score.
The exam will last four days,
with day three set aside
for everyone to rest.
At 8AM, the school will send out
an email to one member
of each group,
who will then be "the VIP"
Two times a day,
the group will meet up
and have a discussion and try
to find out the VIP's identity.
Thirty minutes after
the sixth discussion ends,
everyone will mail their
answer to the school.
Each person can only
submit one guess.
For obvious reasons,
the VIP isn't allowed
to send in an answer.
Let's see. It says here...
There are four scenarios.
"In case one, if everyone in
the group, aside from the VIP
and their classmates, correctly
guesses the VIP's identity.
Then all members of the
group will be awarded
500,000 private points.
And The VIP will receive
an extra 500,000 points."
Whoa! That's crazy!
So, the VIP gets
1,000,000 points?
"In case two,
one or more people, aside from
the VIP and their classmates,
fails to submit an answer in
time, or guesses incorrectly.
If this happens, then only
the VIP will be awarded
500,000 private points."
[AYANOKOJI]
So that's how it is.
Case two represents the scenario
where the VIP keeps
their identity hidden.
And if they succeed, they'll be
the only person in the group
to get points.
[MASHIMA] Just so you know,
you don't have to wait
until the end.
You can attempt to expose
the VIP at any time.
Of course, that scenario is
covered by cases three and four.
Everything he said is true,
according to this.
"Answers will be accepted at any
time during the testing period.
Regardless if answers
are submitted early
or at the end of the last day.
Any incorrect answers
will result in a penalty.
In case three, someone,
other than the VIP,
emails the school before
the end of the last day,
and correctly guesses
the VIP's identity.
In that case, that
person's class will have
50 class points
added to their total.
Also, that student will be
awarded 500,000 private points,
and the testing for that group
will immediately end.
However, correct answers
from students in the VIP's
own class will be
declared invalid
and the exam will continue.
And case four:
someone, other than the VIP,
emails the school
before the end of the last day,
but incorrectly guesses
the identity of the VIP.
If that happens, then that
person's class will have
50 class points deducted
from their total.
Additionally, the VIP will be
awarded 500,000 private points.
Furthermore, their class
will have 50 class points
added to their total."
[AYANOKOJI] And the moment the
incorrect answer is received,
the testing for that
group will conclude.
Oh. It says here if
the wrong answer comes
from someone
in the VIP's class,
their answer is invalid
and won't be accepted.
[YUKIMURA]
I see, this won't be easy.
Honestly, I still don't really
understand what's going on.
I'm in the same boat. This test
is surprisingly complicated.
I'll explain it
to you both later.
Don't bother the
teacher over it.
Last thing. The
school is committed
to protecting our
students' anonymity.
After the special exam is over,
We'll take steps to make sure
that only your group's
final result and class-wide
point changes are announced.
What about the VIP's identity?
[MASHIMA]
That will remain secret
along with everyone's answers.
--[GIRL 201A] This is so weird!
--[GIRL 201B] Right?
[AYANOKOJI] It seems there are
four ways this can play out.
What a pain.
The VIP is identified.
Then the whole group answers
correctly and wins.
If, on the last day
of the test,
at least one person
guesses wrong,
only the VIP is victorious.
Someone betrays the group
and wins points
for their class instead.
[AYANOKOJI]
And the final possibility:
someone betrays the group,
but their guess
turns out to be wrong.
They're evaluating
our "thinking."
Which students will be able
to accurately analyze
the situation,
and if they can effectively
manage their group's actions.
In short, they're testing
our problem-solving ability.
This special exam is
all about anticipating
how others will act and
manipulating their actions
to your benefit.
How annoying.
It's almost time.
Yeah.
I got the same message.
That's a shame. Neither of us
were selected as VIPs.
Agreed. This limits our options.
What do you think
of this whole thing?
The special test, I mean.
It depends on how
the VIP approaches it.
That said, I've come up with
a few ideas for how we can win.
Of course you have.
Seems I can leave
the Mars group to you.
Sure.
I am curious to see how you
handle things with your group.
Do you need my help?
No thanks. I'm fine.
Anyway, I wanted to ask you.
Is there anyone you're wary of
in the other classes--?
[RYUEN]
Oh, what a coincidence!
You don't mind
if I join you, right?
Suzune, you're not
the VIP, are you?
I wouldn't tell you
even if I was.
Really. Who would freely give
away that kind of information?
[RYUEN]
I would, if you just asked.
But I couldn't care
less about that.
What I want to know
is how you managed
to pull off that stunt
on the island.
Based on Ibuki's daily reports,
you did absolutely nothing,
from beginning to end.
It's laughable how much
you trusted those.
I mean, she struggled to
beat me even when I was sick.
So.
Then how about a rematch,
right here and now?
If I'm being honest,
the way you guys won
wasn't all that special,
once you understand it.
That said, few people could've
come up with that plan
and actually pulled it off
under those conditions.
It's certainly not something
a strait-laced little girl
like you could've cooked up.
Suzune.
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but it was my idea.
You see, the truth is,
Anyanokoji, over there
is the closest thing I have
to a friend.
Though he's so useless,
I wouldn't rely
on him for anything.
The kind of bottom feeder
I'd expect from Class D.
[camera shutter clicks]
Delete that picture!
This'll be a fun game.
I can't wait to find out
who's pulling your strings.
They can't hide in the shadows
forever--I'll drag 'em out.
Why are you so obsessed with
the students from Class D?
You're just a bunch of new toys.
I know what the
other classes can do.
They aren't a threat to me.
[AYANOKOJI] You've suddenly
become the woman of the hour
Oh, spare me.
All this is your fault.
[AYANOKOJI] I see.
The more they pressure her,
the more she wants
to fight back.
Seems there's nothing for me
to worry about, then.
What now?
It's nothing.
[sighs] What did I do
to get lumped into a group
with these losers?
Uh--
[ICHINOSE]
All right, let's get started!
Let's go around
and introduce ourselves!
After all, the instructions
specifically mentioned it!
I don't see the point in wasting
our time with introductions.
We're not here to make
friends with each other.
Well, yeah, I guess I can't
force you to participate.
Although, it's entirely possible
that the school put
a bug in this room!
That's a good point.
And you know how the school
is about their rules.
If you don't play along,
you could get punished.
[MACHIDA sighs]
Let's get this over with.
Thanks so much!
[AYANOKOJI] Ichinose's
seized the initiative.
Interesting.
[ICHINOSE] I'd like to nominate
myself as the group's moderator!
If anyone has any objections
to that, please let me know!
I won't mind!
[AYANOKOJI]
So that's how she's playing it.
If anyone here objected,
they'd basically be
volunteering themselves.
The moderator gets
to lead the discussion.
But they risk
revealing too much.
It's safer to let her lead.
Well, since I don't
see any objections,
I guess I'll accept
the position!
To start with, let's all
get on the same page.
Are we all clear
on the rules of the exam?
Does anyone have any questions?
Great! Then, I have a proposal!
If it's possible, I'd like
for all of us to work together!
In other words,
I say we should try
to aim for case one!
That way we can all win points!
What do you guys think?
Obviously yes,
it's a no-brainer!
Naturally, we're in agreement.
I'm on board.
This is a good chance
to earn more points.
And it'll be easier
to cooperate.
Right you are!
We'll overcome this
challenge, post haste!
Jeez, could you
get any weirder?
[MACHIDA] Sorry. Unfortunately,
Class A has decided
not to participate
in any discussions.
Wait. They're saying no?
But why?
Would you mind explaining
why you won't join in?
Don't worry,
it's nothing personal.
I promise you.
It's just that the safest
and most certain way to win
is for Class A to abstain
from any discussions
during the special exam.
[AYANOKOJI]
Katsuragi's idea, I'm sure.
But with that strategy,
you're basically making sure
only the VIP walks
away with points.
Tell me, what is the worst
possible result from this test?
[gasps] Uh, let's see.
I guess, if someone figured
out the VIP's identity
and then betrayed the group?
Close, but not quite.
The worst-case scenario
in this test is if someone
tries to betray the group
and guess early
but submits an incorrect answer
and loses class points.
In order to avoid that,
you're withholding information
to ensure that case two occurs.
That conservative strategy might
seem like it's the safest route.
But ignoring the VIPs
could create a point disparity
between the classes!
We can't be sure
how they decided
who the VIPs were going to be.
And what if, through
a stroke of luck,
most of the VIPs
were from one class?
[AYANOKOJI]
Hamaguchi's got a good point.
Without knowing the class
distribution of the VIPs.
Class A's strategy would be
too dependent on luck.
But he's forgotten
something very important.
The school's policy.
"Fairness for all classes."
As you know, our school
goes to extreme lengths
to adhere to that doctrine,
even in these tests.
Because of that,
I'm confident that there is
an even distribution of VIPs
all across the classes.
I see, makes sense.
[ICHINOSE] I have to admit,
you're making some
very compelling arguments.
Although, executing your
strategy won't be easy.
You're betting that no one
from Class A gets greedy
or lets any info slip out.
Not gonna happen!
We completely trust each other.
Sounds to me like
it'll be less of a hassle.
Well, what do
you think, Yukimura?
Perhaps it would be better
to go along with them.
Doing nothing would be easier.
However, I can't help
but feel this strategy
gives Class A an advantage
over other classes.
Sorry, I'm not following
what you're saying.
By forcing a case two result,
you're making students
from other classes lose
a chance to catch up!
Well, that's, uh...
The major downside
with your strategy
is that no one
can earn class points
to raise their class ranking.
If you wanna talk
about class points,
your plan doesn't help
the lower classes either!
You're wrong! It does help!
You see, the Mars group has four
members from Classes C and D!
But only three
from Classes A and B!
In other words, if we can
get the case one result,
Classes D and C, on the whole,
will each be awarded an extra
500,000 private points!
That may be true. But hold on.
Going with your idea
would also be disadvantageous
for your class!
A small price to pay.
This works out better
for us than letting you
do whatever you want.
After all, if the VIP
was from your class,
then only you would win!
I'm inclined to agree.
[AYANOKOJI]
That was well done.
Class B must've guessed what
Class A was aiming for.
Doesn't matter.
Class A's strategy
remains unchanged.
We won't participate
in the discussion.
Oh, my. What are we
gonna do with them?
[AYANOKOJI] Both Machida and
Ichinose have good points.
It's hard to argue with them.
And I'm sure each class
has their own schemes.
[MANABE]
Yo, Karuizawa, got a second?
Hey! Don't ignore me,
I'm talking to you!
Whadaya want?
Did you get into
a fight with Rika?
Before summer break.
Huh? Rika who?
What are you talking about?
She's a girl in our class
who wears glasses
and puts her hair in buns.
Now do you remember her?
Out with it!
Can't say that I do.
You've got the wrong girl.
Nice try, but Rika
told us what happened!
She said that
a girl with a ponytail
from Class D bullied her!
She was just minding her
own business, then somebody
cut in front of her
and shoved her aside!
[KARUIZAWA] Too bad for her,
but that wasn't me.
Don't give us that crap!
You should own up to what you
did and apologize to her!
Let's just get a picture of her
and check with Rika.
Don't you dare take my picture!
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy? You could've
broken her phone!
Well, you can always just
get a new one from the school.
And what about my pictures
and personal stuff, huh?
Who cares? What do you want?
If you're really innocent,
then why are you being so pissy?
Let us take a pic!
[KARUIZAWA]
I told you, no!
[MANABE]
What's your problem?
[YAMASHITA]
Would you look at that?
She's all shy, now!
[MANABE]
You're kidding me.
[YABU] Stop freaking out.
It's just a picture!
Leave me alone!
[MACHIDA] Hey. You girls
are causing a scene!
[KARUIZAWA]
Machida!
Stop picking on her.
She's nearly in tears.
This is none of your business,
so buzz off, Machida!
Do I need to call a teacher?
Fine, whatever.
Come on, let's go.
[YAMASHITA]
Oh, right!
Hey. Do you think that
she was telling the truth?
If we had a picture,
we could show Rika.
[KARUIZAWA]
Thanks for saving me, Machida.
If we want to avoid
playing into Class A's hands,
we need to have
open group discussions.
[KARUIZAWA] But even then,
it's not like the VIP
is gonna reveal themselves.
It's no use.
This test is too hard.
I'd say that depends
on our approach.
This is kind of like the last
test, while it may seem
difficult at first, I just know
we'll find a way to overcome it!
Worry not, Karuizawa, for I--
I just love being
on this cruise!
Isn't it so fun?
Even if we have to sit
through these meetings,
we can still chat!
And we can use our phones
as much as we want!
I guess it's not so bad.
Exactly! We can
talk about anything!
It must be boring sitting
in silence the entire time!
There's nothing stopping you all
from spending the
whole hour talking.
Just don't expect us
to chime in.
After all, who knows what you
guys from Class B are plotting.
You sure?
Maybe your classmates
wanna join in?
Obviously not.
[whimpering]