Hey, wait!
What do you want?
If you pull out of the festival,
Class D won't have
any chance of winning.
Me coming back
won't change anything!
Right.
After everything I did
for those jerks.
Sudo, I've seen first-hand
how seriously you've
been taking this.
But still, you aren't
blameless either!
If you're just here
to lecture me, Horikita,
I think I'll pass.
I don't really want
to hear it right now.
You're too old
to throw tantrums.
How do you expect to succeed
with this kind of attitude?
[KEN grunts]
Just shut it!
See? This is exactly
what I'm talking about!
Great, another lecture.
[KEN] Give it a rest, already!
I'm sick of everyone riding me!
It's all their fault!
With me in charge, winning this
sports festival should be easy!
But I'm stuck with this class!
They're dead weight,
and all they're doing
is keeping me
from crushing it!
You're upset that we're losing
in a test you excel in.
That much is clear,
but that's not all.
I wanted to show off, I guess.
Get some respect, you know?
I needed to prove to them
that I deserved to be here.
Just picturing the looks
on everyone's faces
who talked smack to me.
I'm pathetic.
Growing up, I was always
the kid from the trash family.
I told myself that
I'd be different.
But every day, I see
more of 'em in me.
[SUZUNE] You shouldn't
think of it in that way.
It's not their fault.
You can't blame others
for who you are.
You have to decide
that for yourself.
Life would be so different
if we simply inherited
the qualities of our family.
What's that supposed to mean?
[SUZUNE]
Your future isn't set in stone.
You can always choose
what you want to be.
Huh.
It pains me to admit,
but you're talented
when it comes to sports.
However, at the moment,
you're worthless.
Even now, you're
trying to run away.
If you refuse to help us
win the festival,
you'll only be proving that
you really are trash
like your parents.
Well, that's perfectly
fine by me!
I couldn't care less
about that crap anymore.
[ANNOUNCER 205AA]
Attention students,
the lunch break
will end soon.
All competitors, please
assemble on the field.
You better get out there.
No, not until you agree
to come back with me.
I'll be waiting right here.
Whatever.
Real quick. Could you
tie our legs together?
[KIKYO] Mm-hm! You know,
it's kinda hard to believe.
Horikita actually chasing
after Sudo like that!
Kushida.
Just a sec! I'm almost
done tying the knot--
[AYANOKOJI]
It's you, isn't it?
You're the person
who betrayed our class
by sharing our submission
form with Class C.
[KIKYO] I don't have a clue
what you're talking about!
Where's this coming from?
I didn't know you
liked telling jokes!
It isn't. I saw
you taking pictures
of our class's
submission form.
I just wanted to make sure
I didn't forget my events!
We were told not
to take pictures.
Oh, really? Whoops,
I totally forgot!
Sorry!
Hope that doesn't
make me a suspect!
But that's not the only reason.
What's been happening
would only be possible
if someone leaked
information to Class C.
Hey, Ayanokoji.
Let's say that you're right
and I was the person
who shared our class's
submission form.
If you knew I was going
to betray everyone,
then why didn't you do anything?
Instead, you just let it happen.
Isn't that right?
You could've changed
the roster, but you didn't.
What's the point?
As long as a traitor existed
in Class D, it wouldn't matter.
What do you mean?
Even if we made changes,
anyone could've checked the form
and it would've tipped off
the traitor we were onto them.
But why couldn't you have
just kept the roster secret?
And then turn it in
at the last second?
That way, if someone wanted to
leak it to the other classes,
it would be too late.
Ah, although, if we did that,
it'd just make things
super confusing for us, too.
I get it now.
But I'm still not the
traitor, you're talking--
[AYANOKOJI] If I asked the
teacher who checked the roster,
I have a feeling your
name would come up.
If that's the case, why would
you come see it again
if you had a picture?
[KIKYO giggles]
Color me impressed, Ayanokoji.
You're really something!
I guess there's no point
in hiding it now.
You're right!
I'm the one who leaked our
submission form to Class C!
So, it was you.
[KIKYO] Mm-hm! Well,
it doesn't matter if you know,
'cause you can't
tell anyone about it!
Don't you forget!
I have that uniform!
I know my hands are tied.
I wasn't looking to expose
you as the culprit.
I was just checking.
[KIKYO giggles]
[AYANOKOJI]
This wasn't the first time.
Class C took first place
in the last exam because
you told Ryuen that you
were the VIP, didn't you?
If I had to guess, he promised
you a favor in exchange.
[KIKYO]
My goodness!
It sounds like
you know everything!
Have you figured out the reason
why I'd betray our class then?
I imagine that it has
to do with whatever grudge
you hold against Horikita.
[KIKYO giggles]
Mm-hm! Amazing!
You really did get to the
bottom of it, Ayanokoji!
It's true!
More than anything, I want
Suzune Horikita to be expelled.
[AYANOKOJI] Although,
I still don't quite understand
your reasoning for all this.
Why do you hate her so much?
[KIKYO]
It doesn't matter.
I'll make sure that
she gets kicked out
and there's nothing you
can do to change my mind.
[AYANOKOJI]
It's that important?
So much that you'd sell out
your own class for it?
[KIKYO]
Absolutely!
I don't really care if
I make it to Class A or not!
The only thing I want is
for Horikita to be expelled
before the year is over!
[AYANOKOJI]
I see.
[KIKYO] Don't get me wrong!
I'm not against moving up!
Once she's been kicked
out of the school,
I'd be more than happy to help
everyone reach Class A.
I think that would be kinda fun!
I'm looking forward to it, now!
Oh, actually,
I just changed my mind
about one part of that plan.
How about...
Since you like her so much,
I'll make sure you get
expelled with Horikita!
That way, I won't have
to look at your face again!
And once the two of you
are out of my life,
I can work with everyone
to get to Class A!
I can't believe you
actually stayed here.
'Course.
Hold on, Sudo!
Where are you going?
[KEN]
Back to my room, where else?
Wait! Over the past hour,
I've been thinking.
About what kind of person I am
and what you told me
about yourself.
I realized we aren't so
different from each other.
Don't make me laugh.
We're nothin' alike.
You've met the student
council president, right?
Oh, That stuck-up bastard?
Yeah, he's my older brother.
Despite that,
he goes out of his way
to pretend that I don't exist.
I disappoint him. And
because of my incompetence,
my perfect brother hates being
associated with me in any way.
[KEN]
Like I'd believe that bull.
You're talented and smart.
That may be so, but I can't
hold a candle to him.
[SUZUNE]
All my life, I've chased him.
Doing everything in my power
to try to catch up.
And because of that...
[SUZUNE]
...I was always alone.
I believed that I didn't matter.
I thought, if I proved myself,
my brother would eventually
see my worth and accept me.
I'm exactly like you.
I wanted to use this
festival to show off.
I was holding onto
some vague hope
that if I could just do well
enough, he'd be proud of me.
I thought I was above
everyone else in our class.
I realize how wrong I was.
I'm not special or exceptional.
I became someone I didn't like.
I can't do this alone.
Working with our team
was the first time
I felt like I could accomplish
something worthwhile.
I'll never give up,
no matter what.
I'll earn my brother's
acknowledgement.
I'll work hard to become
someone I can be proud of.
And if on the way, it looks like
you're straying from the path,
I'll do whatever it takes
to bring you back.
I won't let you run away again.
You're the only one
who understands me.
Please, help me lead
our class forward.
Trust me, you can become so much
more than what people assume.
My entire life,
I've heard that kind of
sentimental junk nonstop.
But somehow, when it's
coming from you,
a part of me wants
to believe it.
So, Ken Sudo. I'll ask again.
Will you help class D win?
Horikita.
Ugh. Damn it!
All right, you've convinced me!
I don't know what your plan is,
but I've got the feeling
that going along with you
is the right choice!
I'll be the person
you think I can be!
[KEN]
Forgive me!
[STUDETS gasp]
[KEN] I'm sorry for losing my
temper and taking it out on you.
This is my fault.
I deserve all the blame
for the position our
class is in right now.
We're just glad you're back.
This is the last event!
So, let's give it
everything we've got!
Let's end this festival
with a bang!
I think I'm going
to need someone
to stand in for me
during the race.
I'm afraid I won't able to do
very much with my leg like this.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, Kushida.
Would you mind going?
Sure, no problem!
Sorry to spring
this on everyone.
But I think I'll have
to sit this one out, too.
You see, I twisted my ankle
during the 200-meter dash
earlier this morning.
I thought it might feel
better if I rested it,
but it still hurts.
That's not good.
It sounds like we'll need to
make a last minute substitution
for the boy's team.
It's fine. I can
run in his place.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[IKE]
Go, Ken! Be one with the speed!
[STUDENTS cheering]
From what I observed
earlier in the festival,
I assumed your class
was beyond salvation.
Although, that no longer
seems to be the case.
What happened?
[AYANOKOJI]
They found themselves
someone to rally behind.
You can thank
your sister for that.
[MANABU]
I see.
[AYANOKOJI] Our class
is only getting stronger.
[MANABU] I'll believe you
when I see it for myself.
[panting]
[AYANOKOJI]
That's right.
Didn't you want to see
what kind of person I am?
I could show you.
What?
If you are interested,
I suppose I could be convinced
to indulge you with a race.
Interesting.
Catch you later, president!
Um. 'Scuse me!
Trust me on this.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] Before we race,
I wanna give you a warning.
[MANABU]
What is it?
You shouldn't hold
anything back.
Here, Ayanokoji!
[STUDENT 206D]
No way!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[AYANOKOJI]
For as long as I've lived,
I've never once had to run
with all my strength
in front of other people.
[AYANOKOJI]
Right. I'll go even faster.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SOTOMURA] Wow, I guess
everything kinda worked out!
Too bad our class
ranked dead last, though.
[IKE]
That's true!
Forget that!
All that matters
is our team won!
On top of that, pretty much
every single class
ended up going
negative, points wise.
So it's not that bad.
[KARUIZAWA]
You were pretty fast there.
Nah, everyone else
was just pretty slow.
That so?
Shame I couldn't beat the
class president in the end.
[KARUIZAWA] It's not like
it's your fault though.
The guy running in front
of you tripped and fell.
A loss is still a loss.
You're probably
the only one here
who's upset with second place.
[KEN] Yo, Ayanokoji!
You're one hell of a runner!
Don't tell me that you've
been holding out on us
this entire time.
I still can't believe you kept
up with him till the end!
I really misjudged you, dude!
It was nothing, just
a surge of adrenaline.
[SUZUNE grunts]
You really expect us
to believe that?
You liar.
I gave it my all
during the last event
and this is how you treat me?
That really hurt.
[SUZUNE] If you ran
like that from the start,
we wouldn't be in last place!
So don't give me that crap!
[SUZUNE]
It's my fault that we lost.
I failed.
I have to do better.
Although, I feel like
this sports festival
was the key to
helping me grow.
Ugh, just listen to me.
Going on about
something as sappy as
"learning from my mistakes."
If it makes you a better person,
then is it really that bad?
This class will become stronger.
I know, eventually,
we'll get to Class A.
Oh.
What's wrong?
I never thought you'd
say something like that;
it gave me goosebumps.
Me neither. It's not
like me at all.
Right. This isn't
going to be easy.
There are gonna be
plenty of problems
that we'll have to deal with.
Problems?
We'll just have to take
things as they come.
Thanks for today.
Wow. Look who decided
to come after all!
Suzune.
[SUZUNE]
If I turned tail and ran,
I don't think I could ever
forgive myself for it.
Let's get this over with.
I like the fight in your eyes!
Feeling nice and
confident now, are we?
There's just one thing
I wanna deal with first.
How long are you gonna
keep up that act?
Huh? What are you talking about?
[SUZUNE] You can stop
playing dumb already.
You're who betrayed our class.
That's why Class C had such
an easy time beating us.
In exchange, you had
Ryuen help you.
I hope whatever you
got was worth it.
Traitor.
My goodness!
Someone from our class
must've spilled the beans!
Hirata? Ayanokoji?
[SUZUNE]
I don't get it.
We're the only ones
here right now.
Why don't you quit
pretending already?
Pretending?
Whatever do you mean?
I actually didn't recognize
you when we first met.
However, the more I saw you,
the more you
reminded me of someone
I went to middle school with.
That's right, though
I was a bit more
of a problem child back then.
And since you've managed
to piece together
that much by yourself,
I imagine you've figured out
what I'm really after, then.
That much is obvious.
Your goal is to try to get me
expelled from the school.
But you have to be careful
with how you do it,
because I know your secret.
Right on the money.
However, I don't think
I have to remind you
that if you tell even
a single soul about me,
then everything
will come to light.
And if that happens,
you won't be able to keep your
precious big brother out of it.
Why take the risk when
you could just ignore me?
You know I don't pry into
matters that don't concern me.
I don't get it.
In order for me to truly
become the person I want to be,
I can't take any chances.
I need to get rid of anyone
who knows about my past.
Oh, really?
Tell me, that list
includes me, doesn't it?
Maybe one day, you never know!
I'd like to see you try.
[KIKYO] I'm glad I can tell
you this to your face.
You're going to get expelled,
and It'll be because of me.
I'd even make a deal
with the devil, himself.
You heard her.
[SUZUNE]
I see.
You got the better
of me this time.
And what about
the sports festival?
Did you plan that out, too?
It's gotta be all
about you, huh?
But let's say that you're right.
I'd be more than
happy to indulge
in your little fantasy story.
Here it is.
Before the festival even began,
I had Kikyo here
take a picture of Class D's
roster and send it to me.
Afterwards, I based my
class's roster around it.
Ensuring that we had the
best matchups against you.
I'll admit that was
a brilliant move.
But you got lucky, too.
[RYUEN]
What luck?
The fact that I got taken out
of the festival due to my leg.
Not to mention Kinoshita
getting injured that badly.
There's no way you planned
for both of those to happen.
[RYUEN] Don't tell me
you seriously think
that was just coincidence.
[SUZUNE]
But how?
[chuckles] It's true, she
really did trip and fall.
But a tumble like that's
only gonna give you
some scrapes and bruises.
That's why I had her act
like she was badly hurt.
Then afterwards, I made sure she
didn't have to pretend anymore.
I made it worth her while.
I see. Got it.
By the way, I've been
recording all of this.
This plan of yours
ends here and now.
If you try to blackmail me
or go to the student council,
I'll just let them listen to
what you have to say about it.
Heh. You never cease
to entertain me
with your little schemes,
Suzune. It's so cute.
But I already told you
at the start.
All of that just now,
was a hypothetical scenario.
Of course, I was
only playing along.
I can always cut around that
and only keep in the parts
where you talk about
your plan, you know.
I guess you could do that.
I'll just give them this.
[gasps]
It's funny.
I've been recording
our conversation, too.
[sighs]
Time for you to grovel, Suzune.
[inhales, sighs] Very well.
Ugh.
[RYUEN chuckles] Well now,
isn't that interesting?
[RYUEN]
Hey, Suzune.
I gotta hand it to you,
whoever's pulling your strings
is truly something special.
They planned this whole thing
out from the very beginning,
and we've been
dancing to their tune.
[RYUEN] If we wanna
crush Suzune Horikita
and the rest of Class D,
I've come up with the
perfect plan to trap her.
And it's practically fool proof.
The first part of
the plan is to put you
in the obstacle course
event with her.
Do whatever it takes
to bring her to the ground.
After that, I'll injure you
for real, she'll think
she hurt you, and then
we'll blackmail her.
Where did they get that?
It looks like Class C
has a traitor, too.
[KIKYO gasps]
[RYUEN]
They played us for fools, Kikyo.
Anticipating our every move,
even accounting
for your betrayal.
[RYUEN] Not many people could've
successfully pulled this off.
I swear, no matter where
they run or try to hide,
I'll find them.
[RYUEN] Suzune, you're off
the hook, for now.