[MANABU]
For the past two years,
I have served the student body
as the student council
president with pride.
I will forever be grateful for
the opportunity I was given.
Thank you all.
And with that, I'll conclude
my resignation speech.
So farewell, everyone.
[applause]
[AYANOKOJI]
Interesting.
She's taking it
surprisingly well.
[ANNOUNCER 205A] Thank you
for all of your hard work,
President Horikita.
And now, we'll hear a few words
from the incoming student
council president.
Hello, everyone!
For those of you who
aren't familiar with me,
I'm Miyabi Nagumo
from classroom 2A.
I'll get straight
to the point.
My vision for this school
is to turn it into a true
meritocracy for every student!
Those with talent and ability
will rise to the top,
while those without
will be left behind.
Just as things should be.
I was surprised
by your performance
in the sports festival.
Oh, thanks.
Give Horikita a warning for me.
She needs to be
on guard for Ryuen.
I'm curious.
Didn't your class form an
alliance with him before?
A mistake I'm still paying for.
I never should've gotten
involved with that snake.
Ryuen is my enemy
as much as yours.
I see. I'll let her know.
[KATSURAGI]
Please do.
They're feeling
the pressure, too.
Interesting.
[SATO]
Hey.
So, um. You mind coming
with me for a second?
There's something
I wanna talk about.
I know this is kinda random,
but I've been
meaning to ask you.
Are you seeing anyone
right now, Ayanokoji?
Just you. No one's here?
I don't mean like
who you literally see!
I'm asking if you have
a girlfriend or not!
So, do you?
No, I don't.
Oh. That's good to hear.
[SATO] Why don't we
exchange phone numbers?
You know,
since both of us are
in the same class?
I'd be okay with that.
[AYANOKOJI]
Hey. Where's this coming from?
During the sports festival...
When I watched your race,
I couldn't help but notice
how impressive you were.
And I realized you're
actually quite handsome.
On top of that that,
you're nice, too!
[SATO]
Um. Anyway.
That's all I wanted! Thanks!
[CHABASHIRA] It's clear you only
have one thing on your minds.
Therefore, I'll reveal your
midterm results now.
[STUDENT 207A]
Are you kidding me?
Dreams do come true!
Whoa! Look at Ken's score!
Yeah!
Hardly worth shouting about.
Yeah, right!
[AYANOKOJI]
Just like a puppy
[CHABASHIRA]
Since you all passed,
no one will be expelled
this time around.
In my three years with Class D,
this is the first group of
students to go this long
without any dropouts.
I'm impressed.
Excellent work.
[MIYAKE] Ms. Chabashira's
saying something nice?
[IKE] It's about time we got
the props we deserve!
[YUKIMURA] It's actually
kind of unsettling.
Of course,
you're not out of
the woods just yet.
You'll have to prove yourselves
during the next special exam,
which will serve as your finals.
This test is called
the Paper Shuffle.
Uh. What's that?
[CHABASHIRA] For this exam,
you will be split into pairs.
In order to pass you'll
need to work together
Will we be competing
with each other?
What are the chances
I get matched with Kikyo?
[KIKYO giggles]
Partners.
You'll wanna be with
Hirata, isn't that right?
Uh. Yeah!
Although, do we even get
to choose the pairs?
That's right!
Can you tell us how our
partners are gonna be chosen?
[CHABASHIRA]
All in due time.
You're getting
ahead of yourselves.
Everything will be explained to
you after next week's mini test.
[GROUP]
Uh--
It's freakin' tests
all the way down!
It's to ascertain your
current academic prowess
and determine where
you stand in the class.
There aren't any penalties.
So don't worry.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[SATO]
Thank goodness for that!
That said,
these test scores are crucial
to the Paper Shuffle.
So, you ought to do your best.
[CHABASHIRA] If, on the
upcoming special exam,
a pair's total score in any
subject falls below 60 points,
both students will be expelled.
[CLASS gasps]
Because only the total is
considered, if one of you
gets a zero and the other
scores a 60, both pass.
And one more thing.
There's a minimum total score
for all subjects combined.
I'll give you a more
accurate number later.
Just know that, on average,
the requirement is
around 700 points.
[AYANOKOJI]
Across eight subjects.
That means, for each exam,
everyone needs to get
an average of 44 points.
And finally...
For this test,
you'll be writing it.
All of you.
Huh?!
[CHABASHIRA]
It's up to you to come up with
the questions for the exam.
Which will be answered by
one of the other classes.
You'll also pick a class
you hope gets your questions.
So, choose wisely.
If a class is picked
multiple times,
the test they will
get will be random.
Additionally, each classes'
score will be compared
to that of the class that
received their questions.
And whoever ends up
with a higher score
will steal 50 class
points from the other.
The test is a direct challenge.
What if they ask something
that can't be answered?
Doesn't seem fair.
Hah. How laughable,
everything has an answer.
[CHABASHIRA]
There's no need to worry.
We've accounted for that.
The teachers will be
reviewing all questions.
Obviously, cheating
will be severely punished,
resulting in
immediate expulsion.
Every year,
a pair or two gets
expelled during this exam.
It would be a shame if you
broke our streak with this.
Something to consider.
[CHABASHIRA] I'll be sending out
an email with more instructions
on how to write your
exam questions.
Everything else
will be up to you.
This "Paper Shuffle."
What do you think?
I already know how to win it.
The teacher's explanation
gave all the hints we needed.
Oh?
Call Hirata and the others.
Let's have a strategy meeting.
--Yes, ma'am.
--[phone chimes]
[KARUIZAWA] Hey, I've got
a question for you.
Earlier. Sato asked
you out, right?
[AYANOKOJI]
Who told you that?
[sighs] It came from
Sato, herself! Obviously!
It's not like it's
a secret or anything!
She told a bunch of people
she was gonna ask you out.
Well, it's not like he'd
know anything about it.
Things work totally
different for boys.
Ugh. He saw me?
Ugh... As dense as that guy is,
sometimes he's
really perceptive.
[HIRATA]
Karuizawa!
We're having a meeting
to discuss the special exam.
[KARUIZAWA]
Uh. Sure! Got it!
If it's all right with you all,
I'd like to start
the meeting now.
What, right here?
Can't we go somewhere else?
Maybe a café!
Come on! Right? It'll be fun.
Fine, then. We'll relocate.
[KIKYO]
Excuse me.
Would you mind if
I joined you guys?
If that's okay.
Well, if you ask me.
Kushida could really help,
she's friends with everyone.
Yes, of course! Appreciate it.
This works out,
since I've been meaning to
talk to you about something.
Thanks so much!
Why don't you all go
on ahead without me.
I'll catch up.
I need to talk with Ayanokoji.
[KEN]
We'll save you guys some seats!
You ok with that?
Letting her come along?
Saying no would've only
caused more problems.
Right. So, what did you
want to talk about?
We can't keep them
waiting too long.
I don't care to meddle
in other people's business,
or air out their dirty laundry.
But you should know
Kushida's past.
[SUZUNE]
Both Kushida and I
went to the same middle school.
It was a rather large school.
So, we never got put
into the same class.
Which is why I hardly
remembered her.
But something happened during
our final year at that school.
[SUZUNE]
No one knew exactly what.
But it completely tore
one of the classes apart.
From all the rumors
that were circulating,
it was caused by one person.
A girl who was in that class.
You believe it was Kushida?
I honestly don't
know what to think.
What could she have done to make
her class break apart like that?
I don't get it.
They were in constant
turmoil until graduation.
But how?
Can a single person really
destroy an entire class?
I can think of a couple ways.
Let me ask.
What's the most surefire method
to get what you want?
I don't know, I'd say
violence, I guess?
Throughout history, there's been
no better tool than that.
[AYANOKOJI]
But that's not Kushida's style.
Whatever her method,
it seems that it's just as
effective as violence is.
We could spend all
day speculating.
At the end of the day,
I'm an obstacle to her.
Even though I don't
actually have a clue
what happened back then.
[AYANOKOJI] You'll have a hard
time convincing her of that.
If you ask me, your
best course of action
may be to take things
into your own hands.
Are you saying I should
get Kushida expelled?
If you do go on the offensive,
it could save you the trouble.
Weren't you the person
who got on my case
when I was thinking about
cutting Sudo loose?
What's changed now?
Kushida will continue to
plague us until you're gone.
She's quite stubborn.
[SUZUNE] Well, things have
only gotten to this point
because I refused to
confront her about it.
And she's a talented person.
She could be a valuable
asset to our class.
So, you think you
can convince her?
I can! I'll keep on
trying to talk to her.
We aren't her enemy.
I'll make sure she sees that.
Very well.
If you're really
that determined,
I'll leave it up
to you to handle.
Just watch.
And this time, don't interfere!
I don't want you to step in
like with the festival.
So, you knew.
I had an idea.
I found it extremely annoying
that you planned around
the assumption
that I would fail.
That said, I guess you did
help me back there.
That's good to hear.
[SUZUNE]
Listen.
I'm not sure what I
would've done without you.
Thank you.
[AYANOKOJI] Is it really so hard
for her to say "thank you"?
[RYUEN]
Now, call me crazy.
But there's been something fishy
about the last couple
of special exams.
I don't believe for a
second it's a coincidence.
Someone's out there
pulling Class D's strings.
Not to mention a spy
helping them out.
So, which one of you
betrayed me?
Really? You can't be serious!
[RYUEN]
A question for you!
Do any of you know what the
strongest force in world is?
It's simple:
unrestrained violence.
I'll give you
one last chance.
Whoever the traitor is,
come clean, and I'll
let it slide this time.
I feel like I'm being
more than reasonable here.
And if you keep trying
to play dumb with me...
[gasps]
[whimpers]
What's the matter?
You can't even
look me in the eyes.
Manabe.
You're the traitor.
Tell me that I'm wrong.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
You think I didn't know
it was you the whole time?
[MANABE]
I'm sorry. They made me do it.
I'll forgive you!
But first, I want
you to tell me.
Who put you up to this?
What's the name
of this mastermind?
I see, now. Bullying's
a fun pastime.
As long as you're careful
not to get caught doing it.
[IBUKI]
How are you this stupid?
You really betrayed our class
because of some recording?
Go easy on them.
They already apologized.
Let's focus on the
person behind it all.
According to you, Yukimura
and Ayanokoji witnessed it.
[GROUP whimpers]
In other words,
the mastermind
has to be one of those two.
Wait a sec.
I've had some dealings
with Ayanokoji
and I don't think he's
that kind of person.
He is suspicious.
It seems almost too obvious.
But it is a possibility.
It's time to call in a favor.
[KIKYO gasps]
Hey, guys! Over here!
Wow! Look who finally
decided to show up!
What took you so long, huh?
[SUZUNE]
We can start right away.
[KARUIZAWA]
Just brushing me off again.
Typical, I guess.
We'll be going over
the Paper Shuffle, right?
Not yet.
We have a more immediate
concern: next week's mini test.
[AYANOKOJI] Let's see how
Horikita does on her own.
Since it won't
affect our grades,
what's the point of it?
The only explanation is that
it'll determine the pairings.
Remember what
Ms. Chabashira said?
...a pair or two gets
expelled during this exam.
It would be a shame if you
broke our streak with this.
[SUZUNE] Doesn't that
number seem a little low?
If the bottom students of each
class were grouped together,
you'd have dozens of people
dropping out each year.
[gasps] That's right!
Good point! That explains it.
The point of the test is
to create balanced pairs!
Yeah.
The teacher also said we'd
be ranked by our scores.
If they put the highest
and the lowest ranking
students together,
it'd ensure everyone got roughly
the same average score.
[KARUIZAWA]
That makes sense!
That means our goal for
this test is to pair up
highest and lowest
scoring students.
We'll start by splitting
everyone in Class D
into four different groups based
on their academic standing.
And then we'll coordinate with
the lowest group and make sure
that they all leave
their test sheets blank.
Oh, that's smart!
That way, they'll definitely get
paired with the top scorers.
Right. In the same vein,
everyone in the
second-lowest block
will only try to get
one question right.
[HIRATA]
I see.
That'll reduce the chance
of making a weak pair!
Are you still
keeping up, Sudo?
Not even a little bit, man.
Just smiling and
nodding over here.
Come on!
It's pretty simple
if you think about it!
[KEN]
Shaddap! Nobody asked you!
[STUDENTS laugh]
That's it for my proposal.
Besides, we still need
to make a decision
on which class we should
have answer our questions.
If we're talking academics.
It might be best to
avoid Classes A and B.
Which only leaves us one choice.
Yes, Class C will
be our best bet.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] I told you to only
contact me in case of emergency.
[KARUIZAWA] Come on,
what's the harm in talking?
Anyway, I just wanna know what
you said to Sato earlier!
[AYANOKOJI]
Really, this again?
I don't see why it would matter
at all to you what I told her.
Huh! What are you
even going on about?
You were blackmailing me
and then made me do
a bunch of weird stuff!
Also, if Sato finds
out about it,
then it's only a matter of
time before it gets around!
[AYANOKOJI]
I see.
I think I know what
you're getting at.
[laughs]
[AYANOKOJI] You're worried that,
if I get close with her,
I might get
distracted and forget
about my promise to
protect you, right?
[KARUIZAWA]
You think I care about that?
Am I wrong?
[KARUIZAWA] Not exactly,
but there's more to it!
I promise you,
that won't happen.
[KARUIZAWA] So, are you
going out or what?
[AYANOKOJI]
Huh. I didn't say we were.
[KARUIZAWA]
Yeah, but you didn't have to!
Honestly, all you boys
are exactly the same!
You've shown your true colors.
Anything to get in
a girl's pants, huh?
[AYANOKOJI]
Where's this coming from?
That's a tremendous
leap in logic.
Is it?
That was the first thing you
did when you blackmailed me!
[AYANOKOJI]
I see.
If I'm the kind of person
you're accusing me of being,
what does that
mean for Horikita?
Yeah right, you wish!
Horikita would never!
[AYANOKOJI] By the way, Sato
didn't actually ask me out.
Uh--
She just asked if we could
exchange phone numbers.
There wasn't anything
more to it than that.
[KARUIZAWA]
Oh. Was that really it?
Do you see now why I
told you it didn't matter?
[KARUIZAWA] You say that,
but I bet you secretly hope
you'll get paired up with her
during the special exam!
[AYANOKOJI]
Absolutely not.
Well, I guess I'll let you off
the hook just this one time!
[AYANOKOJI]
Wow, how gracious of you.
Whatever. Anyway,
that's all I wanted.
'Kay, bye!
[AYANOKOJI] Hold on a sec,
I wanna ask you something.
What's up?
[AYANOKOJI]
Those girls.
They haven't bothered you
since then, right?
Not yet. They just ignore me.
[AYANOKOJI] If they do, make
sure you come to me right away.
No matter what happens,
I swear I'll protect you.
You'd better!
I just mean,
those were the terms
of our agreement after all!
[AYANOKOJI] One more thing,
make sure you that you delete--
...all my call history.
I already know!
[AYANOKOJI]
Perfect, thanks. See ya.
[KARUIZAWA]
Ugh.
[AYANOKOJI] The next day,
Horikita explained the details
of her plan to everyone
else in the class.
They seemed pretty convinced
by her presentation,
and they all agreed
to go along with it.
In the 1960s, a Swiss zoologist
named Adolf Portmann
proposed the theory that all
humans were born premature.
Naturally, a newborn
can't walk on its own.
It has to learn
by trying and failing.
Horikita is the same way.
But that same
underdeveloped nature
doubles as the capacity
for infinite potential.
[AYANOKOJI] This was the
first time that Class D
was completely unified.
[AYANOKOJI] It seems leaving it
to her was the right choice.
[CHABASHIRA]
The tests have been graded.
I will now announce the
pairs for the Paper Shuffle.
Go, Ken!
[AYANOKOJI]
Oh, brother.