Lelouch, a young outcast prince of
Brittania, possesses two great powers:
One of them is Geass.
The absolute ability to compel any
person to do whatever he commands.
The other is the Black Knights.
His military force assembled with the intent of
destroying the Brittanian Empire ruled by his father.
Veiling his true identity behind
a mask, and the code name "Zero,".
Lelouch has made his move to avenge his mother's murder
and to create a world in which his
younger sister, Nunnally, can find happiness.
What will the be the final outcome of these actions?
At this point... no one can predict.
...clearing the last of the debris from
around the Lake Kawaguchi Convention Center Hotel.
It's been two weeks since Zero unveiled his Black Knights,
but there's still little insight
into the man behind the mask.
They weren't able to track his escape route?
They let the hostages go and
somehow made it to the other shore.
Unh! Kallen... I mean Miss.
Forgive me. I didn't wish to wake you...
Again?
I'm sorry, it was the step ladder this time, it broke...
Well, just get it cleaned up!
And be quick about it, I have to leave for school.
Mistress...
You've been attending school quite a bit lately.
Making any friends there?
I don't see how that's any of your business!
Just go, will you...?
I know it's for welfare,
but why waste it on the Elevens?
That's why I'm selling it to you, my friend.
The Eleven population could use a
little thinning out, if you ask me...
Your payment'll be transferred to your wife's account.
Princess Cornelia is a soldier.
This sort of thing doesn't interest her all that much.
Hit the lights! Turn 'em on!
You're... You're the...!
The Black Knights!
Huh?
That's not like you, dozing off in class like that!
Well... I, uh...
You could learn a thing or two from Lelouch.
He's an expert at sleeping in class.
Huh? He's not sleeping now, is he?
I dunno what he's up to, night after night,
but he sleeps through about half of 'em these days.
The E.U.'s starting an offensive
along the El Alamein front.
We can't go on dragging our feet around here.
I want to solidify domestic affairs.
It's high time Area 11 was made a satellite nation.
For that to happen, we need to
stamp out terrorism, of course.
But another major problem is the rampant
abuse of "Refrain" amongst the Elevens.
Productivity is plummeting.
It's coming in on the Chinese Frederation's Kyushu route.
We have to put an end to it.
Yes. But be careful.
You as well.
I don't want you leaving the settlement.
Cornelia... What about the Black Knights and Zero?
I'll let them roam free a bit longer.
I owe them that for saving your life.
However, upon my return...
Once I've cleaned up this area, I'm entrusting it to you.
Try to stay out of harm's way from now on.
All right, Euphie?
Because Clovis was an offspring of the Britannian emperor.
That reminds me...
You're one of his children, too, aren't you?
But I suppose for now...
When he spoke to me that night...
...what was he alluding to?
Suzaku... What would you make of all this?
About what Zero is doing...
And of me.
Man, this double life sure is a killer...
C'mon, Suzaku, hold him down!
Dammit, Suzaku, cut it out!
Stop it! I'm not kidding!
Sorry, Lelouch, but it's the president's orders.
Yeah, like you're not enjoying this at all?!
Will you hold still?
Huh? Good meowning!
Good... morning, I guess...
Huh?
What is all this?
Whaddya mean, didn't we tell you?
It's our welcome party for Arthur.
Sounds like fun...
Well, classes are postponed, we
might as well have some fun, right?
I set some stuff aside for you.
Over here!
To make up for all my getting so upset before.
Take your pick!
What? For me?
She doesn't need a costume.
Wha...?
You're already wearin' a mask, right?
You really are a riot, you know that?
You oughta be on television.
What do you think, Miss TV Star?
Oh, I thought she meant Lelouch.
Would you quit joking about that?
The whole thing's a huge pain in the butt!
We've been hounded with questions day and night!
Even in the bath!
We haven't been able to leave school grounds in a week.
Not that I don't feel for you, but I
don't see why we can't leave either!
Hmm, that's the price of friendship!
The Romance of the Three Kingdoms.
"It matters not that we were born apart,
upon this day we die as one."
Is that you're idea of a love quote?
If I go down, then we all do.
That's a little dark. Right, Suzaku? Huh?
I'm glad...
...that we could all be together again...
Ya know, like this...
Come onnn...
Hey! We're s'posed to be unwinding in here!
That's what's so refreshing about Suzaku though!
Yeah. Though once in a while, you
just want him to get a clue, ya know?
Oh. Sowwy 'bowt dat.
Ah, you love it, Putty-Tat.
It's so funny to think I helped save their lives...
Ever since we made our big splash at the hoteljacking,
the Black Knights have taken the world by storm.
We've become a friend to the weak,
just as Zero proclaimed we would.
Terrorists who involve civilians, overbearing military,
criminal syndicates, corrupt politicians and profiteers...
If the law would not punish them, then we would.
In the blink of an eye, we'd become heroes.
Support for us has swelled,
and we've even gotten our hands on some Knightmares again.
Of course, no one could show that in public...
because...
Stop pretending you're a Black Knight!
But why?!
You musn't ever say anything against Britannia!
We're Elevens, have you forgotten that?!
...because our leader, Zero, had killed Prince Clovis.
There are many in our ranks who
wish to know his true identity,
myself included.
But if we push too hard, I suspect that he would vanish...
And without him...
...I'm fairly certain we'd be finished.
Hey there, pal.
Haven't seen ya much lately.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Are you all right, young lady?
Why would the masses flock
around those who saved Euphemia?
Even Kyoto has said that they would
send the Black Knights the Guren MK-II.
To those would-be Robin Hoods?
They're not part of the resistance.
Killing Kusakabe was proof of that.
The colonel killed himself, didn't he?
Well, I hear they didn't try to stop him.
In any case, Lt. Colonel Tohdoh, we can't let this stand.
Mistress Kallen!
Madame President?
I just dropped by to give you something.
Huh...?
Where would you like me to show her to?
The parlor perhaps? Or maybe...
We'll be in my room.
As you wish.
Oh. I heard you had a friend down here.
I was sure it would be a boy.
Out all night and missing school,
not to mention all your visits to the ghetto...
You're lucky your father's back in the homeland.
No fighting one's blood, is there?
You're the one who's enjoying Dad
not being around here. Aren't you?!
Oh, dear, what have I done?
What's wrong with you?!
Forgive me, milady.
Forgive me...
Can't you do anything right?
Besides selling your body, that is...
Quite the complicated home life you have, isn't it?
So what was it you wantd to give me?
Grandfather asked me to pass this on.
You mean the principal?
Your transcripts since middle school.
I thought I'd better give them
to you off of school grounds.
So my secret's out then.
Isn't it?
That I'm actually an Eleven and Brittanian half-breed.
That was my stepmother down there.
My real mother was that clod of
a maid who knocked over the vase.
And your father...
Is he the head of the Stadtfeld family?
My mother is such a fool...
In the end, she wound up a servant.
She doesn't have any real skills,
and no matter who's ridiculing her,
all she can do is laugh like it's nothing.
She didn't have to choose to stay in this house, ya know?
She just clinging to some old lover who's jilted her...
You really hate your mother, don't you?
I just find her depressing...
Wow, this is getting a little heavy.
Imagine, the wife, and the daughter,
and the "other woman," all living together.
Ah, it could be worse.
Three square meals and a roof, right?
I mean, it's not unbearable...
Most of the time, anyway...
That's good.
Still... some things in life
we can bear on our own, but...
when you add 'em all up, they eventually break you.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't lie, I'm always hungry for secrets.
But I'd never talk about this.
I can't believe you teared up...
It's so embarrassing..
It's called "honesty."
Well, good thing the Black Nights were there to save 'em.
That's all I can say.
If they wanted to catch criminals, they
could've joined the police force, ya know?
Why don't they, I wonder...
They probably don't think the cops are up to the job...
I tend to agree...
The police may not be that effective right now,
but they could evoke change from within!
Yeah, and in the process they get all
tangled up in red tape and bureaucracy.
If they had done everything in their
power to change things, that might hold water!
As long as they don't, then all of
it's just self-righteous posturing!
Self-righteous?
And what constitutes "evil" in their eyes?
What standards are they using?
It's noting but self-satisfying gratification.
Oh? It's just you two?
Anyway.
I guess I've gotta go back to the base pretty soon.
See you around, Shirley.
Uh, ah...
See ya later!
Hmph.
So, Lulu!
I was, um...
I was thinking, if you had some time, You and I...
"Back" to base, now that was
an interesting choice of words...
Go back...
Implying that's where he thinks he belongs.
Refrain?
It's a psychotropic.
Makes ya think you've gone back to the past.
Must be all the rage here in Japan...
Yeah, well...
Who doesn't long for the days
before the occupation, right?
This stuff was specifically targeted at the Japanese.
We can't very well ignore it.
Soon as the Burais are stocked, we move.
Supplies keep rolling in.
And I hear lots of people are ready to join us...
Black Knights sure are popular, huh?
Well, we are the heroic Knights for Justice.
I'll call ya when the ammo gets here.
C'mon, Eleven! Say something!
You are sorry, aren'tcha?!
Bowin' your heads is what you Elevens do best, right?!
Eleven...
Eating bad food really makes us want to off somebody!
Lelouch!
No, there're five of them.
You wouldn't stand a chance at all.
So you think I should just ignore it?!
Go on, take a good look at that Eleven.
C'mon, what's the matter?! Aren'tcha gonna cry?
C'mon, buddy! Just say you're sorry!
If we intervene and help him win,
he wouldn't be able to sell a thing tomorrow.
It was his choice to become a Britanninan slave.
That's just the price you pay
for working in the settlement.
Well even so...
You got a problem over there?
Not feelin' sorry for this Eleven, are ya?
Nah, they feel the same way we do, don'tcha guys?
Not quite.
But you're tired of beating up Elevens now, aren't you?
Yeeah, this is boring.
You guys wanna hit the arcade?
I got no cash!
Well, they got bored pretty quick, huh?
Oh...
Hey, are you all right?
Huh...? A Britannian student!
Wh-What can I get for you?
How about a nice California hotdog, miss?
Ah! I-Is this your boyfriend?!
I can get him something, too!
I have ice cream, if you like!
In some ways,
Area 11 is better off now than the old Japan ever was.
Being made a colony of the empire has stablized
its military and economic position in the world.
Elevens can even attain full
citizenship through the legal process.
It's easy to become an honrary Britannian.
Just a question of pride really.
Though, I can certainly understand why they'd resist...
And?
Hmm?
Knowing all that,
what does Lelouch Lamperouge think about it all?
What do you wanna do?
Nothing.
You know, you've got a lot of brains
but you don't seem to be doing much with them.
It's all Shirley talks about.
Saying how intelligent you are, but
how you barely ever apply yourself.
That's why I don't do anything.
That Eleven we saw back there could tell you.
He can lead a better life, as long
as he bows his head to Britannina.
You must think you're pretty cool, huh?!
Just playing the critic and
judging the world from the sidelines?!
Guess I was a fool to expect anything more from you.
You know, I really thought
you were a better man than this!
Hmph.
So, about this Orange thing...
Sorry to bring it up.
Is this whole thing true, though?
That you can't remember anything about
when Private Suzaku Kururugi was taken?
I don't expect you to believe me.
No, it's just that...
During the whole Shinjuku incident,
I suffered some sort of memory lapse also.
You did?
By the time I regained my senses,
my Sutherland had been stolen.
But right before that entire gap in my memory,
I remember running into some high school kid.
So what you think it was that student?
I can't remember his face,
but there may still be a way to get to the bottom of this.
What the hell is Zero thinking?
After all his talk about bringing down Britannia,
he's just got us running around helping the police.
Still feels pretty good to have the
will of the people behind us though.
Yeah, he's right. We're totally heroes on the net.
Are we in the right? I don't know anymore.
Kallen...
There's the signal from Zero!
I can't believe he got in there.
How many tricks does this guy have up his sleeve anyway?
Is the shipment for Nagoya ready?
Nice 'n safe here in the settlement, huh?
The Black Knights have arrived!
Intruders!
A Knightmare!
Screw this!
These Knightmares really are amazing.
Each one is an army unto itself!
Japan! Japan! Japan!
That's right! I'm getting married next month!
I've been promoted.
I'm going to the Paris office!
You'll see the fireworks with me, right?
Leave it to us!
Japan is on the vanguard of technology!
Refrain...
I'm studying abroad! I can't believe I got in!
When you add 'em all up, they eventually break you.
That's right. Which is why I'm here!
Careful! It's dangerous to run like that!
Mother?!
Really, Naoto!
Please, I need you to keep an eye on your little sister.
My god how weak a woman are you, Mother?
First you give in to Britannia,
then to a man, and now this!
My brother is gone forever!
Let him go!
The Knightpolice?!
Isn't that a police unit?
They're in on this deal? Tamaki!
Don't look at me!
When I checked it out, there weren't any cops involved!
Corrupted filth!
You're in the way!
Dammit! I don't need you!
I don't want you!
Kallen... Naoto...
It won't work on a Knightmare!
Go on... run!
Get moving, you idiot!
I'm here for you.
I'm here for you, Kallen...
I'm here, as I always have been.
Then that's...
That's why you stayed in his house?!
You stayed there for me...?
You fool!
Or maybe, I'm the fool.
Kallen!
I'm so happy for you.
You can finally become a Britannian now, Kallen.
Nobody will ever be able to hurt you now, darling.
And you're free to travel and
use the phone any time you want.
So this... is her mother?
False tears bring pain to those around you.
A false smile brings pain to oneself.
It's an aftereffect of refrain.
She's unable to talk much.
She'll recover eventually, but it will take time.
Mother, your sentence... You got twenty years.
But you wait!
I'm working to change things
when you get out, I swear to you!
I'll make a world where you and
I can live a normal life again.
So, please... Mother...!
Hang in there...
Huh?
Hang in there, Kallen...
My little girl...
Don't you worry.
I will. I promise you!
Memories of the past?
Those who indulge in them are foolishly happy...
because they assume that tomorrow is coming...
But really... what guarantee is there of that?
If Kallen is struggling to dispel such illusions...
I'll stand by her.
All we can do is live each day, one moment at a time.