Open fire!
Gloucesters?!
They're supposed to be in Serupham!
Shoddy oversized imitation Knightmares!
They would've been wise to surrender from the start.
What?!
So, Cornelia, a single unit, did this?!
Another victory.
Area 18 has been established.
My Lady, about our next course of action...
Sorry to have you clean up
after my foolish younger brother.
Please don't apologize, milady.
We live to serve, and our place is with you.
Ha. Do you think Area 11 needs our usual treatment?
Yes, milady.
Good.
I'll drive you into the open, Zero.
Clovis will be avenged.
I'm back.
Welcome home, Lelouch.
I'm so glad. I was worried.
I'm assuming you ate out tonight,
judging from your appearance.
Thank goodness!
I thought maybe you'd gotten caught up
in all the uproar caused by that man Zero.
I tried calling you, but you
didn't answer your cell phone.
I wanted to tell you Miss C.C.'s
been waiting for you, as well.
C.C.?
Your friend goes by such an unusual name.
Only her initials.
Yeah...
I was just wondering, is C.C. your girlfriend?
Huh?
He made a promise about our future together.
Right?
Huh?
A future together? You mean marriage?
No!
No, that isn't what she was talkin' about.
It's like, uh...
She's kidding around.
No, I'm not.
Well, you're certainly doing this sooner than most.
But everyone's different, aren't they?
So I suppose it isn't that strange, and
if you feel like you're ready for... Uh.
Oh, C.C., look what you've done.
You're soaking wet.
C'mon, let's get you to the
bathroom into a dry change of clothes.
Nunnally, stay here, and I'll clean that up in a minute.
And she was kidding before. Kidding!
Just a dumb joke, that's all!
Who are you?
She said my name. I'm C.C.
That's not what I meant. Why aren't you...
Supposed to be dead?
So...
...do you like the power that I gave you?
As I thought. It was you.
Dissatisfied?
On the contrary, I'm grateful.
It allows me to speed up my schedule tremendously,
which is a huge help.
Your schedule?
Yes, my schedule for obliterating Britannia.
I'd have had to wait much longer
before I could've made the initial move.
You believe you can destroy it simply by using that power?
I intended to do it without this power.
I just knew that he'd turn out to be a fascinating guy.
What will you do now?
I'm sure the military is after you.
Not the entire military, only a small faction of it.
So it shouldn't be difficult to find a hiding place.
I can make do here.
What?! You expect to stay here?!
A gentleman would sleep on the floor.
Don't joke around.
My being caught would cause trouble for you, too.
It's dangerous to stay together.
If I wander the streets, they'll find me.
This isn't about you. It's my situation.
I hate stubbornness!
You sure take things casually, don't you?
How did you manage to survive before this?
What did you do before now?
And what's the deal with that
so-called "contract" you spoke...
Goodnight, Lelouch.
Fukushima, Kochi, Hiroshima.
This has been the seventh occurrence
since that man named Zero raised his head.
It seems that the other groups are following
his lead and putting up a valiant fight.
And now suspicions about that "Orange"
thing have cost Margrave Jeremiah his command.
Maybe he wasn't good enough. Thanks to him, connections
between the police and administration are screwed up.
It's made a fine mess for us, as well.
Help them, Tohdoh!
Zero has thrown the Britannians into chaos!
Now's the time for us in the Japan
Liberation Front to make our stand!
Calm down!
The information of Kyoto giving the
Guren MK-2 to Zero hasn't been confirmed.
If we pay too much attention to
Zero, we may trip ourselves up.
So, what did "Orange" turn out to be, anyway?
Hm?
Well?
You know, for someone who isn't
willing to answer any questions,
you certainly do ask a lot of them.
If you don't want to answer my questions,
you don't have to. Just as I don't.
There is no "Orange," it's something I made up.
But... the more they claim to be comrades of like mind,
the easier it is to divide
them with the thorns of suspicion.
Hm.
Everyone on Earth is looking for you.
Because of you, the world is going through an upheaval.
So....
Is this it? Is this what you wanted to see?
No.
This uproar is simply a means to an end.
The world is destined to descend into greater chaos.
Case number 107,
Private Suzaku Kururugi, Area 11 military forces.
In the murder of His Highness Prince Clovis,
you are no longer a suspect and
hereby set free due to lack of evidence.
What happened? I'm free.
Outta the way, please!
Look out below!
Uh... are you all right?
I'm sorry! I wasn't aware you
were down here until I had leaped!
Well, don't worry.
I wasn't expecting a girl to come falling
outta the sky and into my arms, either.
Oh, my!
Huh? Is there something wrong?
Yes! There is something wrong!
Huh?
The truth is, bad guys are chasing me.
So considering the circumstances,
could you help me, please?
We must get rid of this "Orange" character
before Princess Cornelia assumes her new post!
Now the loyalty of us purebloods
is being called into question.
Are the reports we've been hearing true?
Lord Jeremiah was bribed?
Do you know what this "Orange" means?
Uh...
In any case, Lord Jeremiah is definitely hiding something.
Saying he can't recall anything.
Bartley offered the same excuse.
Lord Jeremiah's memory is muddled.
Exactly like those of the men in
Shinjuku whose Sutherlands were stolen.
And...
We haven't introduced ourselves yet, have we?
My name is...
Euphy!
Euphy?
Yes.
My name's...
Don't tell me!
Huh?
'Cause I already know it. You're a celebrity.
Son of Prime Minister Genbu Kururugi,
Private Suzaku Kururugi.
Hm.
You lied before. There's no one chasing you at all, right?
Meow!
What?
Meow, meow!
Aw, does a kitty's paw hurt? Oh.
Meow, meow, meow!
Meow, meow.
Hm.
Oh, my.
We're running late.
I hope he's still waiting for us.
Considering the charge, did they really release him?
Yes, they had no evidence.
I'm sure they put him through the third
degree because of that Zero incident. Huh?
What? Why is he...?
Do you have trouble with cats?
Hm. I like them fine, however...
Hm. The attraction isn't mutual.
I think unrequited love is the mark of a kind person.
Oh!
Uh.
The kitty ran away.
Mm, Euphy...
Why did you tell me that lie when we met?
Do you ask because you're concerned about me?
Huh? Um, of course.
Good! Then you can accompany me some more!
All right.
C'mon, it'll be fun!
You know, being here is just like being in Britannia.
I feel right at home.
Are you from the Homeland?
Uh-huh! I was a student there up until last week.
Last week? So, what are you doing now?
By student, do you mean high school?
You can go sightseeing any time, can't you?
You ask a lotta questions.
Uh. Sorry...
Oh! No, I didn't mean it like that!
You see... today is the last day of my vacation.
I wanted to see as much of Area 11 as I could,
because I'd like to know what kind of place it is.
Well, you didn't need me for that.
No. I'm glad I could see with you.
Is that right?
Suzaku...
Would you mind taking me to one more place, please?
Your wish is my command, milady. Where to?
Take me to Shinjuku.
Suzaku Kururugi.
Please escort me there.
Lelouch?
Hm?
Do you have a minute?
Mh-hm. What is it?
About that phone call the other day...
Phone call?
Yeah... You know, when you and I were in the bathroom.
Uh-huh.
Can you find out what the caller I.D. was?
I want to contact that person again.
It was a school phone.
So I'm no sure, sor... Uh!
I see.
Makes sense. I should've known.
That girl.
Uh. What?
Is there something wro... Uh!
Huh?
No way...
Excuse me.
What're you doing?
Ah. What indeed.
To think I'd return to the Homeland like this.
I wish I'd never involved that damned girl.
Are you insane?!
You can't go walkin' around!
Don't act strict with me.
I never leave the school grounds, so it's fine.
It's not! You can't do as you like here. You don't belong!
I don't belong anywhere.
Hm? What's with her?
Oh. Is she doing it again today?
Again?
She's going to be markin' the wall like that every day,
because I used my Geass on her to make her do it.
Geass?
The name of the power I have.
That's what I heard when we first made contact.
Hm. You're testing how long it lasts?
I need to know the specs of my weapon, don't I?
So behave, or I'll try it on you.
Would it work... on me?
Uh.
Oh, relax.
You and I are in this together.
I won't do anything to endanger
us or our unique partnership.
Hmph.
The Shinjuku ghetto. Ruined again.
The residents were starting to return, too.
Man, they didn't use R-G on the Elevens.
I figured they wouldn't.
Hey, look! Those are marks from hummer rounds.
Get a clear shot of it!
Say "cheese"! Got it! Okay, me next!
This is accurate?
This information about Zero?
Yes, sir. Lord Kewell contacted me.
Right.
Set up a cordon around Shinjuku ghetto sector 4 at once!
Cordon sector 4, roger.
Okay, ball's in your court now, Lord Kewell.
I wanted to put be through to Lord Jeremiah,
but it appears that you're too busy now.
Get out of here, you damn Britannian bastards!
Stay here!
How dare a lowly Eleven speak like...
Don't call me an Eleven! I'm Japanese!
Wrong, you seem to forget that you people lost!
You're nothing but a beaten dog!
You racist pig!
Stop, please! No violence!
Stay outta this!
You're that...
Are you... Suzaku Kururugi?
The guy who killed Clovis?
No, idiot. It was Zero who killed him.
Tch. This guy's nothing more than a slave.
Big deal, you're an honorary Britannian. Nobody cares.
You sold your pride, your people, your soul,
yet you call yourself Japanese?!!
No, you're wrong! I...
I am not wrong!
You stinkin' Britannian lap dog!
Stop, please!
I warn you, I've been trained for military combat.
Don't make me fight against my own people.
Like hell we're "your people"!
C'mon, just let it go!
Ugh! Lousy traitor!
Suzaku!
Oh, my! Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Well, I'm not okay! Just look at my Prime G and my LX-4!
Why did you wait?!
Dammit, some honorary citizen you are!
Why'd you let 'em go?! You shoulda killed them!
What's a few dead Elevens to a guy like you?!
Who do you think's taken care
of you all of these years anyway?!
I'll not allow you to insult this man any longer, you oaf!
To use my Geass, I need to have
direct eye contact with the subject.
Transparent objects like eyeglasses present no problem.
The effective range is approximately 270 meters,
and the subject appears to have no memory of
events before, during, or after the power is used.
I think this is due to damage caused by the
Geass interfering with the brain of the subject.
Also, if the signal's optical, I can reflect it.
In the short time you've had it, you've learned a lot.
My opponent is an empire that controls
more than one-third of the entire world.
There's no such thing as being too careful.
I'd understand if you were an Eleven,
but you're a Britannian, aren't you?
This opponent may be too large and strong
to fight with only Geass for a weapon.
Is it good to be strong?
Is it bad to be weak?
Back then, when I was ten,
the world seemed like such a terribly sad place.
A world without any hope at all.
Starvation.
Disease.
Filth.
Decay.
Racism.
Constant war and terrorism.
Living in a never-ending cycle of hate.
Rat's running in a wheel.
The cycle must be broken.
Somebody has to do it.
How idealistic.
Of course, it's doubtful that the one who
does it will make all the bad things go away.
I'm not that arrogant. And so...
No one should lose more of the people they love.
At least, a world without war.
And to have this utopia you'd...
How would you do it?
It's simple.
When somebody wins...
...the fighting will end.
Somebody?
I don't know how you would do it.
But if I stop trying,
then my father's death will have been in vain.
The Prime Minister's death?
My own father died because he had
to sacrifice his life in that war!
Jeremiah!
You're going to pay for letting
Prince Clovis' murderer go free!
Kewell, you dirty coward!
That sighting of Zero was a lie, wasn't it?!
We have to wipe away our disgrace before
Princess Cornelia takes up her post here.
This is how we keep our officials honest.
Suzaku!
Miss Cecile!
It's dangerous here! Get in!
The purebloods are having a silly squabble.
Better get out of here.
Oh, and by the way, what a shame about your acquittal.
Because now you'll have to work for me again.
Wait, please!
Isn't this an opportunity to
gather battle data for the Lancelot?
Uh?
Oh, ho...
Suzaku...
I'm sorry, Euphy, we have to say goodbye here.
I need to do this. I think I
can stop them with the Lancelot.
I have to try. I...
I must!
Damn! It's four against one!
Cowards!
Don't worry, Jeremiah.
We'll say you died in battle.
Your family's name won't be disgraced.
You're serious then?
You actually intend to kill me?!
Kewell!
Silence, Orange!
We serve the imperial family!
Why else would we be here?!
All... hail... Britannia!
Wha...?!
Stop it! You're all Britannian soldiers!
That's him. It's that honorary Britannian.
The advanced weapon! Lancelot!
What business does the Special Corps want here?!
Interlopers will die!
No!
I can't stand by and ignore this senseless battle!
Oh my god. They've perfected the MVSs.
Too late! I won't back down!
We're on the same side!
Suzaku Kururugi... is saving me?
We can at least kill Orange!
Lord Jeremiah!
Villetta, thanks!
Still wanna fight?
Men, stand down.
Kewell?
You understand, then?
I'm using a chaos mine.
Huh?
No! Stop it now!
What?
That honorary Britannian...
He risked his life for...
Everyone, lower your weapons at once!
In my name, I command you!
It... can't be.
I am Euphemia Li Britannia of the empire,
and the third princess of the royal family!
Euphy?
I'm assuming command here! Now fall back!
It is her. It's the princess.
Did you know it was her, Lloyd?
Uh-huh. But she's been a student up until
now and hasn't made her public debut yet.
We... we're truly...
We're truly sorry, Your Highness!
My lady!
Uh?
I had no idea who you were. Please forgive me, Princess!
Suzaku, you and I bear a similar deep pain.
You have lost your father as I have lost my brother.
Will you let me help you in your quest to ensure that
no one ever again has to suffer the
loss of a loved one on the battlefield?
Yes! I'm... unworthy of your kindness.
I heard what you did, Euphemia.
You shouldn't be so reckless.
I know, sister. Forgive me. But...
You will address me as viceroy here, sub-viceroy Euphemia.
Because we're sisters, we need
to follow a stricter protocol.
Yes. I understand.
Heh.
Now then, give me your report.
Yes. Milady, the first order
of business is a welcome party
we've arranged for Your Highness and... Uh!
Sloppy. Senile. Corrupt.
Where is Zero?! I want the enemy of the empire caught!
Get Zero!
Uh?
I'll be joining the student body
here at Ashford Academy beginning today.
My name is Suzaku Kururugi.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yes. I understand. I'm lying.
To Shirley and Rivalz and the others.
Even to Suzaku and Nunnally.
But there's no goin' back now.
I can't turn back.
As long as C.C. and I are bound by our "contract,"
I have to keep at this.
Beause I don't wanna lie to myself any more.