Huh?
The date was August 10 in the
year 2010 of the Imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had
just declared war upon Japan.
The far east island nation
had held fast to its neutrality,
and now Britannia looms as the world's only superpower.
Rights to Japan's underground
resources became a hotly disputed issue,
straining the already deep-rooted
diplomatic tensions between the two sides.
In the deciding battle for the mainland,
Britannian forces introduced into combat
the humanoid autonomous armored knight
known as the Knightmare Frame.
The enemies forces were far greater than anticipated,
and the Knightmares obliterated the Japanese
line of defense on the mainland with little effort.
Japan became a dominion of the empire.
The country was stripped of its freedom, its rights,
and its name.
Area 11.
The defeated and once-proud nation of
Japan was re-christened with a mere number.
I swear...
Huh?
I swear, Suzaku, so help me!
I will one day... obliterate Britannia!
This is Alpha 3.
Target is traveling from Delta-12 toward
Delta-14 at a speed of 80 kilometers per hour.
CCP to all mobile units.
Declaring a code 3 from floor 5 to floor 2.
All units, take 2-8-8. I want the target intact.
Here's video footage of yesterday's
terrorist bombings in Osaka.
The Secretary reported 59 casualties in this incident.
8 Britannians and 51 others.
You're out of time.
From here on, you'll make your moves every 20 seconds.
Huh! Very well, I'm game.
Hm? Did your substitute arrive?
Thank heavan, I'm saved.
Are things going well at school?
What have we here? School boys?
Hmph.
Well, look at this, a nobleman.
I envy you kids today, you
have so much time on your hands.
Time for regrets...
What's your name?
Lelouch. Lamperouge.
Whoa, now wait a minute!
You can't win this one, it's impossible. Right?
Rivalz.
Huh?
When do you think we would have to leave
in order to make our next class?
Uh, 20 minutes, if we bust our hump.
Then be sure that you drive safely on the way back.
Huh?!
I'll need nine minutes.
And by the way, about yesterday...
Understood, sir. We'll discuss it later.
Nine minutes?
You only have 20 seconds per move.
Enough time.
Hm?
You start with the king?
Where's Lelouch?
He went somewhere with Rivalz.
What, maybe it's poker this time?
They seem to forget that they're on the student council!
They're off gambling for money!
Lulu may be smart, yet he
wastes his brain on stupid things!
If he'd only apply himself in
school, he'd get high grades!
"Oh, I wish my darling Lulu would be a serious young man."
How adorable is that?!
Uh. Please, Madam President...
Perfect!
After we finally steal this damn thing!
It's all because Tamaki couldn't stick to Naota's plan!
And now we've got a problem!
I love playing against the nobility!
When they lose, they always pay out of pride.
By the way, 8 minutes, 32 seconds is a new record!
He also didn't have much time to move, either.
And as opponents go, the nobles are tepid.
They're just over-privileged parasites, that's all.
Well then, why don't you challenge one of the Elevens?
They're nothing like us Britannians.
Huh?
What're they trying to prove by killing innocent people?
Those Elevens terrify me.
We apologize for the delay.
Now, His Royal Highness Prince Clovis, third
prince of Britannia, will address the nation.
To all my imperial subjects!
Including, of course, the many cooperative
Elevens who choose to serve the empire of Britannia!
We're not "Elevens," we're Japanese!
Do you not see my pain?
My heart was ripped from my chest only to be torn apart!
The remnants are filled with rage and sadness!
However, as ruler of Area 11,
I will not tolerate terrorism of any kind!
Because the battle we fight is a righteous one!
A virtuous battle to protect
the well-being of one and all!
Now then, everyone,
I would like you to join me in observance of
the eight who died for justice in the line of duty.
A moment of silence, please.
Well, aren't you gonna join in?
Aren't you?
Heh! It's sort of embarrassing.
And I agree with you.
Besides, spilling tears over those people
won't bring them back to life, now will it?
Dang! That's dark, buddy!
It's all about self-satisfaction.
Doesn't matter how hard you try.
You can't do it.
There's no way you can change the world.
You were magnificent, Your Highness!
One would never guess that you were
attending a party while doing that!
After all, the viceroy is the marquee actor of Area 11.
I need to change costumes quickly.
My! You're so self-confident!
It's all in the performance.
Since the media want a
charismatic prince, I give them one.
Untrue! Prince Clovis, our key purpose in life is
to support and assist your reign in any way we can!
His reign is a pathetic sham.
Y-Your Highness!
Huh? A soldier?
Gad, how boorish of you.
I beg your pardon, Your Highness, m'lord...
Not another appearance for him.
Hope it's not as dreary.
You fool!
Hm?
The police were informed that
it's medical equipment, that's all.
If we scramble the army, there'll be a record...
Deploy the Royal Guard! The Knightmares as well!
Alert 1! Alert 1!
4th, 7th and 8th Rapid Reaction Companies
as well as the 31st Air Assault Team, immediate scramble!
Special Division Nine, stand by for deployment!
That first move you made.
Hm?
Why'd you start with the king?
If the king doesn't lead, how can
he expect his subordinates to follow?
What's with that?
With what?
Do you fantasize about running a major corporation?
No way.
Ambitions like that will ruin your health.
Waaaagggh! We're gonna die!
You idiot! Watch where you're going!
No, not that way!
Eh... Was that our fault?
I don't think so.
Uh?
Control, the target has crashed at the
abandoned V.O. building construction site.
The military will take over General Bartley's command.
Him?!
We have to retrieve it at all costs!
That thing... in the wrong hands...
What the...?
Oh, man, this sucks!
Looks like the power line on the bike got cut.
Yeah... Rivalz, come check this out.
Hey! Over here!
Whoa... nasty crash.
What happened, some sort of accident?
Probably a drunk driver.
It's always some moron!
Hey, maybe somebody oughta go help.
Hmph. All those idiots...
Wait!
Look, the student rescue team has arrived!
So like, why doesn't somebody call for help, y'know?
Hey! Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah, I know it's the right thing to do,
but I wish the guy would quit flaunting
his pride and just give it a rest for a while.
Now we're gonna be late to school.
Nagata! Nagata!
Can you hear me? Are you okay?!
It's you... Finally, I have found my...
But where...?
Are you in there?
Stop! I'm in here!
So, would you call that a hit-and-run?
You'd think they'd stick a ladder on the inside, too!
Stop the vehicle!
Surrender now, and you'll get the
chance to defend yourself in court.
Stop and surrender at once!
Give up now, or we will shoot to kill!
Now whadda we do?! That's the Army!
Have you forgotten? That's what I'm here for!
If I jump out, I have the choice
of breaking my neck or getting shot.
I can try to call... Uh.
Can you enter the subway via the Azabu route?
Kallen! Let's use it here! Why not?!
Because that would mean a blood bath!
You're right...
I've seen her before...
Lelouch, c'mon, where are you?
We've gotta get to school!
Target is moving from the settlement toward the ghetto.
Copy that! Corner 'em!
Roger!
A slash harken?!
A Knightmare!
Crap! These guys are real terrorists!
You fellas know full well what this bad-ass mother can do!
The rest of you, back off.
I'll take this guy.
I can only assume you dug that
obsolete relic out of some scrap heap.
An over-the-hill Glasgow is no match for a Sutherland!
Not to mention a filthy Eleven who spurns
the compassion of our glorious emperor!
Kallen, we should both split up!
Both of us can't risk being killed! Run for it!
But...!
Heh. Simple-minded Eleven.
No way! It's stuck!
Secondhand junk!
I'll admit, I really like your spirit.
However...
Tsk! No cell phone reception...
We're out of range.
Judging from the darkness and road surface,
we must be drivin' along the old subway lines.
They're headed for an exit somewhere in the ghetto.
Getting out will be dangerous.
Still... Okay, I've got it...
I'm not big on the military,
but I'll take their protection.
If I give them a terrorist communicator...
Oh, wait, I forgot...
Some friend! Leaving me behind like that!
Ah-ha!
What're you doing?
Looking at a man who blundered, am I right?
Why you...!
You really screwed this one up.
Terrorists came along and stole whatever
it was that you and Prince
Clovis were secretly working on.
Retrieving it is simple, but you want to
sweep up all of their compatriots, in addition.
Let the terrorists go, and
you can find their hideout, too.
Congratulations! Your reasoning was on spot on!
Uh, it was nothing. I just thought it was strange.
Okay, that's enough!
What is it the special corp wants outta this?
I'm merely saying that I'd
like to assist with the clean up.
To assist?
Correct, because it's data I want.
Excuse me,
but what in the world have they just stolen, anyway?
Chemical weapons.
In other words... poison gas.
The terrorists are hiding in the subway system.
Your mission is to locate the weapon that they've stolen.
Investigate the old subway system that runs through
the Eleven residential district in the Shinjuku ghetto.
Report in the moment you spot them.
Recovery of the target will be
handled by us, the Royal Guard.
You people bear the honorary title of Britannians now,
but you were born Elevens.
Therefore, the stench of these
monkeys oughta be a familiar one.
If you want to earn the right to carry arms,
then show some results!
This is your opportunity to
show your loyalty to Britannia!
Yes, my lord!
An accident? Or else...
No... the tire's stuck...
Please, Ohgi... Find me...
4-0-4 has sighted the target.
Roger! Prepare for recovery!
Now I can use this chance to climb up.
Are you Britannian?
That's enough mindless murder!
Wait! I'm not one of...!
Planning to use poison gas?
Huh?!
Don't play dumb with me!
Get off me!
I'm not here by choice!
And if that's poison gas, it
was made in Britannia, wasn't it?
My god...
Mindless murder?
Then why don't you just obliterate Britannia!
Lelouch...
It's me. Suzaku.
You...
You became a Britannian soldier?
Yeah, and what about you? You're a...
What're you saying?!
That's not poison gas...
What is it?
In all the confusion, I left it in the coat.
It's okay.
The Glasgow's circuits are usable.
So, were we right?
Think so.
I bet it's poison gas, like intelligence said.
And Nagata?
I dunno. I think he made it underground.
Tell me the truth, Suzaku.
Poison gas? This girl?
Hey, it's what they told us in the briefing, I swear!
Huh?!
Stinking monkey.
Being an honorary Britannian will not excuse you!
Uh! But sir! I was told this was poison gas!
How dare you question orders!
This is bad.
A poisonous situation.
Which would pose a threat to
Suzaku's superiors if it's unleashed.
However, in light of your outstanding
military achievements, I'm going to be lenient.
Private Kururugi, take this and execute the terrorist.
But he's not a terrorist!
He's a civilian who got caught up in all this!
You insubordinate little...!
That's an order!
Didn't you swear your loyalty and your life to Britannia?!
Yes, but...
But... I can't.
Uh.
What?
I won't do it, sir.
I won't shoot a civilian.
I can't follow your orders, sir.
Very well.
Suzaku!
Well, Britannian school boy, not a good day to cut class.
Collect the girl.
After you've secured her, kill the student!
Yes, my lord.
Death to...
...Britannia...
Long live...
...Japan.
They got away?!
And you call yourselves the Royal Guard?!
Uh. Forgive me, my lord!
The blast was mainly directed upwards, but the bed...
Why the hell do you think I
only told you people about this?!
W-We'll continue the investigation.
The plan has moved forward to the next phase.
B... But, Your Highness!
If knowledge of her gets out, I'll be disinherited.
Tell them back home we're carrying
out a planned "urban renewal" here.
As Clovis, third prince of the empire, I command you!
Destroy Shinjuku ghetto! Leave no one alive!
W... Why are they doing this?!
Dear, let's go!
H... Hurry!
Okay, let's sweep the next floor.
The enemy is garbage that can never
hope to become even honorary Britannians!
Wipe out every last one of them!
Naturally.
Supervisor Jeremiah,
General Bartley requests that you take command...
Bartley has staff officers.
I haven't had this much fun on the front lines in ages!
Hmph.
What the hell are you?!
This chaos is all your fault, isn't it?!
Aaaggh!
Not only that but Britannia has...
They even killed Suzaku!
Not there?
It looks like he's gone to the front line.
Even though we brought the Lancelot here?
Now what'll do we do?
We steam rolled our way in here,
but we don't have a devisor to use it.
Stay quiet, and wait here.
Report.
We found only Elevens here, sir.
Ahhh.
You're sure of it?
That exit comes out here?
Yes, sir. It matches up with our map of the old city.
Hm?
Huh?
That jerk! He hung up on me! I can't believe it!
What an appropriate location
for a terrorist to meet his end.
You scum...
Still, you did well for a student,
but that's to be expected. You're a Britannian.
Unfortunately, my clever young friend...
...you have no future.
He mustn't die!
You shot her!
Hmph.
Our orders were to bring her back alive, if possible.
Oh well, nothing can be done about it now.
We'll tell our superiors that the Royal Guard
found the terrorist hideout and killed them all.
Regrettably, the female hostage
had already been tortured to death.
What do ya think, school boy?
How can this be happening?
First Suzaku's killed... then this girl...
Now I'm about to die...
...before I've had a chance to
do a single thing with my life.
It's gone in a heartbeat...
Nanally!
You don't want it to end here. Do you?
What?
You appear to have a reason for living.
The girl? That's impossible.
If I grant you power, could you go on?
I propose a deal.
In exchange for this power, you must
agree to make my one wish come true.
Accept this contract, and you accept its conditions.
While living in the world of humans,
you will live unlike any other.
A different providence...
A different time...
A different life.
The power of the king will
condemn you to a life of solitude.
Are you prepared for this?
A convergence with the Ragnarok Connection?
So the myth is beginning once again?
Yes!
I hereby accept the terms of your contract!
Hm?
Say, how should a Britannian who
detests his own country live his life?
Are you some kind of radical?
Huh?
What's wrong? Why not shoot?
Your opponent is just a school boy.
Or have you finally realized?
The only ones who should kill are
those who are prepared to be killed!
Uh... What's happening here?
I, Lelouch vi Britannia, command you!
Now, all of you...
DIE!
Happily, Your Highness!
Fire!
That was the turning point.
Since that day, I've lived a lie.
The lie of living.
My name, too, was a lie. My personal history, a lie.
Nothing but lies.
I was sick to death of a world that couldn't be changed.
But even in my lies, I refused to give up in despair.
But now this incredible power... it's mine.
Well, then!