The date was August 10 in the
year 2010 of the Imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had
just declared war upon Japan.
Confronted by Britannia's newest weapon,
the formidable Knightmare Frame,
Japan fell to its enemy in less than a month.
The conquered nation was stripped of
its freedom, rights, culture, and dignity.
Finally, even its name was taken away.
Eleven.
The name of Japan and its people
was replaced with a mere number.
I don't understand
what it is you wanted me to do?
Why did you give me this bizarre power?
How could all these royal guard be dead?!
What happened here, boy?!
And why is a Britannian student in a place like this?!
Are you deaf?! Answer me, or I'll...
Answer me!
I order you to come out! At once!
Who the hell do you think you are to order me?
I see.
It only works with direct eye contact.
My name is Alan Spacer.
My father's a duke.
Nobility.
My I.D. card's in my breast pocket.
After you confirm who I am, I'll request your protection.
Keep your hands up in the air.
I'll take out your I.D.
Now then, hand your Knightmare over to me.
Understood.
The code number is XG21G2D4.
Got it.
What the...?
So, are we having a bad day?!
Looks like you missed a chance
to go heaven, Private Kururugi.
I did? Uh.
Where...?
Hm? Ah. We're still in the Shinjuku ghetto.
With Prince Clovis nearby, this is
probably the safest place anywhere.
This is what saved your life, Mr. Suzaku.
You're lucky it was under your protective
suit because that's what deflected the bullet.
Is it a keepsake?
Yeah. Very.
You Elevens believe that gods live inside of
everything, even objects, don't you? I guess this one...
Is Lelou...?
What's the latest on the situation?
It looks like the poison gas was released.
Massive Eleven casualties have been reported.
They haven't caught the perpetrators yet.
They haven't, huh? Not yet...
Private Kururugi, how much experience do
you have in piloting a Knightmare Frame?
Wha...?
But... there's no way an Eleven would be made a knight.
Well, supposing you could.
Congratulations!
The only Knightmare of its kind awaits you!
Once you take the controls of this big beauty,
everything will change. You and your world.
Whether you want it to or not.
Those damned Brittanians!
Kallen! Can the Glasgow still move?!
Don't worry, Ohgi, it's all right! I'll decoy them!
Get the people out of here!
The only ones that'll be captured
are those us in the resistance!
I know, but we're trapped!
They've got us completely surrounded!
When that happens, use this sticker.
What's that for?
That's because you don't have enough leg strength, right?
You're wrong. You sink when you get fat.
Because you snack, right?
Huh?
I'll be fine. I burn up twice as many calories.
Uh, Lelou?
Uh, what in the world have you been doing?
Where are you now?
If you keep cutting class, you'll get held back.
Are you near a TV?
A TV?
Sorry, but this is important.
Hmph.
Hang on.
Hey, can I change the channel?
Huh? To what?
The news.
Is there anything about Shinjuku?
News? Let's see...
There's nothing on. Traffic restrictions?
Why is it restricted?
I dunno. They're not saying.
I get it.
Once they finish everything off, they'll
release news that favors the military.
Hm?
Oh, you're gambling again, aren't you?
I've warned you before, more
than once, how dangerous that is!
Yup. You caught me.
By the way, tell my little sister that
I'm gonna be home late tonight, would you?
Thanks.
Oh!
Why does he always hang up on me like that?!
The number you have called is beyond service range.
Oh, darn it, not this again.
They need to keep a lid on this information,
so it'll be hard for them to call in reinforcements.
They'll have to make do with
the pieces they have on the board.
I'm hemmed in here,
it'll be tough to break through by myself.
Gaining refuge carries its own risk, too.
I want payback for bein' dragged into your fight.
It's our Glasgow friend.
Just 30 minutes left!
The west entrance!
Use the tracks to move to the west entrance!
Who's this?!
How do you know this code?!
That doesn't matter!
If you wanna win, you're just gonna have to trust me!
To win?
Okay, what am I supposed to do now?
You pathetic Eleven.
If you simply run away,
this hunt hasn't much to offer in the way of sport.
Since you trusted me, you're gonna win.
Jump onto the train!
Gotcha!
You think you can get through that way, hm?
If that's your plan, then...
You, go after the Glasgow!
Yes, my lord!
What the...?!
Shot by friendly fire?!
What's your name and your unit?!
We're after the one-armed Glas...
Oh my god! A terrorist?!
You son of a...!
You saved me.
But how did you get a hold of a Sutherland? Uh?
What? Where did he go?
Kallen!
What the hell was that radio message earlier?
What? He contacted you, too?!
Sure did. And Yoshida's group oughta be here soon.
Hm?
Are you in charge?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
I present to you the cargo in that train over there.
They're tools for your victory.
If you want to use them to win, then follow my orders.
There's more in here!
Here, too!
Amazing!
Maybe we can give this guy a chance!
All this...
But how...?
Woman in the Glasgow.
Y-Yes!
Stay where you are.
Your unit's gonna run decoy, you got that?
Understood.
Energy filler status?
About 15 minute's worth.
Then recharge it.
In ten minutes, I'll contact
you with your next instructions.
This is wearing me out.
Regardless, I'll need determination to succeed.
After all, I'm betting my life in this game.
The terrorists are mixed among the Eleven populace
and they're mounting a minor resistance against us.
But they pose little threat to our vastly superior army.
We know that. Moving on...
Understood, Your Highness.
The gas capsules will be...
What the public thinks.
Yes. We'll keep searching for her.
Either way, I want her captured, dead or alive.
Hey, are you certain about this whole thing?
They've all had their IFF's removed.
What if this is a trap?
The other side has total advantage in this war.
They don't need to set any traps!
All right, people, let's move!
Get to your assigned points...
P-1, can you move?
It operates basically the same as what you're used to.
Can't you tell us who you are?
At least your name.
I can't do that.
What if these signals are being intercepted?
Any way, if Q-1 is on schedule, enemy Sutherlands,
probably two of them, will reach you in 23 seconds.
Shoot them through the wall.
Aah! He's outta his mind!
Everyone, double-check your weapons.
What?! Are you serious?!
Enemy spotted at point F-31.
A feint, eh? How pedestrian.
Tell Lazlo squad to go straight in!
Have Eugen and Valerie strike from the rear!
Three... two... one... Fire!
What?!
Sir Eugen and Sir Valerie, both lost.
Huh? An ambush?
An I.D. signal can be a double-edged sword.
Besides, if the terrorists follow the orders I issue,
my task at hand is sure to be completed.
P-1, P-4, P-7, move 100 meters to the right.
Fire your slash harkens toward three o'clock.
You heard him! Do what the voice says!
Damn, what else does he want us to do?!
P-5, ready?
Agh! Quit callin' me that!
They're using the same...
The enemy's moving towards G-28!
Send Lazlo squad... I mean Glaube squad!
This means... terrorists have our military weaponry?
Sir Glaube has ejected!
His unit's been lost!
Change our codes! They're intercepting our transmission!
We already have, sir! Four times!
Do it again!!
This failure is unacceptable!
Forgive me!
Good afternoon!
What is it?!
We're in the middle of an operation!
I'd say it's time to deploy the ASEEC's special weapon.
We've no time for this right now!
R-2, fire anchor.
B-7, use U.N. ordnance.
N-Group, you'll continue your advance.
You filthy Elevens.
We just lost Lazlo squad!
So do it! We'll have to bring up Quincy's squad!
My lord, that will break the encirclement!
Now then. The enemy has five options. Their move...
Reinforce the breach with some of the units guarding me.
All we know for certain is that enemy forces are here.
Who ordered them to break formation?
Well, that's a more stupid move than I expected.
You, Q-1, do you have an area map?
Yes, I have a map of the old town.
But it has no current landmarks.
It'll do.
All right. Send in Bertz and the others, too!
Mission Number Three now.
Concentrate our forces there! Surround them!
Is everything prepared?
The enemy's main force is that center dot.
Finish every one of them off!
What?! Where's the enemy?!
With this, I call check.
My plan worked, didn't it?
I can do it! I can! I can defeat Britannia!
Who...?
Who in hell am I up against?!
What if... he's even better than Tohdoh?!
Lloyd!
Yes, Your Highness?
Can it win?
Will your toy beat them?
Hmph.
My lord. Please be so kind as to call it Lancelot.
Z-0-1 Lancelot, now activating.
Lancelot activating. Releasing hatch.
Z-0-1 Lancelot, stand by for activation.
Pallet extension, initiating.
Did you read the manual?
Pretty much.
Well done.
You scored at the top of the class in the simulator.
Hey, look, about what you told me earlier...
Huh?
Ah... It could be, but the possibility is nearly zero.
But that means there's still a chance, right?
Yes, I'm afraid that's true.
Even so, you're not to do anything reckless.
The new system is not outfitted
with an ejection mechanism.
Okay. I understand, Miss Cecile.
That's it?
Yes. The advanced weapon developed by us in
the Advanced Special Envoy Engineering Corps.
Lancelot. The world's first
7th generation Knightmare Frame.
Well, if you're ready, Suzaku, shall
we proceed with the initial start-up?
Initial start-up now proceeding from phase 20.
Equipping energy filler.
Confirm pre-start.
Energy filler now at full output.
Thirty seconds to reach critical voltage.
Core luminous, shifting phase. Yggdrasil Drive...
Initiating Devicer set up.
Confirming entry of devicer into Z-0-1.
Individual ID registration, confirmed.
Confirm man-machine interface, engaged.
Yggdrasil resonance, confirmed.
Rejection response, weak.
Devicer stress response, weak.
All readings nominal.
So far, it's going per the data.
Status, all green.
Status of back-up tactical bank, authorized.
Secondary confirmation given.
Lancelot.
Activate M.E. boost!
Lancelot, launch!
Running full throttle right out of the gate!
Cooler than the manual.
With this... Uh.
Huh? What is that?
It doesn't look like a Suther...
Another push, and the checkpoint with fall...
This is B-Group, reporting enemy presence!
Hm? Reinforcements?
Real battle is different, isn't it?
Status.
Everyone ejected,
but they took out four units in nothing flat!
Enemy numbers?
Just one!
I think it's a new model.
Never seen anything like... Ah!
What's happening out there?!
Bastard!
What?! It reflects bullets?
Ah! What do we do?!
Ishida!
Useless so-called terrorists.
With all the resources they have,
they're being beaten by one unit.
Dammit!
Yes, I can do this!
With Lancelot, I can stop all this at once!
N-4, N-5, hold there.
When the rear units arrive, surround that thing!
Gotcha.
We can't stop it!
N-units, what is it?!
What happened? Something I didn't foresee?
For heaven's sake...
Now I'll owe my older brother
a debt I don't need to incur.
It's for the best, though.
P-1, report!
The enemy...
Can it really be only one unit?
These readings are even higher than predicted.
It's because our pilot is taking his job very seriously.
If I can stop all of the
Knightmares, then this battle is over.
No matter what it takes,
I've gotta save Lelouch and that girl.
Uh?
You mean this thing's what's ruining my plan?!
Are you the guy that's in command?
Nothing more than a pilot! How dare he!
No choice, I've gotta get outta here!
Hey! I'm returning the favor!
I can't...!
I must remember that.
The most vital element in battle is the human one.
That damn monster's unstoppable!
Bastard! He's tearing things up for no reason!
Huh?
In the midst of battle, he rescues someone?
Hmph. I'll concede you the tactical victory here.
Nevertheless...
Huh? He saved someone?
Yes. So it would seem.
Hmm...
It's very strange of him.
Suzaku?
Are you tired? We'll call it quits for today.
No, I'm fine. Please let me keep going.
Be careful with his operational time!
Yes, sir!
My, that boy's an excellent piece of equipment.
Stop there! Your I.D.
This is Prince Clovis' personal transport!
At last, the checkpoint.
And barely guarded, per my plan.
Your plan?
That's right.
Now, I'd like you to let me pass.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Kallen!
It's your fault!
This is what happens when you oppose the Britannians!
What?! Why, you gutless coward!
How many people were killed because of this?!
Shut up! Do you know how many of
us were killed or captured?! Do ya?!
Quit cryin'!
Ohgi, who was that voice we heard?
Damned if I know.
He doesn't answer when I call, so maybe he bought it.
There, you see?!
Instead of following somebody we don't
even know, we should've used the poison gas!
But he...
Damn Nagata to hell!
So, this is where you Eleven vermin scurried off to.
Prepare to fire!
Naoto!
Commence...
Attention, all forces! Cease fire at once!
Uh?
Cease fire?
I, Clovis, third prince of Brittania, and
royal viceroy of Area 11, hereby command you!
All forces are ordered to cease fire at once!
You will also cease destruction
of any buildings or property!
All casualties, whether Britannian or Eleven,
shall be treated equally and without prejudice!
In the name of Clovis La Britannia, you
are hereby ordered! Cease fire at once!
I shall allow no further fighting!
Are you satisfied?
Very. Well done.
And what shall we do now?
Sing a few lively ballads?
Or perhaps a nice game of chess.
That has a familiar ring.
Hm?
Don't you recall?
The two of us used to play chess together as boys.
Of course, I would always win.
What?
Remember? At the Aries villa?
You...
Who are you?
It's been a long time, big brother.
The eldest son of the late Consort Marianne
and 17th in line to the imperial throne.
Lelouch vi Britannia, at your service.
Lelouch? But-But I thought...
That I was dead? You were wrong.
I have returned, Your Highness.
And I've come back to change everything.
How could a single student
ever be able to change the world?
It isn't realistic.
Just think about it for a moment, and you'll see that.
Nevertheless...
Now that I hold the advantage...
...there may be a strategic move I need to play.