The date was August 10 in the
year 2010 of the Imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had
just declared war upon Japan.
Confronted by Britannia's newest
weapon, the formidable Knightmare Frame,
Japan fell to its enemy in less than a month.
The conquered nation was stripped of
its freedom, rights, culture, and dignity.
Finally, even its name was taken away.
Eleven.
The name of Japan and its people
was replaced with a mere number.
Why the hell are we letting the Elevens go?!
What about the poison gas they've stolen?!
But it's by order of Prince Clovis!
What about Bartley?!
Get the general staff on the line!
They're not at their posts, sir.
Are you telling me Prince Clovis is alone on the con?!
I'm overjoyed, Lelouch.
They said you died when Japan was brought into the fold.
What a blessing to have you back.
We should depart for the Homeland immediately.
So you can use me as a tool of diplomacy?
It seems you've forgotten why we
were used as tools in the first place.
That's right.
It was because my mother was killed.
Mother held the title of Knight of Honour,
but was a commoner by birth.
No doubt the other imperial consorts held her in contempt.
Even though you made it look like the work of terrorists,
I'm no fool...
You people killed my mother!
It wasn't me! I swear to you, it wasn't!
Then tell me everything you know.
The truth cannot be hidden from me any longer.
By whose hand was she slain?
My brother, second prince Schneizel, and
second princess Cornelia, they can tell you...
They were at the heart of this?
That's all that you know, isn't it?
I swear it wasn't me!
I had... nothing to do with it!
I believe you.
However...
Please, you can't!
We may have different mothers,
but you and I are still blood!
You can't change the world
without getting your hands dirty...
Wake up, Lelouch!
I know you were sleeping, your hand stopped moving!
Well ya don't have ta beat me up over it, do you?
Ahh, serves ya right for ditchin' me like that.
That's right. What was up with you yesterday?
Oh, well...
That's enough you guys. Let's not get sidetracked here.
If we don't come up with a fix for the club activities
budget, there won't be money left for anything at all.
And if it comes to that point...
The Equestrian Club'll be pissed!
We don't want 'em comin' in here on horseback!
Rivalz, can't you be a more
serious student council member?
You know, it woulda been nice of you if you
would've reminded us about this mess a day ago.
I would have to say a day
later, then we would've given up.
Good idea, we can still do that.
Guts!
Are you tryin' that "guts" spell again?
Yup. I want you people to
start putting your all into this.
I really don't think that your
magic's gonna do a whole lot.
Actually, it's got me going, Madame President!
Supple and willing, that's what I like.
I train hard in the gymnastics club!
That's not what I was getting at.
Huh?
You're a ten.
From what I've seen in the girl's bathroom anyway.
You've been filling out in all the right places, huh?
Wh-What are you talking about, you perv?
Jeez, our president's just a dirty old man on the inside.
Sullying the meeting with her filthy mind.
Yeah, well, that's Milly for you.
Look on the bright side,
we got the budget balanced, didn't we?
They used poison gas?!
Huh?
Man, that's freaky!
Shinjuku's only 30 minutes from here!
Oh my god,
I saw smoke rising over in Shinjuku!
It musta been the gas.
Are they saying anything else about it?
Shinjuku?
I heard about it in real time from a friend.
That's why I called you yesterday.
Hey! Check out the footage of those dead Elevens!
Uh! Don't look at that!
This is strange... Why would they cover it up?
Are they hiding Clovis's death to fend off anarchy?
But if that's the case, when
they finally do announce it...
Hmph.
I guess that I'm not as tough as I thought I was.
That ex-civil servant is such a fool.
So, are you referring to Bartley?
The killer has breached our
heaviest security twice already.
This perfunctory inspection is a farce.
Margrave Jeremiah.
Now that Prince Clovis is out
of the way, we purebloods can...
Let me make that call.
We still need to woo everyone over.
Kallen! It's been ages!
Are you all right?!
Sophie's been worried sick all this time.
You're okay though, right?
Yeah. I just have to go easy for a little while.
Of course, that's why she's so familiar.
Anyway, if I stay home any longer, I'll never catch up.
What's up, buddy? See something you like?
You've got a thing for her, don'tcha?
Just thinking this is a rare event.
She hasn't been here at school
since this whole term started.
Kallen Stadtfeld.
They say she's sick or something.
And she barely showed up school last year, either.
Still, her grades are at the top of the class.
And she's a member of the Stadtfeld family,
which means she's well-bred and rolling in money!
Man, you sure know how to pick 'em!
It's not like that.
Ah, ya don't hafta hide it.
A touch too sheltered, though, if ya ask me.
There's a bee! A bee!
Huh?
Oh my god, Kallen! Run!
Hurry up and run!
I don't get it. Why's a bee after me?
I wonder if there's a hive nearby.
God, I hate this!
I'm sick of acting like a freaking invalid!
Crap! He saw me!
There's no question it's her...
Can... Can I help you with something?
I want answers.
Of course.
Were you the one piloting the Glasgow in Shinjuku?
Yes.
Why terrorism?
Because I'm Japanese.
Though technically I'm half Britannian.
Half blood?
But why go so far?
Um... Did you want something?
No. I got what I wanted here.
Oh wait. Just to be sure...
Don't tell anyone about Shinjuku.
Uh?
What do you mean "about Shinjuku"?
Why would you say that?
Go back to class.
As soon as I get an answer to my question, I will!
It's not working? What's going on here?
Hey, Lelou! Kallen!
You know it's time to head over to the Chem. Lab!
You better get a move on!
Ah, crap, it's my turn to set up for class!
It didn't work? But...
Well, what shall we do?
He may be late again this evening.
I'll wait. He said that we'd have dinner together tonight.
There now. This one's finished.
Uh?
A bird?
Yes. It's a crane.
Amazing. The Japanese are so skillful!
Lady Nunnally? Uh?
I'm sorry I'm so late.
Hi, Lelouche. Welcome home.
Yes, welcome home, my lord.
No place like it, Sayoko. Right, Nunnally?
As you know full well,
the project was a complete failure.
Therefore, this research division is being gutted.
Wha...?!
Yes, but...
I've set up a place in Narita for you.
Move everything out there.
While we may have no memory of it,
the fact is, the other staff officers
and I left Prince Clovis on his own.
I'm gonna be called out on the
carpet for this back at home.
When that happens...
If His Majesty learns this experiment's
gone on without his knowledge, I...
Understood, sir!
We'll start prepping, immediately!
Miss Sayoko was just teaching me about the art of origami.
Fold a piece of paper the correct way and
you can make birds, boats, almost anything!
Uh, easy there, you don't have to
tell me everything all at once, you know.
It's not like I'm going anywhere.
Yeah, you're right. Thank you.
You're very welcome.
I'm so happy!
'Cause last night, you scared me a little.
Did I? Sorry, I just have a lot on my mind is all...
Hey.
Huh?
They say if you fold a thousand of
these cranes, your wish'll come true.
So if there's anything at all
that you've been wishing for.
No. Not really.
What about you? Do you wish for anything?
Hmm...
I wish the world was a gentler place.
When the day finally comes that you can see again,
I'm sure that it will be.
Really?
I promise.
The truth is...
...there are very few paths our future can take.
The Ashford family's sheltering us for now.
But how long can that last?
If our identity is exposed,
even Rivalz, Shirley, and the others will abandon us.
We'll end up political tools,
or a casualty of royal ambition.
I have to build a world where
Nunnally can at least find happiness.
Hm?
Sayako taught me this the other day.
It's called a Japanese promise.
♪ Cross my heart, hope to die, ♪
♪ eat a thousand needles if I lie. ♪
♪ Pinky promise song! ♪
Well, that's scary.
I may have to eat a thousand needles someday!
That's right.
So I better not catch you telling lies, okay?
Don't you worry.
I'll never lie, I swear.
Not to you, anyway.
This is the only weapon I have.
And I don't even know how to use it.
Lelouch!
Huh?
Class'll be starting any minute, you know.
Oh, yes, sir.
Um, sir?
What are the topics gonna be
for the essays on your next exam?
The Humiliation of Edinburgh,
the transfer of the Capital,
and north 'n south war topics.
So. I haven't lost the power then.
Sir?
Hm?
What exactly are the topics gonna
be for the essays on your next exam?
Right, very funny. Maybe you should try studying, huh?
Just apply yourself, you'll do fine.
Yes, sir.
As I suspected...
...I can only use it on a person once.
So, how's campus life treatin' ya?
Stifling.
I was stuck in history class yesterday.
Look, maybe I should just head back.
The army's on a high alert right now.
Stay there and let things cool off.
Like hell what about the voice on the radio?
Can't go lookin' for a voice. Besides...
...Naoto would be happy to see ya back in school.
Forget about Shinjuku for now. I'll be in touch.
Shinjuku... I guess he's right, but...
Don't tell anyone about Shinjuku.
No, it couldn't have his been his voice.
The aristocracy was highly educated.
With such an emphasis on edification and
training, they produced a superior breed of ruler.
And secondly, they possessed heightened efficiency.
Since only a...
Could be...
No. I can't remember well enough to be sure...
Good. That will do.
With the enthronement of Henry the 9th,
son of the great Elizabeth the 1st,
the golden age of the Tudor Dynasty...
All I did was simply mention Shinjuku... But...
If he knows who I really am, then...
At the first opportunity...
I need to take care of him.
And the research center?
Transferred to Narita last night.
Right then.
I pray you forgive me, Your Highness...
Why don't we all go for out for some tea?
Kallen, you should join us.
Yeah, tag along.
Hey, Lelou. You comin' along?
Sorry, maybe some other time.
Maybe I can.
Yeah, I thought so.
You've gotta go straight home then, huh?
What do you have, a curfew?
Hm? What's up?
You think that you could spare
a minute? I need to talk to you.
Huh?!
Huh?
Sure.
I was wondering when you were gonna ask.
Huh?!
I hope you can see how determined we are now!
But... I've already told you!
That you don't remember?
Still clinging to that ridiculous excuse?
Just ask the others! They'll testify that...!
Ducking the blame? You're pathetic!
You shant remain at his royal
Highness's side another minute!
I didn't even know this room existed.
It's the club house for the student council.
They built it as a ballroom for various special occasions.
And we won't be disturbed inside here?
Yes, that's correct.
Here it is!
I found it! Look! This is it, right?
Ah! What a relief you found our lab data!
Ugh, good. My ass is killin' me...
Were you able to find it?
I finished up on my end, shall we dig in?
Aww, wow!
Way to go, Milly!
You adore me, I know.
Um... what is all of this?
Lelouch, don't you know?
I thought that's why you brought her.
We're inducting Kallen into the student council.
It was my grandfather's idea, actually.
The principal's?
He thought it best with her poor health.
She'd have a harder time with regular club activities.
Oh! I'm Milly, the president of the council.
Pleasure to meet you.
Oh. Thank you, the pleasure's all mine.
I'm Rivalz, the secretary!
If there's anything you need help with, I'm your man!
Hi, I'm Shirley.
And I'm a member of the swim club. Welcome.
Um. Hi there. My name's Nina.
It's... nice to meet all of you..
Shirley? I'm sorry, but...
...do you think you could set these on the table for me?
Oh, sure, thanks, Nunna!
Nunnally, what're you doing here?
This is Lelouch's sister.
I'm still in the middle school group,
so I can't be on the council yet.
That's all right, you're an honorary member in our book.
Mh-hm.
Hello, there. It's a pleasure to meet you, Kallen.
Thank you. You as well.
Right! Shall we kick this off with a toast?
Huh? Champagne??
Yeah, but we're on the student council, we shouldn't!
Ah, c'mon, loosen up, you guys!
No way! We're gonna get in trouble!
What's going on?
Here, Nunnally.
Lelouch, heads up!
You're not getting away with this either, Lelou!
What just happened?
We have clothes for her?
Sayoko's on it.
This is why I hate Britannians...
It's Lelouch.
I brought you a change of clothes.
You can come in. I've drawn the curtain already.
Uh... sorry about all this.
I know they can be a little over the top.
That's okay.
Nothin' wrong with cutting loose
every once in a while, ya know?
These are some of my clothes, hope that's okay.
It's cool. Don't worry 'bout it.
That was fast. You went all the way to the boy's dorm?
Actually, I live here.
Uh?
It'd be pretty hard for my
sister to live off in the dorms.
The principal of the school lets us stay here, as a favor.
I see.
Anyway...
Hey, wait!
Can you hand me that pouch over there?
Sure.
You really are a live wire, aren't you?
Were you the one in Shinjuku?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
You brought up Shinjuku the other day. Why?
Why do you ask, is there something wrong with Shinjuku?
Don't answer my question with a question!
Yes or no. That's all I wanna hear outta you.
If I don't answer it, someone'll come.
That okay?
Hello? Ashford Academy student council.
Uh. No, this is... oh...
It's for you.
He says he knows you.
Hello?
Glad you're still alive, Q-1.
Was I wrong?
Sixteen hundred hours, the day after tomorrow.
The observation deck at Tokyo Tower. Come alone.
Who are you?!
How did you arrange that cease-fire order?!
Uh! Hey! Don't hang up!
Did you say "cease-fire"?
Sounds like you keep dangerous company.
Oh, uh, that was...
Let me guess...
You're talkin' about a game? Something online?
Uh, yeah! You got me. 'Cause, ya know...
I've been shut up in my house so long.
That's what I was warning you about,
when I told you not to bring up Shinjuku before.
Seriously, some guys'll try to show you footage of
what happened that day, and it's pretty damn grim.
By the way... you know I can see you, right?
Um, I won't tell anyone! Later!
I was wrong...
Glad you're still alive, Q-1.
Huh?
The council doesn't require much actual work, I guess.
Beyond occasional paperwork,
we'll sometimes plan school events.
So, you mean, like the Culture Festival?
Yup, like that, along with the Cross Dresser's Ball,
the Absolute Silence Party, and Swimsuit Day.
What's up with that? Blame our president.
You'll be spending a lotta
time with her. Hope you're ready.
Lelouch, it's awful!
What is?
Prince Clovis has been found dead!
They're saying he was killed.
Prince Clovis has been taken from us.
He fought for peace and justice
against all of the Elevens!
He died a martyr!
We must all bury our sorrow.
And carry on his will.
We interrupt this broadcast with breaking news.
The man suspected as the murderer has been captured.
According to this report,
the suspect is an honorary Britannian.
What the...?!
Private Suzaku Kururugi.
A former Eleven and Honorary Britannian.
I repeat, Suzaku Kururugi, arrested for murder.
Shouldn't I be happy at this news?
Suzaku is still alive!
But... why has he been arrested in my place?
I have to save him... I don't care what it takes!
If I have to step up my plans... so be it!
For I have the power to do it!