I, Euphemia li Britannia, bid all of you within
the sound of my voice to heed the following command!
Seek out any Japanese you can find...
And please kill them!
Leave not a single one of them alive!
Euphemia has betrayed us here!
All units, descend upon the stadium!
Grind the Britannians to dust!
Damn you, Euphemia! You deceived us!
Damn Elevens!
Now I see.
You were planning this all along!
Crush the Britannians!
Euphy!
Euphy, where are you?!
Get away from me...
I don't have time to waste on you!
Oh my, this is turning into a mess.
How dare you... trampling over the hopes of our people...!
Euphemia...!
Stop it!
Are you Japanese?!
You dare raise a hand against Euphemia li Britannia?!
Huh? A-ha, so there you are...
...you ridiculous royal puppet.
Oh! You were on that island, weren't you?
Yeah.
Now suffer the hand of vengeance...
Wait.
I'll deal with her.
You defiant Japanese!
Now what, Zero? Do we take her prisoner?
There's no point. Leave her.
I have to kill them all!
These Japanese people, they have to die!
It jammed up! I have to...
Hurry!
I think it goes... in here.
Oh! I thought you were one of them.
So, I was thinking we could run the
Specially Administrated Zone of Japan together...
Oh wait... Japan?
Yes...
I would have liked that...
You and I, together.
Euphy...
Lelouch...
Why...?
Farewell, Euphy.
You may have been the first girl I ever loved.
No...!
Suzaku?!
Why now of all times?!
I'm no match for that Hadron Cannon!
I will never allow you to kill Lelouch!
Suzaku!
Get outta my way!
Ahh, dammit!
Please...
You have to save Euphy...
Do something! You mustn't let her die!
You still haven't made contact with Darlton?!
No, Your Highness.
There was a report he'd been injured,
but nothing beyond that.
Viceroy! Emergency message from the Avalon!
From the Avalon?
Yes.
The special zone at Fuji has fallen to the Black Knights.
What was that?!
They're moving to intercept our forces.
Also...
Princess Euphemia...
"Equality"?!
You can shove that straight up your administrative ass!
You lured us into a death trap!
You just made the biggest mistake of your lives!
You got that?!
That's right! Let Britannia burn!
Don't screw with the Japanese!
Lucked out, didn't we?
I can't believe they left all
this footage and equipment behind.
Yes, once we're done editing, we can
throw it on the net for the entire world to see.
It's pretty clear which side justice is on.
How curious...
You don't feel any loyalty toward Britannia, do you?
Loyalty?
Mm-hm.
Btitannia's glory has ripened on the vine.
My talents are wasted serving them.
You're more of an honest man than I thought you were.
And what will you do now?
Hard to say...
The only reason I came here was to gather data.
But I'd feel bad abandoning you all.
And I find Zero so... amusing.
How wonderful to finally meet you!
This girl...
...she's a relative of Suzaku's.
Zero...
Are you prepared to work beside us in what's to come?
The opposite!
From this point on,
the six houses of Kyoto will be under my control.
I won't hear any objections.
All other paths of survival for you...
...have now vanished!
We should inform Viceroy Cornelia...
Don't worry, I'll be taking care of that.
Will she last until we reach the bureau?
I'm afraid not.
I'll contact Prince Schneizel, then.
Excuse me.
Suzaku...
Euphy!
Euphy...
I have to know...
Why did you issue that order at the stadium?
Order...?
What are you talking about?
Never mind that...
Suzaku...
You're Japanese, aren't you...?
Yeah...?
Euphy!
No...
Huh?
I mustn't...
I-I can't even think such a thing!
Oh, please...!
Suzaku?
Yes, Euphy?
The ceremony...
Did it go all right?
Is Japan okay?
Euphy...
Don't you remember?
People of Japan!
And all who are oppressed by the Empire of Britannia!
Long have I waited...
All through the struggles against Britannia's injustices,
I've waited for them to come to their senses!
But that hope was betrayed...
...by an act of barbarism
that can only be called genocide!
How about everyone that was there?
Are the Japanese happy?
Never forgive you!
She's a murderer!
She's a filthy witch!
Liar!
Euphemia is the symbol of Britannia's hypocrisy!
A murderer cloaked in the flag of a nation!
How was the ceremony?
Do you think I did... okay?
I hope that bitch burns in hell!
We're finished with your lies!
Death to them all!
Euphy...
The special zone is...
A great success!
The Japanese people were given back their home!
And you did it!
Oh, thank god...
I hereby declare our independence from Britannia!
But don't take this to mean
the resurrection of your fallen nation...
We will not turn back the hands of time!
The new Japan we go on to build...
shall be one broad enough to
accept all peoples, histories, and ideologies!
Where the strong shall not reign over the weak!
And it shall be called the United States of Japan!
He's done it! This is the birth of a nation!
How strange...
I can't see your face anymore...
Keep going... to school...
I had to stop... before I...
...before I had the chance to finish...
Euphy, you can still go yourself.
I know!
Why don't we go to Ashford Academy together?
The student council is so much fun!
Euphy...
You have to do it... for me...
...'kay?
Please, Euphy...
No, don't go!
Suzaku...
I'm so happy... that we...
Zero! Zero! Zero!
Dear god...
Area Fukushima, Byakko squad, en route to Ibaraki.
Area Tama, continuing with barricade construction.
You plan to assault the Tokyo settlement?
Yes.
This is the best chance we'll get.
Don't worry about it.
Your Geass has no effect on me. You know that, don't you?
That's true, isn't it?
Hmph. With the Geass out of control now,
I can never see anyone.
Yes, Nunnally?
Hi, Lelouch! I was wondering... um...
...do you suppose I could talk to Euphy again?
I was thinking the three of us
could go to the school festival together.
You see, Milly said they were organizing another one,
since everything got all messed up the other day.
So I was hoping we could go to the new one together, too.
Oh... I'm sorry.
I know you don't want us meeting ever again.
But I thought maybe,
if there was some way you and I
could maybe see her just one last time...
Nunnally... Haven't you heard the news?
Oh, well the radio cut off mid-broadcast earlier.
Why do you ask, did something happen?
Of course not. Everything is just fine.
Sorry.
I'll be home by tomorrow. We'll discuss it when I'm back.
Right.
All right, so you can't switch off your Geass.
Are there other changes you've noticed?
Not really. It's just...
Euphy...
She tried to resist the Geass...
...and my orders.
I was wondering if my power had weakened.
But I think...
I think such a malignant command...
...was simply against her nature.
And so?
I guess, that's all.
I-It was something...!
We have our contract.
I promise to stay with you...
...till the very end.
We weren't fast enough!
We may have managed to keep the news off the net, but...
There's insurrections all over the map!
That's correct!
The Black Knights are the largest of the insurgent groups.
They are now absorbing all of the masses
and advancing on the Tokyo settlement!
All our units are in play right now,
we're completely on our own!
Yes, and with so many Honorary Britannians turning on us,
our enemies number in the tens of thousands!
Lord Guilford!
Forget it.
We cannot move without Her Highness's word.
But sir!
The viceroy's been shut up in Princess Euphemia's room
ever since she canceled the attack orders!
And we still can't confirm General Dalton's whereabouts!
Everyone in Toyama Squad is at your disposal.
Roger that. Any weaponry?
Some explosives from Gokayama.
But we don't have enough vehicles.
Can any of us ride with you?
Best we can offer are freight trains.
That okay?
Looks like the groups from Yamanashi joined up with us.
Yeah, and the remnants of the
"Blood of the Samurai" faction, too.
Our numbers are growing by the minute!
I hope everyone in the student council can get away.
On the contrary...
For the first time in a while, I'm glad.
Yes...
I forgot the art of kindness ages ago... Marianne.
You worthless Brits!
I hope you're all right, Kaname.
You're working in Shizuoka now, right?
Yeah, I'm fine over here.
Look, Chigusa...
We need to talk about something important when I get back.
What's wrong?
Well, that's the first time you've called me by that name.
Oh, you're right.
Does it sound weird?
Not a bit!
Anyway, I'll be here.
There she is! That Brit woman!
Watchin' us from your window, huh?!
Admit it, you're some sort of spy!
As the insurgents draw closer,
security in the ghettos continues to worsen.
The government is asking all citizens
to stay in their homes until further notice.
Do you think the fighting will come our way as well?
O-Of course not!
Princess Cornelia has her regular forces stationed here!
There's no way!
I hope so.
Jeez, buck up, will ya? You're scaring me.
Ah, Nunnally, what about Lelouch, is he back here yet?
Lelouch?
Is something the matter?
No, not really...
Man... I wish you'd go back to calling him Lulu.
It's time you two made up.
Lulu?
What, you mean I called him that?
Oh, there you go again...
Lulu...
Nina, they want us upstairs in school.
The insurgents are headed toward Tokyo!
Right. And Zero is coming, isn't he?
Please... Wait for me, Princess Euphemia.
I'll avenge you, I swear!
Euphy...
I just don't understand.
Why did you give that order?!
Shall I tell you?
Huh? A child?
How did you get on board?
How do you do, Suzaku Kururugi?
You may call me V.V.
V.V.?
They've broken the Atsugi line, as well!
Maybe the homeland can help us!
They'll never make it in time!
Then we should evacuate this area right away...
Don't panic!
Huh?
P-Princess Cornelia!
I've put the Glaston Knights on standby.
Place all our forces on the outskirts of Tokyo!
We can end this!
We just need to take down Zero!
Kill Cornelia, and the day will be ours!
You all have your orders.
Now be ready!
Diethard, have Tohdoh handle the front line.
I'm leaving you in charge here.
Yes, very well, Zero.
You're Sumeragi's...
Thank goodness, I made it in time!
That was so mean of you,
the way you headed off to battle without me.
I've been a huge fan of yours ever since your big debut!
I was hoping that I'd finally get to talk to you.
Wow! You're really tall, aren't you?
Don't worry though!
I'll catch up with you pretty soon!
L-Lady Kaguya...
I thought the heads of the Six Houses remained in Fuji.
I followed after you!
So I could watch my future husband fight.
Huh?
Don't joke around.
Well, once you win this battle,
you'll eventually need a wife, won't you?
I mean, I know your identity is a big secret and all,
but you're gonna need somebody as your public face, right?
Really? You believe we're going to win this battle?
Of course!
I am the goddess of victory after all!
I'd be lucky to have you then.
Unfortunately, I've already
made a contract with the devil.
Huh?
I have no room in my life for deities right now.
Hurry! We have to get this
experimental subject back to the Homeland!
The pressure!
The internal pressure is rising!
And now of all times...
Good morning to you, it was.
Hear me, Britannia!
This is Zero!
A rebel against oppressors who abuse their power!
We will wait until midnight.
You have till then to surrender to me.
This is your only warning.
Heed it.
Twelve midnight, not a single second later.
General Dalton, you're in no condition to do this!
I don't care, I have to be... at her Highness's side...!
Your little bluff is meaningless, Zero.
The Tokyo settlement is an impenetrable fortress.
You can still turn back, you know.
Your actions here will affect more than just Area 11.
You... and this entire world... will be steeped in war.
I'm aware of that.
And yet, all the same...
Euphy? How could that be possible?!
No, it must be an imposter.
Lelouch, it's me.
Suzaku.
Why are you calling me now?
Lelouch...
Are you at the school?
No, but I will be soon.
I see.
I called because there's something
I want you to tell everyone for me.
Yes, and what would that be?
The sky...
Make sure no one looks up at the sky.
What?
Lelouch...
Is there anyone you could ever hate so much
that you'd actually want to kill them?
There is, yes.
I used to feel that sort of thinking was unacceptable.
That unless you followed the rules,
killing someone was just murder.
But now...
It's hatred that's guiding me.
I'm fighting to kill someone.
I'm going to become a murderer in the skies of Tokyo.
So please...
Embrace your hate.
Just think of Euphy.
I made my own mind up long ago.
I have no intention of turning back.
For Nunnally, you mean?
Yes...
I have to go now.
Thank you, Lelouch.
Forget about it.
I mean, you and I are friends after all.
For the last seven years.
Right. See ya, then.
Yeah. Later.
What the hell?!
These hands of mine have been
dirty for a long time now, Suzaku.
You're coming to face me now doesn't matter at all.
Hell, I welcome it even.
I mean, of course, you and I are friends.
Perhaps this is what I've longed for...
...ever since that day.
The destruction and loss of everything.
That's right.
Destruction always comes before creation.
And for that goal, even my
own conscience must be cast aside.
The only path left to me is straight ahead.
Now then...
That's right.
Only by pushing forward will I find atonement.
Even if my enemy is the greatest empire on the planet,
there's no turning back for me now!
Everything is in place...
The time has come to overthrow the old world order!