The actions one takes are answered
by consequences waiting at their conclusion.
There are no exceptions,
and even Lelouch's power cannot change this.
Despite his absolute ability to make anyone obey him,
there is no escaping the inevitable.
Lelouch has acted to avenge his mother's death,
and to create a world where his
younger sister, Nunnally, can find happiness.
Now, he is confronted by the results of his acts;
consequences he never imagined.
And there are more to come.
If these unintended consequences
help to create new worlds,
who will bear the blame for the sins that are committed?
Who will take the punishment?
And who will measure it out?
He was a pious soul,
who always looked to God in his life.
And a friend to us all.
To his wife, he was a devoted husband.
To his child, a loving father.
Father...
May he rest in peace, forever
cradled in the bosom of our lord.
No! Stop!
Don't bury him again, please!
He's suffered enough! Oh god, don't leave me...
Mom, he's gone already.
Please, Mom.
Guess what, Papa!
Some day, when I grow up, I'm gonna be your wife!
Oh, that's very sweet of you, honey.
But your teacher told you, didn't she?
Huh?
Someday, you'll meet the man you really love.
More than I do you?
Hm... It's hard to explain.
Well, if you truly love that person,
and he cares for you just as much...
It would make me the happiest father on earth.
Shirley, I'm so sorry this happened...
Oh, stop. What've you to apologize for?
We feel awful!
Huh?
It's just that...
When we were all watching the hoteljacking on TV...
I thought the Black Knights were, ya know, heroes.
I mean, the news was handling it all wrong!
Anyway, I was posting online
how I thought what happened in Narita
was kinda cool and I'm... Forgive me!
Come on, don't be silly.
That has absoloutely nothing to do with this at all.
I mean even I was saying Narita wa...
Shirley, stop.
Seriously, I'm starting to worry about you here.
Have you cried yet?
If you simply hold it in, it's only
gonna be harder for you later on.
You don't have to worry.
Really, I'm fine.
I've cried a lot...
Cowards!
Huh?
Zero and his people,
their methods are just cowardly!
He doesn't even get his hands dirty.
He stirs people into a frenzy, tips the world into chaos,
and then sits back and congratulates himself!
It's not going to change a thing!
Anything gained through
his kind of tactics is just meaningless!
Huh?
Well, anyway, I think it's time we headed back, everyone.
Shirley, we'll be waiting for you.
Back in the old student council room.
Same as ever.
C'mon, guys, let's go.
Hey, uh, Lelouch...
What? Wha'd I do?
Lulu... Forgive me.
What?
It wasn't fair, kissing you like that.
It wasn't fair of me at all.
It was just... something I did...
Forget about it, okay?
I shouldn't have put you on the spot like that.
I'm sorry. It was totally stupid of me.
I mean, you finally kissed me, and I can't even be happy!
Wait, I...! Shirley!
Do you regret it?
That your friend's father was caught up in all this?
You were just accusing Kirihara of being too soft.
What happened to the path of blood?
Shut up.
But it turns out you're the soft one.
Did you think these was all just a game?
You've already killed your fair share of people.
By hand. Or words, more often than not.
Just shut up.
All of them left behind a family.
All had lovers and friends.
Are you really telling me you hadn't grasped that yet?
I would've thought you to be better prepared.
Just shut up! I am prepared!
I have been from the moment I killed Clovis!
Then why this hesitation?
Has she shaken you so badly?
One kiss and you go to pieces then, huh?
Hm. So, for all your preening and posturing,
you're really just a spoiled little boy
with a swollen head and a big fat mouth.
You're in way too deep to be turning back now.
You've past the point of no return.
You need a reason for living, don't you?
You're not going to disappoint me, are you?
Yes!
That is why people discriminate against one another.
So is that the reason why you killed my brother?!
And any ends gained through
contemptible means aren't worth anything.
Are you really going through with this?
That's easy enough to say, isn't it?!
You can't! We may have different mothers,
but you and I are still blood!
It's nothing but self-satisfying gratification!
And to have this utopia you'd...
I wish the world was a gentler place.
You appear to have a reason for living
And I've come back to change everything.
Are you embarking on the path of blood?
Ohgi... It's me. Zero.
Data logger S-4, contact.
Protocol established.
I have some bad news, Suzaku!
We just got word from Cornelia's Royal Guard!
We're on deck for the next operation!
Huh?
Are they acknowledging your skill,
or do they need another decoy?
Oh, Lloyd?
Huh?
Care for a lesson in proper social etiquette?
You look like you have some time to kill.
I'll have to take a pass on that.
Now then, I believe we were talking about your mission...
W-Wait a second, Zero!
I realize this is a request from Kyoto.
I think we could definitely handle it.
And, I'm pretty sure the Japan Liberation Front
would rather join with us than
flee to foreign soil and all, but...
You're the one who brought us this information...
Diethard, wasn't it?
That's right.
It is an honor that you'd meet me like this, Zero.
So, Princess Cornelia is going to deploy
the Royal Marines on Gen. Katase
of the Japan Liberation Front.
Is that correct?
Yes, the Network is already poised
to broadcast a special report on it.
Lt. Col. Toudou will never make it to Katase in time.
Which means the Japan Liberation Front
has no military strength right now.
Their only chance of escape is
the liquid Sakuradite they're carrying.
Which is why we should help General Katase
escape instead of going after Cornelia!
Ohgi! Who are we?
W-We're the Black Knights, Zero...
Then we have but one task!
We will destroy Cornelia's troops, and in doing so,
rescue the remnants of the JLF.
Tonight, we regain what was lost to us at Narita!
What're our chances?
Need you ask?
Understood.
Hm.
Begin preparations.
You all have your orders to carry out.
Uh...! Zero!
I have something to attend to.
Whatever it is, save it for later.
Just so you know...
The viceroy has her reservations about using Numbers.
But use every able body, I always say.
Even if it's the son of the former prime minister.
Our target is Katase.
Take him out and the Japan Liberation Front is finished.
We're sending in the Royal Marines.
Your job'll be to provide supporting fire
from the shore until the marines have Katase...
...as well as annihilating any stragglers left over.
I'm to annihilate them, sir?
Nobody but the target is to survive, is that clear?
Warrant Officer Kururugi, show your loyalty to the crown.
This your chance to get ahead in the world, soldier.
Understood... my lord.
Onward, Christian soldiers. Conflicting morals, right?
No, Lulu...
It can't be true...
He would never get tangled up with someone like that...
There is a possibility that this boy
is linked to the Black Knights.
What're you saying... he's involved?
In terrorism.
I don't belive you!
He can't be... It has to be a lie.
Lulu...
I'm so sorry to be doubting you like this... But...
Please, I wanna believe in you!
Dammit, she lost him.
If she had just called me sooner, I could've had him!
I should've grabbed him when I had the chance.
No, I need proof.
If he talks to her, I can
learn what his role is in all this.
Which is all the more important
if he can manipulate memory somehow.
I won't have to die, stripped of
my position and honor, like Jeremiah.
Hell, this is my chance to move back up again.
So, I have to find a link to Zero...
It has to be me!
Who's there?!
Ah! I-I'm sorry! I'll go...
Second thoughts?
I thought the goal was justice.
The only reason I've fought until now
is because I thought it was the right thing to do.
So I could live with the killing. But now...
Tell me is this real?!
Is what we're all doing here really
going to change the world for the better?!
Yes, it will.
Or rather, it must change the world.
But...!
Will there be sacrifices?
Not only just soldiers, but the innocent as well.
And yet, because of all these things,
we've no choice but to continue on...
...no matter the cost.
Even if people see us as cowards...
We have to prevail!
If that means more blood will be shed, so be it.
We've spilled so much to get here,
we can't let it be in vain...
But I won't force you, Kallen.
If you wish to turn back, now is the time.
I've made my choice. I'll follow you to the very end.
I'm grateful, Kallen.
Yes. You saved me today.
Thank you.
C.C., I need you. I do.
What am I doing?
I just can't afford to make the
same mistake here all over again here.
It's time.
Commence with the operation!
All underwater units, hit the water!
Dive, dive, dive!
Supression Team, you are cleared for cartegory C weaponry.
Our unit'll be covering them from the shore.
Careful though,
we want that tanker in one piece.
Understood, my lord.
Once torpedo attack is confirmed,
all units go to weapons free. Repeat. Weapons free.
Oh my god! Terrorists?!
It looks like it's starting.
Zero...
You wanna move out or what?
Hey! Do you read me?
They're closing in on the JLF! Come in!
We have to hold.
Huh?
Cornelia moved faster than expected.
If we go now, we'll die along with them.
Commence support fire.
All units restricted to micro round ordinance only.
Be careful not to set off that liquid Sakuradite!
Damn those Britannians!
When the hell did they get here?!
Enemy units! They're coming from the water!
Itagaki!
Two-oh-two! Five-oh-three!
Focus fire at nine o'clock!
This isn't battle. This is wholesale slaughter!
Officer Kururugi.
Go ahead.
I certainly know this must be hard for you,
but you're a soldier, remember that.
Right. I understand.
How could they have found us?! Where's Tohdoh?!
We can't locate him! Or the Holy Swords!
What about Kyoto?!
They said they would send help!
Yes, sir, but we have no way of contacting them now!
So they're just gonna sit back and watch us die here?!
We surrender! Please, cease fire!
This is the Japan Liberation Front!
I reapeat! We surrender!
Sir, they're issuing a surrender over an open channel!
Ignore it.
Yes, but, sir!
You see?
They were just buying time. Now, carry out your orders.
Lulu just couldn't be a member
of the Black Knights, could he?
Ugh! Dammit! It'll be too late soon!
When does Zero plan to move?!
I just hope that he isn't just doing all this
to honor some childish notion of justice.
The Knightmares are boarding the ship!
I see.
That leaves only one way out.
They have to be careful around that precious Sakuradite.
Zero! If we don't hurry...
Very well then. Go ahead...
What the hell is going on?!
I can't believe this idiocy!
They blew up the liquid Sakuradite?!
Just what you'd expect of the JLF.
Choosing to take the Britanians out with them!
Suicide? But they never mentioned...!
We're going to rush Cornelia's position head on!
Forget about everything else!
All that matters is achieving our goal!
If you want to avenge the JLF, then capture Cornelia
and show them our strength and determination!
Right!
This is like Narita all over again!
It's outstanding!
Hey! Get back here!
The JLF was just bait!
Their command is wide open now.
Heh. One of the oldest tricks in the book...
Where're you going?! Hey!
It makes perfect sense!
He wanted to cripple his enemy's defenses,
using the Liberation Front as a living trap!
He's excellent material, this Zero.
He's chaos incarnate!
More, show me more of your genius!
Let your ego engulf the world!
E-Enemy attack?!
Two-zero-four, signal lost!
Erickson, form up with three-zero-eight!
Provide support!
All units, status report!
I repeat, what is your status?!
Why would the general kill himself?
It doesn't make any sense...
The main force...!
Could they have used the tanker as a decoy?!
Mount up now and form a defensive line, on the double!
How did they know we were here?!
Your Highness!
Knock their Knightmares into
the sea before the pilots can mount!
Guren Mark-Two, you're with me!
Yes, sir!
Your Highness! We can handle this!
Quiet!
How many times do you think I'll allow them to mock me?!
I haven't even powered on!
Do you think you can best me in Knightmare combat?!
That new model again?!
I'll smash your hatch and drag you out...
Cornelia!
Shirley?!
Zero!
Your methods are not going to change anything!
You're focused on goals,
and don't understand the pain of others!
Zero!
This is payback for Narita!
Well, if it isn't the knight in shining armor!
These are people's lives you're playing with!
You're nothing but a murderer!
Why?!
Why do you keep getting in my way?!
Why do you keep spilling people's blood without meaning?!
If it wasn't for you...!
Because of you...!
Zero... This is the end result.
Lancelot, behind you!
Get the hell away from him!
Is this Zero's?
So... then, with this...
I'll repay you... for my father!
The best laid plans often fall apart.
Doubts can arise at any time.
My heart grows heavier, little by little...
Is this the foundation for the future?
Or merely stumbling blocks from the past?
The answers that I seek...
...lie within me.