We hereby declare the resurrection of Japan
as a lawful independent and sovereign nation!
Atsushi Sawasaki, leader of the forces
that have occupied the Fukuoka military base,
was Chief Cabinet Minister of the
Kururugi Administration in the former nation of Japan.
After the war, he fled to the Chinese Federation,
but is apparently making his move now
in response to the recent civil unrest caused by Zero.
Whether the Black Knights have played a role
in these unfolding events is still under investigation.
We're not part of it!
What does Kyoto say about it?
They didn't know this was coming.
They were just notified about his
unilateral claims over the Sakuradite mining rights.
Zero, it's our move.
What are we gonna do?
Sawasaki's group was working in
conjunction with a terrorist organization in Kyushu.
After cutting off vehicle access from Honshu and Shikoku,
and with support from Chinese Federation forces
from the Liaodong Military District,
they are expanding their occupation
around Fukuoka, Nagasaki, and Oita.
According to General Tsao,
the Chinese Federation is providing humanitarian support,
and is not...
So how's Suzaku doing?
He says that he'll do whatever the mission demands.
I see.
And what about Prince Schneizel? Where is he?
In the Tokyo Settlement.
Got there after his run-in with Suzaku.
Avalon doesn't have its commander right now,
but we have to finish this up
if we want to counter the Gefjun Disturber.
I've dishonored you.
I'm not worthy to be your knight.
If this is about your disobeying orders,
my brother Schneizel said it was an unusual situation,
and you shouldn't be blamed for it.
I can't forgive myself.
Please...
Has knighthood become a burden for you?
Something that troubles you?
No, I'm grateful for it.
Then why?
I've remembered something.
I... I killed my own father.
I was never punished for it.
I just lived on like nothing happened.
And right now I'm being protected again!
While soldiers die and Elevens suffer, I'm unscathed.
A person like me doesn't deserve this!
You don't deserve it?
Then I don't either.
Princess Cornelia, we're taking too many losses!
This tempest is preventing us from using our air power!
We'll have to delay the landing
operation until the weather changes.
It's a stroke of good fortune that this storm hit.
We must use it to tighten our grip on Kyushu.
You see, Gen. Tsao?
Heaven is on our side.
We're going to prevail in this battle with ease.
Martial law is not necessary.
Such measures would only upset and frighten people.
Contact E.U. Foreign Minister Gandolphi.
Oh, and put a call in to the Toromo Agency in Cambodia.
Prince Schneizel,
using the Toromo agency could be a...
Prime Minister!
Yes, Euphy. Something wrong?
Is there anything I can do to help?
I'm the sub-viceroy of Area 11, I should be assisting you.
Thank you.
Just your offer to help me is more than enough.
But I...
The viceroy gave strict orders that
you not be entangled in this matter, Princess.
She did?
Just because I chose my knight without her consent...
Oh, uh, no, that's not correct.
I think even the Kururugi matter...
Please understand, Euphy.
Cornelia can't take any chances now;
the situation is too treacherous.
You mean...
Darlton, concerning the matter we were discussing,
I know someone who has a way in with them.
So, I will ask for help.
Yes, Your Highness.
After all our hard work getting ready,
it looks like they're going to cancel the school festival.
That's hardly a huge consideration since we're at war.
Did you say war?
They're using this government in exile as a smokescreen,
but this is a war with the Chinese Federation!
Oh, I see...
Nina, what about the booths we were
planning to borrow from the art museum?
Uh, I'm going there today.
If I have some extra time,
I'd also like to drop into the science department.
Are you talking about that present of yours?
Huh? What present is that?
Professor Asplund said that I should ask him
if there was something special that I wanted.
You mean Lloyd?!
That philandering playboy?!
That's enough!
Could you get a little work done?
Easy for you to say; this is work for three people!
Suzaku's in the army, Kallen's in the hospital,
and that other fool's nowhere to be found.
There's something's really weird about Lelouch lately.
I was so shocked.
I'm still confused about it.
How can Lelouch be Zero?!
"I still haven't told anyone.
I want to meet you first and ask you face to face."
Did I really write that letter?
How is it possible?
Why did I forget... that Nunna's big brother is Zero?
Z-01, float attachment, contact.
Control line, established.
That's really amazing.
You got a perfect rating on the float simulator.
Thank you.
Tell me, why did you want to
give up being a knight, Suzaku?
Well, because...
Princess Euphemia still approves of me even as I am now.
So if I caused her any trouble,
if I brought her dishonor or shame,
I had a feeling that she would end up hating herself.
A figurehead.
That's all I was from the start; I knew that.
But I thought if I gave my best effort,
maybe I could make some difference.
Forgive me, Clovis.
I met Zero face to face, but I didn't avenge your death.
I have to think of some way to save Lelouch and Nunnally,
but how?
I don't have the kind of power that my sister has;
I'm not like her or Schneizel.
No matter where I go, I'm just a burden
and I act selfishly though I don't mean to.
I chose my knight against my sister's advice.
And now he's resigned.
Oh yeah, they told me about you.
You need to have the documents signed today, right?
But a member of the royal
family is viewing the art right now.
Huh? Which member is it?
Uh, so you're saying...?
We aren't going to collaborate with Sawasaki.
He's not independent.
He's a puppet of the Chinese Federation.
But he says he's fighting for Japan!
We'd get a new name and a new master,
but nothing would change.
His Japan is a sham.
Yeah, so what you're really saying is...?
When Britannia strikes back, we play dead?
Zero, perhaps you'd better
clarify what our overall mission is.
Yeah, he's right.
Even leaving aside the Sawasaki matter,
what's our mid-term goal on this?
To make Tokyo an independent nation!
Independent?!
A nation?!
Are you serious?!
You mean us?
A country?
I thought so.
He's really going all the way!
Wait a minute!
No matter how much the Black Knights have expanded...
Our enemy is an empire
that controls one third of the world!
We can't pull that off alone!
Then answer this!
Are you just going to sit back and
wait for someone else to defeat Britannia?
Who?
You think if you wait long enough,
someday the right chance will finally come?
Don't be naïve!
If we don't stand up and do it ourselves,
that "someday" will never come!
Princess Euphemia!
Secure the perimeter!
Code Delta! We have a Code Delta!
Please! I just want to thank Princess Euphemia!
To get one look at her!
Repeat, lock down all gates leading into the building!
From the hotel!
We've caught a suspicious girl at the building perimeter!
Watch for any unidentified vehicles!
Stop it! That girl is a personal friend of mine!
Good. It's cleared up.
Now we can resume the landing operation.
And we'll try to put Prince Schneizel's plan into action.
You think the Special Corps can break through their line?
With Kururugi, it's possible.
Using him can also mean trouble.
But there's no commander on the Avalon now.
Earl Asplund isn't capable.
Incoming missiles!
Launch point appears to be Fukuoka base!
One minute, five seconds to impact!
Not bad!
They're well prepared against air raids as well.
Are we sending up a barrage?
We'll be fine in this position.
Direct hit confirmed!
The Avalon is destroyed.
Hmph! Even if it is state-of-the-art,
a single ship can't possibly hurt us!
Hm? What the...?!
Lancelot's shield was already proven on the battlefield.
Major Kururugi, I'm laying out
the mission plan for final verification.
This ship will breach the enemy's front line from
high altitude and move directly to the launch point.
The advanced weapon system
Z-01 Lancelot, using the float unit,
will attack the enemy headquarters at Fukuoka base.
The float unit consumes energy fast,
so pay attention to your operation time!
Yes, my lord.
M.E. boost...
Lancelot unit, now launching!
...launch!
The enemy ship seems to have launched a bomber,
but it's moving faster than a fighter plane!
I have picture!
A Knightmare!
It's not being transported,
it's just flying on its own!
That weapons report we got... could this be it?
You mean that novelty weapon?!
But then, the pilot is...
The military force that's
trying to occupy the Kyushu block
is fighting under ex-minister Atsushi Sawasaki.
If they lose him, the new Japanese
government will collapse very quickly.
In that case, the Chinese Federation will lose
their excuse for being here, and have to withdraw.
There it is. The enemy headquarters.
An open channel?
This is Minister Sawasaki.
Is that Prime Minister Kururugi's son in the pilot seat?
I see. I didn't know he had a son like you.
And then when you saved me, Princess Euphemia,
I'll never forget it...
You looked like some kind of goddess,
like you were bathed in radiant light.
Oh! Forgive me!
I should have thanked you for
these change of clothes you gave me!
Oh, don't worry about that, Nina.
Besides, I'm not all the wonderful person you think I am.
I'm no good compared to my brother and sister...
No, that's not true!
How can you say that about yourself?
There's not one good thing about me.
Really, nothing at all.
My parents are ordinary, I'm not the least bit pretty,
and there's just nothing special about me...
That's wrong, Nina.
I think you're a very cute girl.
Oh, no, I'm not really good for anything.
Not at all.
She hates herself.
But, so do I...
I guess I understand, but Suzaku makes me uneasy...
That's it. Suzaku feels badly too!
So please, oh please, don't say that
you're no good, Princess Euphemia, I beg of you!
Because...
Because I need you. I need your goodness.
Thank you so much, Nina.
I'm glad I got to know you.
You've really helped me understand!
This has nothing to do with my father.
I came here to put an end to this fighting.
I will accept your surrender.
You want to rob Japan of its dream of freedom?
Freedom has to come the right way, not like this.
You'll act out of selfishness?
It's justice without ideology.
No, you're wrong! That's not what I...
My V.A.R.I.S!
Those are Chinese Federation Gang Lous.
He allowed me to distract him. He still has much to learn!
Euphy?
Schneizel!
May I have access to a private communication line?
My energy filler!
Are you kidding?! They blasted off the float?!
The Avalon has to strike at the base!
No, the shield doesn't completely surround us!
One direct hit and we'll go down in flames!
Suzaku!
Reroute all power to combat and com-systems!
Got it!
You had better surrender, Suzaku.
Since you're Prime Minister Kururugi's son,
I guarantee that you'll be very well treated, my boy.
I decline. If I used my father's
name for this, I'd never forgive myself.
This is between you and me.
I see. You're very much your father's son,
as foolish and stubborn as he was!
Suzaku Kururugi!
Princess Euphemia!
Suzaku!
The truth is, you and I, uh, that is...
Sorry, but right now...
You see...
I hereby command you to love me!
Right!
Huh?
What?! What is it?!
Uh, sorry, but this is private.
And in return, I will love you!
Forever!
Princess Euphemia...
Suzaku, I love your stubborness
and your kindness and your strength.
Your sad eyes, your clumsiness,
and the way you have trouble with cats.
I love everything about you!
So please, don't hate yourself!
I see that I've made you
even more worried than I did before.
You really are...
Everything you do is impulsive!
When we first met,
when you told me you were a princess,
when you selected my school,
when you made me a knight... Always!
Yes, they were all sudden.
That's because I suddenly realized...
But then it's that spur of the moment
feeling that's opened so many doors for me.
Thank you!
What are you doing?! Stop him now!
Princess, can I make one final request?
Final?
If something happens to me, whatever it is,
please don't blame yourself.
Destroy all the records and erase every trace
so no one knows what happened to me.
I don't want my friends to be sad.
Just tell them I transferred
schools or make up some story.
Suzaku, don't tell me you're...!
Yes, the Knightmare's out of energy.
Oh, and please, say goodbye to Miss Cecile
and Lloyd and to Prince Schneizel for me.
I was stubborn all the way to the end.
Don't die, Suzaku!
You've got to live!
Wh-What the...?
And fire!
Huh?!
What was that?!
Something just appeared on the radar!
A stealth system! We've got picture!
That's...!
I see. So the famous white Knightmare is named Lancelot.
And he's fighting as recklessly as ever.
Yes, but this time he seems to be
following someone else's plan.
They sent a single fighter in
to try to disrupt the main force.
Even if he fails, Cornelia can move right in.
Schneizel... Is he behind this idea?
These people are in my way!
I thought the hadron cannon was still in development.
They made the beams converge?!
But I wanted to be the one to perfect that system!
Hmm, looks like integrating
the Gefjun Disturber has worked.
But that float system is more advanced than mine.
So my opponent is the Earl of Pudding, I guess.
We were collaborating inadvertently.
Oh, how distasteful.
Kururugi, is the Lancelot still operational?
Zero. I thought so.
It's Zero?
Is that an open channel?!
Yes!
Then stay with that source and find out what he's after!
An energy filler?
I'm going to take out the enemy command center.
What will you do?
What?!
Sorry Zero, but you're not going to get your wish.
I'm going to hit them first... my way.
Resume attack!
Stop them! Stop Kururugi and Zero!
Zero! Shouldn't we be fighting together as comrades?
Don't you care about Japan?
The Black Knights stand against anyone
who uses violence unjustly for their own selfish ends!
Selfish?! I'm doing this for Japan!
Sawasaki!
If this is for Japan, why did you
run away to the Chinese Federation?!
You should have stayed, for everyone's sake!
You're still a child!
A joint operation... Gawain!
Lancelot.
So Suzaku and Lelouch are...!
What?! Zero?!
Yes, he saved Kururugi.
Fighting on our side? What the hell is he thinking?!
So his tactic was to bring the
Gawain in alone to get past the Britannians.
That was brilliant.
Maybe, but the Guren MK-II
could have acted as a shield for them.
It's not like I can go home
or back to school at this point.
After all our battles, to be
working with the Lancelot is just...
What's necessary here is not victory.
The Black Knights' participation
in this battle is an undeniable truth.
Of course, it will never be officially reported,
but the rumors will spread and
everyone will know what happened here.
As Zero said, this will show
the world exactly where we stand.
Protecting the nation is our first commitment.
What's wrong with going to another country,
then waiting for the right moment to strike?
That's an effective strategy, isn't it?
We can set up a new line of defense at Kagoshima.
Right. I appreciate your help.
Huh? Huh?!
Sawasaki! That's far enough.
I-Impossible!
They took the largest fortress in
all of Kyushu with hardly any effort!
The terrorism in the Kyushu block led
by an anti-government group was stopped
by Princess Cornelia's sudden attack.
Atsushi Sawasaki and four members of
the former Japanese government were arrested.
Over half the Chinese Federation
troops were captured as well.
In response to this incident,
Chinese Federation leaders are
asserting this was an unauthorized action
by General Tsao of the Liaodong District,
and they are requesting all POWs be released
in accordance with the Tibet Convention.
Warrant Officer Kururugi, reporting for duty.
Welcome back home, Suzaku.
Uh, I...
I...
Suzaku, I finally understand my heart.
It's not that I expect an ideal country
or perfect justice or anything complicated like that.
I just want to see people smiling, that's all.
The smiles of the people I love now
and the people I loved before as well.
Will you help me?
Will you be my knight?
I will, Your Highness.
Now that Sawasaki's been stopped,
we have to make our next move quickly!
Also I need to build a place where Nunnally can be happy.
And for that, I need to create a nation
that can drive a wedge into the world.
Things are proceeding well towards destruction.
And when the time comes, I'll deal with
Cornelia and Schneizel at the same time!