The Japan Liberation Front:
The largest insurgent group in Area 11.
Viceroy Cornelia was determined to crush them.
She encircled the Narita mountains
where her proud Britannian
legions applied overwhelming force,
sure their "inferior enemy" was vanquished.
Then, the Black Knights made their move.
Using the Guren Mk-II's radiant wave surger,
they caused the water veins of
the summit to explode at once.
The mountain collapsed.
Both the Japan Liberation Front and the main
Britannian forces were engulfed in mud and rushing water.
Cornelia was isolated; Most of her forces lost.
Seeking an unprecedented reversal,
Zero commanded the Black Knights to hunt down Cornelia.
In their hearts, everyone has faith in
their own existence and ultimate triumph.
However, when time and destiny unfold,
this faith turns out to be quite fleeting and pointless.
What are our losses?!
I've only got signal from 20 percent of our forces.
20 percent?!
Our command structure can't sustain this!
This is the Marceau unit!
I can't raise General Alex!
It looks like the second division's been wiped out!
Lloyd, what's going on?
Hmm... It's very unnatural.
Unnatural?
There seems to be an unconfirmed report
that the Black Knights have appeared.
Zero!
Congratulations!
This is our chance.
Lloyd!
You're so rash.
Huh? Why's that?
Would you like a detailed explanation?
Uh, no, I'll pass.
Anyway, while the High Command's still gathering data,
all we can do is play it by ear, right?
Is the Viceroy safe?
Yes, she was outside the mud flow.
But the units guarding her flank are lost.
That means she's totally isolated.
What the hell are those Purebloods doing?!
Come on, move!
I can't lose to Elevens! I am a Brittanian!
Lord Kewell!
All right! Guren MK-II, move to the planned point!
We'll break through the last
of their line and take Cornelia!
Right!
Got it! Let's pull this off!
Fight to the death!
Sugiyama! You okay?!
Y-Yeah...
Get them!
That's right, move swiftly.
If you survive this battle, you
can call yourself a true warrior.
And afterward...
The Purebloods are holding their ground?
Yes, sir! Under Lady Viletta's command!
Then use the moment for the
Viceroy to retreat! Send air cover!
No, wait!
Something's approaching the Viceroy from behind!
All units, are you ready?
Yes, sir!
All right. Deploy the custom Burais.
Deploying!
Listen carefully!
If this landslide was manmade,
it should allow us to hit Cornelia from behind.
Capture Cornelia now!
Take revenge for what happened seven years ago!
Yes, sir!
By the honor of the Four Holy Swords!
What?!
Protect Her Highness!
Surround them!
The Japan Liberation Front?!
Slash and encircle!
Right!
These are not just any Burais.
This reminds me of seven years ago.
But it's different now.
This time we have Knightmares as well!
Your Highness, leave them to us!
Please, you have to withdraw for now!
Very well, I know a way to turn this around.
Guilford!
Yes!
After you've driven them back, meet me over at point nine!
Nine?
I understand!
Cornelia!
You weaklings!
All right! Keep this up and crush Zero!
Maybe we should get Kallen over here.
No!
If we break formation now, our plan is ruined!
This is turning grim.
If it goes on, we'll be fighting her royal guard next.
Zero! Cornelia's under attack down below!
What's that? Which team made the move?
It's not our people! Looks like the JLF!
Someone else understands my intent?
How excellent.
They'll hold off the royal
guard, which is just what we need.
I'm sorry for the late arrival, General!
Tohdoh! We've been waiting!
General, please send all remaining units to join me here.
Can you beat them?
Yes, but only if we can hold off their main force!
We have a chance now to turn the entire war around!
I've heard Area 11 has a formidable commander.
Their "shining knight."
Is this him? Tohdoh?!
Fine! Let him try me!
Urgh! At a time like this?!
What do we do?
Fall back!
We have to find a way to link up with Viceroy Cornelia.
But sir, their main base is right in front of us!
And if we're hit from behind, we'll be wiped out!
You fool!
If Princess Cornelia's taken by these Elevens,
this entire battle is lost!
Y-Yes sir!
Sub-Viceroy Euphemia,
you must act now to prevent a disaster.
Send in the G1!
No!
But Commander Guilford is completely
pinned down; He can't get to Cornelia.
Her life is at stake here!
We can't!
There's a field hospital right here! And civilians!
They've been evacuated from all over the area
and brought to this point!
Besides, the G1 base is our command center!
The Viceroy ordered me not to move it, no matter what!
That's why... I just can't...!
Well, hello there, the ASEEC's crew reporting for duty.
Insolence!
You're irregulars!
Your orders are to keep silent and observe!
Um, yes sir, normally we would, but...
But all of this waiting around is boring.
Sub-Viceroy Euphemia...
I beseech you, please order us into the battle!
How transparent!
You just want the glory of rescuing the Viceroy!
Our whole army is out there!
You think one unit is going to change things?!
With an Eleven pilot!
Right, right, but what's the harm in trying?
Since it's just one unit, it won't
look bad for you if we lose, right?
Are you listening?
Euphie!
Yes, I understand. Please do it!
We got it!
Thank you very much!
Right! I won't fail!
Dammit! He's fierce!
Scatter!
Lt. Colonel! What about Cornelia?
If Zero's the man I think he is,
he's moving into position right now!
We've got to trust him.
What? Zero's on the move?!
Right.
We'll keep going and come over and back you up!
Never mind that now, just track Zero!
Y-Yes, sir!
This is his projected course.
The Princess was trying to trap Tohdoh;
Now there's a Knightmare waiting for her!
Princess Cornelia!
I got the message, Guilford.
Advanced weapon system Z-01 Lancelot,
utilize sand panels to climb liquefied slope
at max combat speed and rescue the Viceroy!
Yes, my lord.
Suzaku, there's one thing I want to ask you.
What's that?
More than anything, you hate when people die,
yet, you're in the military. Why is that?
I'm in the military to stop people from dying.
And that self-contradiction will get you killed someday!
Ugh! Sorry about that!
Lancelot, now launching.
Cornelia!
Lowborn scum!
What's this?!
That's not just a customized unit!
Can you hear me, Cornelia?
This is checkmate.
Zero!
Yes. Should we celebrate our reunion?
Of course, you'll have to surrender to us first.
And after that, there are a few questions I wanna ask you.
And in case you're wondering, your
reinforcements won't get here in time.
I win, Cornelia.
You're a fool, Zero!
This one!
If I take this one out, I'm free and clear!
You've got some moves!
Coward! Attacking from behind!
Really?
And your own attack methods don't show acts of cowardice?
They launched a pincer assault before we could regroup!
I'll never be able to reach the Princess now!
Lt. Colonel, we've crushed the enemy reinforcements!
Right!
Switch to spinning life-or-death formation!
Yes, sir!
If this goes on, Princess Cornelia will be....
Guilford...
Guilford, my knight. You and Darlton protect Euphie.
Your Highness!
I won't surrender.
As an imperial princess, I'll fight to the last!
Princess Cornelia!
Huh. She's so predictable.
Oh my.
As reckless as ever, eh?
He's used the V.A.R.I.S. to
clear the obstacles in his path.
Viceroy, are you all right?
I came to help, Your Highness!
Special Corps? Who authorized you?
He can get her out of there if it's the Lancelot unit.
Hey, isn't that Knightmare...
Yeah. The one from Shinjuku and Lake Kawaguchi.
Again?! It's him again?!
MK-II, destroy that unit immediately!
It's interfered with us enough!
Right!
You handle that thing! I'll take out Zero!
Now you'll pay for Shinjuku!
It's as fast as the Lancelot?!
If I can take it down...
Is that all you've got?!
Blocked!
Hey! Are you okay?!
I am...
Ohgi!
Yes.
How's the Guren MK-II?!
The right hand's wrecked. We've gotta fix it.
Retreat!
All Black Knights, move to your escape points!
This has become a war of attrition. Retreat!
Viceroy!
Go after Zero!
But...
My energy filler's just drained!
Go!
Right!
Ugh, I'm hating this retreat thing.
We thrashed 'em, but if we keep pushing...
Face it, we left the JLF there as bait while we ran away.
I hate when you say it like that, but...
Yeah, but people aren't just pieces in a chess game.
Zero wouldn't think like that.
If he did, he'd end up using us as pawns, too.
I don't believe he'd do that.
His rage is real.
He hates Britannia as much as we do.
And I think a person who knows rage also knows sorrow.
Special corps head trailer.
Found Zero. Going in for capture.
Zero, I owe you; I know that.
You've saved a lot of people.
I know there are lots of Elevens
supporting you from the shadows.
However, your methods are...
...very wrong.
Th-That's...
Is it the girl from the capsule in Shinjuku?!
Stop now!
Don't even think about hurting him!
C.C...
She's working with Zero?
Wait! What are you doing?
You're challenging a Knightmare?!
It's a problem if you die.
It'll be indirect contact, but it's worth a try.
Father... You're dead!
That's impossible!
No! I didn't mean to!
No, I... I just...!
Hey! Are you using Geass on him?
I'm just feeding him some shock images.
I can't tell what he's seeing though.
Anyway, you've got time to get away now.
What about you?
I can't move yet.
You go first!
Don't be foolish.
I can't keep owing you favors...
No, not now!
What? This is different.
That's...
S-Stop it!
Stay... out... of my mind!
Stop it!
Why now?!
You're... unveiling me...
I had to do it!
What's happening to him?!
Idiot! Get away now!
C.C.!
Hurry!
Damn you!
Don't follow!
I have no idea what Zero is trying to do now.
Our only course of action is to get
to the General and get him out of here.
Your Highness! I'll be right there!
Guilford, relay this message to all units:
Prepare to retreat.
There's no reason to waste
the lives of any more of my men.
Stay in formation and fall back cautiouslly.
We have to face facts. We've been defeated this time.
You see? Britannia sure had its hands full
just dealing with the Liberation Front!
Yeah.
That gave us the chance we needed to escape.
Hey, where's Zero?
I can't raise his Burai.
You don't think he's been captured, do you...?
This girl, she can't be human.
She recovers from wounds in ways that are beyond normal.
She was shot in the head in Shinjuku, and yet...
Clovis confined her for his private experiments,
so she's not connected with Britannia.
Her vital signs are at human levels.
I'd better analyze a blood sample
later and photograph the wounds.
What?
You finally called me... by my real name.
So Zero escaped again.
The Japan Liberation Front hammered our defenses
and he slipped away in the confusion.
Despicable. Using someone else to cover his movements.
Oh, what about Kururugi?
He's safe now.
We had to wait till his energy
filler ran out to finally stop him.
Stop him from what?
Was there a problem with his unit?
Apparently. It was going berserk.
A failure unworthy of my older brother's forces.
I removed the shrapnel and cleaned the wound.
That wasn't necessary.
Apparently not.
So, there was no point in protecting me at all.
Your pride always gets in the
way at the most ridiculous moments.
But then I learned something from it.
Hmph.
That's your name, isn't it?
You have a bad habit of eavesdropping.
Well, it's a good name.
It's a lot more human than C.C...
Oh, that's a joke.
As if I want to be more human.
After all, I've... I...
I've forgotten everything.
Every single thing...
So what's the use of it?
A name? But why?
It's a good time to say this.
Yes... You saved me today.
You did that before and gave me Geass.
That's why... I'll only say this once...
Thank you.
No one's ever... thanked me before.
Well then, can you show your appreciation?
Say it again, like you did before.
Uh? Oh, you mean the name.
Just this once, with tenderness,
like you treasure it in your heart.
Very well then...
How was that?
It was bad. It was completely bad.
It wasn't tender. There was no honesty or sympathy in it.
You spoke it oddly. And worst of all, it was cold.
You're a picky girl.
Exactly. That's why I go by the name C.C.
Ugh. Another soldier.
No wonder our battalions fell apart!
I swear I'm not Orange.
ZERO!
Looks like our ride's here.
Zero! Are you okay?
The others went on ahead, and...
Who's that?!
Oh, you needn't worry.
She's a very important friend.
Huh...?
C.C., I don't know why snow is white,
but I still think snow is beautiful.
I don't hate it.
I see.
Still not enough!
I need something more to checkmate Cornelia.
And I have a feeling that what's missing is inside of me.
Something I have to face and overcome.
Then, I can lead the Black Knights to the next stage.
Yes.
And if necessary, I'll even...