Lelouch, a youth of Brittania,
had been granted special abilities by a mysterious girl.
Geass.
The power to command others. To do absolutely anything.
And Lelouch is determined to use that power
to bring the Britannian Empire to its knees,
to avenge his mother, and create a world
where his younger sister Nunnally can find happiness.
All the while knowing at the end of his quest,
the Britannian Emperor, his father, awaits.
Or at least.
that was the hope Lelouch carried in his heart back then.
Do you know anything about this weapon,
Suzaku Kururugi?
It was the one used to rob Prince Clovis of his life.
The barrel striations leave no doubt.
And we've done a little homework on you as well.
You're the eldest child of Japan's
last acting Prime Minister, are you not?
Your motive here is clear.
You're making a mistake.
I have never even laid eyes on that gun.
We found your fingerprints all over this weapon.
You're also suspected of
murdering members of the Royal Guard.
Come clean now, and you'll be judged
as though you were born a Britannian,
not some worthless Eleven.
You're wrong! I've done nothing!
That was Suzaku they mentioned on the news, wasn't it?
Yep. It looks like he's still alive.
Yeah. It's been ages.
We haven't seen him since the war ended.
Even we...
And, Lelouch?
What is it?
It wasn't true what the news said, was it?
Of course not.
Suzaku would never do anything like that.
They've just made a mistake.
Yeah... Must be.
Right. Well... Good night, Nunnally.
That's why we should've issued
a friggin' statement sooner!
We could've taken credit for it!
Naoto... I'm not cut out for this.
I'm no leader...
Yes, everything is just as you requested.
We have the best in the business working on it.
Once the slide system is in order, it's all yours.
Once I've erased all of the evidence, I
should forget this ever happened, right?
Truly this has been a painful incident for all.
The Viceroy of Area 11, our beloved
Prince Clovis, has been lost to us forever.
However, we can and will bear the weight of this tragedy.
And from this darkest of hours, draw strength.
We've lose the most crucial part of the equation...
Can we do it without him?
Don't I wish.
The other units never let go of a good pilot.
And even if we got one, they'd never match his readings...
His operational efficiciency clocked in at 94%!
And you wanna replace him?
You should tell them that, perhaps they'll let Suzaku go.
He's an honorary Britannian, they'd never listen.
Ever since General Bartley's disgrace, the
purebloods have the military in an iron grip.
The purebloods what?
Well, from what I understand, they're
saying that only pureblood Britannians
should be allowed to serve in the military.
Their view is, one of their own can never be a criminal.
But if the criminal is an Eleven,
it paves the way for Margrave Jeremiah to shut
down the practice of granting natives Honorary status.
And what of Suzaku?
His fate's all but decided.
Hey, Lelouch, you got anything goin' on later?
After all, classes have been canceled for the day.
Folks have been askin' for a rematch!
You are not gambling, you guys!
C'mon, don't be such a stick in the mud.
She's right, though, maybe it's time to quit.
Huh?!
I've found a better opponent, actually.
You did? I don't get it?
You're cuttin' me in on the action too, right?!
Better not. It's not really up your alley.
Britannia's resounding victory over
Japan opened the unenlightened nation's eyes
to its true place in today's world order.
Since then, the Empire and Area 11 have
walked hand in hand down the road to revival.
Sixteen hundred hours at Tokyo Tower.
Why here of all places?
It was Kururugi who contacted us, wasn't it?
Hard to say.
Yeah, but he might have been arrested
after his communciation with Kallen.
Then we're in danger here, we should go...
Attention please.
Paging a Miss Kallen Stadtfeld of Ashford Academy.
One of your personal effects has been turned in
at the kiosk on the observation deck. I repeat...
Hi, I'm assuming this phone is yours, ma'am.
Um, something wrong, it is yours, isn't it?
Uh... Yeah. Thank you so much.
Oh yeah, there's no debating it,
life is better here thanks to Prince Clovis.
I mean, it's all due to Britannia that
we could rebuild as quickly as we did.
I'm happy about that...
Zero?
Um... Hello?
I want you to board the outbound train on Loop Line 5.
And bring your friends.
What?!
You handled His Highness's memorial program very well.
A little too weepy for my tastes, but...
Yes, well, the masses tend to
like tearjerkers, Your Excellency.
Spoken like a true TV man.
Still, I have to acknowledge the finesse you've shown.
You did well in the short time you had.
One would almost think you were expecting
His Highness to meet his untimely end.
It's quite common for memorial programs
to be set in advance for important people.
Does that include me as well?
Recent events may've bumped you
up the list a bit, Your Excellency.
I wasn't deemed important enough till now, is that it?
How forthright of you.
I'm afraid so, sir.
Ever thought of enlisting?
The army could use more men like you.
I don't think it would be a very good fit.
Not really my cup of tea.
You prefer the civil sector, I take it?
No matter. I have another favor to ask of you.
Tomorrow night, Suzaku Kururugi will
be transferred to his court martial.
We should line the road with good, patriotic Britannians.
Excellent, you catch on quickly, don't you?
Be sure the rabble can see his face.
Lord Jeremiah.
There are those among the Elevens
who see Private Kururugi as a hero.
Some might very well make an attempt to free him.
I'll be there personally aboard my Sutherland.
If anyone even thinks of causing
trouble, they'll be executed on the spot!
Attention, all passengers.
If you become aware of any suspicious items onboard,
please alert metro personnel by using the nearest...
What now?
Uh.
Face forward and look to your right.
What do you see?
The Britannian city.
It was stolen away from us... and built on our sacrifice.
And on the left?
I see our city.
Remants of a desiccated city
after the Britannians sucked it dry.
Good answer.
Now make your way to the front of the train.
The next stop is Okubo. Okubo is next.
Those wishing to transfer to the Chuo Soubu Line
should exit at the next stop. Okubo will be next.
Once again, those wishing to transfer to the
Chuo Soubu Line should exit at the next stop.
Was it you... on the phone?
Whoa... Do you think it's a trap?
Well? Was that you in Shinjuku?
Was that cease-fire your doing?
Hey, we're talkin' to you!
What do you think of my tour of the settlement?
Your tour?
Aw, come on, there's no way it was this joker.
I wanted you to fully grasp the two.
The settlement and the ghetto.
Yeah, we know.
There's a difference between us and them.
A very harsh one.
And that's why we resist them.
You're wrong.
Britannia will not fall to terrorism.
Fall...?
It's little better than childish nuisance.
What was that?!
You callin' us a buncha kids?!
You should know your enemy.
It is not people... but Britannia itself!
It is a war you must wage, but not on the innocent!
Take up your sword! Fight for justice!
Heh... Oh, please.
That's all easy enough to say, isn't it?!
Hiding behind that mask.
Why should we even trust you?!
She's right!
Lose the mask!
Right. Are you going to show us your face or not?
Very well. I'll show you.
But rather than my face, bear witness to my power.
If I deliver to you the impossible,
then I might have earned your trust.
He killed a Prince of Britannia!
Suzaku Kururugi should be treated as a hero!
But he's an honorary Britannian!
Prime Minister Kururugi was his father!
So what!
The bastard gave up Japan!
Our people don't know that about him!
The whole Shinjuku business was the
work of Kouzuki's group, wasn't it?
Yes, sir, they're being led by
a man named Ohgi at the present.
Hmm...
Has Kururugi's family said anything?
No, sir, they broke contact with
him once he joined the military.
Tohdoh, what are your thoughts?
We should not become involved in this public execution.
That's cowardly.
You're Tohdoh the Miracle Worker, right?
There is a difference between miracles and foolhardiness.
Congratulations!
Those two you asked me about
weren't on the list of casualties.
That's good to hear...
Not much luck on your end though.
You may be getting a trial, but no
one is pulling for you, certainly.
But the courts are where truth comes to light.
I expect there'll be more smoke and mirrors than anything.
"The truth" is scarce of late...
If that's how the world works, then...
...so be it. I've no regret.
Any moment. Any moment now.
It's a sight to see.
The throngs lining the route.
All of them waiting on bated breath.
Waiting for the accused murderer
of Prince Clovis to pass by.
Honoary Britannian, and former Eleven, Suzaku Kururugi.
Camera five's a little slow.
Talk to me, Charles. Your team been deployed yet?
What? The studio? Let 'em wait.
Nothing's been pushed back,
everything's going according to plan.
Here we go.
I-I can see them!
They have the suspect!
Suzaku Kururugi is headed this way!
Like clockwork.
Heh. What a circus this is.
And I'm as corrupt as any of 'em.
This is insane. We know that Suzaku is innocent.
The court deemed our testimony inadmissible.
There's nothing we can do.
Yes, but...
Is that altruism or humanitarianism?
This isn't the time for a game in semantics!
Not much else to do.
We both know where this case is headed, don't we?
We couldn't reach him at the summit.
All we can do is cut our losses, really.
Voices of scorn, growing ever louder.
Voices bearing testament to a
people's love of their prince.
Raining their judgment down on a terrorist.
Suzaku!
Margrave Jeremiah,
integral in settling this case, will be
presiding over the trial as acting consul.
No way the three of 'em can pull this off on their own.
He told us...
He said he'd make the impossible possible...
He gave his word... to save Suzaku Kururugi.
Right. No need to turn back. The die is cast.
Acting Consul Jeremiah!
What is it?
Vehicle approaching the main highway from Third.
We just let it through, as you instructed, but...
Do you believe the target could be a terrorist vehicle?
Well, sir... it's Prince Clovis's car.
The prince's car?
Well, looks like we've got a comedian.
Don't worry about it, just let him through to us.
All forces, halt here!
Hey, they stopped, they really did.
It's just a coincidence.
Yeah but he said Jerimiah would try to hog all
the limelight and make some sort of stand about it.
Coincidence!
This is not a scheduled stop.
Could there have been some sort of accident?
This is site five.
There's a vehicle approaching them.
Hmph.
It's... It's Prince Clovis's personal transport!
And it's heading straight for the cavalcade!
He's heading straight at 'em...
What's he planning?
Hope they can't tell it's fake...
I see. Just you two then.
I'm sorry, we just need a little more time.
If more people understood what we...
No, the two of you will do just fine.
Come on, that's ridiculous, there'll be too many of them!
With your help, clearing the
task at hand will be child's play.
I'll need this by tomorrow.
All that matters is the exterior...
You dare desecrate His Highness' transport?!
Come out of there!
Huh?
I am...
...Zero!
Zero?
Wh-Who is this person.
This man calling himself Zero,
standing before a full military convoy?!
What is all this?
What the hell does he think he's doin'?
Who is this man calling himself Zero?!
Ladies and gentleman...
Zero? Whaddya mean, like "nothing"?
Are we gazing on a terrorist?
Certainly not the wisest if such is the case.
Is he... an Eleven?
Now to return the favor, Suzaku...
I've seen enough, Zero. This little show of yours is over!
First things first.
Why don't you lose that mask?
What in the...?!
Lord Jeremiah, be careful, he's got the...!
Yes, Jeremiah...
You never saw inside this thing,
so you assume it holds poison gas.
Wait, you don't understand... Ah!
Can all of you watching at home see this?
It's some sort of device,
although it's purpose is unclear.
Stay with us, and we'll see if this
so-called terrorist has anything to say.
You... bastard...
He's taken every Britannian here hostage.
And he's done it without them even knowing it!
You intend to shoot?
I think you know full well what...
Unit six, bring up the sound!
And get that camera right in his face!
Sir, it's too hairy out here.
Amateurs.
Fine. What are your demands?
An exchange. This for Kururugi.
Like hell!
He's charged with high treason for murdering a prince!
I can't hand him over!
No. You're mistaken, Jeremiah.
He's no murder...
The man who killed Clovis...
...was myself!
Ah-ha.
Unbelievable!
The real culprit, eh?
What? Wh-What does this mean?!
This masked man called Zero...
No, we can't be sure who he is.
But in any case...
...he claims to be the real assassin!
So, where does this leave the
current suspect, Private Kururugi?
Ah, crap, there's no way outta this!
We are so screwed.
For a single Eleven,
you'll save scores of precious Britannians.
I find that to be a bargain.
This is all one big performance to him!
He's mad, I tell you!
Disguising this truck as His Highness's!
He'll pay the price for mocking the crown!
Careful.
You don't wish the public to learn of "Orange," do you?
Huh?
Orange? What's he talkin' about?
I don't know.
If I die, it'll all go public.
If you don't want that to happen...
What are you talking about? What is this?!
You'll do everything in your power to let us go.
Your prisoner as well!
Right, understood.
You there, release the prisoner!
What on earth are you doing, my lord?!
Get that man over here!
Huh?!
Should we? But...
Hand him over! Nobody gets in his way!
No, what are you thinking?!
You can't do this!
Lord Kewell, this is an order!
It's hard to tell what's happening from here,
but it seems that Kururugi's release has been brokered!
So, who the hell are you... Uh!
As I thought, they didn't allow you to speak.
If they get away, we'll lose everything!
It's time to go, Zero.
Well then, till next time.
You cowardly Eleven!
Lord Jeremiah, what are you...?!
You heard me, stand down, now!
They're not alone at all! They jumped right off!
It worked! Now we can...
You imbecile! There's nowhere for you to run!
Lord Kewell!
Are you going to follow orders or not?!
And believe me, there will be repercussions.
All units, do I make myself clear?!
Do everything in your power to help them get away!
Man... I didn't really think he could do it.
Yeah, who is this guy?
That's crap!
How many times can a bluff like that work, anyway?
Ya gotta give the guy some credit, though.
Huh?
Gotta admit it, nobody else could 'a pulled that off.
Not the Japanese Liberation Front.
Certainly not me.
We've always thought that a full on war
with Britannia wasn't a possibility at all.
But maybe with him... it is.
It looks like they treated you rather roughly.
Now you know what they're really like, Private Kururugi.
Britannia is rotten.
If you wish to bring change to this world, then join me.
So is it true?
Are you really the one who killed Prince Clovis?
This is war.
Why wouldn't I kill an enemy commander?
And the gas? Those were civilians out there!
A bluff. To help things along.
The result: Not a single death.
The result?
That's all that matters to you, I suppose.
Hmph.
Come, join me.
The Britannia you serve is a worthless dominion.
Maybe that's true. But...
But this nation, it can be changed for the better.
And from within.
Changed?
And any ends gained through
contemptible means aren't worth anything.
Wait! Where are you going?!
My court martial begins in an hour.
Are you mad?!
The only reason they're giving
you a trial is to find you guilty!
The judge, the prosecution, and defense!
Rules are rules.
And if I don't go, they'll start cracking
down on Elevens and Honorary Britannians.
But you'll die!
I don't mind.
Don't be an idiot!
An old friend of mine always used to tell me that.
He'd say I was a fool...
It's my weakness, I guess.
I'd try to bring you in, but you'd just end up killing me.
And if I'm going to die, it'll
be in the service of the people.
Even so. I thank you.
For saving me.
You... fool!
Yes, apparently.
Private Kururugi has made conatct with the authorities.
It would seem this Zero has released him.
However, now that the original charges
against him have been thrown into question,
it's very possible Kururugi will
be found innocent and acquited.
Thank goodness.
Miss Sayoko?
So naive...
I was sure Suzaku would understand.
Change the system from within?
Ridiculous!
The system will just swallow him up!
It'll eat him alive!
I can't beg for their charity to live my life.
I just can't! I won't live by their "rules" anymore!