Lelouch, a young, outcast prince of Britannia,
possesses two great powers:
One of them is the absolute ability to
compel any person to do whatever he commands.
The other is the Black Knights,
his military force assembled with the intent of
destroying the Britannian Empire ruled by his father.
Veiling his true identity behind
a mask and the code name Zero,
Lelouch has made his move to avenge his mother's murder
and to create a world in which his
younger sister Nunnally can find happiness.
What will be the final outcome of these actions?
At this point, no one can predict.
The Japan Liberation Front
was nearly wiped out by your Narita operation, Viceroy.
Now we're hunting down the survivors one by one.
Are you being sarcastic?
We're barely pulling our forces
back together after that fiasco.
No! I-I didn't mean to...
The occupation government is responsible for this!
They've done nothing about
Area Eleven's subways and mining railways!
In the ghettos, they falsify
the registries and property deeds,
as the rebellion spreads unchallenged!
Uhh, the subway tunnels stretch over the whole country.
We can't just fill them all in. We don't have the budget.
The terrorists are using them
as their strike bases and escape routes!
P-Prince Clovis instructed us...
Uh, he said...
...forcing them would fuel the rebellion,
giving the Chinese Federation an excuse to attack.
They've already got their excuse!
Zero's growing stronger and bolder every day!
Vice-minister, Internal Affairs has appointed
a special group of Elevens to
self-govern this area, isn't that right?
A group who are called the N.A.C.
When we stormed Narita, we looked
for evidence of the N.A.C.'s conspiracies.
But it was buried in the landslide...
Still our suspicions remain high.
If we supress them now...
Hm... A group of blue bloods and plutocrats.
Relics of their dismal past.
W-Wait, please!
These are just rumors; there's no evidence of that at all!
I-If you suppress them, then the
Elevens' economy will certainly collapse!
That means no tax revenue to send to the homeland!
Also it's a prime directive of the empire that
Numbers should take care of their own kind!
And what have you done to find the Black Knights?!
We unearthed a shield machine they left
showing Zero was behind the Narita operation.
B-But that's all we've got;
you can't squeeze information out of corpses.
So you can't catch Zero
and you don't want us to hit Kyoto.
Do you know the word "incompetent," minister?
It's for people who can't get results.
So, the Britannian viceroy has gone this far already.
With the Liberation Front smashed,
the last embers of Japan have died away.
No!
He may be on the run,
but Toudou is still strong, still fighting!
Even if that's so,
I heard he lost his custom Burais, so there's no hope...
There is hope.
Hm?
The Black Knights? You've been infatuated
with Zero since he rescued Suzaku Kururugi.
We even sent him the Guren MK-II.
And after the defeat at Trafalgar,
Elizabeth the 3rd found herself
surrounded by revolutionaries in Edinburgh.
Oh, father...
However, with the help of Lord Britannia,
she fled to the American colonies,
now known as our homeland, Britannia.
Hmm...
Huh?
Okay, what's got you so worried?
Constipated? Your monthly?
Uh?! T-That's not it!
Ah. You're lonely 'cause Lelouch is gone, aren't you?
We-eh...
It's more like, Kallen's absent the same day he is.
Again...
Oh, so carefree while the rest of the
world grapples with what happened at Narita.
Suzaku's been out for two days because of that, too.
I know that!
But Lulu and Kallen? Gone on the same day together?
That's serious!
I envy you, Shirley. That's what I love about you!
Don't make fun of me!
Then just tell him already!
Three little words: "I like you!"
U-Uh... I couldn't! I just couldn't!
I mean, what if...
"What if he rejects me?!
It could ruin our great friendship!"
You don't have to laugh that hard, you know?
It's comfortable, isn't it?
This place now. The way we are together.
That's true.
Still, we should prepare ourselves a bit.
The fact is, nothing stays the same forever, you know.
Oh, forget it! Please don't take me too seriously.
If it's bothering you, why not
just ask him the next chance you get?
So, how do you feel about it from your side?
L-Lulu! I thought you were absent!
Nunnally had a little fever this morning.
And Sayoko was busy, so I stayed home to help.
Oh, really? You don't say...
So is Nunna feeling better now?
A bit.
Madame President, those papers?
Oh, right.
Make sure you organize
all of them by year and class, okay?
Yeah, I will.
You have a talent for ordering people around.
And you're a great subordinate!
Subordinate? I guess that's what I am.
Oh, Madame President!
You nearly gave me a heart attack doing that!
Huh? Where's my tickets...?
Ah?!
Lulu!
What is it?
Um, is my dad's letter mixed up with that paperwork?
Hmm? Oh, sorry...
What's wrong?
Ah, Lulu!
Shirley?
Huh?
Stop being so suspicious.
That's hardly the case.
To me, he's nothing more than a...
I did it! I actually really did it!
So now what happens? He'll come, right?!
I mean, he didn't say no.
Then again... uh-uh, he's just
coming with me to little a concert...
So it's no big thing. But, still, it's a chance!
Thank you, Father.
Kyoto praised us for using the Guren MK-II so well.
I thought that was encouraging.
But there was the White Armor...
Don't sweat it! It was a tie, right? A tie!
Why would Shirley just out of the blue...
My dad works a really, long way from here,
but he likes to send me great stuff like this
to keep my spirits up, y'know?
So, I was just wondering...
Here.
Hm? What's this?
A love letter.
Oh? From you?
And they say you have no sense of humor!
You laugh too much.
It's an official letter from Kyoto.
They urgently request a meeting.
Is this really such a big deal?
A big deal? It's Kyoto!
If they accept us, it means funding and support.
It could solve our financial crisis.
Crisis?
There shouldn't be any problem
if you're following the budget I laid out.
Well, uh...
Hey, it's not my fault!
We're turning into a big organization now!
That means new expenses, y'know.
Like fancy dinners for the
new recruits so you can show off?
Hey, you...
I know where you've been taking them, "big spender!"
You know about it?
We'll put Ohgi in charge of the treasury for now.
Hold it right there! I'm the one
that's in charge of the cash!
That's my job!
If you want me to trust you,
then show me some results.
Did you actually just say "trust"?!
A guy who hides his face from his own partners?!
How about it, Zero? Huh?!
Hold on, that's, uh...
Zero's not the problem here!
Who cares who he is?!
He had the skill to outwit Cornelia, didn't he?
That's why he's the leader of the Black Knights!
Do you really need to know more?
Nina is that you?
If you're not feeling well, then...
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
So what do we do?
I don't know...
We were in Naoto's unit.
I don't mind about his kid-sister Kallen, but...
You were next in line to be leader!
No one said that at Narita.
'Cause Zero practically forced us.
We're the senior commanders, and he keeps secrets from us!
I've narrowed it down to 12 possibilites.
Now let's see which bets pay off.
For that, I'll have to meet them face to face.
Who is it?
It's me.
Um, I'm sorry if I was out of line
when I spoke up back there.
Kallen, tell me, do you wanna know my identity as well?
That girl knows, doesn't she?
No. Sorry to bother you.
Lelouch?
Looks like your fever's gone.
Maybe I was just a little moody.
Moody?
It just seems to me, lately,
that you've become a little distant,
like you have other things weighing on your mind.
Perhaps my body just did this
on its own to get your attention.
You're wrong. I haven't changed.
No matter what, I'll always be at your side, Nunnally.
So, then, can I be a little selfish now?
Please hold my hand just a little bit longer.
If I fall asleep alone...
I'm afraid, I'll have that dream again.
You're serious? You're asking me for a favor?
Yes. I got the idea from something that you said.
No matter what Kyoto's intentions are,
I want their power.
Is that what you truly wish for?
If it's at the very core of your reason for living,
then I'll try to help you.
Then do it. C.C., I need you.
I understand. By the way, you forgot something.
I didn't forget.
I don't know when I'll be back tonight,
so I was planning to call her and cancel.
Stick to your contract...
It's me.
Oh, good timing. I wanted to call. Y'see...
Um, listen, Lulu...
Hmm?
I-I know I made a date with you, but I may be late.
Sorry, but, anyway I'm sure it'll be fine, really!
But I promise you that I'll be there.
Please bring your command staff along,
as per my master's instruction, understood?
They're patrolling the perimeter
in case of any unpleasant contingencies.
I'll call them soon. However, before I do...
Severely damaged corpses should be brought to tent 2.
I.D. all personal items.
Bring remains with identifiable faces to tent 1.
Note locations and times.
Medical team 2 will arrive at Narita shortly.
Transport personnel, report to tent 2!
Was it really her? Did I really see here there?
And then...
Just forget it!
She doesn't show up in any of the data!
Dug enough bodies out of the landslide yet?
I'd like to continue with
recovery operations if that's possible.
Be my guest till it's out of your system.
Consider it Princess Cornelia's pleasure to indulge you.
Ah, Lloyd, Zero and the Black Knights,
what are they trying to do?
What do they hope to achieve
by sacrificing all these lives?
They're "Nights for Justice," haven't you heard?
Is this "justice"?!
Hey, hey, I hope you're not going to start spouting
some embarassing theory about the nature of justice.
We're soldiers, after all.
All set!
I replaced the energy filler for you.
Uh, okay!
Cecile?
I checked the units, including the Purebloods'.
And I was right, wasn't I?
Yes. A radiant surge.
Rakshata!
I never thought she'd work with our enemies.
Plus their pilot was extremely skilled.
Suzaku's mental state is so unstable now,
if we have to fight that knightmare again...
You don't think it could win?
Against my dear Lancelot?
This is taking too long. When do we get there?
Could you chill out? You're embarassing.
Hu... What the hell?!
We're going up?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
The master is waiting for you.
This is... the Fuji mines?!
That is not possible! There's no way we could be here!
It has to be Mt. Fuji!
There's only one mountain like this.
That means the Sakuradite is right below us?!
The damn treasure that caused this whole war!
You know what they do to intruders here?
Execute them!
Their power reaches all the way out to here?
The Kyoto Group is amazing!
It's repulsive!
Mt. Fuji, a sacred mountain
once known for its clear water and quiet beauty...
Now, it is bent to the empire's will,
a place of hideous violation;
a reflection of what Japan has become.
It pains me so.
I apologize for not showing my face.
But, Zero, your face is hidden as well.
Unfortunately, I cannot allow this.
To trust you, I must know who you are.
Therefore, you will show me your face!
Please wait! Zero has given us power and victory!
That should...
Silence!
Now, which of you is Ohgi?
Uh, that's me!
You will remove Zero's mask!
Ohgi!
I'm sorry, Zero, but we need
a reason to put our faith in you, too.
So help us...
...to put our trust in you!
A woman?!
It can't be!
It's not!
This isn't Zero! I saw her before.
She was with Zero after Narita!
You there, girl, is this true?
It is.
So, you are not Japanese?
Correct, clan-chief of Kyoto...
...Taizou Kirihara.
Anyone who can identify him must die!
Especially one who is not Japanese!
Hey! Hold on! I'm not part of this!
You're soft!
And your methods and thinking are outdated!
That is why you'll never win!
Zero?
Wh-When did you...
Hold on! He can fire at us with that remote!
Everyone, stay back! Don't make a move!
Taizou Kirihara.
Founder of Kirihara Industries
which has a monopoly on Sakuradite mining.
Formerly a key backer of the Kururugi regime.
However, when Japan fell, you dodged the tribunals
by collaborating with the colonial rulers.
Commonly known as "Kirihara the Traitor."
In reality, you are one of the
leaders of the "Six Houses of Kyoto,"
who support resistance groups throughout Japan.
A double-agent. How cliché...
Show some respect, you swine!
Stop!
It's as you guessed though.
I... am not Japanese!
Is he serious?!
No wonder he never showed his face.
If you are not Japanese,
why do you fight for Japan? What is it you want?!
The destruction of Britannia.
And so do you believe that this is possible?
That you can do it?
I can, because I must.
I have reasons which compel me inexorably!
I'm glad I'm dealing with you.
You!
It's been a long time. Lord Kirihara.
Is it really you?
It's 8 years since that family received you as a hostage.
Yes. And I appreciate you taking care of me then.
If I hadn't come tonight,
were you planning to take a messenger as hostage?
Not at all.
I came to ask for your help;
that's all I'm seeking from you.
So, the flower planted 8 years ago has finally bloomed.
Oh, I can't see 'im!
Ohgi!
Yes?
This man is a true mortal enemy of Britannia.
His face must remain hidden for vital reasons.
I urge you to follow Zero, and I guarantee that if you do,
we will assist you generously
with intelligence and strategic support.
We thank you!
I am grateful, Lord Kirihara.
Are you embarking on the path of blood?
Indeed. If that is my destiny.
Second, fifth, seventh,
eighth, and ninth platoons,
please continue confirmation...
Yes, the spelling of Fenette matches this one.
I'm afraid this is him.
I'm sorry you had to learn about it like this.
It's all right...
Can you please identify the body?
Of course it's too late all ready.
Anyway, things are finally moving forward.
Now, the Black Knights will operate as I envisioned.
Ah, I'm sorry I was late.
I thought you'd already be back home by now.
Anyway, never mind that.
Come on, let's go someplace to get out of the rain now.
Lulu, tell me...
Zero, he fights for the weak, doesn't he?
Wha...?
Yeah, well, that's what he says.
Then... Then why did he kill my father?
You know, my father... was so gentle...
He never, ever hurt me...
He didn't do anything wrong!
But he was buried alive... He couldn't... breathe...
Why...?
Why did my father have to die?!
I... don't want this...
Nooo!
Please, Lulu...
Help me...
Yes, I understand my actions have consequences.
I know that now, so why?
It'd be so easy to vanish from the stage.
Just stop being Zero.
If I can keep Kirihara quiet,
I can go back to being merely Lelouch Lamperouge.
But, even so...