Your Majesty, the remains have arrived.
I was just conversing with Clovis, actually.
Huh?
The project must proceed. Without a moment's delay.
What's an Eleven doing here?!
He was a suspect in Prince Clovis's murder!
But the teacher said the charges were dropped.
He was suspicious enough to arrest though, right?
You don't really think he's a terrorist, do you?
Um?
Of course he isn't.
The school board would know something like that.
An Eleven here at school?
He is an honorary Britannian.
I know but still, all the same.
Well, he doesn't look all that scary to me.
Why don't we just talk to him, I'm sure he's totally...
Hey.
The guy just got here, give him some space.
Seven years since we used this signal. Long time, huh?
Meeting on the roof like the old days.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're okay. I've been worried.
Alive and kicking, thanks to you.
You almost died... trying to protect me...
I was just returning the favor. From seven years ago.
What about the girl? You know, from the capsule?
I don't really know, we got seperated during the fray.
But you would know more about her than I do, right?
No. The only ones who knew anything
were the inner circle of the Royal Guard.
I see.
And your name, do I still call you Lelouch?
The records count my old identity among the dead.
I go by the name Lelouch Lamperouge now.
Oh.
And you? What happened at your court martial?
And why did you enroll at this school?
I'm as surprised as you are.
What're the odds that we'd end up at the same school?
Truth is...
...someone arranged for me to
receive a proper investigation.
And that person said that a
17-year-old should be in school.
Were all of these painted by Clovis?
Yes.
Such gentle colors... Very much akin to my brother.
We've successfully identified the guerillas.
That's good. Now all we need is their hideout.
Get that intel to the viceroy!
Yes, my lord!
What the...?!
Is that Cornelia?!
Relics of a forgotten age.
Darlton! In here, correct?
Yes, m'lady. Shall we accompany you?
Not for this level of resistance.
Understood.
Surrender at once, you feeble-minded Elevens!
Down with Britannia!
Doesn't seem Zero is here.
No point in going after them one at a time, I suppose.
Vermin.
Rot like the filth that you are!
Hi, Lelouch. I've returned home.
Hi, there. Welcome back. Miss Sayoko.
I've got a special present for you today.
Really? What could it be?
Huh?
This hand.
Thank heaven.
I knew it. I just knew you'd be all right!
It's been a long time, Nunnally.
So tell me, you will stay the night, won't you?
Suzaku's enrolled as a student at Ashford Academy now.
So you can see him anytime you want.
Is that true?!
Well, I still have military duties,
so I can't be here every day.
Oh, you're... you're still in the military?
Don't worry.
I've been re-assigned to the engineering corp.
It's a lot less dangerous.
Oh, cool. Engineering, huh?
Oh! Lemme help you!
You just sit down.
Unlike seven years ago, we get to be your host now.
Uh.
It's funny, you're a lot more mellow than you used to be.
And you're a bit more rough.
Ha, I suppose.
Hm?
I told you to stay in my room.
That boy out there.
He's the Britannian soldier from Shinjuku, isn't he?
Is that wise?
Don't worry, it's fine. He's...
Hm?
He's a friend... from the past.
You're getting out, Jeremiah.
Lord Guilford!
You see I'm innocent, don't you?!
Well it seems in the eyes of the court you are anyway.
Orange boy.
Whatever the truth is, Zero got away.
And you purebloods let it happen.
You've been demoted three ranks for failure.
You have two options to choose from.
Starting over as a pilot,
or cultivating an orange farm.
You should come by again.
Nunnally would enjoy it.
Sure. But...
Hm?
Lelouch, I...
I don't think we should be seen together at school.
What do you mean?
Think. How would you explain it?
Being friends with an honorary Britannian?
We have to guard your secret.
No one can know you're royalty.
Uh.
And the same goes for Nunnally.
I don't wanna cause you any trouble...
Doing it again, huh? Everyone's needs but your own!
Again?
Forget it...
Uh...
Thanks for having me. It was a lotta fun.
I'll, uh... see you later.
Right.
I'm so glad, ya know?
Huh?
I never thought we'd get another chance...
...to talk like this.
So, what's the deal?
Something happen to you yesterday, or what?
Ya didn't even show up for the council meeting.
You know, I kinda tanked that history exam.
Please, I don't buy that.
The way you study? I...
Stop it, you guys.
Huh?
It hasn't made the news yet,
but the "Blood of the Samurai"
faction was wiped out by Cornelia.
They were the largest group we had in Central Japan.
Look, Zero, it won't be long till she comes after us.
Just keep your head. Our chance will come.
But...!
Sit tight, I'll contact you later.
He's getting too overly familiar...
Maybe I'd better cut my ties with them.
Huh?
Nina?
I'm sorry, am I too loud?
Not at all. Why are you here? What about class?
Oh...
Something wrong?
Well, it's... I dunno... a little scary.
Scary?
We have a transfer student in our class now.
It's that boy who was accused of murdering Prince Clovis.
He's an Eleven.
Oh. Thanks for all the repeat business.
Although the name on the account we
debit has a guy's name on it, is that okay?
Huh? Trying to you hide your mask, huh?
Unlike my Geass, the mask is a physical piece of evidence.
Huh?
All right, Lelouch. The tea is ready when you are.
That smell. Hey, did you ordered pizza again?
I'm racking up reward points.
I'll be right down, okay?
Lelouch.
Hm?
Maybe you should cut down on the pizza.
You don't want a blubbery belly.
Just don't touch or rub it, okay?
Ooh, scary!
Hm? What the heck?
Yeah... I was wondering if that was going on.
They're just being cruel to Suzaku.
No. It's just...
These things take time. People will come around.
Isn't there anything you can do though?
I mean, he is your friend.
Huh?
Hey! Give that back!
Uh... Lelouch?
A cat...
A... stupid, little cat! You've gotta be kidding me!
There's no way I'm getting exposed by a lousy feline!
Huh?
That wasn't my fault... was it?
I didn't touch or rub anything. Hmm.
Yeah, that's right. I think a cat ran
off with something pretty important to him.
Important?
I'm not sure what exactly,
but I'm positive it was something of value to him.
Because... I've never heard my brother sound like that!
He was completely hysterical!
That's weird.
What could be so important to the guy?
A love letter?
An embarrassing photo?
Poetry he wrote?
Poetry?
Leave it to us! We'll get our hands on this
thing before Lelouch has a chance to blink!
Just you wait!
If I had those terrorists with me,
we could encircle the enemy! Maybe Kallen?
No... She's suspicious of me as it is!
Get it together.
So anyway, I told him to buzz off, he know?
Totally. And then?
C'mon, you can guess, can't you!
Hm? What's up with that cat?
Is that the mask Zero wears? Or am I crazy?
No way. Why would it be here?
You two saw it?!
Forget everything you've just seen!
Sure, no problem at all.
Good.
This is Milly Ashford, your student council president.
Cat hunt, everybody!
Cat hunt?
There's a cat loose on campus that needs to be rounded up!
Put everything on hold people.
Participating clubs'll get budget priority!
And whoever catches our feline
friend will get an extra special prize!
A big 'ole kiss from one of the members of the council!
Members of... Wait, like me?!?!
Exactly!
You've been hangin' the student council haven't ya!
Wouldn't mind a taste 'a those lips!
It's not gonna be like some lame
peck on the cheek though, is it?!
A kiss on the cheek would be fine with me!
Wait, we can choose where she plants it?!
Whoa. Yeah.
All right!
There's no way that's how I'm gonna get my first kiss!
What? From a member of the student council?
Does that include Lelouch?
Actually, I would prefer Milly.
Ugh. Could you get back in the closet please?
Hut-hut-hut!
We have the advantage in mobility!
Hurry, look for catnip!
Science will prevail!
And when you do catch that cat,
bring what it's carrying to me! To me! To meeee!
Milly! Stay out of this, will ya!
Offering people up as prizes.
That's why I hate Britannians.
I know, crazy, right?
Yeah, I can hardly believe it.
I was, like, floored when I heard it.
All I can say is sign me up!
Dammit! Why do I have to pretend like I'm sick and feeble?
Jeez, I'm sorry about that...
Shirley, why are you dressed like that?!
I didn't have time to change!
They're gonna make us kiss somebody. We've gotta hurry!
I'm with you!
Nunnally, is there anything about this cat that's special?
Hm...
I think that its leg must be hurt
because it's footsteps sounded off to me.
And uh... Oh! I almost forgot!
It meowed like this...
Meooowwww!
Meooowwwwwwwwww!
This school seems so laid back.
In spite of the fact that they're in mourning.
You suppose Sukzaku will be all right in here?
Never mind that. The university here...
Don't worry, I've made arrangements with them.
Hmm...
They still didn't have to kick poor Lancelot out though.
I know.
Even if they did say Elevens aren't acceptable.
'Kay! Let's go!
What happens if a member of the
student council catches the cat?
We don't get a prize do we?
Do we get a kiss? But of course.
Is that so?
Well, what are we waitin' around for then?
This is my day t'shine...
Hey! No speeding on campus!
Okay, we do this right and our lips will be safe.
Shirley, you cover the rear.
Wait a sec!
What's the matter?
Who would you wanna get a kiss from?
Is there anybody in particular?
Huh?
It wouldn't be Lelou, would it?
Just what would make you think that?
Oh, well... I guess... it's just...
Hey, that's...
Suzaku?
Lelouch?! You're looking for the cat too?
Up there...
Suzaku, wait!
Don't go up there!
But the student council president said to catch it!
Don't worry about it, I'll get the cat!
I was always more agile than you!
Remember when that little bird got loose?
Quit talkin' ancient history!
It was only seven years ago!
Oh, for Pete's sake.
He always was an exercise nut...
So someone's got it cornered, huh?!
Who's the lucky winner?!
Up there!
Suzaku?
Easy now. You don't have to be scared.
Suzaku! Come back!
It's all right. Leave this to me.
That's funny.
He never went along with the crowd like this.
Huh?
Lelouch!
Are you... okay?
Y-Yeah...
Is it possible... those two are?
Pretty calm for someone on the verge of death.
Yeah, right. I was just limp with fear.
Huh?
Hey, what's going on?
That transfer student just saved
Lelouch from a really close call.
Uh.
I think it's the same cat from the other day.
Huh.
You saved him! Thank you so much, Suzaku!
Yeah, way to go there, new guy!
That cat was carrying something, wasn't it?
Yeah, there was something on its head,
but I never really got a good look at it.
Guess it slipped off when I wasn't looking.
So where is Lelou?
He said he forgot something. Told me to go ahead.
That's it! The embarrassing secret that he's hiding!
Hm?
So that's it, Madame President?
Aww. After all this time, I
thought I had some dirt on you.
Yeah, he almost lost his cool for once.
So, uh, do you two know each other, then?
Yeah, but, he's an Eleven.
No, I just...
He's my friend.
Madame President,
would you permit him as a member of the student council?
Huh...?
The rules are clear.
All students are required to join a club.
Although...
Well, you are the vice president.
I s'pose I can't refuse.
Well then, I'd say that's the end of that.
Now c'mere you two, lend me an ear.
Nunnally?
There you go, the reward Miss Milly promised.
Since you both caught the cat,
you'll just have to settle for me.
Almost a real council member!
All right then!
Let's celebrate the catching of the cat!
Everything's on the new guy, naturally!
Oh, back off!
Hi there, I'm Shirley!
Pleasure to meet 'cha!
Oh, right, I'm Rivalz!
Milly Ashford. Student council president.
The pleasure is mine.
And now, his royal majesty,
the 98th emperor of the Holy Britannian Empire!
All men.. are not created equal...
Some are born swifter of foot. Some with greater beauty.
Some are born into poverty.
And others born sick and feeble.
Both in birth and in upbringing.
In sheer scope of ability, every
human is inheritantly different.
Yes,
that is why people discriminate against one another.
Which is why there is struggle, competition,
and the unfaltering march of progress.
Inequality...
...is not wrong. Equality is.
What of the EU, which made equality a right?
Rabble politics by a popularity contest!
The Chinese Federation with
its equal distribution of wealth?
A nation of lazy dullards...
But not our beloved Britannia.
We fight. We compete. Evolution is continuous.
Evolution. Such a pretty little word.
Britannia alone moves forward,
advancing steadily into the future.
Even the death of my son Clovis,
demonstrates Britannia's
unswerving commitment to progress.
We will fight on!
We shall struggle, compete, plunder, and dominate!
And in the end, the future shall be ours.
All hail Britannia.
All hail Britannia!
So... This is Lelouch's enemy. Well.
The word "hatred" is not strong enough...
If my father is the embodiment of Brittannia,
he must be detroyed!
And if Cornelia gets in my
way, she'll suffer the same fate!
You may not know it yet, but I have power!
So long as I possess Geass, I can go this alone.