[AKIHO]
Oh, wow. This is beautiful.
Everything is so elaborate.
So, have you seen that version?
[AKIHO]
No.
I do have a few pop-up
books about Alice,
but I've never read
this one before.
[SAKURA]
Yay, good!
Rika will be so
happy to hear that.
How is she?
[SAKURA] Great! She
wants to get together.
Oh, that's right.
I actually have a book to return
to her next time we meet up.
This girl, Rika, does
she like books, too?
[NAOKO]
Yes.
As much as she likes
reading, though,
I think she's more into music.
She's great at
playing the piano,
and you wouldn't believe
how many songs she knows!
And next, she mentioned learning
flute was also a possibility.
That sounds like her.
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
[TOMOYO]
I think she's also learning
how to play the harp, too.
Your friend must
be very talented.
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
I've actually been
thinking about
learning to play
an instrument, too.
Really? Which one?
The matryomin .
[AKIHO, SAKURA]
Hm?
Confused?
[AKIHO, SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
Have you ever heard
of matryoshka dolls?
Okay, well imagine one of
those with an antenna in it.
You just put your
hands up like this,
and then you move them
around like this, see?
Pretty cool, huh?
Oh, I get it. So it's sort
of related to the theremin.
Yes. In fact, they're actually
very similar instruments.
I've heard of a theremin before.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
[NAOKO]
With the matryomin ,
the outside can be
basically anything.
I think it would be
fun to make one.
[CHIHARU]
With what?
[NAOKO]
A kokeshi maybe?
[CHIHARU] As long as you don't
make it too scary looking.
[NAOKO laughs]
If it can literally...
[AKIHO]
Sakura, what's bothering you?
Oh, nothing. I'm fine, really.
You could make it look
like Akiho's charm.
A Momo bunny!
Great idea!
Or you could design a Kero one!
Uh. Yeah, I guess so.
[CHIHARU]
Speaking of making things.
Cooking class was kind
of weird yesterday.
I spent all that time making
a cake that looked like Maru
and it vanished!
[NAOKO] Maru's the name
of your dog, right?
[CHIHARU]
Mh-hm.
[TOMOYO] I love all the
pictures you show us.
It really is the cutest puppy!
Aw, thank you.
But we never found out what
happened to the decorations.
[NAOKO] Didn't you say you
hadn't used them all, though?
Was that before or
after you fell asleep?
Before, but then when we woke
up, everything had disappeared.
Yes, what a mystery.
[NAOKO]
Ah!
[SAKURA yelps]
What? Wait, did
you figure it out?
No, but I was thinking
this would be perfect to use
in the script I'm writing for
the Drama Club, you know?
[SAKURA grunts]
[AKIHO]
Uh, are you okay?
Look on the bright side,
at least the cakes we got
to remake turned out well.
Right, Akiho?
That's true.
Oh, Sakura, how did
your cake turn out?
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Uhh... Fine, I guess.
[SAKURA] After everything that
happened with the new card,
it didn't turn out as well
as I would've hoped.
[SAKURA] Here. I made
this during cooking class.
For me?
[SAKURA]
Um, yeah.
Is it okay to open it?
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Sure, go ahead.
[gasps]
[SYAORAN]
The design.
[SAKURA]
Originally, I had planned
to make your entire outfit.
But there weren't enough
supplies left over.
[SYAORAN]
Sakura.
Yeah?
Thank you.
[CHIHARU] Earth to Sakura.
Your face is all red.
I guess whoever you gave that
cake to must've really liked it.
Oh? Akiho's face is red, too.
[SAKURA] Well, lunch break
is almost over, so...
[AKIHO]
Oh. Here's the book back.
Thanks so much for
showing it to me.
You can hang on to it.
Rika said that she was
done with it, anyway.
Yeah, she wanted me
to give it you.
No, I couldn't.
[SAKURA]
She insisted!
Still though.
I'm positive it would make Rika
much happier if you kept it.
[CHIHARU]
Yeah, for sure.
What would be even
better is telling her
what you thought of the
book when you're done.
[TOMOYO]
Great idea!
Are you really sure
it's okay to keep it?
[ALL]
Mh-hm!
All right then.
Thank you so much!
I'll be sure to talk to
your friend about it later.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
[gasps]
[AKIHO]
Sakura!
Be careful! You
almost fell down.
Are you feeling okay?
Do you think you're coming
down with something?
Nuh-uh! I just spaced out
for a minute, that's all.
I was thinking about
what I would do
if I got called on
in math class.
I get nervous even
though I studied.
[AKIHO] Let's see,
this should go right here.
[AKIHO]
Kaito!
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Oh, no. Sakura gave me a book
and I was putting it up.
An Alice book?
Uh-huh. I love all books,
but in the end... I don't know.
The Alice one's are
special, right?
They are.
[KAITO]
Especially...
Alice in Clock Land .
Uh, Kaito?
I was thinking of making some
hot cocoa. Would you like some?
Sounds lovely.
[AKIHO] Why didn't you
call me in the library?
[KAITO]
I thought about it,
but then I suspected
you might be
too absorbed in your
books to hear it.
[KAITO]
I was also curious.
You were?
[KAITO]
When you came home from school,
well, you seemed a little down.
[gasps]
[AKIHO]
I'm sorry!
There is nothing
to apologize for.
I'm just worried, see.
Sakura seemed really out
of it at school today.
Is it possible she
might be taking ill?
[AKIHO] I asked, but
she said she was fine.
Right before that, she had
just suddenly spaced out.
Almost like her mind left
her body and wandered off.
[KAITO]
Akiho?
I heard...
...something. A clock?
Perhaps it was my pocket watch.
Not that. It sounded different.
Much bigger.
[stomach grumbles]
[AKIHO gasps]
It appears the clock in your
tummy thinks it's time to eat.
Why don't we have dinner
first, and then cocoa?
[AKIHO]
Uh, okay!
Akiho.
Kaito?
[KAITO] Are you happy that your
friend gave you that book?
Yes.
How wonderful. I hope you
become even better friends.
You and Sakura.
[SAKURA whines]
[TOMOYO]
Ah!
Beautiful! Simply beautiful!
It's been forever
since I've been able
to film you in costume!
Come on, give me a smile!
[chuckles nervously]
Check out my smile!
Ha-ha! Cheese!
It's dashing as usual, Kero.
Tell me somethin' I don't know.
[TOMOYO] Since you're here,
Li, why don't you join her?
Uhh... Like right now?
[KERO]
Still kinda hard to believe
you sensed a card
this late at night.
I mean, it sorta
brings back memories
of the good ol' days, you know?
Now that you mention it,
I do remember that.
In fact, this is where I
originally caught the Fly card.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
You guys, this is
practically the birthplace
of Cardcaptor Sakura!
Actually, when I really
stop to think about it,
you were pretty pushy
back when we first met.
You suddenly popped out
of that book, and...
Hidey-howdy-ho!
[SAKURA] After that, he just
kept on talking and talking.
And then Kero said: "Witness
the birth of the Cardcaptor!"
And the only reason the
cards were scattered
everywhere in the first
place is because
he fell asleep and was
like, "Stuff happens!"
What's really weird is
that I never even agreed
to any of this
Cardcaptor business.
[KERO] Hmm... Are you sure
that's what happened?
Yes, I'm sure!
I didn't know what to
do with the Fly card,
but I was desperate,
so I just jumped on.
Now that I think of it,
what would've happened
if I'd fallen off?
Aw, you didn't
fall off, slugger.
I never doubted your
skills for a second!
[SAKURA]
Only because I got lucky!
Well, even if you had fallen,
I woulda had your back.
[SAKURA] You got blown away
at the very start of the fight!
Wait, Kero, so what
would've happened
if Sakura had refused
to help you back then?
Would it have dissolved
the contract?
[KERO]
Nah!
That's not fair!
Well, when it comes to things
like magical contracts,
once it's been formed,
it can't be broken
unless something
really serious happens.
[TOMOYO] Wow, conditions
are pretty strict
even in magical contracts.
That's really not fair.
[SAKURA gasps]
[yells]
What is it?
Feels like a card!
[KERO]
That's hot!
[TOMOYO]
The heat is intense!
Let's hurry!
Kero, keep Tomoyo safe!
Right! Come on, over here!
[TOMOYO]
Okay!
Sakura.
Sit tight and don't
do anything reckless.
I don't wanna risk
you getting hurt.
Right, please be careful.
My magic also uses fire,
meaning anything I try
would probably just
make things worse.
Water, rain down and
extinguish the fire!
Aqua!
That's it! Give 'em
the ol' one two!
Now what?
Let me try.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
What's your idea?
[SYAORAN]
Here's the plan.
Use Flight's magic to get as
close to the bird as you can.
The moment it falters,
turn it into a card!
Right!
I need to get closer
to the fire bird.
Lend me your power!
[SAKURA]
Flight!
[inaudible]
[yells]
[SAKURA]
Oh, wow.
Do it now, Sakura!
Right!
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Secure!
[SAKURA]
This is...
"Blaze."
Oh, Syaoran! Tomoyo! Kero!
Great job! Are you okay, kiddo?
I'm fine!
The two of you were incredible!
I can't really take
credit for this one.
[SYAORAN]
Hm?
The wind magic you
used was so amazing!
Oh. Or was it a technique?
Whatever, as long as you
turned it into a card,
that's all that matters!
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
Still, if this was fire magic,
then that would mean,
this set of cards
has the wind, fire,
and water elements
just like the Sakura cards.
Maybe, but it feels like these
new cards are much stronger.
You saw how they were
blasting each other
with their "roars," yeah?
Totally, it was like one
of those cool movies
with giant fighting monsters!
But is it like a movie
if it actually happened?
Oh, that's true.
That Blaze card just got lucky.
If it'd been like a water
magic or somethin',
I woulda taken it
down a peg or two!
Roar! Like that.
Like you did with the Fly card?
Come on! That was forever
ago, why bring it back up?
I was kidding. I'm sure you
would've been a big help!
Calm down, Kero!
[KERO]
It's not fair!
You know my power
is weaker at night,
but you were all about
the cards comin' out then
because at least that way,
there aren't any cake monsters
tearin' up the school, or
weird trees walkin' around,
or whatever else
happens durin' the day!
Honestly, they're kinda tough
to deal with any time of day.
Well, no matter what
time of day it is,
I think you handle each
situation perfectly,
like a true Cardcaptor!
Yeah, I agree!
[SAKURA] It's too bad
the arch got burned,
but at least the fire
didn't spread anywhere.
[SYAORAN]
We'd better get you back home.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
You'll get in trouble
for sneaking out.
I live alone, so...
[SAKURA]
Don't worry, I have it covered.
No one will ever know.
Only if no one actually looks,
but sooner or later,
you're gonna get caught.
I used to sneak out
my window all the time
back in the old card
capturing days,
and it worked out fine.
I mean, sure, if you say so.
I have a bodyguard
waiting nearby.
You can use our van to change
into your regular clothes.
Once you're done changing, she
can drive you both back home.
It'll be as if you were never
gone in the first place.
Leave it to us.
[SAKURA, SYAORAN]
Thank you.
Uh. Hey, where are you going?
Toya?
It's pretty late,
she's probably asleep.
Uh!
Stop! What do you
think you're doing?
[TOYA]
This was her bright idea?
All that magic and she uses
a bag and a hat as a decoy.
[YUKITO]
Shame on you.
It's rude to go into a
girl's room uninvited.
[TOYA]
She's not in there.
The plushie thing's gone, too.
I don't like this.
[TOYA]
That was sudden.
But... I guess it's okay
since Dad's not home.
Try not to worry.
She's on her way back.
Are you sure?
[YUE]
Yes, I sense her.
Well, that's handy.
[YUE]
Sometimes I cannot sense her.
There are times when I'm
unable to trace the mark
of my master's power.
[TOYA]
What times?
There's not any sort of pattern.
Her power's gotten strong.
Even I'm starting to
sense it more often.
[YUE] Perhaps it's because
your power is returning.
What do you intend
to use that power for?
I won't say.
[YUE]
Why not?
Didn't I mention before that
you and Yuki are a lot alike?
[YUE]
Yes, though I disagree.
[TOYA]
No surprise there.
It's my power.
I'll be the one who decides
when and how I'll use it.
You're so easy to read.
How do you mean?
[TOYA]
When you're angry or upset,
you may try to hide it,
but it shows on your face.
Like that.
Yuki told me your
name, but, uh,
please don't be
mad at him, okay?
It seemed strange not
knowing your name,
especially since you've
been around for so long.
So I asked him.
[YUE]
It's not as if I can rebuke him.
Yeah, good point.
[TOYA] I'll do whatever I can
for my family. For Sakura.
No matter what happens.
I'm sure of that.
You always have been very loyal.
So just wait a little
bit longer, Yue.
[TOYA laughs]
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Sponsored by awesomeness,
it's another great episode
of "Leave It to Kero!"
where we will talk about yet
another adorable costume!
This exotic get-up combines
genie in a bottle pants,
various bijou accents,
a sash, wrist bangles,
and of course a flame-inspired
hair ornament!
As per usual, Tomoyo
never ceases to amaze
with her genius ideas, huh?
I bet ya could fry up
a ton of okonomiyaki
with that card's flames.
Maybe Sakura will let me
try it out sometime,
but for right now, buh-bye!
[SAKURA] I'm excited to
tag along with Yukito
and help him read to
children at the hospital.
I invited Akiho and
Syaoran to come as well.
It's gonna be so much fun!
Next time, "Sakura
and Akiho's Lullaby."
Say it with me: Release!