[TOYA]
Hey, I'm home.
[FUJITAKA]
Thank you. Yes, I appreciate it.
Right, of course.
Yes, I just got home myself.
What a nice surprise.
[FUJITAKA]
No, that's all right.
Yes. Oh. She collapsed?
And what about right now?
Is she conscious?
Uh-huh. I see. Yes.
So she's better, then?
Thank goodness!
Ah. That makes sense.
I appreciate it very much.
Right. Well, thank you again.
Have a good day.
[FUJITAKA sighs]
[TOYA]
Who collapsed? Sakura?
Uh-huh.
But they immediately had
her checked out by a doctor.
I'll go get her.
Someone'll be driving
her home soon.
She seems fine now.
Apparently, she laughed
it off and just told him
that she probably
didn't get enough sleep.
I wonder what kinda trouble
she got into this time.
[FUJITAKA]
Hm?
Nothing.
Where's she at?
Mom's grandpa's place?
[FUJITAKA]
Yes.
Masaki said he had two
things related to Nadeshiko
that he wanted to give Sakura.
But I think one of them may
be a little too big for her,
so I asked him to
hold off on that gift.
At least for now, at any rate.
Too big?
Yes, it's the house
she's currently visiting.
It was actually one
of Nadeshiko's
favorite secondary homes.
So he thought it would
be a nice gesture
if he gave it to Sakura.
She's a little young
for that, you know?
I do. And that's why I
asked him to hold onto it.
You want some tea?
[TOYA]
Sure.
[FUJITAKA]
Okay.
[TOYA]
I brought home some sweets.
[FUJITAKA]
Oh, thank you. Sounds good.
[TOYA]
How many would you like?
[FUJITAKA]
How many are Sakura's?
[TOYA]
Four.
[FUJITAKA]
Then, just two for me, please.
I hope you don't mind
if the tea is strong.
[TOYA] Does Great-grandpa
look like Mom at all?
[FUJITAKA sighs]
[FUJITAKA]
I'm not sure.
I've always thought they
had very similar eyes,
but Sonomi thinks that
Nadeshiko took more
after their grandmother.
Masaki said he'd love to
meet you, if you want.
Maybe. I'll think about it.
Aw, feeling a bit shy?
You're alike, you know.
You and Masaki, I mean.
Really?
[FUJITAKA]
Mh-hm. Yes.
It'd be interesting, I think,
to do a side by side comparison.
You two are related. I bet
there'd be a few similarities.
As Sakura gets older, she
looks more and more like Mom.
I agree.
She definitely has that
same infectious smile.
And then, that
mysterious quality.
[TOYA]
Huh?
[FUJITAKA] For instance,
Nadeshiko would talk to things
that weren't there, or try
to reach an understanding
with things that couldn't speak.
It was all beyond me.
Of course, that goes
for you, too.
And, um, none of that
seemed sorta crazy to you?
[FUJITAKA]
Not at all.
But since I didn't have
the ability to hear
or see those things, I did
sometimes feel left out.
It's the same with Sakura.
I'm unable to understand
what's happening with her.
[gasps]
So you know what's
going on with her?
Not as much as I'd like.
I know that it's
something I can't fix,
and that whatever
the trouble is,
it's been happening on and off
since she was in
the fourth grade.
At least, I suspect as much.
[TOYA]
You really are amazing, Dad.
Huh? How so?
For starters,
it's your attitude.
You know something's
up with Sakura,
but you just leave her be.
[FUJITAKA] Of course.
It is Sakura, after all.
She's a smart girl.
And, well, I just have
faith in her abilities.
Besides, if something
were to happen,
she has a wonderful big
brother to back her up.
You'd probably be more
help to her than I would.
These are so beautiful. I almost
can't bear to eat them.
I know, right?
But I can bring home more
from my work anytime, so.
Thanks, Toya.
Just don't work too hard.
[MASAKI] You should try
to get some more rest.
No, I'm okay.
Besides, the doctor said there
was nothing wrong with me.
I know, but--
[SAKURA]
Oh, yeah.
Didn't you say
there was something
that you wanted to give me?
[MASAKI] Very well. Could you
please wait here a moment?
Sure.
[SYAORAN]
Try not to force yourself.
[SAKURA]
It's fine.
I'm sorry. I hope I didn't
cause you any sort of trouble.
Don't worry about it.
Still though, if you're dizzy,
or if you're in any kinda pain,
I want you to
tell me right away.
No matter how small it is, 'kay?
[SAKURA]
The same goes for you.
[SAKURA] If something's hurting
you, then I want you to tell me.
[MASAKI]
Thank you for waiting.
I brought it.
[MASAKI]
Here you go.
Open it up.
[SAKURA]
A key.
Yes, for some reason Nadeshiko
cherished that particular item
when she was just a small girl.
It was a present,
one that my wife and I found
when we were in England.
[SYAORAN]
England?
But that's where
Hiiragizawa is, and...
Yes. Hi. Yuna D. Kaito.
[SYAORAN]
What are you talking about?
[ERIOL] Here in England,
there's a magic association
that grants its highest-ranked
magic users the title of "D."
[SYAORAN]
Yuna D. Kaito.
[KERO] So Akiho's butler might
actually be a magician.
[ERIOL] Yes, and the
house they're living in,
well, it was demolished.
Afterwards, they built
a theme park there.
[KERO]
Hm? A theme park?
So why turn it back into the
same ol' house as before?
[ERIOL]
Ah.
I believe because that
location is perfect
for storing magical objects.
It has the ideal shape.
[KERO] So a magician
changed it back then.
[ERIOL]
Most likely.
What about that
magic association?
[ERIOL]
I reached out to them.
Their response was
rather ambiguous.
Though, I did learn one thing.
Which was?
This Yuna D. Kaito was
excommunicated last year.
From the association? No way.
All you need is strong magic
and to follow some basic
rules and you're good!
Other than that,
you can pretty much do whatever
the heck you feel like!
What'd he do to get
excommunicated?
[ERIOL]
I didn't know.
So I looked into it
via another source.
I asked the head of
the Li family for help.
[KERO]
The brat's mom, huh?
[YUE]
What did you learn?
[ERIOL]
He was excommunicated
because he lost
a powerful relic,
which was never supposed to
be removed from the association.
[KERO]
What? Are you serious?
Is he some kinda klutz?
[ERIOL] That's what they
wrote in the records.
But the rumors suggest that he
simply took the item and left.
[KERO] Would they even allow
somethin' like that?
[ERIOL]
No, obviously not.
However, their hands
are tied. They're stuck.
[YUE]
Why?
Well, because no one's
able to defeat him.
He has the "D" title, after all.
The association was
hiding that relic.
Which means it was
probably taboo.
They're scared of his
power and the relic.
That's why there's nothing they
can do, because of his strength.
Just what can the relic do?
Is it strong?
If you're asking whether
it's more powerful than I am,
yes, it is.
The Li family
attempted to discover
the exact power it
holds, but failed.
[KERO] That's pretty serious if
even they couldn't find out.
[YUE]
And our master, what of her?
[ERIOL]
Sakura doesn't rely on objects
that someone else has made.
Nor is she even aware
when she creates the cards
that embody her magic.
In other words, she has created
her own magical items.
Ah, like when she had the
power to see the past,
that was just her.
She didn't know
she was doin' it.
Why not say something sooner?
[ERIOL]
Sakura's power is strong,
but it's also very chaotic.
She is unable to control
it most of the time.
Additionally, I still
don't have the faintest idea
what Yuna D. Kaito
wants from her.
But if I had to hazard a guess,
I would say he's after
Sakura's new cards.
[KERO] Right, well I get
not tellin' her, then,
but why didn't you
tell me n' Yue?
Because the worry would've
shown on your face,
and then she'd know
something was wrong.
[KERO]
What?
Whatever, I have an
awesome poker face.
[ERIOL]
Yes, you do.
Yue, however, does not.
What now?
Yeah. That's true.
He's terrible whenever
it concerns Sakura.
Shut up.
Whoa, what the--?
Eriol!
Can't you fight back?
We have to discern where
the attacker is first.
[ERIOL]
You needn't do anything.
The assailant is targeting me.
Duh, that's why we
gotta help you!
[ERIOL]
Don't worry.
I'll do everything
I can from here.
Watch over Sakura.
And Syaoran Li.
Please help them both.
[KERO]
Eriol!
[ERIOL] This is a
powerful enemy, Sakura.
No, Eriol!
The connection is lost.
[KERO]
Then, I'll just call him back!
[KERO yells]
No dice. Dumb phone
won't even ring!
I cannot reach him, either.
[KERO]
Spinny! I'll try him!
No good.
Same with Ruby Moon.
[KERO]
What's goin' on?
It seems non-magical
communication
has been severed as well.
[KAITO] I expected no less
of Mr. Eriol Hiiragizawa.
I've always wondered
why they say
he is one of the most
powerful living magicians,
and now I know.
This watch, which has
remained intact all this time,
has finally broken.
Still, I will obtain
these new cards.
[KAITO] Then I can use the
relic from the association,
and activate that magic spell.
Kaito, please.
I understand using any means
necessary to achieve your goal.
Just be careful
not to lose sight
of what is most important
to you, Yuna D. Kaito.
[MASAKI] Make sure you go to bed
as soon as you get home, okay?
[SAKURA] I will. I'm really
sorry if I worried you.
I apologize for calling
you here so suddenly.
But I appreciate you coming
on such short notice.
I hope you'll both
come visit again.
Okay. Definitely!
[MASAKI]
Huh?
See ya! I'll take
care of the key!
What is it?
Uh, do I have something
on my face?
[SAKURA]
Mh-mh.
I was just thinking
that the Syaoran I see
and the Syaoran that you see
must be completely
different from each other.
It's like, I can see you
in person, right?
But you can't do that if
you wanna look at yourself.
You have to use a
mirror or something.
Yeah, that's true.
[SAKURA]
The same goes for me.
Out of everyone, I'm the one
who understands
myself the least.
Maybe that's why they're
all worried about me.
I wish I had a magic mirror.
So I could see what
everyone else does.
If I could see the
real me like they do,
I'd be able to keep everybody
from worrying so much.
Sakura.
[DRIVER A] Excuse me,
miss, but we've arrived.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
[SAKURA, SYAORAN]
Thank you for the ride.
Okay, you should go
and get some rest.
I'll try. See you
at school tomorrow.
[SAKURA]
Hm?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Thanks again! Bye.
[SAKURA]
My house, but--
I don't get it.
[gasps]
Sakura?
[SAKURA]
It's backwards!
My house is turned
around backwards!
Is this--?
It must be a card.
It's okay, no one's
around right now.
Release!
[SAKURA]
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Secure!
[SAKURA]
It says...
"Mirror."
The Sakura Cards had
a Mirror one, too.
And look. The picture
is sorta similar.
[SYAORAN] She's the one creating
the cards in the first place,
so it makes sense the
illustrations would be the same.
We literally just spoke about
a magical mirror in the car,
and then she made a
card that relates to it.
[SAKURA]
Hey, Syaoran?
[SYAORAN]
What's up?
Mind if I try it?
[SAKURA]
Flight!
Would you like to help
me out for a little bit?
[SAKURA]
Stay right there.
Reflect the card's magic
so that I can double its power!
[SAKURA]
Mirror!
It worked!
Guess I'll use this one.
You ready?
[SYAORAN]
Huh?
Whoa!
[SAKURA]
Uh! Syaoran!
[yells]
Thanks a lot.
Since it's a mirror,
I thought it might be able
to reflect magic, too.
I can't believe
it actually worked!
[SYAORAN]
Of course it worked.
Your magic is just
that powerful.
Even though that's not
something you want.
[SYAORAN] My mother and
Hiiragizawa said the same thing.
[SYAORAN]
When a power is that strong,
it will only bring
unhappiness to its owner.
[SAKURA]
Syaoran?
[SYAORAN] Sakura, I won't
let you be unhappy.
I promise.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Are you folks ready for this?
Well, hang on 'cause
in this cool-tastic episode
of "Leave It to Kero,"
we're gonna list
the collection of Clear
Cards we've captured!
Gale, Siege, Aqua, Reflect,
Action, Gravitation,
Record, Flight, Lucid,
Spiral, Snooze, Labyrinth,
Reversal, Hail, Mirage, Swing,
Struggle, Appear, Blaze, Mirror!
Exactly 20 altogether!
Man, Sakura's really good at
collectin' things, isn't she?
Sometimes she gets two
cards back-to-back!
I'm tired just thinkin' about
it, so I guess I'll say buh-bye!
[SAKURA]
Kero and I were in my room
getting ready for bed,
but suddenly,
I noticed the robed
person from my dreams
right outside of my window!
Next time, "Sakura's
Clear Cards."
Say it with me: Release!