[SAKURA] "Then, you will place
it through the door and say,
'I would like to buy mittens
for this hand, please.
Make sure you mind
your manners, too.
And no matter what,
do not offer your paw.'
The mother fox repeated herself
so he would remember,
'You are not to show
anyone your paw.'
'But why not?' the little
fox asked his mother.
'Because if the humans
were to find out
they're actually
speaking to a fox,
they won't want to sell
you mittens anymore.
In fact, they'll chase
you and try to catch you,
so they can put you in a cage.'"
[SAKURA]
How was that?
No stuttering, and I
could hear every word.
Sounded good to me!
You mean it?
Oh, yeah!
I can tell that gettin' up early
every morning to practice
is really payin' off for ya.
[SAKURA] It was so nice of Rika
to lend me this picture book.
I just hope I can read it well.
[KERO]
You don't need to worry.
Yukibunny will be
there as well, right?
He will!
We'll be going to visit
one of the hospitals
where he volunteers
all the time.
Will it be just you two?
[SAKURA]
Yeah, that was the plan.
[KERO]
Hm?
However, I think I'll
invite some more.
You want me to read
to people? Out loud?
It's easy. Have you
ever done that?
No, I never have.
The books have pictures,
and, let's see.
C'est comme une
histoire, Akiho.
Les livres sont
pour les enfants.
Make sense?
[AKIHO]
Ah, je comprends .
Are you going to be reading?
I am!
We'll be going to the pediatrics
ward at the hospital this time.
That's amazing, Sakura!
It's not that big a deal.
Um, you wanna join me?
[AKIHO]
Huh?
You too, Syaoran!
We could do it together,
wouldn't that be nice?
Then we'd be able to act out
all the different parts!
[AKIHO]
I don't know.
I'm just not that
confident in my reading.
Don't worry,
you'll be just fine.
When you read
Ten Nights of Dreams
that time in Japanese class,
it sounded lovely.
[SYAORAN]
Well, I can't do it.
I was awful in our
elementary school plays.
I will say,
your portrayal of the
princess was rather unique,
but when you played that prince,
you were practically perfect!
You really were.
[SYAORAN]
How do you know?
I still don't think I can do it.
[SAKURA]
Huh? Hmm...
Play the piano!
You can play an accompaniment
to the story, can't you?
Meh. Daidouji's way
better at piano than me.
Sorry! I'll be
shooting the video!
His face just got all red.
Obviously because
Sakura's attack managed
to reduce his HP down to zero.
Fine! I'll do it!
I'll do the music.
[gasps]
Thank you so much!
Welcome.
So, Akiho?
Um, well, if you're certain
I won't be in your way.
You won't! Thank you!
Yeah. You're welcome?
Aw, and now Akiho's
HP also dropped
all the way down to zero!
[WEI]
How nice, sir.
So you'll be playing
the accompaniment.
[SYAORAN] I guess so.
It just kinda happened.
[WEI]
What sort of story is it?
The book's about a fox
that goes to buy some mittens.
Why would a fox do that?
[SYAORAN]
Because he's cold?
[WEI] Does the fox
not have his own fur?
[SYAORAN] Yes, but it's
still cold in winter.
[WEI] Does the story
have a happy ending?
[SYAORAN]
Yeah, seems like it.
[WEI] Then, I believe I know
the perfect score to play.
Although, I will need
a little bit of time
to get it prepared for you.
Check your email in about
half an hour, all right?
[SYAORAN]
Great, thanks.
[WEI clears throat]
[WEI] Other than that,
is everything going well?
I've noticed you haven't been
calling me terribly often.
[SYAORAN] Meiling filled
you in, didn't she?
[WEI]
Yes, she did.
She told me how much she
enjoyed being in Japan again,
as well as how delighted she was
to be able to see her friends.
She also told me
something very interesting.
It seems you have made
a rather serious decision.
[WEI] Listen, I'm aware that
from the day you came home
until the day you
returned to Japan,
your mother took
care to train you.
And it was truly rigorous
training, at that.
Also, I'm aware of how
strong you've now become.
Yet, I am still
worried about you.
After all, my only wish
is to protect you, sir.
No matter what happens.
[SYAORAN]
I know. Thank you.
Do me a favor, please.
Will you turn on video mode
so I can see your face?
[SYAORAN]
For my sisters, right?
I know you're there!
Ladies, look.
I know you care, but
no more food pictures.
Those and your video messages
take up too much space.
[FUUTIE]
Doesn't seeing delicious food
and your beautiful sisters
make you happy, though?
Not really.
[SISTERS]
What?!
[SISTERS shouting]
[SYAORAN] Wei, I'll be
waiting for that piano score.
[WEI]
Very good, sir.
So whaddaya say?
Should we message him
an even longer video?
[OTHERS]
Oh, yeah!
[ALL chattering]
[WEI]
You are a very kind person,
which is exactly why
I worry about you.
[AKIHO]
"The little fox did his best
to stay beneath
his mother's belly
as they walked and walked.
Blinking his large round eyes,
he tried to see as much
of the forest as he could
as they continued their journey.
Eventually, their pass"...?
[KAITO] Do you think it
might say, "their path"?
Yes, that's it.
What's that?
[AKIHO]
I'm writing down the parts
where I need to be more careful
and the ones I keep messing up.
Why are you not writing these
notes down in the book?
No, I can't do that.
I don't wanna ruin it!
The author worked
hard to make this.
Not to mention the artist who
drew all the pretty pictures.
Wow, you genuinely are a big
fan of books, aren't you?
More like lover.
Uh!
Book... lover.
[KAITO]
I assume all this practice
must be making you thirsty.
[MOMO]
You didn't need to freak out
just for being honest, Akiho.
[KAITO
How about some tea?
[AKIHO]
Um, yes, please.
Is it black tea
with honey today?
[KAITO] Yes. Appropriate since
honey is good for the throat.
[KAITO]
And chocolates, naturally.
Thanks.
Goodness, this seems
like an awful lot
for only the two of us.
[KAITO]
Don't worry.
I have a feeling it
will be exactly enough.
Huh?
[MOMO] Just enough to
fill my beautiful body.
[YUKITO] "Of course, there was
quite a bit on Giovanni's mind.
Without thinking, he quietly
turned from the professor.
He had to hurry home now,
for he needed to bring back
some milk for his mother.
And he wanted to tell her his
father would be back very soon.
So he ran along the river bank
toward town as fast as he could.
The end."
[KIDS gasping]
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
[GIRL A]
That was really great.
Where's Heaven?
Well, thank you.
He is good.
So good.
[AKIHO]
Yukito was unbelievable.
I know, right? I think
I'm too nervous to do this!
Yeah. I get that.
I'm anxious, too!
[SYAORAN]
You'll be fine.
You both practiced a
ton, so you're ready.
Thank you.
We're ready.
All right. Put these on.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[music plays]
[clapping]
"The winter was cold.
It took the animals of
the forest by surprise,
including a little fox who
lived with his mother.
One morning, the little fox
decided to go exploring"...
[KERO]
Hm?
I had a feeling you'd have
costumes ready for them.
[TOMOYO] Well, they're
very simple ones.
[KERO] Unfortunately,
he refused to wear his.
He had to play
the piano, though,
so I gave up on him, this time.
Guess I'll let him
be comfortable.
--Uhh, yeah.
--[TOMOYO chuckles]
"The mother fox became worried.
She didn't want her sweet
baby to develop frostbite.
She decided to go into town
and buy woolen mittens
to fit his paws.
Surely that would keep her son
warm during the long winter.
Then, the dark of night came,
wrapping forest and
field in its shadow.
Darkness spread, covering the
earth like a great blanket,
but no matter how
hard the night tried,
the snow was such a bright white
that it shone through
the shadows.
After some time,
their path brought them
within view of a
single bright light.
When the little fox saw it,
he became very excited and
frightened all at the same time.
'Mother, look how low
that star has fallen,'
the little fox exclaimed."
[SAKURA] "'No, my dear, that is
not a star,' his mother said
as she felt what seemed to be
her feet freezing in place.
'What you're looking at is
the light of the town.'
Seeing that light suddenly
reminded the mother fox
of when she and her friend
had gone into town
and had an experience that can
only be described as terrible.
The mother fox had pleaded
with her friend to stop,
but the friend ignored her
because they were determined
to steal a duck from one
of the farmhouses.
The farmer spotted both of them,
and, enraged, he gave chase.
So they fled, barely
escaping with their lives."
"Tragically, she
was too scared to go.
But he still needed mittens,
so the little fox would have to
go into town all by himself."
"'My son. I want you to
hold out one paw.'"
[AKIHO] "The mother fox
then did something amazing.
She held one of her sons tiny
paws in her own for a time,
and using some unseen force,
turned it into an adorable
human child's hand."
No way!
[YUKITO chuckles]
That is amazing.
"The little fox
had a human hand.
'Listen to me, son.
When you go into the town,
you will see many,
many human homes.
I want you to look for
one particular house
that has a sign hanging in front
with a rounded hat on it.
When you find that house,
knock on the door and
then say, 'Hello!'
Make sure you're loud enough
for someone to hear you.
After you do that,
a human will open the door
a tiny bit from the inside.
You must only use the
human hand, all right?
Then, you will place
it through the door
and say, 'I would like to buy
mittens for this hand, please.'
Make sure you mind
your manners, too.
And no matter what,
do not offer your paw.'
The mother fox repeated
herself so he would remember.
'You are not to show
anyone your paw.'"
[AKIHO] "He saw signs with
bicycles, with glasses,
and many other unusual
looking items on them.
Some were newly drawn with
what looked like fresh paint,
while others looked weathered
and were peeling
like an old wall.
However, he had no idea what
any of the signs meant,
as the little fox had
never been to town before.
Finally, he found the hat shop.
He saw a sign hanging
with the large, black,
rounded silk hat
exactly as his mother
had described to him
earlier that day.
He only saw the sign
because it had been
illuminated by a blue light.
The little fox was nervous,
but he knocked on the door
just as his mother had
instructed him to do.
'Hello!' the little
fox said loudly.
He heard the sound of movement
come from inside the house.
The door opened
just a few inches."
[SAKURA] "Then, a ribbon of
bright light stretched out
over the white snow on the road.
The little fox was so startled
by the brightness of the light
that he placed his paw
through the door
instead of the human hand.
He did exactly what his mother
told him he mustn't do!
But it was too late, he already
showed the humans his paw!"
[BOY B]
No! He can't do that!
Yeah! That can't be good!
He's gonna get chased,
just like the other foxes!
[GIRL B]
Will he get caught?
Oh, boy.
[KIDS chattering]
[AKIHO]
Um, what should we do?
[SAKURA]
Uh.
[AKIHO] "'Please give me mittens
that fit this hand.'"
[SAKURA] "The hat maker
thought, 'What's this, now?
What a strange request!
This is a fox's paw.
Why in the world would a fox
be asking me for some mittens?
How is he planning to
pay for these mittens?
With silly old leaves?'
'You'll have to give me money
before I can give you
mittens,' the hat maker said.
The little fox had been
holding two silver coins,
and he obediently passed
them over to the hat maker.
Holding each coin between
a thumb and forefinger,
the hat maker tapped
them together.
When he did, they made
a fine clinking noise,
so he knew they were real coins
and not just silly old leaves.
Since he'd been paid,
the hat maker took a pair
of children's woolen
mittens from a shelf
and handed them
to the little fox.
The little fox thanked
the hat maker
and then turned back
toward the way he'd come."
[AKIHO] "'How funny!
Mom told me humans were scary.
That didn't scare me
at all, though!
The hat maker saw my paw, but he
didn't do anything bad to me!'"
[SAKURA]
"the little fox thought.
Then, as he passed
beneath a window,
he heard a human's
voice from inside.
It was such a gentle
and beautiful voice.
In fact, it was one of
the most calming voices
he'd ever heard."
♪ "'Go to sleep, go to sleep, ♪
♪ rest your head on
Mother's breast, my dear. ♪
♪ Go to sleep, go to sleep, ♪
♪ rest in Mother's
loving arms.'" ♪
[SAKURA]
"As he listened to her song,
the little fox knew
without a doubt
that the voice belonged
to a human mother.
His own mother sang in a
similar sweet and gentle voice
when she rocked him
to sleep, as well.
Mothers have an instinct about
these things, after all.
Hearing the lovely song
made the little fox
start to miss his own mother,
so he decided he better
run as fast as he could
back to where his mother
was waiting for him."
[AKIHO] "As the mother fox
waited for her son to return,
she became so worried she
started trembling with fear.
'What could be taking him
so long?' she wondered.
When he finally arrived, she
held him to her warm chest
and felt like weeping with joy."
[SAKURA]
"The two foxes then returned
to their home in the forest.
The reflection of the
moonlight made their coats
shine like silver,
while thin, cobalt shadows
stretched away from
their running feet."
[AKIHO] "'Humans aren't
scary at all, Mother!'"
[SAKURA]
"'Why do you say that?'"
[AKIHO]
"'Well, I put my real paw
through the door by mistake.
But the hat maker
didn't try and catch me.
He just asked me for money,
and after I paid him,
he gave me these
lovely mittens.'"
[SAKURA]
"And with that,
the little fox clapped his warm,
woolen-mittened paws together.
Shocked, his mother
gasped, 'Oh, my!
I'm so glad he was kind to you,
but I wish you would've
been more careful.'
And then she murmured, 'I wonder
if I've been wrong about them.
Maybe, humans are
good after all.'"
[applause]
[BOY B]
The fox got his mittens!
[GIRL C]
That hat maker was so cool!
You're really good at music!
Can you play a song from TV?
The way you sang
was super pretty!
Thank you. I'm
glad you liked it.
Why is your voice so shaky?
[BOY B] Are you going to
come read to us again?
I'm not sure. What do
you think, Sakura?
I think we probably should!
Yeah.
[KERO] You really did an
awesome job today, ya know?
Aw, thank you.
I kinda got mixed up in
the middle, but it was fun.
Next time, though, I'd
rather be in the audience.
If ya wanna see how
everything looked,
Tomoyo got it all on video.
[SAKURA]
Release!
Record!
[SAKURA]
I used it before we started.
[KERO]
How'd I miss that?
Gather what you've
recorded and show me!
[BOTH gasp]
Look, it's Tomoyo!
[KERO chuckles]
[KERO]
That means I'll be there, too!
Wait a sec, who's that old guy?
Wait. Where's Akiho?
No Syaoran, either.
[SAKURA]
None of them are here.
[SAKURA] Hold on.
This isn't today's reading.
I guess I did it wrong, then.
[clicking]
[SAKURA]
Hm?
What are you doing?
[KERO]
I just got an email from Yue.
He said he's got a ton of
sweets that expire today.
So he's gonna let
me have 'em all!
I gotta go there, now!
What? Like right now?
It's kinda late!
[KERO]
Uh, expiration date!
[SAKURA] Yeah, I'm pretty
sure you'd be okay
even if they were a whole week
past their expiration date.
Ya got me there.
[YUE]
Is this it?
[KERO]
Yeah.
These were in the
recording Sakura played
with the Record card.
The uniforms the
nurses are wearing
haven't been used in 30 years.
They certainly don't
match the ones
they had on at today's reading.
Which means...
A different time. The card
recorded footage from the past.
Indeed.
Of course, Sakura doesn't
appear to have any idea.
There aren't many
magicians powerful enough
to show the past.
I have only met a few.
Clow is one.
And there are three others.
She inherited her cards
from a descendant of Clow.
She then transformed
the cards into her own.
And yet, she's still...
[KERO] I was aware her magic
had been getting stronger,
but I didn't expect this.
Sakura's magic has
grown significantly.
Her power is immense.
We should contact Eriol.
[YUE]
Yes, no matter what it takes.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
It's "Leave it to Kero" time,
and today, we're gonna introduce
Akiho's adorable stuffed
bunny friend, Momo!
Her blue muffler adds a pop
of color to her white body,
and she wears a very fancy
accessory on her left ear.
And doesn't that beauty
mark give her character?
Now, I thought she seemed
like a sophisticated plushie,
but low and behold,
this bunny is alive!
Yes, the full cast
is here, people,
and I can't wait to see
what happens next.
I'm so excited,
I'm getting hungry.
Can someone bring me
homemade chocolates?
Buh-bye!
[SAKURA]
Syaoran and I are going to visit
my great-grandfather
at his villa.
I wonder what he
wants to give me.
Next time, "Sakura,
Rainbows, and Grandpa."
Say it with me: Release!