Oh. All done with
your bath, Sakura?
[SAKURA]
Yeah. It felt really great.
You should've come in with me.
Sorry, but I couldn't
put this down
now that I'm so close
to finishing it.
What? You mean it
was the other guy?
I don't understand!
How could he even do that?
Really? He went through the
crack that was in the ceiling?
There's no way!
That's just crazy!
Nobody could get through there!
Do you know how flexible
he would have to be?
I don't buy it for a second!
You were so sure you
knew who it was, too.
Guessed wrong, huh? Sorry.
No! Not yet. There could
till be a twist coming.
[gasps]
No way! It's over!
That's just ridiculous!
No one's that flexible.
No one, I tell you!
[SAKURA] You're really
upset about this, huh?
[KERO]
Well, yeah.
Spinny's the one who told me
to read it in the first place,
and then, two-thirds
of the way through,
the author challenged
readers to solve the mystery.
So we sent each other our
guesses on who the culprit was.
And you thought the
wrong person did it.
What about Spinel?
[KERO]
Hmph.
He was right, huh?
It was a fluke! He got lucky!
Next time, we're gonna read
about something I know.
Yeah, like trains, maybe.
Really? I didn't realize
you were a train expert.
Well, yeah!
Going on trips and eating
yummy food is my specialty!
I still don't see what that has
to do with solving mysteries.
[phone ringing]
Hey! What's up, Rika?
[RIKA]
Hi, how are you?
Fine, thank you.
[RIKA] I was calling about the
flower-viewing party tomorrow.
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm. I saw your message.
[RIKA] Sorry I can't make it.
[SAKURA] It's okay. You said
you have a school event, right?
[RIKA]
Yeah, that's right.
It's too bad they
scheduled it on the weekend.
[RIKA]
At least it's in the afternoon,
so I can still sleep in.
I'm sad I can't see
you all, though.
So am I.
And I'm really sorry that
I couldn't schedule it
for a day when you're free.
[RIKA] Don't worry about it.
There'll be others, right?
Oh!
I heard you and Chiharu were in
the Cheerleading Club
together again.
Yeah, it's great!
[RIKA] Make sure to send
some videos to me, okay?
Yep! And you send
some to me, too.
[RIKA] I will. Well,
I'll talk to you soon.
Sure. See ya!
One of your friends?
Yeah. It was Rika.
Oh, she's the one who went
to a different middle school.
That's right.
It hasn't been very long, but
she already sounds different:
So much calmer and more mature.
And she looked prettier than
ever in the picture she sent
of her new school uniform.
So she's the exact
opposite of you, huh?
[SAKURA, KERO laughing]
I may not be like Rika,
but I think I've grown
up at least a little
since middle school started!
[KERO] You kick off your blanket
and sleep hugging your pillow.
That doesn't look
exactly grown-up to me.
That's not nice!
See? A grown-up wouldn't
get mad about that, either.
Yeah?
If that's how you feel,
maybe I won't save you
anything from lunch tomorrow.
[screams]
[KERO]
I'm sorry, Sakura. Forgive me!
The mini Hamburg
steaks are all done.
Awesome, thank you!
Great day for the party,
huh? Nice weather.
I know!
The forecast said it
was gonna be sunny,
but I was still kinda nervous.
It's clearly a reward
for my good behavior.
Ah!
Huh? Ugh, bonito?
Salmon's better.
Then why don't you
go make your own?
We still have plenty
of rice left.
It's too tough. Next time
don't squeeze the rice so hard.
All you ever do is complain!
Think I can have
some of those sides?
Sure, there's extra.
Do you need to take lunch?
[TOYA]
Mh-hm.
My job today doesn't provide
one, so that'd be great.
You can take one
for Yukito, too.
I'll make the rice balls for it.
Are rice balls the only thing
you can make, monster?
No, I made the rolled
omelets, too.
And I am not a monster!
You take that back!
--I mean it, you big meanie!
--Hey, it's me.
[SAKURA]
Quit calling me a monster!
Sakura's making me lunch.
For you, too. Sound good?
No. Dad's helping her.
It should be safe enough.
Huh? What's that
supposed to mean?
[TOYA]
Here.
He wants to talk to you.
Hi, Yukito.
[YUKITO] Hey, Sakura.
I hear you're making lunch.
[SAKURA]
Yeah, I am!
You don't mind making mine, too?
[SAKURA]
Nope!
You're sure there's enough?
[SAKURA] If there's not,
I'll just put less in Toya's.
[YUKITO laughs]
[YUKITO] Well, I'll take you
up on it, then. I can't wait.
[SAKURA]
Great! Have a good day at work.
Thanks, I will.
Okay, I'll give the
phone back to Toya now.
Dad, Yuki wants me to
tell you thanks, too.
Tell him he's welcome and
to come visit us again soon.
You hear that?
Yeah. See ya then.
Let's do this!
I was wondering.
[TOYA]
What?
Have you noticed
whether Yukito's
been eating a lot lately?
Not as much as he used to when
you were in elementary school.
But he still eats a lot,
considering his size.
His appetite hasn't been
bigger recently? Really?
Y-You know. It's spring, right?
The warmer weather
and the sunshine,
that makes some people hungrier.
Not Yuki, I guess.
Okay.
[SAKURA]
He's always eaten a lot,
but especially when he needed to
make up for his dwindling power.
If he's not doing that now,
I hope it doesn't mean Yukito
and Yue are having problems
because of the new cards
that have been showing up.
[FUJITAKA]
Hey, Sakura.
Bunnies or octopuses
for the wieners?
What do you think?
Bunnies would be great!
I'll do them with you, okay?
Sounds good.
Here. Be careful with
the knife, though.
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm!
[FUJITAKA] Nice job. You've
gotten very good at that.
Really?
Yep, really.
Now, for the vegetables.
You prefer them grilled, right?
And you want squash?
That's right.
Also, corn with butter.
[SAKURA]
I'm heading out!
[KERO] Have fun out there,
and be careful!
Now then...
[yells]
Flower-viewing for them,
TV-viewing for me!
I'm so glad it's sunny!
Tomoyo!
[TOMOYO]
Hello, Sakura.
Good thing it's nice out today.
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm!
Poor Rika. I wish
she could've come.
Me too.
Hey, wait. I know, the movie!
You mean the one we're
planning to go see
with Chiharu and Naoko?
Why don't I invite Rika, too?
Sure, if it will fit
into her schedule.
Okay!
[TOMOYO]
So how did your lunch turn out?
Good, I think. Dad and I
actually made it together.
The rolled omelets came
out really well this time.
Great! I can't wait to try them.
I made rice balls, too,
but Toya was being a
big jerk like always
and told me that I
squeezed them too much.
Plus, he kept stealing bites,
and complaining
about the filling.
Huh?
Hey, is something the matter?
[SAKURA]
Mh-mm.
I'm fine. Let's go.
Are they here yet?
Do you see anybody?
[CHIHARU]
Sakura, hey!
[SAKURA]
There they are!
Have you been waiting
a long time?
No, don't worry. You weren't
late. We're just early.
You can put your shoes there
with ours if you want to.
We'll do that. Thank you.
Thanks for inviting me.
This park is beautiful.
I'm so glad you're getting
to see the flowers.
Li's not here?
He sent a text saying he was
gonna be a little bit late.
Hey, try this.
There's enough for
everybody to have some.
Who doesn't like fresh
lemonade, right?
[BOTH gasp]
Here.
Thank you.
It looks wonderful.
Okay, now that Sakura
and Tomoyo are here,
let's all have a toast!
Yeah. I prepared a
speech for the occasion.
Yay, cheers!
[GIRLS]
Cheers!
It's so good!
Yes, delicious!
Good, I'm glad.
Should we wait to eat
until Li gets here?
Nah, he said to
start without him.
Yeah, he would probably feel bad
if he thought he
had made us wait.
We can just eat really slowly.
That sounds good.
Right, let's get started.
Here.
Great, thanks.
So Yamazaki took care of lunch
for the both of you today?
Uh-huh. Since I was the one
in charge of snacks and drinks.
Oh, do you enjoy
cooking, Yamazaki?
Uh, it's not my favorite hobby,
but I like it well enough.
I see it as a chance to
experiment more than anything.
How so?
Like, what's going to happen
if I combine this seasoning
with that one, do you see?
Or if I do this
to this ingredient,
what will it transform into?
Transform?
It's crazy, you never know
what you're gonna get.
Sometimes, things end up
in the lunches he makes
that I don't even recognize.
That sounds pretty cool!
[SAKURA gasps]
Your lunch looks really
beautiful, Akiho!
It does!
[TOMOYO] And just look
at all the lovely colors!
Did ya make it?
No, someone made it for me.
I'm not exactly the best cook.
So are you living with somebody
while you're here in Japan?
Or do you live by yourself?
Actually, I live
with the same person
who's taken care of me
ever since I was little.
Family member?
Oh, no. We aren't
related or anything.
But we're quite close.
Family or not, you must
really love them.
It shows on your face.
[AKIHO]
Huh?
You looked so happy
and relaxed just now.
What do you say
we trade dishes
so we can all try each other's?
That sounds divine. Let's trade.
I made yakisoba if
you guys want any.
[SAKURA]
Hm? For a picnic?
I read about a way to
make it so it's still good,
even when it's cold.
So I thought I would
practice it, y'know,
for the next play I'm writing.
There's yakisoba in your play?
[NAOKO]
Mh-hm.
I figured this would be
a good chance to try it.
Here, have some of mine, too.
The special for today:
Squid takoyaki !
So are they octopus or squid?
You made the rolled omelet?
It's quite tasty!
Oh, good. I'm glad.
The sandwiches from your
lunch are as delicious
as they looked like they'd be!
Yamazaki's squid balls
are pretty yummy, too.
I especially like
the cheese on top.
[chuckles]
That's the secret.
There's nothing secret about it.
[SAKURA gasps]
[SAKURA]
Huh?
What's wrong? You look startled.
For a second it felt
like there was somebody
pulling at me from behind.
I'm just imagi-- Uh!
[gasps]
Sakura?
Uh, I'm sorry, just...
Phone call! I need to
make a phone call.
Are you okay?
Hey. Slow down for a second.
What's happening?
Where are you taking me?
Is it another card?
[gasps] It's a tree!
[SAKURA]
I'm gonna crash into it.
Release!
[SAKURA]
Siege!
Now make yourself more flexible.
[SAKURA] No good.
I'm still being pulled.
Show me what lies
in front of you!
[SAKURA] I'm being pulled
toward that cherry tree.
If a card is behind this,
that's where it must be hiding.
[SAKURA] Still, I can't
do anything from here.
I need to get closer.
[SAKURA] But if I undo my magic
and crash into that tree...
[SAKURA]
It'll be okay.
Relax. One thing at a time.
Now, go!
[SAKURA]
There it is!
Force without master,
heed my Staff of Dreams,
and become my power!
Secure!
[SAKURA yelping]
I made it in time.
Gravitation.
"Gravity."
[phone ringing]
Yes?
[TOMOYO]
Sakura! Are you all right?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
Sorry I ran off like that.
Turns out it was a card.
[rustling]
[TOMOYO]
What? Is something wrong?
No. Sorry. I'm fine. Listen...
It's incredible.
I had no idea there was such
a big cherry blossom tree here.
This is one enormous,
well-kept secret.
Yeah, you'd think
that everybody
would be talking about
a tree this huge.
Good thing it's in a spot
where flower-viewing
parties are allowed.
This was a great find,
Sakura, way to go.
[SAKURA chuckles]
What's wrong, Tomoyo?
It's just... I can't
believe I missed the chance
to film your heroic deeds again.
Perhaps if I purify myself,
I'll be worthy to serve
as your videographer.
[SAKURA chuckles nervously]
Ah. There he is.
[SAKURA gasps]
Li! Hey!
Sorry I'm so late.
[CHIHARU]
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Li. Found us, huh?
Yeah.
Looks like you went
ahead and started.
That's good.
Have you had lunch yet?
Yeah, I have.
Oh, here. I brought these.
Yay! Your peach buns.
It's been too long!
Syaoran makes the most
delicious sweets.
He's super talented.
You don't wanna
miss out on 'em.
Sure, I'd love to try one.
It's wonderful!
Thank you.
And you made them yourself?
You really are talented.
It's not as difficult
as it looks.
Wow. I'm amazed. This has
been such a good lunch.
All of the dishes
were delicious.
I wish I knew how to cook, too.
I can teach you
how to make sweets.
I'd be happy to help.
I think she wants to
learn normal cooking.
Thanks, that sounds great!
Speaking of sweets,
they got their name from
an upper-class tea party
when one of the guests said
something sweet to the host.
Are you okay?
It was a card.
I can fill you in later.
Well, sure, that too.
But a second ago,
when I said that I'd eaten,
you looked kind of sad.
That's actually what
I was asking you about.
[gasps]
Um, nothing's wrong.
Please don't worry!
I have to. It's you.
Well, it's just...
I made you lunch.
Like I said I wanted
to on the phone.
But it's okay. I can just give
it to Kero when I get home.
I'll make you
another one sometime.
You think... I could
have that one?
[SAKURA]
But, Syaoran--
Please.
You don't have to.
You said you already ate.
I want it. Please?
No, it's okay.
I can't?
No, of course you can, but...
I don't want you to
feel like you have to.
Looks delicious.
So good!
So rolled omelets!
They're like castella .
Castella sponge cake
was originally made
using cast-off crumbs.
Just like how "offal"
got its name
from the "off-fall"
during butchering.
As for where the "-tella" part
of the word comes from,
well, you see, temple priests
would "tell a" friend
when they had leftover sweets
so they'd get together
and make castella .
And those priests
sure could bake!
They brought in so much money
from the cakes they sold,
they added buildings
to the temple
and eventually opened
multiple branches.
It's a temple,
not a bank, dummy!
--Fascinating!
--[SAKURA, SYAORAN] Oh, wow!
Is it just me,
or does it seem like
he'll take any opening
he can find lately?
I can't believe how
full I am already.
The temple went on to
expand globally. You see--
Tomoyo, will you sing
something for us?
I would love that!
Yeah, me too.
Will you, please? I would
love to hear you sing.
If it's all right with everyone.
♪ Look to your dreams
for the answers. ♪
♪ Look to the sky above for
the light to guide your way. ♪
♪ Reach for tomorrow. ♪
♪ The morning light
will shine... ♪
[SAKURA, AKIHO]
♪ ...through the haze. ♪
♪ There may be
clouds up above, ♪
♪ casting shadows on the land. ♪
[TOMOYO]
♪ Listen to your heart. ♪
♪ Only then you'll understand. ♪
♪ It's up to all of us
to create a better world. ♪
♪ Never give up,
keep on smiling ♪
Hidey-howdy-ho!
It's "Leave it to Kero" time.
The segment that enriches
your hearts and minds!
Today we're taking a closer look
at the lunches Sakura
and her friends ate
at the flower-viewing
party in this episode!
Don't they all look tasty?
Akiho's is so pretty!
I wonder who made it for her.
It's no fair!
I wish I could've shared
all the yummy food!
I'm not the only one whose
mouth is watering now, am I?
Oh, well, a little drool
never hurt anybody!
Bye-bye!
[SAKURA] All these strange
things keep happening.
Spending time with Akiho
is really great, though!
Speaking of which, I wonder
what club she's gonna join.
Next time, "Sakura, the Rabbit,
and the Song of the Moon."
Say it with me: Release!