[TOMOYO] Again? And you said
there were two cards this time?
Yeah. That's right.
At home?
Akiho had come over.
And what was she doing?
[SAKURA]
Sleeping, thanks to this.
[SYAORAN]
Okay.
And, once again, I couldn't
sense a darn thing.
Did you, though?
It was just barely
there, but yes.
I could tell something
was different.
[SYAORAN]
How so?
I'm not sure how to explain it.
I guess something felt
kind of "off." You know?
Just off?
[KERO] So right now,
Sakura's the only one
who can sense the cards.
[TOMOYO gasps]
Hold on!
[SAKURA]
Go ahead. What is it?
Well, I noticed something,
but it may not
be that important.
Tell me. At this point,
anything'll help.
[TOMOYO] These two cards,
Labyrinth and Snooze,
they seemed familiar to me.
And it's because their
powers are similar
to the Maze and
Sleep Clow Cards.
[SAKURA gasps]
[TEACHER A]
Formulas are your friends.
You'll be using them
for a long time.
I strongly suggest
you memorize them.
All right, we'll
start with equality.
This should look familiar.
Today we'll be learning about
formulas called equalities
and how they use the equal sign
to express relationships
between numerical values.
We call everything to
the left of the equal sign
the left-side value.
Everything to the right
is the right-side value.
Though they may be expressed
in different forms...
[SAKURA]
It's like Tomoyo was saying.
These new cards
that are showing up
seem to have a lot in
common with the old ones.
Aqua is similar to Watery.
Flight is like Fly.
And Gale, Gale resembles Windy.
[SAKURA]
But would that mean...?
Miss Kinomoto.
[SAKURA]
Uh. Yes, sir!
[gasps]
[KERO]
Uh? Huh?
[chuckles]
Oh, did I startle you?
Dozed off for a
little there, did we?
Well, that's good, but
I would like you to pay
a bit more attention
going forward.
Uh. Right.
Okay, we got it, Teach. Will do.
Oh, wow.
You were called out in
front of the whole class?
It was totally embarrassing.
Yes, but at least you weren't
actually taking a nap, right?
I was still spacing out, though.
I can't believe I did that.
[CHIHARU]
It happens to everyone.
Don't beat yourself up.
Like just the other
day in class.
I was thinking about
a story I'm writing,
and then the teacher
suddenly called on me
and I had no idea what to say.
A story? Yay, I can't wait.
What will this new one be about?
[NAOKO]
I don't wanna say just yet.
Oh, I do have an
announcement, though.
I get to write the script
for our next play.
They're letting first-years
do most of the work.
You'll write it all?
Yeah.
That's why I joined the drama
club in the first place.
The Literature Club
would've worked too, I guess.
Except, lately I'm a
lot more interested
in scriptwriting than
writing novels.
You remember those photos?
Back at my house?
From when you played
a beautiful princess?
Um, right.
It was a school play, and
Naoko wrote the whole thing.
[gasps]
[AKIHO]
You must be so talented!
[NAOKO] I don't know.
I still have a lot to learn.
[AKIHO] You'll show
me the video, right?
Yeah, sure.
[TAKASHI]
You guys having fun?
I'm sorry we're late.
[TOMOYO] So how did your
meeting with the teacher go?
Not bad, we were talking about
the next sports tournament.
Li and I are working on the
operating committee together.
That sounds like fun.
[TAKASHI]
It is, once things get moving.
But first you have to decide
who's going to be
in which event,
and that can be difficult.
[SYAORAN]
Very.
I guess no one would wanna be
in an event they're not good at.
What about you, Akiho?
Play any sports?
I guess I'm all right at tennis.
I've played it ever
since I was little.
That's too bad.
There's no tennis this
time around, sorry.
So what events are in
the tournament, then?
There's volleyball,
and basketball, ping-pong.
Oh, and badminton.
Okay, that's kind
of like tennis.
Is it?
Allow me to enlighten you.
In badminton, two players
stand on either side of a net
that's stretched
across the court,
and volley a shuttlecock back
and forth to score points.
The shuttlecock
actually moves faster
than any other object in sports.
Also, many people mistakenly
call the event "bat-minton."
But that's wrong.
It's actually "badminton."
[CHIHARU]
Huh?
Wait. I can't find anything
to criticize in that.
It sounded like a thorough
explanation to me.
[ALL]
Mh! Mh!
Yamazaki actually told
the truth for once?
[chuckles]
You've gotta keep
people guessing.
Ah! This just feels wrong!
You're you! You're not
supposed to tell the truth.
[SYAORAN] So all of you have
the day off from your clubs?
Yeah. No cheerleading today.
[AKIHO] And we're on break
so the piano can get tuned
and the teacher can get
some arrangements done.
[TOMOYO]
There was a meeting about
the joint recital
we're putting on
with another middle
school next month.
Everyone's getting
really excited.
[SAKURA] A recital?
Can we come see it, too?
[TOMOYO]
Yes! It'll be in our auditorium.
What do you think,
Syaoran, you wanna go?
Sure.
Okay then, we'll be there.
You'll do great.
I know you will!
[TOMOYO, AKIHO]
Thanks!
We're not going to
disappoint you, I promise.
[KAITO]
Akiho.
[AKIHO]
Uh?
It's Kaito!
Hello there.
[SAKURA, TOMOYO]
Nice to see you!
Are you on your way
home from school?
Yes. What are you up to?
Just finished shopping.
Why don't I take a bag?
Thank you, but I'm all right.
[KAITO]
Where are my manners?
Please, forgive me.
I look after Akiho.
My name is Yuna D. Kaito.
And you? May I ask yours?
I'm Syaoran Li.
Now then, do you need
to make any stops?
I don't.
[KAITO]
Very good. Shall we head home?
Yes!
Ladies, do come
visit again soon.
And you, please.
I'm so hungry!
[yelps]
What are you doing?
Coulda sworn I
smelled fresh bread.
Sorry, that was Kaito's.
It's not for you.
[KERO groans]
I was stuck in the bag while
you guys got to eat lunch.
It's like you're
trying to starve me!
But I packed a ton
of snacks for you.
You thought those would be
enough to keep me going?
Don't go blaming
me if you get fat.
[KERO]
A little bit of extra padding
isn't gonna change
this smokin' hot body!
[SAKURA] But we're talking
about more than a little.
[KERO]
Good thing I'm charming, then.
Is something bothering you?
Good morning.
Actually, I suppose it's
evening where you are.
So someone with magic.
How does Sakura know him?
You remember the transfer
student she's friends with?
He's some kind of
caretaker for her.
[ERIOL]
His name?
Yuna D.
[SYAORAN]
Do you know him?
I'm not acquainted with him, no.
Although, the "D" in his name...
if it refers to what I think...
[SYAORAN]
What are you talking about?
[ERIOL]
Well, you see,
here in England, there's
a magic association
that grants its highest-ranked
magic users the title of "D."
[SYAORAN]
I've never heard of it.
That's all right.
Your mother must not've
taught you about them yet.
Some rumors concerning
them aren't good.
So he's part of
this association?
[ERIOL] I cannot say for
certain, but it is possible.
Okay, but I don't get
why he would do something
to make his affiliation
and status so obvious.
[ERIOL] It may make
no difference to him.
Not if he's powerful enough.
Does Sakura know?
[SYAORAN]
She hasn't said anything,
and I haven't told her.
Interesting.
Then it's a power that
she cannot detect,
but one that you can.
So you think this guy
has Moon magic, too?
[ERIOL] It is a reasonable
assumption, yes.
In which case, you
need to be prepared.
If anything unfortunate happens,
it may be problematic for you.
As one who draws from
the same power source.
[ERIOL] You said that nothing
about the transfer student
seemed unusual, correct?
Right. She doesn't set off
any alarm bells for me.
[ERIOL] Perhaps not, but
she did move into the house
in which I once lived.
It would be logical for someone
with the same type of magic
to have made that choice.
It's an ideal location
for preserving people
with magical power.
That's why they chose to live
there? Because they knew?
[ERIOL]
It's a possibility.
Let me look into this.
I'll tell you what I find.
'Kay, thanks.
[ERIOL]
Certainly.
We must do what we can
to help Sakura and the
people she cares about.
[KAHO] Another magic-user
so close to Sakura.
There does seem to be a pattern.
Those with great magical power
tend to converge around her.
But why?
They're drawn to her,
because she possesses
immense power herself.
[ERIOL]
Sakura is very strong.
I doubt anyone knows
that better than I.
[KAHO]
You're right.
Besides, she has
someone by her side
who treasures her
above all else.
That's worth a great deal.
[SAKURA]
So how's school?
[TOYA]
It's fine.
[SAKURA] Come on,
that's all you ever say.
[TOYA]
You?
[SAKURA] It's been fun.
But English is hard.
[TOYA]
What about math?
[SAKURA] It's not too bad.
It's gotten easier.
I feel like this teacher's
better at explaining everything.
Hey. This is good.
Did you do something
different with it?
Added some butter.
You're right.
I can totally tell!
All right, whatever you say.
Hey, I'm serious!
The butter adds richness
and a softer texture.
You sound like a TV food critic.
I was trying to be nice!
Oh, yeah.
Dad's going to be away
this weekend, again.
[SAKURA]
Aw, really?
Oh, I promised my friend
that she could come over
and look at our library.
I asked Dad, and he said it was
fine, so you don't mind, right?
[TOYA] Yeah, if he said
it's okay, then sure.
I'll move some books
around for ya.
It's pretty crowded in there.
Okay, that's great!
Thanks so much for
the delicious food.
G'bye! Have fun at work.
All clear. You can come
downstairs if you want.
Guessing your brother left?
Yep.
Yukibunny said he
was going out, too.
I didn't know you guys were
full-fledged texting
buddies now.
We are.
But sometimes I think
he's trying to torture me.
Sending yummy food pics right
when I get hungry. Look!
[SAKURA giggles]
He told me you send him
pictures of food too.
Trying to get revenge?
[KERO]
Yep, an eye for an eye.
Take that! And that!
Man, that's a good one!
Wait a second,
you're in all of them.
How did you take all those?
[KERO] Tomoyo gave me a
remote-control button.
That thing is every
selfie taker's dream.
You can have the cupcakes
on the table if you want.
Toya got them from
one of his jobs.
[KERO]
Yay!
Yum! Get a picture!
Okay.
[KERO]
Hm?
You all right over there?
[KERO]
It's another card, isn't it?
No, stop! Wait a sec.
[SAKURA whines]
[KERO] Tomoyo had to do
something with her mom today,
so she needed some backup.
And, that would be me.
She gave me very
strict instructions.
Dress you up in that and
then film you using this!
Oh. Oh, yeah. The camera loves
you. Come on, give me more.
Give me more.
Right. Why am I surprised?
[KERO]
Being in Penguin Park at night
sure brings back
memories, doesn't it?
No kidding.
There were so many crazy
things that happened here.
That time with the King Penguin
when he was flipped upside down.
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
[KERO gasps]
[KERO]
Kinda like he is now!
[screams]
[SAKURA] It's gonna be
on the news again!
[KERO] This little guy's
standing on his head, too.
It's not over. All of
them are flipping.
[rumbling]
[BOTH scream]
Why is this happening?
[KERO]
We gotta stop it.
I know that, but how?
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
There! That smoky stuff.
So that's what's behind
this crazy prank?
I think so.
Great! Let's go get it, then!
Right!
Release!
[SAKURA]
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Sec--
[screams]
[screaming]
Good catch, thanks.
Jeez, you scared me!
Looks like we can't
get too close.
[SAKURA] Not without being
turned upside-down.
[KERO] We'd smack our heads
on the ground for sure.
That would give us
a couple of nasty bumps.
I don't want a bump on my head!
So we gotta
figure somethin' out.
We're runnin' out of time, here.
So what now?
[gasps]
I've got an idea!
[SAKURA]
That's enough!
All right!
If you're airborne, you can
control your movements!
[SAKURA]
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Secure!
[SAKURA]
There, gotcha.
"Reversal."
Accurate, huh?
Uh, yeah.
Right. We've gotta be quick.
We'll use the card to
put everything ba--
What happened?
Wow, this is crazy.
Look at that.
[WOMAN B]
Why's it upside-down?
[BOTH yelp]
[TOMOYO] When everyone showed
up, you flew back home?
If we'd hung around any longer,
somebody would've seen us.
And there's no hiding from
social media these days.
[TOMOYO] I don't think
you need to worry.
Your secret's safe.
It doesn't look like you
were caught on film.
Turn on the TV and check.
We're live from Penguin Park
where all of the
playground equipment
has been turned upside-down.
[BOTH scream]
[REPORTER A]
According to witness statements,
the crime appears
to have occurred
over a span of about 20 minutes.
The responsible party
has yet to be identified.
Whoever they are,
they remain at large.
We'll continue to cover the--
Well, it's big news now.
Yeah, maybe we
shouldn't have run off.
It was the only way
to keep the world
from finding out about
the Cardcaptors.
You two made the right decision.
After things settle down a bit,
we can go back and
fix the playground.
Yeah. You're right.
At least, we hope so.
[TOMOYO]
Now that that's settled. Kero?
Yes?
How did your stint
as a cameraman go?
[KERO]
Great! I got it all.
Could I see some
of the footage now?
Sure!
You're setting it up so
we can all watch the video
at the same time?
Yep! This. This. This.
Now we... push the button!
[whines]
[SAKURA]
Ugh. It's making me dizzy.
Hm?
It looks like something's
blocking the camera.
Oh, whoopsie.
You remember when you first
got flipped upside-down
and I had to catch
you in my mouth?
My daring rescue must've
knocked the camera over.
[KERO chuckles nervously]
[KERO laughs]
Well, accidents
happen sometimes.
That's showbiz for ya.
[TOMOYO]
Yes, that's true.
[TOMOYO] Irregularities
are a part of filming.
But, Kero.
[KERO]
Yes?
[TOMOYO]
Your training starts tomorrow!
[KERO]
Uh. Huh?
For what?
[TOMOYO]
What else? For videography!
With both of us as
filmmaking experts,
we'll never miss a moment
of Sakura's heroics.
[KERO]
Oh, boy.
You're not joking
about this, are you?
[TOMOYO]
Together, you and I will become
masters of the camera!
I should probably
say no. But sure!
Okay, how's this angle?
[TOMOYO]
That looks good.
[KERO]
And maybe like this?
[TOMOYO]
Yes, wonderful!
[KERO]
How 'bout now?
[TOMOYO]
Perfect!
[KERO laughing]
Hidey-howdy-ho!
It's "Leave it to Kero" time.
Today we're gonna take
a closer look at the park
that just keeps on showin' up.
Everyone calls it Penguin Park,
but its official name
is Tomoeda Central Park.
There's an awesome playground
with a penguin-shaped slide,
nicknamed King Penguin,
plus swings, see-saws, a jungle
gym, and lots of other stuff.
It has plenty of greenery,
and it's in a great location.
It's nice to relax in
the park sometimes.
In fact, I could use a nice
park nap right about now!
Bye-bye!
[SAKURA] It's my first
ball-sports tournament.
I love P.E. stuff,
so I'm really excited!
What?
Akiho and Syaoran will be
facing off in badminton?
Next time, "Sakura and the
Icy Ball-Sports Tournament."
Say it with me: Release!