[rumbling]
Uh! Over there!
What the heck?
[SAKURA]
Looks like it's underground!
It's stopped!
[KERO]
It's gonna get out!
I'm on it!
Huh? Are you gonna close
off the entire garden?
Siege!
[SAKURA] I need you to surround
the whole mansion, go!
[MEILING screams]
[MEILING]
What the heck is happening?
[KERO]
Phew. Just in time.
All right, it can't get out.
Uh, now what?
[KERO]
I think we made it mad!
Oh, no, it's headed
for Tomoyo's house!
Come on!
Oh, no! I hope we'll
be safe in here.
[TOMOYO]
Please be careful.
[KERO]
Aw, man! So much for the maze.
[BOTH gasp]
[SAKURA]
It's headed for the others!
We gotta go!
[SAKURA yelping]
Hey, come back!
Shoot, she's goin' too fast!
Right there! Do it, Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Secure!
[SAKURA]
"Swing."
[KERO]
You did it! Way to go, kiddo!
[SAKURA]
But... look at all the damage.
[KERO]
Don't be so hard on yourself.
That stuff's not your fault.
Thank you for working
so hard today.
[SAKURA screaming]
[SAKURA]
Hey! Wait!
Wow, it sure loves her.
[SAKURA]
Tomoyo!
[TOMOYO] You're back!
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine.
And I got the card.
Also, we may've messed up
your garden a little.
Please, don't even
worry about it.
What's more important is that
both you and Kero are safe.
Thanks, Tomoyo.
Yeah, thanks!
Oh, and by the way, Kero.
Were you able to capture
Sakura's greatest
moments for me?
[KERO]
Y-Yeah...
I can't wait to sit down
and review it later.
[TOMOYO giggles]
[SONOMI] Goodness, that
earthquake really scared me!
Is everyone okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
We all are.
[SAKURA]
Hm?
Is something wrong, Akiho?
Well, it's just...
I'm a little upset
that I fell asleep
at a friend's house again.
It's not yer fault.
It was magic induced!
I still can't believe I slept
through an earthquake! Really?
Also magically induced.
Seriously, c'mon.
Oh, well,
falling asleep is better
than being injured, right?
Yes, that's true.
Still, are you absolutely
sure that you're all okay?
[GIRLS]
Yes!
All right. Who wants more tea?
[ALL]
I do, please!
[ALL giggle]
No fair! Someone better save
some snacks for me, or else!
[TOMOYO] Well then, please
be safe on your way home.
You girls are welcome
to visit anytime you like.
Oh, Sakura, before I forget.
Yeah?
Grandfather called.
He wants to know if you
have plans for summer.
I'm sure he would love
for you to go visit him
at the villa again.
Does that sound like something
you would be interested in?
It's up to you.
I'll have to ask my dad first,
but I would love
to see him again!
[chuckles]
[AKIHO]
Tomoyo's mother is so nice!
Not only is she beautiful, but
she's smart and a great cook!
I know! That clotted cream
she made was simply divine!
Yeah, totally.
Tomoyo said she'd ask
her mom for the recipe.
That's so nice.
Make sure you guys save
some afternoon tea
for me, okie dokie?
[AKIHO] Well, this is
where we part ways.
Thank you for inviting me along.
[SAKURA]
I'm glad you came!
I'll text you the pictures
I took later, 'kay?
[AKIHO]
Great!
Bye, Akiho! See you
at school tomorrow!
[AKIHO]
Have a safe walk home!
[AKIHO humming]
[KAITO]
You're in a good mood.
[AKIHO]
Kaito?
What are you doing here?
[KAITO] The message you sent
said you were on your way home,
so I came to meet you.
[AKIHO]
That's so thoughtful.
As always, you have
a voice like an angel.
You could hear my singing?
Quite clearly.
[AKIHO whines]
I believe you mentioned the
friend you were visiting today
was also a good singer, yes?
That's right, we're both
in the Chorus Club.
Her house is amazing,
and her mother makes the
most wonderful tea ever!
She even offered to
give me the recipe
for the clotted cream she made.
[KAITO] It sounds like
you had a great time.
I did!
[AKIHO] You know, my family
has traveled constantly
all over the world to find
the books that we collect.
Sometimes, we'd move so quickly
after we found what
we were searching for
that I wouldn't even have a
chance to make any real friends.
Though to be fair, that might
have been my own fault.
[KAITO]
I think maybe you're being
a bit too hard on yourself.
[AKIHO]
But here in Japan,
I was able to make
friends right away.
[KAITO]
They seem like nice people.
[AKIHO]
They really are.
[KAITO] Who would you
say you're closest to?
[AKIHO]
Sakura, for sure.
[KAITO]
That's Sakura Kinomoto, right?
Yes.
Ever since the first time I met
her, she's been so kind to me.
She offered to show me
her family's library
the next time I visit her house.
[KAITO]
That sounds exciting.
I understand her father
specializes in archaeology.
I'm sure he has some
rather interesting books.
[AKIHO]
Hm?
Oh, I didn't realize that I had
already mentioned Sakura's
father to you before.
Kaito?
Tina. Rie. Triax.
Time, in accordance with
the covenant, turn back.
[AKIHO]
Huh?
[KAITO]
Is something wrong?
[AKIHO]
Uh, no?
Well, then.
You were saying Sakura
was going to show you
her family's library.
Yes. That's right.
[KAITO]
That sounds exciting.
What shall I make for you
to take to her house?
Oh, maybe...
Could you and I make her
something together?
I'd like that.
Perfect, I can't wait!
[MEILING] That's what
I call birds of a feather
flocking together.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
[MEILING]
You and Shinomoto, duh.
You're pretty similar, and I
don't just mean your names.
We are?
Is that news?
Not really.
Of course.
[BOTH laugh]
[MEILING] I'm curious, what are
the people in your life like?
[SAKURA]
Well, they're all super nice.
I kind of have this theory
that when you believe
everyone you meet is good,
then you only
attract good people.
And when you believe all the
people you'll meet are bad,
then you don't notice when you
meet someone who's good.
But you know, when
I watch good people,
I always feel a little sad.
[MEILING]
Who's that?
Do you know her?
[SAKURA]
Nuh-uh.
[screams]
Kinomoto!
[MEILING]
What's her deal?
Meiling!
That was close. Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Now what do we do?
I think it might be a card,
but I can't sense anything.
[MEILING] Looks like your
cheerleading practice
is paying off.
Take that!
[MEILING]
What the heck?
How do we defeat this thing?
[SAKURA] It's kind of
like that Clow Card.
Do you remember the
one I'm talking about?
[MEILING] Yeah, but
there were two of them!
Syaoran and I had
to work together!
It was the only way we were
able to take them out.
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
Over here!
[MEILING]
No! Over here!
[SAKURA]
Meiling! Watch out!
I'm okay!
What are we gonna do?
If it's anything like the Twin,
maybe we can turn it
back the same way!
[MEILING] But how do we do
that when there's only one?
On the shoulders!
We'll break the stones on both
shoulders at the same time!
Kinomoto!
Okay!
[MEILING]
Just move the way I do!
[SAKURA]
Got it!
[MEILING]
Get ready.
Left!
[SAKURA]
'Kay!
Now, move right!
[SAKURA]
Yeah!
[MEILING]
Back three steps!
Jump!
Here we go.
[gasps]
[SAKURA, MEILING yell]
[MEILING]
Do it!
Key that hides the
forces of dreams,
I bid you to show
me your true form.
Release!
Force without master,
heed the call of my
Staff of Dreams.
Become my power.
Secure!
[MEILING] Wow, looks like
it really was a card.
"Struggle"? Yeah, no kidding.
Meiling, are you okay?
Your cheek is kind of red.
Please tell me you're not hurt!
It's no big deal.
[KERO yawns]
What happened?
Are we back home already?
It's been a heck of a day
and this Guardian of the
Clow is ready for a bath!
[SAKURA]
In the end, I was still able
to turn it into a card
with Meiling's help.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
[KERO] I slept through
the entire fight.
What if Tomoyo finds out
I didn't get it on video?!
I'm dead. Tomoyo's
gonna kill me.
Yep. This is the end
of our friendship...
[knocking]
Come in!
That bath was heavenly.
Does your bruise hurt at all?
I'm fine. Stop being
such a worry-wart!
Can I at least dry
your hair for you?
Uh, sure, but aren't you tired?
[SAKURA]
Nuh-uh! I feel great.
Maybe I'll start
with an apology.
I mean, Tomoyo's not
one to hold a grudge,
and there's no way she could
stay angry at someone
as cute as me.
[SAKURA]
I need to apologize.
What for?
It's all my fault you were
put in danger earlier today.
[SAKURA] But also,
I'm glad you were there.
When I think about it,
we've never had the chance
to really do anything
together before.
You helped me a lot when we
were gathering Clow Cards,
but it was never
just the two of us.
So it made me super happy to
catch this card with you today.
Thank you.
[yelps]
[MEILING]
I'm glad, too.
You are?
But seriously, if you apologize
to me even one more time,
I promise I will lose it.
That being said,
it also made me happy
that I could help you
with a card for once.
[SAKURA]
Meiling.
Hey. Do you remember
what I said earlier?
When we were walking home
from Daidouji's house?
[SAKURA] About how when
you watch good people,
it sometimes makes you feel sad?
Wanna know why?
Sure.
So the thing is, there are
lots of different kinds
of good people in this world.
But it seems like the
good people I know
are always worried about
everyone else's happiness.
It feels like they're
super focused
on how to make
other people smile.
And that's not a bad way to be,
but if they spend all their time
thinking about other people,
then when are they
going to find time
to take care of themselves?
I guess what I'm saying is,
you and Syaoran are like that.
You're always worried about
making other people happy.
Especially Syaoran, since
he's so incredibly stubborn.
I think you should find
your own happiness first,
and then make him open his eyes.
[SAKURA]
You think so?
Definitely.
It feels like... a lot of
things are different somehow.
And not just with the new cards.
Like something really important
might be different, too.
I don't know much
about the cards,
so I can't help you there.
Also, don't forget you have
your own special kind of magic.
"It's okay.
Everything'll be okay."
Yep, that's right!
[KERO] Hey, do you think
I should tell her tonight?
Or wait and see if it just
comes up tomorrow?
Help a fella out here!
[MEILING]
Thank you for calling the cab.
[FUJITAKA]
Oh, you're very welcome.
[MEILING]
And for your hospitality.
It was no trouble at all.
Though I feel I should apologize
for not being home
during your visit.
Don't worry, Kinomoto
took great care of me.
[FUJITAKA]
I heard you taught Sakura
how to make some Chinese dishes.
I'm sure they'll be delicious,
I can't wait to try them.
Okay, can you take her straight
to the airport, please?
So you won't get to
see Syaoran? Sorry.
Nah. It's fine, he can
always come visit us.
Besides, I've almost
accomplished everything
I came to Japan for.
"Almost"?
Question!
Uh, okay.
From here on out, may I
always call you Sakura?
Yeah, of course!
Mission accomplished!
Now everything is done.
See ya, Sakura!
Thanks for coming!
Goodbye, Meiling!
Have a safe trip!
[SYAORAN]
Hello?
[SYAORAN] I told you I woulda
taken you to the airport.
[MEILING]
I can get there myself.
You are both total worry-warts.
[SYAORAN]
Both?
Guess what! I asked Kinomoto
about something earlier.
She said I can call
her Sakura from now on.
[SYAORAN]
What brought that on?
Well, we are comrades
in battle now.
[SYAORAN]
Battle?
What do you mean?
Did something happen?
I suppose it slipped my mind!
You should probably ask Sakura.
[SYAORAN]
Come on, Meiling.
[MEILING] Listen, I don't
know what's going on,
or even the reason
you came back to Japan,
but if anything
happens to you,
I definitely know who
will be the saddest.
I've grown pretty
close to Sakura,
and if you make her cry,
you'll regret it.
[SYAORAN]
I know.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Are you ready, guys and gals?
It's time for
"Leave It to Kero,"
where today I'm gonna be
talkin' about Yuna D. Kaito!
This guy is Akiho's
personal butler
and he's full of elegance
and what not!
He's an awesome chef
and can make a cake
like nobody's business!
Kaito also knows his way
around English teas.
Guess you could say he's
one heck of a butler!
But that pocket watch is
somethin' else, am I right?
The guy definitely seems
kinda suspicious though,
and my super cool Guardian
of the Clow senses
are totally tingling!
Anyway, I gotta run, so buh-bye!
[SAKURA]
Everyone's really excited
to make roll cake
in Home Ec. Class.
But just as we're about to start
adding the finishing touches,
the decorations start moving!
Next time, "Sakura and
the Crazy Sweets."
Say it with me: Release!