[SAKURA]
You know Toya.
The only thing he
said was "not bad."
I want to know what someone
else thinks, though,
so I packed some in my lunch.
I'd love to be your
taste tester.
Great!
Look at those clouds.
I wanna use the Flight card
to walk up there with them.
I'll film you.
That would make for
some lovely footage,
especially with
the right costume!
[SAKURA chuckles]
And since we're on the subject,
the latest costume I designed
for you is coming along well.
And Li's, too. You'll love it!
Oh, wow. You've gotten taller.
Oh, have I?
Yes, you look so
much manlier now.
[SYAORAN]
Um.
So, uh, what are you doing
all of this for, anyway?
I need your measurements.
I'm going to make a costume
for you like I do for Sakura.
Just you wait, when I'm done,
the two of you will
look more beautiful
than you ever have before!
[SAKURA, SYAORAN]
Huh?
Right now I'm working
on the tacking,
but when I'm done, I'll need
both of you to try them on.
That's okay, isn't it?
[SAKURA] I can't wait to see
what Syaoran looks like
in his costume.
[AKIHO]
Sakura! Tomoyo!
Oh, hey, Akiho.
How has your morning been?
Good! How about yours?
[SAKURA]
Not bad.
I'm glad I caught up to you.
Nice to see you again, Momo.
"It's nice to see
you again, too!"
Did you bring your
little friend along?
Yep! Here he is if
you wanna say hello.
Well, good morning,
Kero. How are you?
[KERO]
Can't breathe. Being strangled.
[SAKURA gasps]
[SAKURA chuckles nervously]
[TOMOYO] I didn't realize you
walked to school too, Akiho.
[AKIHO]
Yes. I don't live far.
What's the house you're
staying in like?
Well, it's very nice.
Apparently, the person who
lived there before I moved in
was a boy our age, who had
come here from England.
Could that be--?
Can we see a picture
of the house?
Um, okay.
[SAKURA, TOMOYO gasp]
[SAKURA]
It's Eriol's old house!
[AKIHO]
So it's true?
There was another overseas
transfer student before me?
Yes, when we were in
elementary school.
Eriol Hiiragizawa. He was
really nice and so grown-up.
He's not here anymore, though?
He went back to England.
We keep in touch with phone
calls and emails and stuff.
[SAKURA] Except that he
still hasn't replied.
[AKIHO]
Hey, Sakura?
You look upset.
Is something wrong?
No.
You told us that you've been
to England before too, right?
[AKIHO]
Yes.
What's it like there?
Foggy a lot of the time.
It rained a bunch, and it was
very cold in the winter.
Although...
...it's where I found something
incredibly important to me.
So, um...
It's sort of funny that you
asked me about my house today.
The thing is--
[KERO groans]
Gimme a second here.
I'm recovering from a
near-death experience.
[SAKURA]
Sorry, Kero!
Well, maybe you can be
a little more careful
how you handle me from now on!
Okay, you told him
what she said, right?
[SAKURA]
Yeah, I did.
She really moved
into his old place?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
Kind of crazy, huh?
I told Akiho that a friend
of mine used to live there.
She was pretty surprised
about it, too.
You know, she invited
all of us to come over
and visit her this Sunday.
To come to her house?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
You remember how she's
traveled a lot, right?
Well, she's going to show us
some of the books
she's collected.
She doesn't know
all the languages,
but I guess some of them have
pretty drawings and photos.
[SYAORAN] Sorry. I have
something to do on Sunday.
Oh, yeah? Too bad.
[SYAORAN] Tell Shinomoto I'm
sorry I can't make it, okay?
[SAKURA]
Sure.
Uh, actually...
I was wondering about
the Sunday after that.
Are you free?
It's because I...
I've been cooking.
Practicing rolled omelets.
And it's warmer now,
so if the weather's not bad...
...then we could go
out... together?
[SYAORAN]
Sure. You really want to?
Of course I do! I love
spending time with you.
[SAKURA gasps]
[SYAORAN]
Uh.
Sorry, there was a flower.
Hey! I'm still here, ya know?!
You're not the only two
people in the world!
I deserve some rolled omelets
after you almost strangled me!
Lots--
[snoring]
[MORI]
One, two! One, two!
And turn!
That's it. Watch your
timing on every move.
Kinomoto, step
forward a bit more.
Right!
[distant singing]
[SAKURA]
That's Tomoyo and Akiho.
[MORI]
All right, be sure to practice
that choreography at home, too.
Good work today.
[CHEERLEADERS]
Thank you, Miss Mori!
[BOTH]
Great job out there!
Most of it's not too bad,
but that pose after the
turn is pretty hard, huh?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
You have to turn at just
the right time, or else the--
[distant singing]
The Chorus Club. It sounds
like they're working hard.
Yeah, so let's make
sure that we do, too!
I wonder what's for dinner.
Hm?
Oh, hey.
You're back early.
One of my jobs was called off.
The cake place?
[TOYA]
No, the movers.
We've got pork chops tonight.
Yay!
I'll go change. Can I help you?
Nah, they're almost
done already.
Just do your homework.
'Kay!
[TOYA]
Sakura.
What's up?
[TOYA]
It's just...
Do you mind if I put
broccoli in the rice?
[SAKURA]
Don't you dare!
Ugh! Are you ever not a jerk?
Still happening.
No way. You better keep
your hands off my takoyaki .
[giggles]
[SAKURA] You said you'd always
be there if anything happened,
but it seems like
all you do is sleep.
Hey, I'm home.
I'm really excited
about this Sunday,
but I'm even more excited
about the one after it!
[giggles]
[gasps]
This again. I'm dreaming.
[SAKURA] I was right.
It really is a clock.
Will you tell me who you are?
Why do you keep showing up
in my dreams like this?
Or is this even really a dream?
Is there something you
wanna say to me?
Or something you want me to do?
Come on, please! Answer me!
[KERO]
Sakura! Good, you're awake!
The dream again?
Yeah. It just keeps happening.
You okay?
Yep. Fine.
That person... Who are they,
and what do they want?
[SAKURA] We were right.
It really is Eriol's house.
It sure is.
Feels like it's been so long
since the last time
we were here.
It still looks the same, though.
[SAKURA]
I'm actually a little nervous.
But why? You've
been here before.
I know, but it's the
first time I've been here
since it was Akiho's house.
[AKIHO]
Yes?
[SAKURA]
Uh, hi, it's Sakura.
[TOMOYO]
And Tomoyo.
[AKIHO]
Great! Just a second.
[KERO gasps]
[KERO]
So cool how it opens like that!
Uh-huh.
[AKIHO]
You can just come on in.
Oh, right!
Why are you walking
all funny, Sakura?
[TOMOYO giggles]
[AKIHO]
I'm glad you could make it!
It was really nice of
you to invite us over.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
I'm just happy you're here.
Thanks for coming!
Hello, ladies.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
It's such a pleasure
to have you.
Thank you for coming.
Oh, no! We should
be thanking you!
That's Kaito. He's watched
over me since I was little.
And I've been making trouble
for him ever since.
My full name is Yuna D. Kaito.
It's my honor to look out for
Akiho to the best of my ability.
I'm excited to be
meeting her friends.
And you couldn't trouble me
even if you tried, Akiho.
You know that.
Please come inside.
Of course. Thank you.
[SAKURA gasps]
The inside looks different
than when Eriol was here.
I thought so, too.
Can you tell me more
about what he was like?
He was super grown-up.
That's how you described him
when we were talking earlier.
What exactly made
him so grown-up?
Well, the thing is,
Eriol's actually--
He just seemed so mature
because he was always
calm and collected.
[knocking]
[AKIHO]
Yes?
[door opens]
[KAITO]
Pardon me.
That smells so nice!
The tea your friends brought,
it has a delicate
cherry-blossom aroma.
That was thoughtful. Thank you.
We had fun picking it out.
You serve the tea beautifully.
I've had plenty of practice.
[TOMOYO] Is tea what you
usually like to drink?
I've never been a fan of coffee.
[SAKURA]
Not even café au lait?
It's not too bad as long as
it has lots of milk in it.
Hey, that's how you
like to drink it, too!
Be quiet!
[AKIHO]
Huh?
[SAKURA clears throat]
[TOMOYO chuckles]
There's nothing wrong with tea.
No need to force yourself to
drink something you don't like.
Yes. You're right.
[KAITO]
Enjoy.
[GIRLS]
Thank you very much, Kaito!
[AKIHO, SAKURA]
Delicious!
I've had this tea before, but
it is especially good this time.
Must be how you prepared it.
I'm glad to hear it.
Something to eat, as well?
[gasps]
[GIRLS]
It looks so good!
Wow-ee!
[SAKURA gasps]
Ignore me! I didn't say
anything. Just keep eating!
What's the matter?
I sound silly when I
get excited like that.
I think it's adorable
Maybe it would be if I was
still in elementary school,
but it's embarrassing now.
I've really been trying
to stop doing it.
The cake's very tasty.
[AKIHO]
Mh-hm! Mh-hm!
Excellent. Thank you.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Hey, don't I get some?
[KERO]
So yummy!
I can't eat it fast enough!
I'll have to visit the shop
you got it from sometime.
Actually, I made it.
[TOMOYO]
Oh, do you do a lot of cooking?
He does! Breakfast, lunch,
dinner, and snacks.
Kaito makes everything for me.
Wow, that's really great of you!
[KAITO]
Oh, no.
It is my job, after all.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Is there something wrong?
Now, then. Please make
yourselves at home.
I'll be available. Just
call if you need anything.
Thank you for
everything, Kaito.
Are you feeling all right?
[gasps]
Of course! Let's finish eating.
And then I'll show you the
books I told you about.
[gasps]
Look at 'em all!
Are they all yours?
They aren't mine, exactly.
It's a collection my family
has put together over time.
[TOMOYO] Your family must
really like to read, huh?
[AKIHO]
Yes.
We all love books,
so we acquire them from
every country we go to.
This is just a small
part of the collection.
Wow. It's incredible.
I'm always adding
to the collection.
That's why I came to Japan.
Because there's a book I wanted.
[SAKURA]
You came for a book?
[AKIHO]
It's weird, but yes. Partly.
[gasps]
Is something wrong?
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Oh, no. Uh, I was
thinking about earlier.
You said something about
a book you really like?
Yes?
[SAKURA]
If you wouldn't mind,
I would love to
take a look at it.
Not at all!
It's in my room.
I'll go and get it!
Is there a card?
Yeah. I think so.
How do you know it's here?
I just sensed something.
This way, I think.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
There aren't any books here.
But only in this spot.
It looks like volumes one
through nine are all here.
Then there's a gap
before it picks up again
with volume 18.
I guess Akiho could be in
the middle of reading them.
Hm?
It's not just the books.
The shelf is gone, too!
[TOMOYO]
Um, Sakura? What are you doing?
I'm not really sure.
It's just--
[SAKURA]
Huh?
I'm definitely
touching something.
Maybe, the books are here.
[TOMOYO] If they are,
why can't we see them?
I'd guess a card.
Hey, Tomoyo.
This could be dangerous,
so stand back a bit, okay?
[TOMOYO]
Sure.
Key that hides the
forces of dreams.
I bid you to show
me your true form.
Release!
[SAKURA] Force without master,
heed my Staff of Dreams,
and become my power!
Secure!
I was right. A card.
"Lucid."
[SAKURA]
Okay.
Well, we got another one!
It looks like this card
makes things invisible.
[SAKURA whines]
I'm worried about
blurring and film quality,
but we all make
sacrifices, don't we?
All right, Sakura, smile and
pose with the card for me.
Okay, how's this?
[gasps]
Kero! I left my phone
behind, and he's with it.
That's right, I forgot!
He's been really upset about
missing out on stuff lately.
There's gonna be
a lot of pouting.
[AKIHO]
Sakura! Tomoyo!
It took longer than I thought,
but I got the book.
Sorry, did I
interrupt something?
Oh! No!
So that's the book you like?
It is. What do you think?
[SAKURA]
Huh? It doesn't have a title.
[AKIHO] Well, the title's
not written on the cover.
It's strange,
but the book's actually
called Alice in Clock Land .
You're sure it's
Alice in Clock Land ?
Isn't it supposed to be
"Wonderland," though?
No. It's a different author.
Although, obviously, the
titles are very similar.
Anyway, I like it a lot.
The cover's so interesting.
With that cool clock design.
[SAKURA]
Wait a second.
I've seen that clock somewhere
before, but where was it?
Sakura?
Sorry! I was just
fascinated by the cover.
What's it about, anyway?
Um, I can't read this.
What language is it written in?
[AKIHO]
I don't know, actually.
But I have learned
how to read it,
so I understand
most of the story.
Wow, you're amazing, Akiho!
No. I'm not.
So do you think you could
tell us what it's about?
Of course.
[phone ringing]
[AKIHO]
Excuse me!
Hello? Okay.
It's Kaito.
He wants to know if we'd like
something cold to drink.
He doesn't mind?
'Course not!
I still don't understand
why we can't go!
[SPINNY]
Remember what Eriol said?
It's not time to
get involved yet.
[NAKURU] Who cares?
Sakura is having trouble.
Scary things might be happening
to her. To Yue and Toya, too.
[SPINNY] I realize you want
to see them, but we can't yet.
Don't act like it's just me!
I know you must be worried
about Cerberus, too.
Well, not worried, per se.
Oh, just be honest for once!
[SPINNY] You're being honest
enough for both of us.
If we went to Japan,
there might be something
we could do for them.
[ERIOL]
There isn't.
[NAKURU]
Eriol.
For right now, all that
we can do is wait.
The time will come.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Hey, everybody.
Do you have a
passion for fashion?
Because today on
"Leave it to Kero,"
we're takin' a look at
another battle costume!
This is the one from when Sakura
captured the card
at Tomoyo's house.
Notice the symmetrical
placement of the stars
and how the sleeve is elegantly
fitted on the upper arm
but open at the end.
And the best part is
that it matches mine.
But hey, how crazy
is it that Akiho
lives in Eriol's old house?
Things just keep getting
weirder and weirder.
I wonder what's in store next!
Bye-Bye
[SAKURA]
Dad gave me tickets,
so I'm going to the
aquarium with Syaoran.
This is so exciting!
Wait, Toya? You're working here?
Next time, "Sakura's
Thrilling Aquarium Visit."
Say it with me, now: Release!