[YUE]
So another new card?
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
It was in the music
classroom at my school.
[YUE]
What card is it?
[SAKURA]
I'll get it.
[KERO]
It says "Record."
There is no need
to get so close.
Master is right beside you.
[KERO]
Yeah, but I'm feeling lazy.
I mean, she's all
the way over there.
[YUE]
What does the card do?
Haven't had a chance to try it.
Although, given the card's
name and picture,
I'd say it's a safe bet
that it can be used
to record something.
And when you captured it,
anything notable happen?
[SAKURA] No. I heard a strange
humming noise, that's all.
Right! Fact is
stranger than fiction.
Let's take that baby for a spin!
Yeah, um, I'm pretty sure the
phrase you're looking for
is "seeing is believing."
[KERO] Whatever.
They're basically the same.
[SAKURA]
Let's check it out.
I really don't think they are.
Anyway, it's time to set
things up. Let's go!
Wait, what?
I'm not coming.
Why not, party pooper?!
Yukito has work and
club commitments.
Okay, I get that
he needs to work,
but what's he wasting time
doing club stuff for?
He doesn't view the
Recitation Club as a waste.
It matters to him.
That's what Toya was up to.
[KERO]
What?
He was picking out
some books online.
[KERO]
Huh?
[YUE]
Call me if you learn anything.
Jerk! Why can't he ever be
bothered to say goodbye?
Yue has things to do, too.
[KERO] Yukibunny's the one
with things to do!
Yeah, well, either way, they're
both a lot busier than you.
Oh, what d'you know?
I've got a jam-packed schedule,
thank you very much.
[SAKURA]
Sure, sure.
Anyway, what were you
saying about setting up?
Huh? Oh, yeah. Here's my idea.
I'm honored to help.
Thank you for thinking of me!
[whimpers]
Well, when it
comes to recording...
...who better to ask?
Thanks, Kero. I'm flattered.
I'm sorry. I know
it's your day off.
Did you have stuff to do today?
It's no trouble at all!
Nothing could possibly
be more important
than filming my adorable Sakura.
[TOMOYO] Besides, it made
someone very happy.
Huh?
[footsteps]
[knocking]
[TOMOYO]
Come in.
Sakura, dear!
Oh, hello. I hope I'm not--
[SONOMI] It's been so long!
How are you, darling?
Uh, fine.
You are just as adorable
as ever! And also...
You look more and more
like Nadeshiko by the day.
Really, I do?
[SONOMI]
Yes!
There's always been
a resemblance,
but looking at your eyes now,
I see even more of her.
So you're here today to try
out one of our products.
Or so I've been told.
Yes, the new one, Mother.
It's in the trial stages,
but I'd love to
hear your thoughts.
Sure, okay.
[SONOMI sighs]
Unfortunately, I have
a meeting to attend.
I'll finish it up just as
soon as I can, though.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
[SONOMI] All right, I'll be
back in a bit, Tomoyo.
Okay. Hope you have
a good meeting.
[SONOMI]
I'll see you soon, Sakura!
I'm so glad you're here!
[sighs]
I swear, just a couple
minutes of plushie mode
and all my muscles
tense right up!
A new product, huh?
So what is it?
I'll show you!
[KERO]
Yay!
How's that?
Captured you perfectly.
[KERO laughs]
That's really amazing.
I can't believe something
so small can take pictures,
and fly.
[TOMOYO] I've missed out on
far too many opportunities
to record your
heroic deeds lately,
so I consulted with
my mother's company,
and they made their
fastest prototype yet.
What? They made it
just for this?
Yes!
[SAKURA]
Wha...?
One of the coolest features
is that you can control
it using a smartphone.
Making finer adjustments
is a bit tricky.
There are still some bugs
that need to be worked out.
Hey! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
[TOMOYO]
Let's save that one.
Now then, what do you say
we give your new card a try?
I can film it with
the prototype.
Good idea.
Are you sure it's okay to
do it right here, though?
I checked ahead of time
and no one else will be
in the garden today,
so we shouldn't have
anything to worry about.
Well, let's give it a go!
Key that hides the
forces of dreams.
I bid you to show
me your true form.
Release!
Now, Record!
What?
[KERO]
Hm?
Okay.
[KERO]
It's just sitting there.
[SAKURA]
Uh, yeah.
[TOMOYO] Is there something else
you need to do to activate it?
[KERO]
Hey, she might be right.
It could be waiting for
you to give it an order.
Oh, yeah, right.
Start recording!
[KERO]
Still just sittin' there.
Yep.
Oh, I know.
Maybe it needs more specific
instructions from you.
Like about the
exposure or speed.
But I don't know anything
about all that technical stuff.
You're the camera expert here.
[TOMOYO] Okay, how 'bout telling
it what to record, at least?
[SAKURA]
Hm?
Record the area
directly around me.
[gasps]
[whining]
Did it take pictures?
Any idea how we're
supposed to view them?
[SAKURA] Camera, show me
what you've recorded!
[KERO]
Whoa!
This is better than 3D.
It's like there's actually
another Sakura here!
[SAKURA gasps]
Well, all right. I guess
the mystery is solved.
[KERO]
Isn't this great, Tomoyo?
Kero, stop!
Now that we've got
this Record card,
you'll never miss
anything again!
[TOMOYO] Actually,
that's not entirely true.
I'm sure the Record
card will be useful,
but while it may film her heroic
deeds in perfect detail,
it won't be the same.
Don't you see?
With my eyes and my hands,
I can truly capture Sakura!
Magic or not, there's no card
that could possibly convey
the depth of her
cuteness like I do.
[SAKURA]
Um, Tomoyo...?
[TOMOYO] We must continue
to hurry the development
of this camera.
And of course, one more
that works underwater.
Why underwater?
If we're going to be doing that,
we'll need proper costumes,
with oxygen tanks.
Yes, that's a great idea!
And we'll make them the
cutest oxygen tanks ever.
You'll have to keep the
masks from fogging up, too.
[TOMOYO]
Definitely.
[KERO] How 'bout a
costume with fish on it?
[TOMOYO]
That sounds wonderful!
[SYAORAN]
Looks like you're havin' fun.
Sorry to interrupt.
[SAKURA]
Syaoran!
[KERO]
Heya, kid.
I'm sorry I'm late. I really
wasn't sure where to go.
The person who answered
the door sent me out here.
No, it's all right.
I'm sorry we weren't
there to welcome you.
[TOMOYO]
Doesn't Sakura look adorable?
This is my best work.
Yeah.
[SAKURA gasps]
Uh. Um, well...
Hey! Hey, look!
Check me out. I'm
pretty awesome, huh?
See this? And this? And this?
There it is!
I've got moves, boy!
Thanks so much.
It looks great.
This is starting to get old.
I spend way too much time
pretending to be a stuffed
animal and hiding from people.
[gasps]
[KERO]
It all looks so delicious!
I made sure they
prepared enough for you
to have some as well.
Help yourself.
[KERO]
Alrighty!
Don't mind if I do!
Oh. But first.
[clicking]
What's up?
Just sending some
pics to Spinny.
Does he reply?
[KERO]
No, but I do it anyway.
And now...
Sakura, the cards, too.
Huh?
[KERO]
Lay them in a row on the table.
[SAKURA]
Okay.
[KERO]
Facing me, please.
That's good.
I'm gonna get shots
of all the cards.
Then I'll send 'em to Spinny
and tell him to
show them to Eriol.
Figure the more info they've
got, the better, right?
And we might actually
get a reply this time.
Yeah, good call.
Thank you, Kero.
Now I'll get one of me!
[KERO]
All right, time to send 'em.
Is that the card
from the music room?
[SAKURA]
Hm?
It really does record
things, just like it says.
We were even able
to play it back.
You know, I've never been there
when a new card appears.
I couldn't...
You told me after that
you didn't feel anything.
Yeah.
[SAKURA]
Kero and Yue can't either.
It's so strange.
I wonder what it means.
And what about the dreams?
[SAKURA]
I still don't understand
what they're trying to tell me.
I'm standing there with
some person in a long robe.
Someone who's about my height.
And then, there's a sound.
A sound? Like what?
[SAKURA]
Well, it changed.
When the dreams started,
it was like breaking glass,
but for some reason,
it's a different sound now,
like a big clock ticking.
And I can see pieces of it, too.
Huge gears and clock hands.
It's weird.
Anyway, I just hope it doesn't
mean that trouble's coming.
Hey, uh... did you...?
The wind?
Or was it...?
There it is!
That wasn't just the wind.
Something kind of like
a scrap of cloth, I think.
[SYAORAN]
Tch.
I can't see anything.
[KERO]
Is that it?
All right, that's
no ordinary wind.
[yells]
[gasps]
Whoa! When did you learn to
use a technique like that?
[gasps]
[SYAORAN]
Thunder god, come forth!
It dodged me.
Where is it now?
[SAKURA]
No!
Sakura!
Wait!
[SAKURA]
Release!
Gravitation!
[SAKURA]
Come back!
[sighs]
[SAKURA] Wind?
If it's wind, Gale could--
[SAKURA]
No, that would risk hurting it.
Action!
[whines]
[SAKURA]
Okay, I'll use Siege.
No.
[SAKURA]
Not that way.
I shouldn't capture it by force.
[SAKURA]
Patience.
Be more...
[SAKURA]
Almost.
More...
Be more friendly.
I'd like to be friends
with you, if that's okay.
Great, thank you!
Force without master, heed the
call of my Staff of Dreams,
and become my power.
Secure!
[SAKURA]
"Flight."
Flight.
I'm so glad we're friends now!
[yells]
[KERO]
Sakura!
I always say... it is
better to be prepared.
This is why!
[SAKURA]
Tomoyo. Catch your breath.
[SYAORAN]
You okay?
Tomoyo's cinematic genius
obviously owes a lot
to her incredible persistence.
I'm sorry for getting
so worked up.
Are you sure you're okay now?
Yes, I'm fine.
Besides, there's a more pressing
issue we have to deal with.
[SAKURA, SYAORAN]
Hm?
The card! I need to see
you use it immediately!
[whines]
I'm sure you want to
see it too, right?
Uh. Yeah.
Well, I, uh... I would really
like to see the card in action
if that's okay.
Just the card, right?
[SYAORAN]
Wha--?
No. I didn't mean to--
To what?
Ugh.
If Yue were here,
he'd teach this kid a thing
or two about manners.
If you don't mind, please?
I think we'd all like to see it.
Okay, everything is all set.
Flight, go!
[KERO gasps]
[KERO]
That's awesome, Sakura!
It really does make you fly!
Yep!
[SAKURA] This is great!
I can move however I want.
And it's pretty amazing
how Tomoyo's camera
follows you, too!
Yeah.
[SAKURA giggles]
[SAKURA yelping]
I like this card.
Though the others are
pretty great, too.
If there are more,
they'll be amazing in
their own unique ways.
I know it.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Hey, everybody!
We're back with
"Leave it to Kero,"
or "Leave Kero" for short.
Today, we're gonna take a closer
look at somethin' real special:
Sakura's new key and staff!
This mysterious key came
to Sakura in a dream.
She wears it as a pendant.
This is how it looks as a staff.
Pretty, huh? With that
shiny star in the center.
And the big wings
are super cool.
Not as cool as mine, but--
Anyway, wasn't
Tomoyo's house huge?
I wanna build one like
that for myself someday.
Bye-bye!
[SAKURA] It turns out Akiho
moved into the house
that Eriol used to live in.
She invited me to come
over on the weekend
so she could show me a book.
I wonder what it's about!
Next time, "Sakura, the Clock,
and a Hide-and-Seek Game."
Say it with me now: Release!