[MEILING] Your lunch got soaked
by an exploding fish tank?
[SAKURA]
Yep, totally ruined.
[MEILING]
You finally had a date,
and those cards messed
everything up again.
Nothing's simple
for you two, huh?
[SAKURA]
No kidding.
[MEILING]
That explains why you're making
yet another batch
of rolled omelets.
[SAKURA] Yeah. I'm not
in any hurry, though.
I can finish them up later.
[MEILING] What? Can't you cook
and talk at the same time?
Get it together! You're
in middle school now.
It's time to act your age
and learn to multitask.
Anyway, still no clue why
these cards keep showing up?
[SAKURA]
Nope.
[MEILING]
Any injuries?
[SAKURA] Syaoran and Tomoyo
are fine, don't worry.
[MEILING]
Good, but what about you?
[SAKURA]
Oh! I'm great. Not a scratch.
[MEILING] All right,
but don't lower your guard.
The others would probably
turn on the waterworks
if you got hurt.
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
[MEILING] And I might
even cry a little, too.
Just one or two tears.
[SAKURA]
Getting soft on me?
[MEILING] Okay, I'll let
you get back to cooking.
Sorry to interrupt.
[SAKURA] No problem.
Thanks for calling. Later.
[phone rings]
[SAKURA]
Hm?
[MEILING] Good luck. I hope the
rolled omelets turn out well.
[chuckles]
[SAKURA] All right then,
let's get back to work.
[SAKURA]
And voilà !
[phone ringing]
Hey, Dad. How's it goin'?
[FUJITAKA] Not too bad.
You been keepin' busy?
Yeah. I just finished a
batch of rolled omelets.
[FUJITAKA] I wish I was there
to help eat them.
[SAKURA] Are you gonna be
stuck at work for a while?
[FUJITAKA]
Yeah, we're just getting
to the important
part of the dig.
Looks like it's gonna
rain all next week,
so we wanna get as much done as
we can before the weather turns.
Well, I know your
research is important,
but don't push yourself
too hard, okay?
[FUJITAKA]
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
So what have you been
up to besides cooking?
Uh. Not much.
I did swap out
Mom's photo, though.
I found a great one
in an old album.
[FUJITAKA] I can't wait
to see what you chose.
[SAKURA]
Well, the sooner you come home,
the sooner you'll
get to find out.
[FUJITAKA]
Yeah. I'll do my best.
Oh, tell Toya I called, okay?
'Kay!
[SAKURA]
I'm worried about Dad.
It seems like he's
always busy lately.
I'll work extra hard
around the house
and cook for him more often.
I think that should help some.
Don't you, Mom?
[phone ringing]
I sure seem to be
popular today. Jeez.
[SAKURA gasps]
[AKIHO]
Hi, Sakura.
Hey, how are you?
Here, let me get this open.
[AKIHO] Are you sure you
don't mind me coming over?
I don't wanna bother you.
[SAKURA]
Of course not!
I'm here all alone today.
My dad's at work and
my brother's got class.
I could use the company.
Okay, then.
I'm glad I came.
It smells good!
[SAKURA] I wanted to
make something special
since you were coming over.
You'll stay for dinner, right?
[AKIHO]
Sure, if you don't mind.
[SAKURA] Not at all! Cooking
for two's more fun anywaw.
You told Kaito?
[AKIHO]
Yes. He knows I'm here.
Speaking of Kaito,
he sent these.
He said they were for us
to share while I'm here.
[SAKURA gasps]
Open it now?
[gasps]
They're adorable!
They taste great, too!
[AKIHO] I'm sorry. I got
kind of carried away.
I can't wait!
Let's eat in my room.
I even made iced tea, too.
Great.
It's small, I know.
I was just noticing how
cute and perfect it is!
Oh, thank you.
I guess I'm not
the neatest, though,
'cause my brother is always
telling me to clean it up.
[AKIHO]
Mh-mh!
It looks very clean!
From what I've seen
of your house,
I bet your room's beautiful.
[AKIHO] It isn't special,
really. It's just full of books.
[SAKURA]
I'd still love to see it.
Maybe you can show me the next
time I come to your place?
[AKIHO]
Absolutely!
You know, you and Tomoyo are the
only people I've invited over
since I moved into the house.
No one else?
It probably sounds strange,
but in my family, we
only invite people over
if we're very close to them.
[SAKURA] So since you
asked me and Tomoyo
to come to your house, does that
mean you feel close to us?
[AKIHO]
Yes!
[SAKURA] I mixed a little bit of
soda water into the iced tea.
Do you mind the bubbles?
[AKIHO]
No. I really am glad...
[KERO] I'm glad those
two get along so well.
I wish I'd chosen a different
hiding spot, though.
It's really cramped in here.
[SAKURA]
These are so good!
I guess we shouldn't eat too
many before dinner, though, huh?
You can save the rest.
Kaito said they'll
stay good for a while.
I bet your dad and
brother would like some.
Yeah, I'll put them away
after I have just one mor--
Is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing!
[chuckles nervously]
[SAKURA]
Kaito sure knows his way
around the kitchen, doesn't he?
There's nothing he can't do.
I've been trying to take
care of more things myself
to make it easier on him,
but I think it might
be a lost cause.
Hey, I'm sure there's plenty
of stuff you're good at.
[AKIHO]
There really isn't, though!
I'm extremely clumsy.
And I'm hopeless when it comes
to cooking and sewing.
Ask Tomoyo. I'm sure she'd
teach you how to sew.
[SAKURA] She made this.
And this. And this.
All these costumes are
Tomoyo originals.
[SAKURA] She did everything
for them by herself,
from the designs to the sewing.
Amazing!
I never know what she's
gonna come up with next,
and they're really comfy, too.
She's so talented!
But what did you
need costumes for?
[SAKURA gasps]
Oh, well, I, uh...
[KERO]
Ah!
Can't exactly pass those off
as regular street clothes.
They don't even
look like something
you'd wear to a fancy party.
I was in a play. Yeah!
That's why I have them.
[KERO]
All right! Good save!
I wish I could've seen it.
Oh. Do you have
photos from the play?
[SAKURA]
Not of these outfits.
But I do have some
of another costume.
You played a princess?
Um. Yeah.
[AKIHO] It looks like all
the others were in it, too.
I don't see Tomoyo, though.
[SAKURA] She wasn't in the play
itself. She did sing, though.
See this picture?
I'm not surprised. She has
such a wonderful voice.
Yep!
[AKIHO]
Who is this?
[SAKURA] Oh, that's Meiling.
She's Syaoran's cousin.
She's back in Hong Kong now.
[AKIHO]
She's very pretty, isn't she?
[SAKURA] Yeah! I was actually
talking to her earlier today.
[AKIHO] Oh, and there's Li.
Is he playing a prince?
Yes.
[AKIHO]
You both look fantastic.
Is there a video
of it by any chance?
[SAKURA]
Oh. Yeah, actually.
Say you'll let me
see it, Sakura!
Okay, sure. But, um,
how about next time?
Perfect! I can't wait!
[gasps]
So I guess this was
a school production.
It looks like so much fun!
[AKIHO giggles]
[SAKURA] What about you? Do you
ever like to get dressed up?
[AKIHO] Occasionally.
When I go to a party.
If you have any pictures,
I'd love to see them sometime.
What? You really would?
Why not? I'm sure
you look great.
[AKIHO] Well, I don't
know if I'd say that.
But, okay. I'll
show you sometime.
[giggles]
[SAKURA] Looks like it's
about time for dinner.
Would you come and
help me set the table?
[AKIHO] Sure! I can
carry this if you want.
[KERO] Don't forget about me!
I expect leftovers!
[SAKURA]
You can leave the door open.
[AKIHO]
Okay.
Should I just put this
down over here?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm!
Hey, you don't mind
onions, do you?
They're fine.
[SAKURA] Is there
anything you don't like?
[AKIHO]
No, not really. Uh...
[SAKRUA]
Huh?
Actually, yes. There's konjac .
[SAKURA]
Really?
I know the konjac can't
help being the way it is.
It's just the texture.
I feel the same!
I can't stand it either!
So you understand?
But don't worry!
Even if we don't like
konjac , it's okay.
Because there are people we
love who will eat it for us!
Like, at my house,
there's my brother.
Well, now that you mention it,
Kaito likes konjac , too.
Right! So it's okay!
Yes! I'm so relieved!
The konjac won't be
lonely after all.
Yeah!
[GIRL chuckling]
[KERO]
Well, I'm glad we settled that!
[SAKURA] I hope everything
turned out okay.
I know the bread'll
be good at least.
My dad made it earlier,
and he knows what he's doin'.
[gasps]
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
[BOTH]
Thank you for the food.
So it's okay?
Wow! Yes! It's wonderful!
That's good to hear!
I've made it a bunch of times,
and I thought it tasted fine,
but I was still a
little nervous.
It's seasoned very well.
I can't say what exactly,
but there's something different
about it from other beef stews.
It's the miso.
I add a little to it.
It has a secret
ingredient! How fancy!
It's not that special,
just makes it a bit richer.
A little cooking trick
my brother taught me.
[AKIHO]
Well, it seems like a good one.
Does everyone in
your family cook?
Yeah. We take turns, see?
When I was younger, I could
only do really simple stuff,
but now that I'm older,
I'm allowed to fry
and chop things, too.
So does that mean
you made this?
Oh, yeah.
I'm still trying to get
the hang of it, though.
Delicious! I think
I'll have another one.
What about you, Akiho?
Does anyone in your
family like to cook?
No, everyone is
always too busy.
So the people who work for us
take care of things like that.
Like how Kaito looks after you?
Yes.
That's pretty amazing.
You'd think, but look at you
and all the things you
can do on your own.
To be so independent,
that's what's amazing.
You're giving me
too much credit.
I do my best, but my
friends and family
still help me all the time.
Will you teach me how to cook?
Then there will be at
least one thing I do!
[SAKURA gasps]
But I'm really not
that good, and besides,
I'm sure Kaito would be a
much better teacher than me!
He's the more experienced one.
I'm hoping to learn
without him knowing.
That's why I asked
if you'd do it.
[SAKURA] Oh, I understand.
You wanna cook for him.
And you want it
to be a surprise.
I know exactly how you feel.
You wanna make something special
for the person that you like.
[SAKURA]
To show him how much you care.
Yes.
All right! Then we'll
learn together.
Together?
Yeah.
There's still plenty of stuff
I don't know about cooking,
so I'll have to work hard
right along with you.
Great!
Want some more stew?
There's a ton left.
Absolutely!
Oh, I forgot!
I just borrowed this cool book
on cat's cradle
from the library.
Wanna check it
out after dinner?
That sounds perfect.
[SAKURA]
Here we go!
Just let me know
if it's not enough.
You can always have thirds.
[SAKURA]
Hm?
Hey, Akiho?
[AKIHO gasps]
Didn't sleep too
well last night?
I slept fine. I don't
know what's wrong.
I just feel so tired.
Maybe you're getting sick.
Do you need to lie down?
[AKIHO]
No. I don't need...
Are you okay?
Sakura, what's goi--?
Sakura, what's going
on down here?
It's Akiho.
She just fell asleep.
[KERO]
What? Really?
Please wake up!
Are you all right?
[KERO] Was she feeling
sick or something?
She seemed fine during dinner.
But then...
Kero, look!
At what?
Uh?
Do you think that sparkly,
floaty thing put her to sleep?
That's my guess.
She's not hurt.
Just out like a light.
[SAKURA] Yeah. I need to
take care of that thing.
If I don't, who knows
when she'll wake up?
[KERO] It looks like we've got
another card to deal with.
Just hang in there.
I'll fix this.
Well?
Yeah!
[KERO]
Got you, floaty thing!
[screams]
Are you okay?
[KERO]
Forget about me! Go after it!
Right!
Come back!
[KERO]
Sakura!
Well? Did you get it?
Ah! What the heck is this?!
That's not what the world's
supposed to look like!
It's like the house
has been transported
to another dimension
or something!
Do you sense anything?
[KERO]
No. I've still got nothin'.
We gotta catch it somehow!
You ready?
Let's do it!
I'm kind of having fun.
Things haven't gotten
this crazy in a long time.
Quit dartin' around, would you?
Come on, you sparkly
pest, hold still!
[SAKURA]
Release!
Gravitation!
It's too fast. So what now?
Use Siege to capture it.
I'll try...
Siege!
[BOTH yelp]
What was that?
I think the space that we're
in now might be a card.
[KERO]
So using Siege is a no-go.
[SAKURA] What's our next plan?
Try flanking it again?
[KERO]
That thing is crazy-quick.
I think we're gonna have to
find some way to ambush it.
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
I might have an idea.
If we can keep it
from noticing us...
Kero, go after it!
Sure thing!
Come here, you! I'm gonna
get you this time!
Okay, I see what you're doin'!
Now, Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Secure!
[SAKURA] "Snooze." So this is
what made Akiho fall asleep.
[KERO]
Sakura.
I'm sorry.
Much longer and that would've
been eternal sleep for me.
[KERO]
Quick! We've gotta hurry!
[SAKURA]
Right!
Force without master, heed the
call of my Staff of Dreams,
and become my power.
Secure!
[SAKURA]
"Labyrinth." It's like a maze.
Now I get it.
We couldn't trap the
other card using Siege
because we were already
trapped by this one.
[SAKURA screams]
[KERO]
This is where we ended up?
[SAKURA] We have to get inside
while Akiho's still asleep.
[KERO]
Be careful!
[AKIHO] I can't believe
I fell asleep like that.
I'm so embarrassed!
No! It's okay!
[KERO] Funny story,
there was this magic card...
[SAKURA] This just means you
have to come back sometime.
It'll be great. We have
a library downstairs.
I'm sure my dad won't mind
if I ask to show you.
So how about a do-over?
A do-over?
[bell rings]
[SAKURA]
Huh? Just a sec, okay?
Yes, hello? Who is it?
[KAITO]
Good evening. It's Kaito.
[AKIHO] Thank you for coming to
get me. I know you're very busy.
Please, think nothing of it.
Miss Kinomoto, thank you
for your hospitality.
Please just call me Sakura.
Really?
[SAKURA] I'd prefer it,
if you don't mind.
In that case, please
allow me to thank you
for your hospitality, Sakura.
Um, sure.
[AKIHO] Thanks again for
having me. I had a great time.
[SAKURA]
So did I. I'm glad you came.
[BOTH]
I hope soon we can do it again!
[KAITO chuckles]
Oh. Do forgive me.
Please. I couldn't help myself.
[KAITO] Sakura seems
like a wonderful person.
She really is.
She's nice, and
pretty, and smart,
and you can tell that she truly
cares about other people.
[KAITO]
Including you?
Yes.
[KAITO]
I'm glad to hear that.
[SAKURA] We're gonna be great
friends. I can feel it!
Hidey-howdy-ho!
It's "Leave it to
Kero" time, folks.
I know you all work hard,
and what better way
is there to kick back and relax,
than by listening to
me talk about--?
Ugh. Okay, fine.
The battle costume Tomoyo
made for that kid.
This is her own interpretation
of the ceremonial outfit
he wore back in
elementary school.
It's tailored perfectly,
so it's super easy to move in.
Man, I'm so jealous!
Apparently the kid also
picked up the ability
to pull a sword from his hand.
That's one heck of
a party trick, huh?
Bye-Bye!
[SAKURA] I've come to Penguin
Park, and it's awful!
The playground equipment
is upside down.
I have to fix this before
it makes the news again!
Next time, "Sakura and
the Upside-Down Penguin."
Say it with me: Release!