[GIRL A]
Morning!
[GIRL B] Morning! Did you see
the new episode last night?
[GIRL C]
First period is English, right?
[TOMOYO]
You got a new card?
Yeah, see?
Also...
...a key.
You can see right through it.
[SAKURA]
Except...
Turn it over and the
other side isn't visible.
That's crazy.
First, the cards you
already had turned clear,
and now you've recovered
an entirely new card.
So many strange things
keep happening.
But still, there's a far more
important issue at hand.
What is it?
I didn't get to film
your first new card capture.
Do you have any idea
how sad that makes me?
Just look!
I had a beautiful new outfit
ready for you and everything!
[KERO]
One for me, too?
Of course, silly!
There you go.
Yay! Yay!
She hasn't changed,
has she? Not at all.
[SAKURA chuckles]
Oh, well.
What matters most is that
you weren't hurt, right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
[SAKURA]
So what do you think?
I don't sense any
power but yours.
Neither do I.
But I'm still confused.
Why are these things
happening in Tomoeda again?
[bell tolls]
Let's talk more
about it later, 'kay?
Sure thing.
Sakura.
Hey, good morning!
Same to you!
Hi, everybody. Good morning.
Whew, we made it. Looks
like we beat the teacher.
[CHIHARU]
Hey, there!
You two having a
good morning so far?
Yeah, it's not bad. Thanks!
So what have you got there?
[CHIHARU] Here. I brought
you my cheesecake recipe.
Oh, perfect.
Thank you so much!
Please, it's nothing special.
Sure it is!
I've been wanting to
try out this recipe
since the first time I had it.
And the fruit sauce you
served with it was divine!
We'll try making it today.
Hope we don't mess it up.
[CHIHARU]
Let me know how it turns out.
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm!
[MORITA]
Good morning!
Now, take your seats, please.
--[STUDENTS] Yes, ma'am!
--See you later.
[SAKURA] If the cheesecake
turns out well,
I'll share it with everyone.
Including Syaoran.
[MORITA]
All right.
As you all know,
your club applications
are due to be turned in
by the end of the week.
I hope you've made
your decisions.
Which club are you going for?
Have you picked yet?
Do you know which
club you're joining?
Yeah, how about you?
I'm thinking of applying
for the Chorus Club again,
like in elementary school.
Yeah! I wanna stick
with cheerleading again.
I wonder if Chiharu will, too.
[TOMOYO] Hmm. Let's ask
her about it later.
And what about Li? Any idea
which club he'll join?
I don't really know.
Yeah, it's kind of hard to guess
since he wasn't in
any clubs before.
He's got a lot of options.
I'm sure he'll find
something to enjoy.
And you know, if he joins
one of the sports clubs,
the Cheerleading Club
would go root for him.
Obviously, that's something
you'd wanna catch on film,
and I promise I would be more
than happy to help you out.
[SAKURA squeals]
[CHIHARU]
I'm going for cheerleading, too!
We'll be together again.
Yeah, it'll be great!
I decided to apply
for the Drama Club.
Apparently, they put on
plays written by students,
so hopefully I'll get to see
my work in action sometime.
Well, the script you
wrote for our play
in elementary school
was really good.
I'm sure they'll love you, and
I can't wait to see your plays!
Same here!
You're gonna be great.
I hope so!
What about you, Yamazaki?
The Basketball Club scouted me.
If nothing else, you've got
the tall thing going for you.
[TAKASHI] If we had a Rakugo
Story-telling Society,
that would've been
my top choice.
[CHIHARU]
Well, we don't.
Exactly, and that's why I'm
joining the Lacrosse Club.
[CHIHARU] That doesn't make
any sense, and you know it.
[TAKASHI laughs]
What about you, Li?
I don't think
I'll join anything.
Really? Why not?
[SYAORAN] I only just
got back from Hong Kong.
There's still a lot
I need to do.
Oh, bummer. What sort of
things need to get done?
All kinds of stuff.
There's a lot of organizing to
do after a move, you know?
Well, I hope you can join a
club once you're all settled in
and things calm down a little.
Yeah. I hope so, too.
[SAKURA]
Did Wei come back with you?
[SYAORAN]
No, just me.
But he's gonna come and
check on me in a while.
[SAKURA]
What about Meiling?
You exchange messages
with her all the time.
I'm sure she keeps you updated.
That's true.
She is really good about sending
us fun pictures and videos.
[CHIHARU] The outfit she wore
for that festival a while ago
was so adorable!
Yeah, I thought it
was perfect for her.
I used it as inspiration
for something.
Yeah, for what?
An outfit that's going
to look wonderful on you!
Now that I think of it,
I don't remember seeing you
in the photo with her, Li.
Yeah, you're right. I didn't go.
There was something else
I needed to take care of,
so I had to miss the festival.
That's really too bad.
Could've used your
outfit for inspiration.
For what?
To make something that would
look wonderful on you,
of course!
[TAKASHI]
Speaking of festivals,
there are many such celebrations
all across the globe,
but a particularly unusual
one occurs in Bulgaria.
It involves yogurt and
salted fish guts, which--
Our lunch break is almost over.
Less talking, more eating.
You'll be doing us all a favor.
[TAKASHI]
Yum.
[SAKURA, SYAORAN] But I wanted
to hear more about the festival!
[NAOKO]
You two are the best.
We've already said it to Li,
but please, Sakura,
never change.
[TOMOYO giggles]
[SAKURA]
Hmm...
[CHIHARU]
Okay?
It's pretty tough, actually.
[CHIHARU]
Hm.
I bet Naoko would have no
problem with this at all.
[chuckles]
Yeah, you're right.
She is pretty gifted
when it comes to drawing.
[CHIHARU]
Can I see yours?
Uh. Um, sure.
[CHIHARU]
Nice! It looks really good.
Oh, you think so?
Truly! Very lifelike.
Thanks for saying so,
but it's nowhere near as
good as the drawings you do.
That's nonsense.
Both your drawings are
lovely in their own way.
Don't sell yourselves short.
Yeah, but look at yours.
There's something so
sophisticated about it.
[TOMOYO]
Thanks.
I'm still trying to decide
how I feel about it, though.
[CHIHARU] It reminds me
of a design illustration.
That's not too
surprising, really.
When I make new outfits,
I always draw out designs first.
Really? I didn't
realize you did that.
[TOMOYO]
Sometimes I sketch the outfits
directly onto pattern paper.
But I always make sure
to draw my designs
for the finished product
so I won't forget them.
Wow, that's amazing!
Next time we go to Home Ec.,
will you help me
with some sewing stuff
I'm having a hard
time figuring out?
I'd be happy to!
[CHIHARU]
Ah! Great, thanks!
[BOYS shouting]
[SAKURA]
Uh?
--[net rustles]
--[whistle blows]
Wow, look at Li go.
Pretty athletic, isn't he?
Yeah, he really is.
[CHIHARU] I hope things settle
down so he can join a club soon.
Definitely.
[KERO]
Did I do it right?
Yes. That should be fine.
Everything's looking
good on my end, too.
Let's see now.
According to Chiharu's recipe,
the next step is...
Place softened cream
cheese into a bowl.
Then, stir continuously
until it's smooth.
I think we've
almost got it now.
Just like this.
Add confectioner's sugar
to the whipping cream.
Honey makes a good
addition, too.
Beat the mixture at medium
speed until it forms soft peaks,
then add the cream
cheese and lemon juice
and mix until all ingredients
are thoroughly combined.
Like this?
Then we add the cream
cheese like this.
Oh, boy!
Place gelatin powder and a small
amount of water in a bowl,
then microwave.
Add the melted gelatin to
the mixture while beating.
Like this.
Pour mixture into prepared pan,
straining it through a sieve.
Like this!
Let it set in the refrigerator
for two to three hours,
until firm.
[TOMOYO, SAKURA, KERO]
Like this.
Top finished cheesecake
with sliced fresh fruit,
sprigs of mint, or fruit sauce,
as desired, and enjoy!
[KERO, SAKURA, TOMOYO]
The rare cheesecake...
--[SAKURA, KERO] ...is done!
--[TOMOYO giggles]
[KERO]
Ohh!
[SAKURA]
Mmm!
So good!
I love Chiharu's recipes.
They turn out perfectly.
Yummy!
The secret to true happiness
is eating large amounts
of delicious food!
[SAKURA]
I definitely agree.
With all that's happened, I've
got a lot on my mind lately.
The new staff and card,
Eriol not calling me back.
It's been pretty rough.
But spending all my time
worrying won't help.
Whether I'm at
school or at home,
I'll just do what I
need to do every day.
If something bad happens,
all I can do is try my
best to make it better.
You're amazing, Sakura.
You know that, right?
No, please, I'm really not.
That is true.
You're in middle school and you
still hit snooze on your alarm
and then have to rush to
get ready in the morning,
running around like
a frantic chicken
with a bad case of bedhead.
That's not nice!
Kero!
[TOYA]
Hey, I'm home.
Hi, Toya. Welcome home.
Thanks.
[SAKURA]
Yukito!
Good to see you.
Sakura. Tomoyo.
[TOMOYO]
I hope I'm not intruding.
[TOYA]
Hm?
So, Tomoyo, are you
spending the night, then?
I am. We're having a sleepover.
[YUKITO]
I'm staying, too.
Really? You're
spending the night?
[YUKITO]
Mh-hm!
Do you mind?
No, it's great to have you!
What's so great about it?
What do you mean?
"Great to have him,"
so you can do what?
Well, show my hospitality.
Oh, yeah? How?
[growls]
By... By, you know...
Just hearing that's
enough for me.
Thank you for the hospitality.
You're very welcome!
It's too bad my
camcorder's upstairs.
[KERO]
Typical Tomoyo.
I'm cooking. How's okonomiyaki ?
[KERO]
Mmm!
I love okonomiyaki !
Yeah, same here.
Okay. Modanyaki, too?
We have soba.
Modanyaki !
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Ke--
"Ke"?
Ke-- Ke--
Ke-Key to good health.
That's what
modanyaki is, y'know?
Key to good health?
[SAKURA] Yeah, with all
the cabbage and stuff.
[SAKURA screams]
[TOYA]
Hmm...
Not bad, I guess.
Stealing mine after I set
some aside just for you?
Well, now you don't get any.
Keep your hands off!
They get along so well.
They really do!
[SAKURA]
Stay away...!
[KERO] Guys. Stayin' in plushie
mode for this long isn't easy.
[SAKURA]
Ugh. He's still such a jerk.
You'd think college would
make him act more mature.
I dunno.
Somebody who makes
okonomiyaki that's this tasty
can't be all bad, can they?
You're just a glutton. You
only think with your stomach.
Making delicious food is a
redeeming quality in anybody.
[KERO chuckles]
Okay, that's the perfect length.
[SAKURA] It's been so long
since I've worn one of these.
It looks so beautiful on you!
You know, wearing these outfits
always seems to cheer me up.
They give me a confidence boost.
Thank you for making them.
I'm happy to!
[TOMOYO] All right. Now to mark
the occasion with a video.
I really shouldn't be
surprised, should I?
Woo-hoo!
[TOMOYO] That's it, smile!
You look so cute.
Hey, did you see that?
Huh?
What's goin' on?
I'm confused.
How did we get here?
Weren't we in your room
just a second ago?
[SAKURA]
Yeah, we were, but now...
[SAKURA] What is this?
Maybe I'm having another dream?
[SAKURA]
Ow!
--Well? Can you feel this?
--[SAKURA] Stop! That hurts!
Which tells us...
Whatever this is, it's no dream.
[SAKURA]
So we're awake.
[SAKURA] Which means this most
likely has something to do
with my new staff and card.
Well, yeah. Seems that way.
[SAKURA]
Okay. So what is this place?
It's like before.
I don't sense anything.
I'm going to see if
there's a door somewhere.
[TOMOYO]
Be careful, Sakura.
I will.
[KERO]
Well?
Just like you said.
There's nothing.
[gasps]
What is it?
It's like the wall
is running from me.
[TOMOYO]
Huh?
[yelps]
[KERO]
Whoa! What the heck?
There're no doors or windows...
It stretches when pushed...
[SAKURA]
How do we get out?
[KERO yelling]
[KERO yells]
Seriously, what is the deal
with these stupid walls?
[chuckles]
Great, now what?
Tomoyo!
[TOMOYO]
Sakura!
I don't like this place!
What's it made of?
It feels so weird.
Uh! Hey, I know what
it is! That stuff!
C'mon. You know what
I mean. That stuff!
What stuff?
It's all bouncy and stretchy.
[SAKURA] I don't know
what you're talking about!
That stuff! It stretches,
then contracts. You know!
[gasps]
--[SAKURA, TOMOYO] Rubber!
--Yeah!
It's all rubber. Okay.
So it's sort of like we're
trapped inside a big balloon.
That makes sense.
In that case, what would
happen if we popped it?
But how would we do that?
Good thing I was just
working on your dress.
[BOTH gasp]
Key that hides the
forces of dreams.
I bid you to show
me your true form.
Release!
Are we ready to go?
[KERO]
Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Right.
Force without master, heed
the call of my Staff of Dreams.
Become my power.
Secure!
[SAKURA]
The Siege card. Wow.
[knocking]
What was that noise
a second ago?
We were playing with a balloon,
but it ran into something
sharp and popped.
We're very sorry
for bothering you.
[TOYA]
Hm.
Try to keep it down, okay?
Yeah. Sure.
[door closes]
--[SAKURA sighs]
--Oh, wow.
That was close,
but we pulled it off.
What'cha thinking?
Another one.
Why is this happening?
[SPINNY]
Ruby is asleep, finally.
She kept saying she wanted
to go to Japan at once.
Kaho was able to calm her down.
I see.
[SPINNY]
You're not going to call
a certain young lady in Japan?
She's waiting to hear from you,
right? Shouldn't you reply?
Perhaps, but not yet.
Not until the time comes.
[gasps]
Wait, no!
No! Not that way!
No! You can't go!
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Who are you? Please!
[SAKURA] The cards are
still totally clear.
Whatever's going on,
I hope they'll be all right.
[KERO groans]
[SAKURA]
Huh?
It's not a real modanyaki
without squid and pork.
[SAKURA chuckles]
[SAKURA]
I'll do what I can.
There must be a reason these new
cards have started showing up.
I'll just have to
find out what it is.
Whatever it takes, I'll do it.
I'll find a way to
restore the cards.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
How's everyone doin' out there?
The "Leave it to Kero"
segment has begun,
and we're kicking off
our first installment
with a look at the Tomoeda
Middle School uniform.
Snazzy, huh?
Black is its base color,
with red lines to
create a focal point.
The insignia on
the left shoulder
is the same as
Tomoeda Elementary's.
Ha-ha!
Oh, this is the boys' uniform.
I'll be bringing you all kinds
of handy information
in this segment every week,
so make sure you tune in!
Bye-bye!
[SAKURA]
I submitted my application
to the Cheerleading Club!
I'm so excited!
But it's raining non-stop.
Could this be the
work of a card?
Next time, "Sakura's
Heavy Rain Alert."
Say it with me: Release!