[KAITO] You seem like you're
in good mood this morning.
[AKIHO] Really?
What makes you think that?
It's just, you've been
smiling quite a bit.
[AKIHO]
I guess it's because I was able
to read more of that book.
So last time, one
of Alice's friends
grew kitty ears and a tail,
but every time Alice tried
to tell her about them,
they would suddenly disappear.
I think I told you
about that, right?
[KAITO]
Yes.
[AKIHO] Well, in the
next part of the story,
all of Alice's friends turn
into different animals.
There's a bear, a squirrel,
and even a sheep.
That sounds rather interesting.
I thought so, too!
And you, Akiho? What kind
of animal would you be?
[AKIHO]
Good question.
How about a rabbit?
Yes, I do love rabbits!
[KAITO] What happened next?
In the book you're reading?
[AKIHO] So then, the weather
takes a turn for the worse.
Alice was really scared
for her friends,
but she refused to give up
and was able to turn
them all back to normal.
[KAITO]
That's a nice story.
Alice sounds like she's
working hard. I'm glad.
[AKIHO]
Uh?
Kaito?
Are you going out again today?
Yes. I have plans
at a friend's house.
That sounds like fun.
I hope you have a good time.
Thank you, I will.
[KERO]
Go. Go. Let me through!
You little--
Try this on for size!
Boo-yah!
Did ya see me
destroy those guys?
I'm almost done.
Don't look in the mirror yet.
Like I'm really gonna peek.
[KERO] I can't believe her
hair is more interesting
than my awesome driving skills.
[SAKURA]
There.
I'm finished.
'Kay. So what do you think?
I've never braided
long hair before.
Looks good, thanks!
Aw, yay!
If your hair were longer,
this style would be
super cute on you.
[SAKURA]
You think so?
[MEILING]
Have you always had short hair?
[SAKURA] Yeah. My dad helps
me keep it trimmed up.
[MEILING]
What? You don't go to a salon?
Nah. It's just
always been my dad.
Oh, and Yukito cuts
Toya's hair for him.
Who cuts your dad's?
Toya!
[KERO]
Do I want a V8 engine?
Or a Straight-8?
But if I go with a Straight-6,
I can reduce my weight,
which'll really enhance
the seed of my kart.
Tough choice!
You know, come to think of it,
Syaoran's mom used to cut
his hair when he was little.
She told me something
about how it's dangerous
for magic users to expose
their necks to blades
before they're strong enough.
He hated salons because of
that, so Wei had to cut it.
Isn't that crazy?
Does he cut yours?
I always go to a salon.
Ah. I see.
Still though, I wonder
where he gets his hair cut
now that he lives here.
[SAKURA sighs]
What's wrong?
[SAKURA] I've just been
worried about Syaoran
ever since the other day.
[MEILING] Didn't he send
you a message, though?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
But...
[MEILING]
But written words don't tell you
if he's really okay, huh?
[MEILING]
So why don't you call him?
[SAKURA] What if he's
sleeping and I wake him?
Fine, what if I do it, then?
[phone ringing]
[MEILING]
Syaoran, zou san !
Did I wake you?
Have you had breakfast yet?
Jeez, you'll never recover
if you don't eat something.
Well, yeah, Kinomoto did.
You tell her.
I'm not your messenger.
It's for you.
[MEILING]
Take it.
[SAKURA]
Um, hello?
[SYAORAN]
Sakura?
[SAKURA]
Yeah, it's me.
[SYAORAN] I'm sorry if I worried
you. I'm doing fine now.
[SAKURA]
Are you sure?
[SYAORAN] Yep. In fact, I was
just making something to eat.
Try not to push yourself.
Also... get lots of rest.
[SYAORAN]
I will.
[SYAORAN] I hope Meiling
isn't being a bother.
[SAKURA]
Not at all.
She's the one who's
been taking care of me.
[SYAORAN]
She loves lookin' after others,
but doesn't always come off
that way with her personality.
Hey! Give that back!
She's really nice.
[SYAORAN] Aren't you going
to Daidouji's place today?
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
[SYAORAN]
I'm sorry I can't go, too.
Don't worry about it.
Focus on getting better.
[SYAORAN]
Thanks. See ya.
[SAKURA]
Oh, hold on a minute.
[KERO] You're not even payin'
attention to the game!
[crash]
Never mind. Bye, Syaoran.
[KERO groans]
Sounds like he's okay.
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
[MEILING]
Do you feel better now?
[SAKURA]
I do. Thank you for calling him.
[MEILING]
I'm always happy to bug him.
Look, maybe it's
just my opinion,
but I think you worry too much
about the little
things, Kinomoto.
[KERO] Hey, you guys,
we better make tracks
or we're gonna be late.
[SAKURA gasps]
Good morning, Akiho!
[AKIHO]
Good morning to you both!
Thank you for inviting me.
Morning!
[AKIHO] Are you sure it's
okay for me to tag along?
I don't want to intrude.
[MEILING]
Oh, come on, not you, too!
You worry more than Kinomoto.
If it was a problem, we
wouldn't have invited you.
Besides, Daidouji is the one
who technically did
all of the inviting,
so you'll just
have to blame her.
Amusez-vous, oui ?
Merci beaucoup.
C'est très bien, Meiling !
[whines]
What's your problem?
That's like basic
Middle School French.
You sound so fluent, though!
You're both amazing.
[MEILING] Syaoran could help
teach you some French.
Or Shinomoto, maybe.
[SAKURA]
Hm?
Sure, I'd love to help!
Really? Wow, thank you!
[BOTH giggle]
Wow, it's almost like
Kinomoto has a clone.
Uh-huh!
[doorbell rings]
[TOMOYO]
Hi, come on in!
[MEILING] I always forget
how huge this place is.
[SAKURA]
I know.
I remember how blown away
I was my first time here.
It was crazy!
[SAKURA]
Hello, anyone there?
[SONOMI]
Sakura!
It's so good to see you!
You look adorable,
but that's nothing new!
Thanks, Ms. Daidouji.
But wait, does this mean you
don't have to work today?
I cleared out my schedule
for the afternoon.
Free time's important, right?
[TOMOYO]
Mother spent all of yesterday
rescheduling her meetings.
[SONOMI]
Yep!
It's worth it, though.
It's nice to see you, Meiling,
and you must be Akiho.
Thanks for having us.
[AKIHO] It's very nice
to meet you, ma'am.
You have a lovely home.
My, you're so polite!
I hope you'll all stay
for snacks and tea later.
Akiho, is it true you've
also lived in England?
[AKIHO]
Yes.
[SONOMI] Well, I hope my tea can
compare to what you're used to.
[MEILING] I'm sensing we should
save Kero some snacks.
[TOMOYO] ...she's very
excited about today.
Mother, let's not keep
our guests waiting.
[SONOMI] Right, of course,
please make yourselves at home.
[GIRLS]
Thank you very much.
Ah! Afternoon tea,
yay! Afternoon tea!
[AKIHO] Your mother seems like
such a fun person, Tomoyo!
[TOMOYO]
She's wonderful.
[MEILING]
And powerful to boot!
[SAKURA] Huh? We're
not going to your room?
[TOMOYO] Not today. There's
something I wanna show you.
Here, through these doors.
[gasps]
[MEILING]
Wow!
[TOMOYO] Come on in.
Sit anywhere you'd like.
Let's go sit in the front row!
'Kay!
No way. You watch
movies in here?
Well, sometimes we do.
Mostly, I review footage of you.
[SAKURA whines]
[MEILING]
Hey, Daidouji! What's this?
Go ahead and try it. Go on!
It's lemonade!
[TOMOYO]
Yep!
[MEILING]
Oh! Oh my gosh...
So what did you wanna show us?
[STUDENT A] The following
is a play presented
by the students of class Six-Two
from Tomoeda Elementary School.
Please enjoy the show.
Whoa, seriously?
[AKIHO gasps]
Yay!
[SAKURA whines]
Come on! Akiho has been waiting
to see it after all, right?
[MEILING]
Look, I'm in it, too!
[SAKURA]
Aww. Why this movie?
[MEILING]
What's the big deal?
It'll be fun to watch.
Here, Shinomoto.
You sit in the middle since
you've never seen it.
[AKIHO] Are you sure? Okay,
if you insist. Thank you.
[TOMOYO]
Then you sit over there, Sakura.
Right next to Akiho.
[SAKURA whines]
[gasps]
It's wonderful! And all
of our friends are in it.
What's really cool
is that Daidouji
made the costumes for everyone.
[AKIHO]
Wow, really?
Yep.
[MEILING] Then all you have
to do is follow his lead...
[MEILING] I forgot how
awesome my acting was!
[AKIHO]
Yes, you sound amazing!
[MEILING]
Right? I'm a natural.
[giggles]
Did you know that Syaoran
and I were actually living
in Hong Kong at the
time of this play?
But we were back visiting
during summer break,
and they were practicing
for the festival,
so they put us in it!
Syaoran didn't want to
participate at first,
but then Yamazaki got hurt
so he had to stand in for him.
[AKIHO]
Sounds like a fun time.
[MEILING] Thank goodness
Syaoran's acting got better.
He played a princess
in the play before that
and it was not easy to watch.
[AKIHO] Maybe next time
we could see that one.
[SAKURA] It would be
better if the magic stone
we've been fighting over
disappeared forever.
What I believe in my heart
is no one person should have
that kind of magical power.
[SYAORAN]
Absolutely!
[MEILING]
There's Syaoran!
I couldn't agree with you more.
Who're you?
I can't say...
[MEILING] He learned all his
lines for the play in one day,
and the dance steps.
[AKIHO]
That's impressive!
Mine, too!
He sounds great.
It's amazing. Everything
about it feels so natural.
You'd never watch this
and think he's acting.
It's almost like he's saying
what's in his heart.
[KERO] This is torment,
plain an' simple!
Hang in there, Sakura!
[SYAORAN]
We're very similar, aren't we?
[SAKURA]
No. I can't.
These feelings I have for you...
I shouldn't say them.
So I won't say it.
Please, I beg of you.
Move on with your life
and just forget about me!
Promise that you'll banish
me from your heart!
[SYAORAN]
Princ--
[gasps]
[AKIHO]
Huh?
[TOMOYO] There was an
earthquake during that scene.
So in the end, we never got
to finish performing the play.
[AKIHO gasps]
Did anyone get hurt?
We were fine.
[SAKURA]
If you need me,
I'll just be here
dying of embarrassment.
[AKIHO] There's nothing
to be embarrassed about!
Your performance was
really breathtaking!
Actually, I have
more to show you.
Hold on, I'll put it up.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Thank you. Unfortunately,
I'm not good at dancing.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
No need to fret.
We'll find you a partner who has
a natural talent for dancing,
then all you have to
do is follow his lead.
I wish the magic stone
would just disappear forever.
What I believe deep in my heart
is no one person should have
that kind of magical power.
[NAOKO]
Sorry, Sakura.
Instead, can we try "It would
be better if the magic stone
we've been fighting over
disappeared forever"?
You really recorded
our rehearsals?
[TOMOYO] Only occasionally.
When the teacher said I could.
I just have a few pieces from
different parts of the day.
You'll probably need to
practice the dance steps, too.
So I'll go ask the teacher
to write them down.
Ideally, I would teach you
all the dancing stuff
myself, but I can't.
[CHIHARU]
Okay, I'm back!
Now we should be
able to get started.
[NAOKO]
Great! Thanks for doing that.
[CHIHARU]
Since Yamazaki is hurt,
we'll do our best to
get you up to speed.
Don't worry, Li!
[TAKASHI chuckles]
[CHIHARU] Oh, ha-ha...
That wasn't a joke.
[NAOKO] Okay, why don't
you and Li get started
on learning the dance?
[CHIHARU] One, two,
three. One, two, three.
Left and right. Left and
right. Left and right.
Terrible.
But he got better.
One, two, three.
[NAOKO] Right, now you should
practice with the princess.
Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Coming!
Start from the moment
where you walk up
from behind him, okay?
Place your hand like this,
and yours goes here.
[SYAORAN, SAKURA]
One, two, three. One, two--
I'm sorry!
No, it's my fault.
I went too fast.
I'll just try to slow
it down for you.
Oh, thanks.
[SYAORAN, SAKURA] One, two,
three. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
One, two...
[ALL]
...three. One, two, three.
One, two, three. One, two,
three. One, two, three.
Good job!
Yeah.
[clapping]
[RIKA]
That was amazing!
Syaoran! You actually
looked cool for once!
That was beautiful.
You both worked so hard
and the end result
was simply brilliant!
[TOMOYO]
Heartwarming, isn't it?
[MEILING] It's kind of precious
how seriously they took it.
My question is: How many cameras
did Daidouji have set
up in that room?
Sakura. You really are amazing.
Honestly, I'd love to
see the whole thing.
Thanks, Akiho.
[TOMOYO]
That's a great idea!
[SAKURA]
Hm?
Just think.
Now that Li is living
in Japan, we could...
...we could finish the play
and I could film it!
Ahem.
I totally meant watch it!
And since Naoko is a
part of the Drama Club,
I guarantee she'd be willing
to help us make it all happen!
Oh, yeah! You know what else?
At the festival,
Tomoyo sang, too!
We recorded it.
Do you wanna see?
Ah, yes please!
[SAKURA] Remember that song
you sang, Tomoyo? Your solo?
Yes, I sang, but it
wasn't that interesting.
[AKIHO]
Can I see it?
[KERO]
And enthusiasm gone!
[AKIHO gasps]
[applause]
Hey, didn't you make
your own costume, too?
For the song, I mean?
Really, Tomoyo?
Yes.
[AKIHO]
You're so talented!
[SAKURA]
Oh! It's starting!
♪ Sunlight burning bright,
painting everything in red. ♪
♪ As daytime now ends. ♪
♪ Moonlight shining bright,
stars make constellations. ♪
♪ As nighttime begins. ♪
What's that?
[ALL yelp]
Shinomoto!
[TOMOYO]
Stop, it's dangerous!
[AKIHO]
I can't leave it on the floor!
Kero?
This earthquake ain't natural!
Yeah.
[SAKURA]
Release.
Ready? Snooze!
[MEILING]
Quick, get back in your seat!
Uh, okay.
[MEILING gasps]
[MEILING]
Kinomoto!
Try and sense where it is.
Like is it in this room?
[SAKURA]
I don't think so.
[KERO]
A little help here!
She's okay. I put her
to sleep with magic.
All right, you keep
an eye on her!
Don't boss me around!
Tomoyo. Come on, let's
go check on your mom!
Right!
You should get under the table.
It's safer there.
[SAKURA]
Which way should we go?
[TOMOYO] Head back the way
we came, toward the kitchen!
Jeez, seriously?
That's so like her.
Whatever this thing is,
it's shakin' the whole house!
[SONOMI]
Tomoyo! Sakura!
Are you okay?
[TOMOYO]
Mother!
Oh. Thank goodness you're safe.
We just came from checking
the electrical room.
[SAKURA]
Excuse me.
Is this everyone
who's in the house?
[SONOMI]
Yes.
What about the other girls?
Are they in a safe place?
[SAKURA]
Mh-hm.
I'm sorry.
[SONOMI]
Huh?
Sakura!
Ready? Snooze!
[SAKURA]
I'm so sorry! Please forgive me
for putting your mom and
all her bodyguards to sleep!
I guess you never know when
you'll need to use magic, huh?
It's not safe while the
house is still shaking.
I need you to stay here.
[TOMOYO]
You're right. Of course.
You can't do your job if
you're worried about me.
[TOMOYO]
Kero. It's up to you now!
Don't you worry, I got this!
I've been trainin'
for this moment!
[SAKURA]
Flight!
It almost seems like it's happy.
Aw, maybe it likes you!
That means a lot.
Thanks, Flight.
Kero!
Yeah!
[rumbling]
Hidey-howdy-ho!
That's right, kiddos,
the time has come!
Who's ready for
"Leave it to Kero!"?
This episode, I'll be
introducin' Akiho Shinomoto!
Check out those adorable curls,
and she's a great
singer to boot!
She's lived in England,
Italy, Germany,
France, Hong Kong,
and now Japan!
'Cause of this,
she has great manners
and is always polite
when she speaks!
What do you call someone who
speaks multiple languages again?
Is it polylingual?
Not that it matters,
'cause I'm the only one
who's fluent in "awesome"!
Gotta go. Buh-bye!
[SAKURA] Meiling and I were
heading home from Tomoyo's
when we suddenly ran into a girl
wearing Chinese clothing.
I wonder if it could
be another card.
Next time, "Sakura and
Meiling's Friend."
Say it with me: Release!