[VOICE]
You can never return.
[SAKURA]
It was a dream, right?
[KERO]
What's wrong?
I'm not sure. I think
it was a dream.
Everything was really vivid.
But at the same time,
I don't think it was reality.
I dunno. It was scary.
Akiho, tell me more about
this nightmare you had.
It started fine.
It felt like I was in the book,
which was kind of fun.
[KAITO]
In Alice's world?
[AKIHO]
Yes, in Clockland.
I met Alice and a bunch
of different creatures
who were very unusual.
It was a strange experience.
Also, there was a mirror there.
A special one that
could copy magic.
But the clock was loud,
and it just kept getting
noisier as the dream went on.
Then I heard a sound,
like something breaking.
Someone spoke to me.
[AKIHO] They said,
"You can never return."
And, you know, in the dream,
I found myself thinking.
It seemed to me that Alice
and I were very similar.
But now...
[KAITO] Have you heard
of "contrary dreams"?
It refers to dreams
opposite of reality.
Do you understand?
Not really.
For instance, if you had a
scary dream, the opposite is?
Uh, something fun
happening for real?
Precisely.
Speaking of real life,
it's almost time for school.
I'll go get my bag.
[sighs]
I hope it was a contrary dream.
But it could also be
one that comes true.
[KAITO]
I won't let it.
No matter what.
[KERO]
You sure you're okay, Sakura?
I dunno, maybe you shoulda
stayed home from school.
Nah, I'm fine.
Besides, I can't exactly tell
my teacher I missed school
because of a weird dream.
That'd be silly.
[KERO] I wish I could tell
her that weird dreams
are the least of her problems.
The dream mighta been
caused by her magic.
[KERO]
Listen, Yue,
I don't think we should tell
Sakura about this just yet.
There must be a reason
Eriol hadn't told her
she was the one
making the new cards.
Ya know what I mean?
And we can't exactly ask him now
since we can't contact
him or anything.
But I don't think
he'd make a decision
that wasn't in
Sakura's best interest.
That's true.
[KERO] Plus, there's that whole
conundrum with Eriol's old house
and how everyone knew it'd been
replaced with a theme park,
but then it got put back
together like nothing'd changed.
More disturbing is how
no one has questioned it.
As for the magician...
Well, he hasn't tried
to do anything to Sakura
that I know of.
It stinks because now she and
Akiho are all buddy-buddy.
I don't wanna put a strain
on that new relationship.
For the time being,
I'll say nothing.
You keep her safe.
Don't leave her side.
[KERO] I can watch over
her in real life,
but I can't follow her
into her dreams.
And what if it wasn't a dream,
but more of a premonition?
[yelps]
Are you okay?
[KERO]
Huh?
You're unusually quiet.
No way! I'm super awesome!
I'm just quiet because
I'm so gosh darn hungry!
Even after you ate those five
rice balls for breakfast?
[KERO]
I'm a growin' Guardian!
[KERO chuckles]
[MIKE]
Dreams.
We all have them. Some are
good and some are bad.
There's even such a thing
as a "waking dream."
They're similar to what
we also call "daydreams."
The word "dream"
has multiple meanings
because it not only refers to
the dreams we have at night,
but also the things
we strive for in life.
In fact, the latter
is often expressed
using a different word.
Miss Kinomoto?
[SAKURA gasps]
[MIKE]
Do you know what it is?
[SAKURA]
Hope.
Yes, exactly!
Wow, good job, Sakura!
Yeah. I'm glad I got
the answer right.
[NAOKO]
Dreams?
Yep! They came up in class.
We talked about good
dreams and bad dreams,
and even waking dreams.
Cool.
I guess I never really
gave any thought
to all the different kinds
of dreams there are.
[CHIHARU] And the word itself
has different meanings, too.
[TAKASHI]
Speaking of which...
Like the word "dream,"
the word "chow"
has several different
meanings, as well.
It can mean "food,"
but it's also a type of dog.
So chow for a chau chau.
[CHIHARU] Okay, hold on.
That doesn't make any sense.
[TAKASHI]
Does too.
So one is slang for food,
and the other refers to a dog.
That's right!
Hey, that was only two.
Yes, but two still
counts as several!
[TAKASHI laughs]
[CHIHARU]
You don't make any sense.
It was better when
you flat-out lied.
[KERO]
Chow is serious business
and he's making
a joke out of it?
How dare he sully the noble
pastime of stuffing one's face
with such a lame
attempt at a pun!
Of course, with words, it's all
about personal interpretation.
See, to one person, a word
will have a certain meaning,
but someone else will
define it differently.
Words are a form of expression.
Everyone uses them
in their own way.
What I think is most
important is using words
in order to bring
people happiness.
That's a very good point.
Yes, I agree.
Hey, sorry I got
here so late, guys!
Oh, it's okay, but we
just went ahead and ate.
Did you finish everything?
No. I couldn't get
my call to go through.
Maybe it's a bad time for
whoever you were calling.
[TOMOYO] That's true, or maybe
the battery on their phone
needs to be charged.
[KERO] The brat's communications
are being blocked, too?
[SYAORAN] I'll try again
when I get home later.
I'm sure it's nothing
to worry about, though.
[CHEERLEADER A]
One, two, three, four.
One, two-- Mihara,
move left a bit, please!
'Kay!
Kinomoto, your
timing's a bit off,
and be careful
when you turn around.
'Kay!
[CHEERLEADER A]
One, two, three, four.
Good! Let's take a break!
It looks like the cheerleading
club is out there
working extra hard today, huh?
I'm sorry! I guess we should
be working hard, too!
We can't just yet.
We're still missing members.
[AKIHO] You know, this is going
to sound kind of strange,
but... I feel like
Sakura and I...
You feel like you might
be similar? That's true.
And it doesn't sound strange.
I bet it'd even
make Sakura happy.
Do you really think so?
Yes, absolutely.
Does it bother you?
[AKIHO]
Mh-mh.
No, in fact it makes
me very happy!
Except... that's what
makes it so hard
when I think I might be doing
something to bother her.
[TOMOYO]
What sort of something?
Well, I have these dreams.
Remember the book I showed you
called Alice in Clockland ?
I dream about it.
The dreams follow
the book's story,
and it progresses
a little each time.
Lots of different
things happen to Alice,
but... in the one I just had,
something scary managed
to catch her, and...
And this time it wasn't Alice.
It was Sakura instead.
[VOICE]
You can never return.
[gasps]
What's wrong? You okay?
Uh, yeah. I just spaced out.
I'm finished with the bath.
Okay.
All right, Toya. Wanna go next?
[TOYA] Sure. This is
the last one, anyway.
Are those Hamburg steaks?
[FUJITAKA]
Yes, I thought we could eat them
for lunch tomorrow and
then freeze the rest.
[SAKURA]
I can't wait!
Hm?
What is it?
[yelps]
Go to bed early tonight, 'kay?
Even monsters need sleep.
You jerk.
By the way, I heard
it's supposed to get
pretty chilly tonight,
so try and keep warm.
[phone ringing]
[SYAORAN]
Tch.
I still can't get through.
His magic's really
that powerful?
[SYAORAN]
Even if it is...
I will protect her.
I'm still surprised
you didn't wanna
take a bath with me, Kero.
Pop a squat!
I'll dry your hair.
Wait a minute.
I'm almost positive I didn't
give you any extra snacks.
[KERO] I'll have you know
I don't need a food bribe
in order to do something nice!
Yeah, I know.
Hey, Kero?
[KERO]
Yeah?
[SAKURA] I was thinking about
that day in the basement,
back when we first met.
I had no clue who you were
or why a stuffed animal was
suddenly talking to me.
And next thing I knew,
I was a Cardcaptor.
[chuckles]
[SAKURA] It wasn't long after
that I met Miss Mizuki.
And then I found out
about Yue and Yukito.
Eriol moved here with
Spinel and Ruby Moon,
and a bunch of things
happened, but...
I'm glad I met everybody
because it made me really happy.
It means so much.
Sakura?
You know, Kero, there's
still a whole lot
that I don't really understand.
I'm always making other
people worry about me
or causing them trouble.
Some of the times we had
together were difficult,
but it didn't matter because...
...everybody's there for me.
And I...
[gasps]
[clock ticking]
Uh, hello?
[KERO]
Sakura!
[gasps]
[KERO]
Are you okay?
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
Are you sure?
[SAKURA gasps]
[KERO gasps]
[KERO]
Whoa, who is that?
[SAKURA] It's the person
from my dream.
Am I dreaming?
Nuh-uh. So...
it's definitely real!
Release!
[SAKURA]
Flight!
You're scared?
I'm sorry. Will you
still fly with me?
Thanks very much.
Let's go, Kero!
[KERO]
Right!
Come on, a barrier?
[gasps]
It's no use! I can't get
through it, even with my fire!
Kero.
Are you from my dreams?
Is there something
you wanna tell me?
Or maybe something
you want me to do?
[SAKURA]
Please.
Talk to me.
[gasps]
[KERO]
Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Kero!
[KERO]
It's okay, I'm fine.
Get going!
[SAKURA]
Blaze!
Aqua!
Spiral!
[SAKURA]
No!
No. Please don't leave me!
Release!
[SAKURA]
Flight, no!
[gasps]
[screams]
[SAKURA]
Akiho?
[MOMO] I can't believe you
used the time magic again.
Well, it was an emergency.
How is she?
[MOMO] Akiho's dreaming,
like she always is.
To put it more simply,
she's basically
acting in her sleep.
[KAITO]
Will she remember?
[MOMO] Even if she does, she'll
write it off as being a dream.
[KAITO]
What about Sakura?
She'll likely remember.
[KAITO sighs]
[KAITO]
I see. Then I have no choice.
[MOMO] Hold on, you're
really going to do this?
These cards won't be
enough, so I'll have to.
[KAITO] It's the only way
to activate that magic.
[KAITO]
Tina. Rie. Triax.
Time, in accordance with
the covenant, turn back.
I do what I must.
[gasps]
That's weird.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
[MOMO]
You may be powerful,
but turning time back that
much is insane, even for you.
[KAITO]
Perhaps.
But you won't stop?
[KAITO]
And neither will you.
The only reason
you're still here
is because you wanted to see the
activation of the taboo magic.
Well, that's part of it.
But there's another reason.
[KERO]
And?
[SAKURA]
Huh?
You were just telling me
about how everyone's
always there for you, and
then you stopped talkin'.
Sakura?
[SAKURA] I meant that it's
nice to know I'm never alone.
It's okay.
Everything'll be okay.
Aw, yeah! I've always
known you were awesome.
Cardcaptor Sakura!
[giggles]
See ya later!
Bye!
[SAKURA]
Morning, Syaoran!
Hidey-howdy-ho!
The time has come!
The last episode of
Cardcaptor Sakura: Clear Card
and this segment,
so today we'll discuss
the best thing ever,
which is me!
Behold!
A sleek golden body
with pearly white wings
and a luscious tail
that just won't quit.
Obviously, I'm a model built for
speed and power, am I right?
And next time I'll
have a new show,
"Kero's Eat Till You Drop"!
I'll eat delicious foods
and describe them all
in extreme detail!
Alas, it looks like
we're out of time.
Thanks for tuning in
every week, Kero-fans!
Buh-bye!