[gasps]
[SAKURA screams]
[KERO]
Oh. She's awake.
[MEILING]
It's probably my fault.
My stare is so intense,
it pierces slumber.
I don't wanna brag,
but my stare is like
way more intense!
Behold!
Um, yeah. It's the same look.
No, it's not! You can't
handle all this intensity!
Okay, whatever.
[BOTH]
So, good morning!
Oh, good morning.
[SAKURA, KERO, MEILING]
Breakfast time!
[ALL gasping]
[SAKURA]
Delicious!
[MEILING]
Good to hear!
Yeah, for something a
brat made, I gotta say...
...it ain't half bad.
Well, for something
that "ain't half bad,"
you sure are scarfing it down.
I might even be able
to stomach seconds.
The chicken meatballs
are good, too!
Thanks, my dad taught
me how to make them.
I bet they'd taste great
in Chinese porridge.
My belly loves that plan!
[MEILING] So are we meeting up
with everyone after breakfast?
Yeah! We can leave
right after we eat.
Yay, I can't wait!
I wanna go, too!
[SAKURA] Make sure you
stay in my bag, Kero!
And try not to talk
in your sleep.
[KERO]
You can count on me! Ha-ha!
More, more, more.
[sighs]
While he eats, let's talk hair.
Okay?
I wanna get cotton candy,
and a caramel apple...
I don't think we brought
that much money.
So this is a real
Japanese shrine.
You've never seen one?
Well, in pictures, sure,
but never in person.
It kind of reminds you
of Miss Mizuki, huh?
Who?
She was our homeroom
teacher back in elementary,
but she lives in England now.
Besides being a teacher,
she was also a shrine maiden.
How interesting.
Speaking of shrines--
[MEILING]
Thanks for waiting!
[CHIHARU]
There you guys are!
[AKIHO]
Good morning!
[SAKURA]
I'm sorry we're late.
[NAOKO]
Uh, it's no problem.
What's up?
Your hair is simply
adorable today!
Uh, thanks. Meiling offered
to style it for me.
It's so cute!
And it suits you.
She's super good at doing hair.
I don't have any curlers,
so she just braided it
and used tissue.
Too bad you don't have
hair spray, but no worries,
it should last for the day.
[NAOKO]
You did that with tissue? Wow!
What's wrong?
Well, here lately,
it seems like the powers that be
keep interrupting
all my stories.
It just isn't fair.
If I see the great
"powers that be,"
remind me to thank them.
Oh. Li said he's running
a little behind.
But he's going to send us a
text whenever he gets here.
Oh, you're right.
That's kind of
unusual for Syaoran.
Especially since he's the guy
who tends to arrive
ten minutes early.
He probably just had
something to do this morning.
He'll catch up
with us, I'm sure.
Totally. Besides, today
is about yours truly!
Yeah, right, you wish!
Wow!
It must be market day!
I've never been here
while one was happening.
That's what I thought.
Since you've never
seen the market,
and Akiho had never
been to a shrine,
I thought maybe it
would be a nice way
to spend the day, you know?
I wasn't sure what everyone
would like better,
this or the zoo,
but Yamazaki looked up
when market day was
and it just so
happened to be today.
Thank you for
doing the leg work.
No problem at all.
Zoos are pretty much
the same anywhere,
but the shrine is unique!
Oh, yeah! Speaking of shrines--
Ah, so I bet you've never
drawn a fortune before, either.
What do you mean?
You pick a piece of paper
and it tells you your fortune.
[AKIHO]
That sounds fun!
Yeah, but I think the zoo
would've also been fun.
Next time, then!
[SAKURA]
I like the zoo.
Now that I think about it,
was I just imagining
things last night?
In a way, Meiling
does remind of a cat,
but I wonder what
everyone else would be.
Oh, I kinda wish they
had cats at the zoo.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Sorry, I was daydreaming!
[AKIHO] Wow, it looks like they
sell a bit of everything here.
[SAKURA] Yeah, they used to
only sell antiques and stuff,
but recently, some of the stalls
started selling sweets
and tableware, too.
Oh! These are adorable!
[AKIHO] They have so
many different shapes!
[SAKURA] Hey. Doesn't
that look like Momo?
It really does!
I'll take this one.
Sure. That'll be 100
yen a piece, please.
Thank you so much.
Here.
It's a gift.
Oh, I couldn't.
You have to. Please?
Thanks, I'll treasure it!
I'd prefer you just eat it.
This is so pretty.
I love the detail.
It would be perfect
for serving pickles.
[TOMOYO] Naoko's very good at
making pickled vegetables.
She uses rice bran.
[AKIHO]
What's rice bran?
Ooh, I know! Doesn't it
have a lot of enzymes?
Is it supposed to be tasty?
No, you don't eat the
rice bran by itself.
It's basically used
for pickling foods.
[AKIHO]
I didn't know that.
Did you know the best thing
to put into rice bran
is a helicopter?
See, each year NASA--
[NAOKO]
Uh! Look, a helicopter!
[SAKURA]
Hm?
What the--?
[MEILING]
Huh?
Hey, sorry I'm late.
It's no problem.
id you get everything done, Li?
Oh, yeah, I finished it all.
So you got to try the
new breakfast restaurant?
[CHIHARU] Yeah! And
their pancakes are amazing!
They're super fluffy.
Next time you should go with me.
Isn't the café
au lait delicious?
Uh-huh! Look, I bought
their coffee beans.
[SAKURA]
Oh, as a gift for Kaito?
Yes.
Didn't you guys come
to Japan together?
Well, yes.
You don't have to be so nervous.
I don't bite or anything.
Okay. Says the lion!
Must be hard living abroad.
It's hasn't been that bad,
and at least I'm not alone.
Miss Li, what about you?
Please, call me Meiling.
Okay then, Meling.
So how was it
when you lived here?
Pretty fun! I had someone
to help me out, too.
Are you used to Japan yet?
[AKIHO]
I'm getting there,
even though I still
get confused sometimes.
But everyone I know
is very nice.
Good to hear.
Some of these people
can be real pushovers.
It's funny because they
usually don't realize it.
[AKIHO]
Hm?
[MEILING] I guess birds of
a feather do flock together.
[MEILING sighs]
Again?
Stop that. It's bad
for your eyes.
Uh, okay.
Is something bothering
you, Sakura?
Well, uh...
[SAKURA yelps]
[MEILING]
Huh?
[AKIHO]
What's the matter?
Uh.
[NAOKO] Are you guys
done with your drinks?
Yep.
Where should we go next?
[yelps]
What's up?
Are you okay?
You look kinda pale.
Whoa! What's going
on with your ears?
[CHIHARU]
Our ears?
Where'd you buy them?
Who was selling animal ears?
[NAOKO, CHIHARU]
Hm?
And tails? They've
got those, too?
You're acting strange, Kinomoto.
Meow, what's this about tails?
"Meow"?
Maybe you ate something baa-ad.
"Baa"?
I'm not sure what's hop-pening.
--[SAKURA] "Hop"?
--You seem a little arf.
"Arf"?
It's bear-y true.
[SAKURA screams]
Hey, what's wrong?
I dunno, but everyone suddenly
grew animal ears and tails!
They grew animal ears?
[gasps]
What's going on?
Where'd everyone go?
Hey, Syaoran!
[yelps]
[KERO]
What in the hay?
Kero!
[KERO] What is this place? And
when did we leave the shrine?
[SAKURA]
We didn't!
I saw ears and tails on
everyone, and then we were here.
[MEILING]
Meow!
[KERO]
Hm?
What in the hay?!
You already said that once!
Yeah, sorry, it's been
kind of a weird day.
How'd they get like this?
[SAKURA]
I don't know.
It's obviously the work of
a you-know-what, am I right?
Key that hides the
forces of dreams.
[SAKURA] I bid you to
show me your true form.
Release!
[KERO] Why animals, though?
And why this place?
[SAKURA] It must have
something to do with
whatever the new card is.
Can you sense where it
might be coming from,
like a specific spot?
Let me see.
[SAKURA] It's hard to tell,
but maybe the whole area?
[KERO]
Seriously?
[SAKURA] It's not in one spot.
It's coming from all around us.
[KERO] Then how are we supposed
to turn it into a card?
Okay, what about your
friends over there?
It's not them.
I wonder why they're turning
into animals, though.
They're kind of adorable.
Get a grip! Gotta focus.
Hold up.
Huh? What?
[KERO] Is it just me, or do
they look even less human
than they did a few minutes ago?
[SAKURA gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
They're almost totally animal!
We have to help them, fast!
Let's do it!
Wait!
[SAKURA whines]
What should I do?
What if I can't figure out
how to turn them back?
Sakura!
That doesn't look good!
[thunder rumbles]
We'd better hurry!
[ALL whimpering]
Oh, no!
[ALL screaming]
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
What's happening?
Hey, Kero!
[SYAORAN]
I used magic... to stop time.
I'm sorry, but it
won't last long.
Find what caused this.
[SAKURA] I've already tried.
It's coming from everywhere.
[SYAORAN] Didn't you say
something about animal ears?
Maybe it's related
to that somehow.
[SAKURA]
Hm-hm.
[SYAORAN] It can be anything,
no matter how small.
[SAKURA] I wasn't sure whether
we should all go to the zoo
or the shrine today.
I was thinking that the zoo
would have also been fun.
[SYAORAN]
And?
[SAKURA] And, well,
the next thing I knew,
I was surrounded by this field,
and everyone started
to look like animals.
They're... They're
only getting worse!
I have no idea what to do!
And I... I'm scared!
[SAKURA]
Syaoran.
[SYAORAN]
It's okay. I'm here.
Are you still scared?
[SYAORAN]
Try taking a deep breath.
My magic is gonna wear off soon.
You have to think.
What do you want to happen?
[SAKURA] I want everyone
to go back to normal.
I want to go back
to our own world.
[SYAORAN] Then wish for
that with all your might.
Sakura.
Sakura?
[SAKURA] I want everyone
to go back to normal.
I want to go back
to our own world.
With Syaoran!
[SAKURA]
Force without master,
heed the call of my Staff of
Dreams, and become my power!
Secure!
Syaoran! Kero!
[CHIHARU] Where on earth did
you guys go? You scared me.
[NAOKO]
Yeah, what happened?
I'm afraid it's my fault.
I had asked them to go check
something out for me.
Oh, is Li gonna be okay?
[TOMOYO] Do you maybe need
some more water, Li?
I'll go buy some.
Wait for me, Sakura.
[TOMOYO]
Wow, I guess that explains
why he isn't feeling well.
Yeah, he probably over did it
a bit when he stopped time.
How do you feel, Kero?
I must've lost consciousness
when we teleported
back to our world.
Talk about pathetic.
Don't worry about me,
I'll be a-okay!
Thank goodness.
Still, this was all my fault.
You know, your parents mentioned
that you'd pushed yourself
too hard during training.
Was it still not enough?
[SYAORAN]
No.
I see. This is all for Kinomoto.
Well, at least, you're
more help than I am.
I'm useless without magic.
You shouldn't say that.
I really think you underestimate
how much help you've
been to me and Sakura.
What's wrong?
[MEILING chuckles]
So you call her by
her first name.
[SYAORAN gasps]
[MEILING] Jeez, you don't
have to be embarrassed.
Don't want you to
pass out again.
Oh, yeah.
Did you tell Kinomoto what
you thought of her hair?
[KERO]
"Mirage."
Now it makes sense.
[SAKURA] It's like
whatever was in my head,
was instantly a reality
because of this card.
And then when I got scared,
it went and made
things even worse.
Thankfully Syaoran
was there to help me.
Still though, he
pushed himself too far.
Well, you know, stopping time
is some pretty advanced magic.
And I have no doubt that
anyone in the Li family
would know lots of different
spells and techniques,
but those things
take a lot of energy.
[SAKURA]
It must've been hard.
More new cards might appear,
and who knows what
they'll be capable of.
And so, I wanna make sure nobody
else gets hurt or scared
when that happens again.
I will get stronger.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Are y'all gettin' lots of rest?
Good things come to those
who wait on "Leave It to Kero."
Today I'd wanna talk about
Tomoeda Middle School,
okie-dokie, folks?
It's a stylish building,
with a canal
that flows past the front gate.
The classrooms have high
ceilings to promote an open,
spacious feel--
perfect for studyin'.
Then there's the back courtyard,
with an arch that is a great
spot for sharing secrets.
Whoever cares for the roses
must love 'em a lot!
The kid showed up right
when Sakura needed him,
so I guess he ain't
always annoyin'.
I won't lose next time. Buh-bye!
[SAKURA] I wonder what
Tomoyo wants to show me.
Wait, I think I know this play.
Ahh! This is so embarrassing!
Next time, "Sakura's
Nostalgic Viewing Party."
Say it with me: Release!