Entertainment... District?
Y-You know, that place with all the beautiful...
th-the shapely... Y-You get what
I'm trying to say, right? Come on!
Huh?
Listen up!
I am a god!
You three are trash!
That's the first bit of info
you need to pound into your heads,
so drive it in!
You turn into dogs if I say so!
Arf, arf, arf, arf!
Turn into monkeys if I tell you!
Whoo-hoo!
So be ready to bend over backwards,
pander to my every whim, and worship me endlessly!
That's right.
And remember above all else...
I am a god!
Oh, this guy is crazy.
Quick question, Lord Uzui.
What exactly are you the god of?
Please tell me he's playing dumb.
Good question, pupil.
Huh?
You have great potential.
What potential lies in a stupid question like that?
I am the god of festivals,
the god of flashiness.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it.
He's the god of stupidity and idiots.
Well, I am the King of the Mountains!
It's a pleasure to meet you, God of Festivals!
I've never heard of you.
That's odd.
Something about you creeps me out.
You're kidding, right?!
You two are match made in heaven! Cringeworthy!
You want creepy? I'll show you creepy!
Take it easy now, Inosuke!
Super creepy.
Eh?!
He's totally oblivious to the fact that
they're basically the same person, isn't he?
Tear that flashy...
Right.
That's enough fooling around. Let's go.
Follow me.
Huh?
He disappeared?
Look!
He's fast! Look how far he got!
He's the size of a sesame seed!
So this is the power of the God of Festivals.
No way. He's just Mr. Uzui Tengen, a Hashira.
What are you waiting around for?
We have to go after him!
Please be careful!
Safe travels!
Listen, you three.
Try not to stand out.
We're only here to case the joint.
And whatever you do, don't get out of the carriage.
Uh...
Stop it! What do you think you're doing?
Where are you going?!
Come back, you two!
What a bunch of hardheaded idiots!
Settle down, Inosuke.
Get back here, damn it!
I'm talking to you too!
Are you listening to me?!
It's so bright.
It looks like it's daytime.
Allow me to introduce you to the
Yoshiwara Entertainment District,
awash in vanity and desire.
Flashy, isn't it?
What kind of place is this?!
There's too many people to even count!
Make way, chumps,
'cause I'm comin' through!
Hey!
Get back here, moron!
A boar is on a rampage!
Hey! Where'd the annoying kid with the yellow hair go?
What?
Well, aren't you a handsome one?
Why don't you come and join us?
If you're hungry, we have candy.
No need to be shy, young man.
Beautiful ladies who make the first move?
What am I gonna do?!
Not so fast!
You're too young for that kinda stuff.
Take notes, you three.
During the day, this place is quiet as a ghost town,
but at night, it roars to life with all kinds of people,
ideal circumstances for a demon.
The women here are also unique.
Many become courtesans and
are sold off to pay their debts.
In return, they're given food, clothing, and lodging,
and if they climb up the ranks, a
rich man might buy out their contracts.
The highest-ranking courtesan is referred to as oiran,
and she's on a whole different level.
Her beauty and intelligence are unrivalled,
and she's mastered every traditional art.
A woman of distinction
bathed in her house's resources
to become their shining star.
She sounds incredible.
I think that's enough reconnaissance for now.
Let's go.
Sorry to impose!
Listen up, you three.
Once you're in the Entertainment District,
you should try to seek out my wives.
I'll search for any info on the demons.
This is completely ridiculous!
Huh?
You're joking, right?
How dare you order us to waste our
time finding a bride for you, huh?
What?! When did I ever ask for something like that?!
Shut up! I'm not done talking here!
Zenitsu, please!
Just because a freak like you has no
luck with the ladies doesn't make it okay
to use Demon Slayers like us for such a pitiful reason!
We're not helping you find a wife, you creep!
What are you babbling about, idiot?!
I'm talking about my wives who've
infiltrated the Entertainment District
and are hard at work gathering intel!
I've stopped receiving regular check-ins,
so I need to ensure they're still safe!
I suppose that is what a guy like you would fantasize.
You damned punk!
Here's your proof,
letters that were sent to me by Kasugai Crow.
There's quite a lot of them here.
She must have been undercover for quite some time.
Oh, well, I do have three wives.
Huh?
Did you say, "Wives"?
And, "Three"?
Three?! Three?!
Three wives?! There's no way!
How did you, of all people, manage to get three wives?!
Is this some kind of sick joke?!
You got a problem with that, kid?
Um, excuse me,
but I noticed that in the letters they sent you,
they all seem to keep reminding
you not to stand out when you come.
Which is why I'm sending you three.
So what are we going to do, exactly?
Disguise yourselves, of course,
and as much as I hate it, in an unflashy way.
All three of my wives are
brilliant ninjas known as kunoichis.
I was almost certain that this district
would be the perfect place for the demons,
but when I went in as a customer,
I couldn't get any info on 'em.
So I sent each of them in to get
closer than a customer ever could.
Since I've already narrowed
down the likeliest houses to three,
you all will search for my wives there
and try to gather information.
Suma of the Tokito House,
Makio of the Ogimoto House,
and Hinatsuru of the Kyogoku House.
They're probably all dead if they stopped writing.
Pardon my intrusion, sir,
but I brought back all of the items you requested earlier.
Thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
These three girls... are certainly
a homely bunch, aren't they?
Sorry. I'm afraid we're not looking to hire at this time.
I beg of you to find it in your heart to reconsider.
I believe that under your training, Madam,
their beauty'll bloom in no time.
That's very flattering, but...
mmm... Eh?
Well, I suppose taking in one wouldn't be a problem.
I can assure you that you won't be disappointed.
You may pick whichever girl you'd like.
If we can choose, then I think
we'll take the one in the middle.
She looks the most obedient.
I promise to work as hard as I can.
Great! Now I'm stuck with you two brats.
I'm gonna have to pay someone to take you.
Stop talking to me. I don't want to hear it from you.
Are you upset you have to dress up as a girl?
You said you'd do anything I asked, right?
I don't give a damn that I'm
dressed up like a girl, you moron.
It's that face of yours.
You think you're such hot stuff,
and it pisses me the hell off!
Hey, look! Seems like there's a whole
bunch of people swarming around over there.
Hmm?
Eh?
Ah! That there is House Tokito's oiran.
Her name is Koinatsu.
The highest-ranking courtesan
is going off to meet her suitor.
How's that for being flashy?
That her?!
Are you telling me that's your wife?!
How did you get with a knockout like her?!
And what?! You have three of them?!
Do they all look like that? Huh?! Do they?!
She's not my wife!
Why does she walk so slow?
She'd be killed instantly if we were in the mountains.
Hmm?
Excuse me, sir,
but I'll be taking this girl back to my house now
if that's all right.
I see. And you must be...
Forgive me. I am the chaperone of the Ogimoto House.
Well, if she managed to catch the eye
of the Ogimoto House, how could I refuse?
May I ask what it was about
her that caught your attention?
Yes. Her beauty is unlike any I have ever seen.
Take care of yourself out there, Inoko!
Oh.
Oh, no! I'm the only one left here!
Take a look at her now!
She's perfect!
I wasn't sure with all that makeup
plastered over her face, but my goodness!
I can't believe I was able to buy this
unrefined beauty for such a low price!
Mm?
I'm going to train this woman like nobody's business!
When I'm through, she'll be in more demand than
Kyogoku House's Warabihime or Tokito House's Koinatsu!
This girl certainly has some
heft to her, though, doesn't she?
Well, it's better for a girl to be
plump and curvy than scurvy, right?
It certainly seems like she's more muscular than plump.
Wow, that girl sure can play the shamisen.
No kidding. So dynamic.
Do you know anything about her?
I know she has a good ear for music.
I was told she could play the
shamisen or koto after just one listen.
It's a pity about her looks, though.
I'm surprised she got taken in here.
She may be hideous, but I heard the man
who brought her here was drop-dead gorgeous.
Oh!
Was he, really? I wish I could have seen him.
The chaperone lady was totally smitten!
I've never been more certain.
That girl will rise to the top.
What?
Her shamisen is speaking for her.
She intends to get back at the man who abandoned her.
That girl has serious backbone.
I-I see.
If you take her, you can have her clean
the toilets or do whatever you want, really.
Hell, you don't even have to pay! Just take her!
I'm gonna make that jerk pay for this!
Just watch me become the Number one oiran in Yoshiwara!
Sumiko, do you have a minute?
Sure!
Sorry to bother you, but we're short-staffed.
Could you help carry these up the stairs?
It'd be my pleasure.
I'll take care of it, no problem.
Thank you, Sumiko.
Nice to have a hard worker around.
I apologize for removing your makeup yesterday.
I feel like it's partially our fault
the House Madam found that scar of yours.
Relax, my dear!
There's no use lashing out at this poor child!
I'm fine, just thankful that they're letting me work here.
My, my.
That new girl is rather burly.
Indeed.
Hmm.
They say the Kyogoku House's Madam
died from falling out of a window.
That's awful.
Let's be careful, okay?
And have you noticed some of the older
girls running away, committing ashinuke?
That's scary.
What even is ashinuke?
That's a lot of baggage to carry.
There we go.
I think they're all gifts for Oiran Koinatsu.
You said you've never heard of ashinuke?
It's probably a good thing you haven't.
"Ashinuke" means to run away
without paying off your debts.
And it's really bad if you get caught.
Why do they do that?
Some people try running away in order
to be with the man they're in love with.
Right, like Oiran Suma did the other day.
Suma?
That's Mr. Uzui's wife.
Listen...
You two shouldn't be spreading rumors.
After all, nobody knows her whereabouts now.
Who knows what happened to her?
Fine.
You brought these up by yourself?
Thank you.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Come here.
Take this candy as my thanks.
Keep it secret, or you'll have to share it.
Hey, I want some candy.
Me too! Me too!
Now, now. I gave you some earlier.
Um...
did Oiran Suma really commit ashinuke?
May I ask why you're so curious about that?
She has her guard up,
but I've gotta find a way
around it and ask about Miss Suma.
It's just...
Candy, please.
Oiran Suma is...
She's actually...
Believe it or not...
she's my...
elder sister.
What?!
I think I understand now.
So you were sold shortly after your sister.
Yes, that's right.
The entire time she was here with
you, I was exchanging letters with her.
I promise you she isn't the type
of person who would commit ashinuke.
Oh, I had no idea.
I was surprised as well.
I could hardly believe that Suma would commit ashinuke.
She was such a well-behaved girl.
There were no signs that she was infatuated with any man.
But they ended up finding her diary.
I heard they read through the entire thing
and found she'd written about running off.
Ashinuke...
demons couldn't ask for a more perfect coverup.
Even if someone were to vanish,
people would only assume that she'd run away.
The diary could have been forged.
I pray that you're safe, Miss Suma,
but if you're not, we're going to rescue you.
Another day, and nothing.
Yet I can't shake this feeling
something is creeping in from the fog.
How can they avoid detection with such ease?
Could it be that the demon residing
here... is an Upper Rank demon?
If that's the case, we might be in
for an ultra-flashy fight to the death.
It's so hot, I feel like I'm
gonna die in this stupid thing!
And wearing this stupid outfit is dulling my senses!
Oh, Yae, can I ask you something real quick?
Do you think Makio's adjusting here all right?
Hmm?
Well, she's been locked up in
her room ever since she got here.
She mentioned not feeling very well,
but keeps refusing to go to a hospital.
If she doesn't do something,
the Madam's going to drag her out.
I brought a meal to her room,
but she didn't come out to get it,
so I ended up having to leave it outside her door.
Makio?
That's Uzui's wife.
'Bout time we found a new lead.
Not feeling well shouldn't be
enough to stop her from checking in.
Well, if she is sick, she'll be inside her room.
Guess I'll take a look.
Careful, Inoko!
You'll hurt yourself rushing around like that.
What a quiet little girl.
You've got the voice of a
dying animal, so don't say a word.
Oh, and if you try putting on a girl's
voice, it'll just make you creepier,
if that's even possible.
Then what am I supposed to do, damn it?
Now, then, answer me.
Who was it that you were writing
all of these little letters to?
What was your name?
Oh, I remember.
It's Makio, isn't it?
Answer me at once, Makio.
Nin-nin!
Eh?
I hate that you're prettier than me.
What was that?!
Now it's time for a Taisho-era secret.
Zenitsu seems to have taken an interest in the
shamisen, and he's actually become quite good at it. Huh?
I'm scared to be alone in the
house, so can I come over to yours?
But I heard all the girls are
taking an interest in you over there.
Wait, really? Then I'm going to
aspire to be the number-one oiran!
Huh?
Now what?!
Uh, next episode: "What Are You?"
Zenitsu, are you okay?
Zenitsu!