Kamado!
Kamado! Get up!
It's not over yet!
What... What is he saying?
Does it mean...
I didn't cut off his head?
Mr. Uzui is...
...saying something.
You gotta run!
Nezuko.
How awful.
Everything's destroyed.
Mm?
You saved me, didn't you, Nezuko?
I owe you one.
Hold on. What about the others?
I can't move my body.
Wait...
how am I able to move at all?
How am I alive?
Wasn't I poisoned?
Tanjiro!
I hear Zenitsu.
Help me!
Tanjiro!
I woke up, and my body hurts all over!
Are both of my legs broken?!
What's going on?! Who did this to me, Tanjiro?!
I'm in so much pain! It hurts so bad, I can't look!
Oh, good. You're okay, then!
I'm anything but okay!
I deserve pity too, but Inosuke's in even worse shape!
The sound of his heartbeat is getting fainter and fainter!
Inosuke! Where is he?
He's right over there, but you better get to him fast!
Inosuke!
Inosuke, just hang in there, all right?!
Stay with me!
I can feel his heart growing weaker by the second.
I've gotta neutralize the poison.
I know. What about sunlight?
Daybreak's too far, though.
What do I do? What do I do?
Send a crow to Ms. Shinobu?
No, there's not enough time.
If I don't something right now, Inosuke's going to die.
Why was my life the one that was spared? Why me?
His skin damaged by the poison...
it's starting to heal.
I'm starving.
Give me something to eat!
Inosuke!
Knock it off!
You're creeping me out!
No!
Please don't die on us!
You can't just leave us all alone like this, Lord Tengen!
Not after we managed to survive!
Not after we won the fight!
Not here! Not here!
The antidote still isn't working!
How are we supposed to deal with demon poison?!
Why is God so cruel?! Why?!
Listen closely, for these are my last words.
My life, up until this very moment...
If you let Lord Tengen die, then
I'm never gonna pray to you ever again!
There's no way I'll ever forgive you! Do you hear me?!
Would you just shut up, already?!
Lord Tengen is giving us his final words!
I'm gonna stuff your mouth with rocks, you moron!
You both need to quiet down!
I can't do that if Makio keeps bullying me like this!
Shut up, idiot!
You're kidding.
Am I gonna die without saying my last words?
That's enough, you two!
The poison's starting to make my tongue stiff.
What am I supposed to do?
Don't spit it out!
I could've left those last words, but...
Why are you putting rocks in my mouth?!
Seriously?
Huh?
What?
Hmm?
Hey!
Just what do you think you're doing?!
And who are you, anyway?!
Isn't this a little early to be cremating him?!
Look at him! He's not even dead yet!
Who does something like that?!
You deserve a spanking, young lady!
Hold on a second.
Huh?!
What on Earth is happening to me?
She removed the poison.
Lord Tengen!
Thank goodness. You're safe!
Sorry, you three, for making you worry.
Nezuko's Blood Demon Art,
it must have burned away all of the poison.
Not that I'm really sure how any of it works.
Please take it easy, though.
It didn't heal your wounds.
I'm so glad you're safe.
But how can this even be possible?
I'm totally lost.
Hey, wait.
You need to rest too.
Look at you.
Thank you!
I'm gonna go search for the demons' heads.
I have to find them, or I can't rest easy.
Nezuko, head that way!
I can smell demon blood.
That must be what I smelled.
Is it a pool of demon blood?
All right. It won't be attacking anymore.
I collected the blood of an Upper Rank demon!
Take this to Ms. Tamayo.
I'm counting on you.
There's no one in sight.
Makio and the others must have
managed to evacuate everyone.
What a relief.
Nezuko, that way.
Let's head over there.
The demon scent is getting stronger.
I can't believe you got beheaded by a couple of amateurs!
So you were watching after all!
Why didn't you save me, then, huh?!
I was too busy battling a Hashira!
I don't care if you were!
You should have finished him off when you had the chance!
You could have just split his head wide open!
And I was about to!
Yeah, right!
But that kid with the earrings was somehow still alive,
so I figured I should kill him off first!
Since you weren't doing a damn thing to help out,
you should have been the one to finish off the Hashira!
Well, maybe you should have just
controlled me so I could do that!
But instead you went and let your guard down as usual!
Shut your mouth!
They're still alive?
Not only that, but they're arguing.
You should at least be able to handle...
It also looks like their bodies
are starting to disintegrate.
You're the only idiot here!
What'd you say?!
A hideous person like you
couldn't possibly be my brother.
I mean, just look at you.
I bet we're not even related by blood,
not with how ugly you are!
And now you're useless!
Your one saving grace is your strength!
And that's all you ever had!
You're completely useless if you end up losing,
so you're just a worthless, ugly freak now!
Don't give me that crap!
If you were on your own, you'd be dead now!
How many times have I saved you?!
You're the worthless one, and you know it.
You're too weak to stand on your own two feet.
I can't believe I wasted my entire
life protecting someone as useless as you.
If it hadn't been for you, maybe I
would have done something with my life!
Maybe I wouldn't be dying right now!
If only I didn't waste all of my
time cleaning up after your messes.
You should have never been born in the first pla...
That's not true.
I know you don't really feel like that.
You don't mean it.
Think it over.
You two have no one but each other.
There's no one who will forgive you for what you've done.
You'll be resented, despised, and
denounced by everyone you've killed.
Nobody will ever be on your side.
So quit cursing each other out like this,
because all you have is each other in this world.
Why don't you mind your own damn business?!
What gives you the right to sit there and lecture us?!
As if a brat like you knows anything!
Do us all a favor and get lost!
I can't believe this is happening.
I'm not ready to die yet.
Please do something!
Do something, Brother!
I don't want to die! I don't want to die!
Help me, Brother!
Help me, Brothe...
Ume!
That's right.
My little sister's name was never Daki.
It was Ume.
Daki's a godawful name.
To be fair, "Ume" was pretty bad too.
It's hard not to hate it, since you were named
after the very disease that killed our mother.
The Rashomon Riverbank,
the lowest class of the Entertainment
District where we were born.
Children here were seen as extra mouths
to feed, so we were cursed for being born.
My mother nearly killed me more
than once while I was in her womb.
She also tried to kill me after I was born,
since I was nothing but a burden.
And yet, I survived.
My body was weak, like a withered leaf,
but I clung to life with the strength I had left.
Worm, moron, cretin...
coward, good-for-nothing, dead weight.
I was mocked for my ugly voice and appearance.
Sometimes, they'd even throw rocks at me for it.
It felt like every insult in the world
was created to leave an emotional scar on me.
Not only was I hideous,
I was filthy too,
covered in grime from head to toe
and giving off the stench of death.
It didn't help that I lived in the Entertainment District,
where beauty was the measure of your value.
I was treated like a monster.
Whenever I would get hungry,
I would eat mice and insects.
My only toy was a sickle a customer left behind.
Soon though, things started to change for me...
after Ume was born.
Ume...
you were my pride and joy, you know.
Even at a young age, people couldn't help
but marvel at the sight of your beautiful face.
I quickly discovered I was good at fighting
and started working as a debt collector.
I might have revolted everyone, but they feared me too,
and that brought me pure joy.
My ugliness became my source of pride,
and because I had such a gorgeous sister,
my sense of inferiority was washed away as well.
Call it wishful thinking, but I really had the feeling
that we were on the fast track to a better life.
Until you turned 13.
She stabbed a customer in the
eye with a hairpin in self-defense.
When news got out that it was a samurai,
her hands and feet were bound,
and then she was burned alive.
I wasn't there.
By the time I got home from work,
you were burnt to a crisp.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
What did I do to deserve this?!
You're taking her away after so
long of not giving me anything?!
I won't forgive you!
I'll never forgive you!
Bring my sister back now, damn it!
If you don't, I'll kill every one of you!
None of the gods are safe from my rage!
Is this the one causing you trouble?
Oh, yes. That's the one, all right.
Thank goodness.
You've done everyone a favor getting rid of that nuisance.
He was nothing but a savage.
All he did was cause trouble and severely
injure the people he was collecting from.
I suppose it's a shame that we lost Ume,
but as soon I find another cute girl, she's all yours.
So, um, about the money you owe...
Yeah, yeah.
After I finish him off.
Huh?
Look at you.
That's a fine kimono you're wearing, isn't it?
You're clean, and you have such smooth skin as well.
I bet someone like you lives pretty comfortably,
with plenty of food and a nice clean bed.
That kind of life is all you've ever known, isn't it,
living in a house that shelters
you from the rain and wind.
Good for you.
Good for you!
But when you've got it as good as
you do, you don't get to complain.
Losing one of your eyes is nothing,
compared to what we go through every day.
It's almost laughable, really.
No one ever offered to help us.
No surprises there.
That was just the story of our daily lives.
No one batted an eye to our suffering, even at its worst.
And then it would start to snow.
Day in and day out, we were neglected
and denied any bit of mercy from bystanders.
Why was that?
So much for "fortune and misfortune are intertwined."
Our entire lives were filled
with tragedy, pain, and suffering.
You two don't look so good.
Aw, you poor things.
You're lucky someone as
kindhearted as me stumbled upon you.
I hate to say it,
but that girl is nearly dead.
How 'bout I give you some blood?
What do you think of that?
That way, you can become demons, if he chooses you.
Life is far too sacred to let it go to waste,
and you should treasure it while you can.
Now, then, can you become worthy demons?
Maybe you'll be a Twelve Kizuki like me
and rise to the Upper Ranks.
I wonder.
To be honest,
I don't regret becoming a demon.
No matter how many times I'm reborn,
I'll become a demon every time
if that's what it takes to enact vengeance.
I'll never show mercy to anyone
who has a better life than me.
However...
there is one thing I regret that continues to haunt me.
Ume, had I never taught you my way of
life, you might have turned out differently.
Had you only worked at a better House,
you might have become a respectable Oiran.
And if you'd been born to normal parents,
maybe then you could have lived a normal life.
Who knows? If you'd been born into a good family,
maybe you would have become a well-bred young lady.
You do have a very impressionable personality, you know.
Maybe you only turned out this way
because I was the one who raised you.
"Take before someone takes from you,"
that's what I taught you,
which led to you stabbing that samurai in the eye.
But if you'd done as he said,
maybe you could have actually
made a better life for yourself.
My only regret as a human...
it was you, Ume.
Where exactly am I?
Is this place Hell?
Is that you, Brother?
Eh?
Wherever we are, I wanna leave!
It's awful here.
Please take me home. I'm begging you!
Look at you.
Why are you in a place like this?
Is the exit that way?
Please, Ume.
You don't have to follow me anymore.
What do you mean, Brother?
Of course I do! I've always...
Don't follow me!
Are you mad about what I said?
I'm sorry for saying that stuff!
I promise you I don't think you're ugly at all, Brother!
I was just bitter! I was bitter because we lost!
I said it because I didn't want to
admit that it was my fault it happened!
I'm sorry for not putting up more of a fight against them!
I'm sorry I wasn't useful enough!
I'm sorry I caused us to end up
here, that I'm always dragging you down!
Forgive me! Please!
From here on out, you're not my sister anymore.
You're nothing to me.
Do what you want, but don't follow me.
It's time we go our separate ways.
You walk towards the light.
Stop!
Brother, please!
Please don't leave!
You can't! I won't let go!
We're always going to be together!
No matter how many times I'm reborn,
I'll always be your sister, no matter what!
Please don't hate me or scold me.
Please don't leave me here all by myself!
I'll never forgive you if you leave me behind!
You said we would always be together!
How could you? How could you?
Don't you remember the promise we made?
Have you forgotten?
If we're together, nothing can shake us...
cold or hunger doesn't bother us at all.
I promise you we'll always be together.
I will never leave your side.
See?
You're not afraid of anything now, are you?
Did they make up?
I hope so.
It's finally over.
I've never been so tired.
Hmm? I see.
Really now?
Upper Six, eh?
Unfortunately that would be the lowest of the Upper Ranks.
Well, Six or not, you still defeated an Upper
Rank, so I believe congratulations are in order.
Though it was Six...
I guess you've earned some praise.
I don't know if that was a compliment or not, but thanks.
What he said!
You took your sweet time getting here.
Y-Y-Yeah, you showed up after all the fighting!
How convenient!
Scary!
What exactly do you plan on doing now
that you've lost your left hand and left eye,
and how long will it take you
to return to duty after this?
You'll need a replacement in the meantime.
Any ideas of who can fill in for you until then?
I'm actually retiring.
There's just no way that I can still fight.
I'm sure the Master will understand that much.
Don't be ridiculous.
I don't allow it.
Too many swordsmen have fallen
for you to consider retiring.
We still haven't filled the
Hashira spot that Rengoku left behind.
Even being in your present condition
is better than nothing at all.
You'll fight until you perish.
Nah...
I know just the young swordsman to replace me.
Do you remember that new kid that you love to hate?
What?
You're joking.
You mean he survived?
A battle like this?
Tanjiro Kamado survived?
You're positive?
They defeated them, two Upper Rank demons?
You have my thanks, Tengen,
Tanjiro, Nezuko, Zenitsu, Inosuke!
Master Kagaya.
One hundred years.
It took 100 years for something to finally change,
and it actually happened.
Amane...
Yes?
Don't you see? This must be an omen.
Fate is about to take a dramatic turn for us.
The effects will be widespread.
Everything will be shaken to its core.
And eventually he will feel it as well.
Muzan Kibutsuji...
we will defeat you.
Our generation will put an end to you without fail,
and then you, the sole blemish of my family,
will be gone.
Children, quick, boil some water.
Go fetch his medicine and get some towels.
Quickly!
Father!
The alternate dimension...
The Infinity Castle.
The fact I was summoned here can only mean one thing.
They managed to kill an Upper Rank.
Damn it!
It really hurts.
Thank goodness.
Oh, Lord Tengen, I'm so relieved that you're okay!
Yeah, no kidding.
You really had us worried there.
And, hey, all four of us are returning still intact.
You're right.
Now let's go home...
in a flashy way!
We all survived!
Yeah, yeah.
We did it,
and we all lived to see it too.