Wha...
Hmph.
Please tell me it worked,
even if just for a second.
If it did...
then someone should be able to behead him!
If my siblings were still alive...
maybe we would have gone drinking one day.
Forgive me,
but I haven't died just yet.
So I brought some fine sake to try to make up for it.
I promise we'll all grab drinks
in the afterlife at some point.
Now dig in everyone, and make it flashy!
Whoa, these are tasty! Don't hold back, you three.
Pardon me, Lord Tengen.
Hmm?
Forgive me for asking.
Do you think about your departed siblings often?
Of course.
Not a day goes by that I don't.
I always think about the day I
left my homeland with you three.
It feels like only yesterday it happened.
Hey, this one's tasty too!
Come on! Join me!
Right.
It's delicious!
Slow down! Would it kill you to show restraint?
Settle down.
But Lord Tengen told us to dig in!
Here you go, Makio. Open wide!
Mmm. It is good.
Isn't it?
Mmm.
In the end, I'm going straight to hell.
Hmm?
Whoops. Shouldn't have said that out loud.
I guess I just earned another
tongue-lashing from you three, huh?
Mark my words.
I'm gonna live the flashiest life
possible for my fallen siblings.
With you three.
Right.
How lovely.
Oh, you didn't have to do that.
No?
Lord Tengen, look at this!
I've got a few in my hair too.
Why do I feel like you put those on yourself?
What makes you think I would do that?
Lord Tengen,
if you don't mind,
could you give me that petal?
I don't mind at all, but there's tons of them everywhere.
The only one I want is that one.
Thank you, Lord Tengen.
Lord Tengen, I want one, too!
Huh?
Just pick up one of the petals yourself!
You're so cruel!
Lord Tengen!
He regenerated his legs?
Damn it! He's already neutralized the poison!
Man...
that poison sure packed a punch, but now it's my turn.
Blood Demon Art.
Rotating Circular Slashes... Flying Blood Scythes!
He can attack without swinging his arms...
with such range?!
Sound Breathing.
Fourth Form...
Constant Resounding Slashes!
He's gone?
Lord Tengen, watch out!
Hinatsu...
I'll draw the belts' attention.
Don't mind me! I'll take care of her!
You find that dem...
You've got some nerve jumping into this fight.
But now you have to suffer
the consequences of that choice.
Hinatsuru!
Damn it!
These belts are blocking me!
Hinatsuru.
Wow! It's beautiful here, don't you think, Lord Tengen?
Dragonflies!
I wish I could soar like one of them.
Hey, now that's a flashy dream if I ever heard one!
There you go again, spouting nonsense like a lunatic!
What?! Why do you have to be so mean all the time?
I hate you, Makio!
What was that? I dare you to say that again!
Hmm?
Lord Tengen...
once we've defeated an Upper Rank demon,
what do you think about us all stepping back
from the front lines and just living as civilians?
While none of us chose to become shinobi,
we can't just walk away after all the lives we took.
We still need to set things
right somewhere along the line,
Otherwise, we could never hold our heads up
again or dream of ever living a normal life.
When that day comes, one of us might not make it.
But no hard feelings, right?
Leave her alone!
Move.
Move, move, move, move!
Another person is about to be killed before my eyes.
Close the distance!
Quick! Jump up on the roof!
You can't always be the one being protected!
You have to be useful here!
Because I'm weak...
he doesn't acknowledge me as a threat.
So if I make an unpredictable move,
I can save her!
I have no choice.
I have to use Hinokami Kagura!
Maybe I can reach him with that!
It's no good.
I'm out of stamina. I can't pull it off!
What do I do?
Think. Think!
What do I do? What do I do?!
Focus. What else can I do right
now that's gonna be able to save her?
I have to act before it's too late!
I didn't think that kid was capable
of such a lightning-quick move.
Judging from his fatigue,
there's no way he can move like that again right now.
I did it. I did it.
Keep blending the Breathing Techniques.
Use Water Breathing and Hinokami Kagura in combination.
That'll give me more attack power
than I'd have with just Water Breathing,
and I'll also be able to move
longer than with just Hinokami Kagura.
I bet the swordsmen who have fought the
demons 'til now have been doing that all along...
pairing the Breathing Techniques with
the sword skills that suit them best
and modifying them into a form
that draws out their full power.
I'm sure those same swordsmen were able
to create different techniques like that.
Modify it... into any form.
Be flexible.
That's the kind of fighting style
that Mr. Urokodaki taught me to use.
Even if I can never fully master
Water Breathing like Mr.Tomioka,
no matter what, I won't let what
Mr. Urokodaki taught me go to waste!
Enough fooling around. You're going down!
Tanjiro Kamado!
You have my utmost gratitude!
Whoa! Hey! Watch it!
There's too many of these things to keep up with!
They might be slithery, but
these things are hard as a rock!
There's no end in sight to 'em, either!
Huh?
Yaah!
Damn it! Damn it!
They're gonna decapitate him without me!
Inosuke, incoming attack!
The only way to bring this one down
is for us to strike at the same time!
We're able to hold our own by dodging her belt attacks,
but we can't expect to win just by avoiding her.
We have to act!
If we can close the distance, we can go for her head!
Inosuke, calm down!
We don't have to strike simultaneously.
We just need to make sure the
two demon heads aren't connected!
Even after they've beheaded their
demon, we have to fight with all we've got!
Wait, you're...
you're like...
You're like a completely different
person now, aren't you?! What gives?!
Stay alert and use this chance to go for his head.
I can do it!
Damn. He won't budge!
You really think you're capable of cutting off my head?
Hate to break it to you, but that's not gonna happen!
My blade is stuck!
Of course a freak like you can swing
his head all the way around like that!
Not again!
Kamado, hang on tight!
Mr. Uzui!
Lord Tengen!
Look out!
Inosuke! Zenitsu!
They're forcing us to change our strategy! Muscle!
I can't close in on the Worm Lady, no matter what!
So us three will take her on, while the old
man deals with the praying mantis guy alone!
Well, at the very least, she's the weaker of the two.
We need to behead her first.
Tanjiro, can you still move?
I can move!
However, Mr. Uzui has been poisoned,
and he's in bad shape 'cause of it.
So we have to hurry, or else he won't make it!
I barely blocked it.
That was close.
He's attacking us even as he fights Mr. Uzui?
Miss Hinatsuru!
You shouldn't worry about me at all!
I'll hide for now! You just focus on winning!
Look out! Behind you!
Are you all right?
Yes, thanks to you!
I can see that your movements
are getting more and more sluggish.
I wonder which of you will be the first to fall apart?
Damn it!
Monichi and I are still practically unscathed!
We've got to start getting serious.
The other two are banged up from giving their all.
What was the point of all that brutal training?
What was the point?
What was the point?!
Inosuke!
This demon's neck is too soft to cut normally!
It's going to take a lot of speed! Otherwise...
we'll have to slash her from multiple directions!
Got that?!
Now that it's heading toward Tanjiro as well,
it seems like the attack has...
ever so slightly slowed down.
Maybe I'm seeing things here, but I'm gonna assume it has!
All right!
You want multiple directions, leave it to
yours truly, Lord Inosuke, the dual-wielder!
As long as you two have my
back, together, we can beat her!
Understood!
Zenitsu, protect Inosuke!
Got it!
You can bring all the ugly freaks you want to the fight,
but it's not gonna change a thing!
Now, Inosuke!
Let's go!
Stay close and don't let me down, underlings!
Beast Breathing.
Eighth Form...
Explosive...
Rush!
Water Breathing.
Third Form...
Thunder Breathing.
First Form...
...Flowing...
...Thunderclap and Flash!
...Dance!
Eightfold!
What?
He's charging straight towards
me without any type of defense!
I'm getting it done this time.
You can't cut it off.
There's no way you can,
not with these beat-up blades of yours.
Sixth Fang...
...Palisade Bite!
Inosuke, you did it!
Using your swords like saw blades was genius!
I got her head! I got her head!
I'm gonna take it far away so she can't stick it back on!
Whoa!
You two go help the old man!
I'm gonna run around with this head
until you guys beat the other one!
Will do!
Be careful, Inosuke!
Got it!
Mr. Uzui!
We've got to help him... before it's too late.
Let me go, you hideous boar!
I said let me go!
Yaah!
Is that all you got?
Man, you suck now.
What did you just say?!
You might not die when your head is cut off,
but you're so damn weak, you might as well be dead.
Inosuke!
Inosuke! Inosuke!
This is bad! The poison!
Was he stabbed in the heart?
It's too dark to see!
Damn it!
What's he doing here?
He was fighting Mr. Uzui.
Mr. Uzui!
Tanjiro! Look out!
Damn it.
Zenitsu, forget about me.
This happened because I wasn't paying attention.
I'm sorry, Inosuke.
If only I'd noticed him sooner, then maybe...
No, if I hadn't left Mr. Uzui's side in the first place,
this never would have happened.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry...
Nezuko.
Nin-nin!
Beast Breathing.
Eighth Form, Explosive Rush!
Thunder Breathing. First Form,
Thunderclap and Flash! Eightfold!
Water Breathing.
Third Form, Flowing Dance!
Inosuke! Zenitsu!
Mr. Uzui!
Can we really still win this?
Don't give up!
Don't give up! Don't give up!
Next, Episode 10...
"Never Give Up."