[whistle blows]
[TAKAO] Huh?
[INADA] Everyone still standing
moves on to the second round!
Good for you!
[TAKAO]
Wait, I, I made the cut?
[TO] Heh, heh, ha!
There's quite a few survivors.
[OSAKI] Heh! But victory
will be mine nonetheless!
[JIJOU]
No, it'll be mine!
[SHINAGAWA]
You mean mine!
[SHINONOME]
It's gonna be me!
[GROUP laughs]
[KAZAMA groans]
Aaaahhhh!
What happened?!
Where am I?!
[SIOU]
You're finally awake!
And not a moment too soon!
I've been so
worried about you!
Why're we holding hands?!
Hey! C'mon, man!
Let me go!
[SIOU laughs]
What's so damn funny, huh?
Whoa, you're a lot
stronger than you look!
[FUNABORI] I'm so glad you're
awake again, Kazama.
[KAZAMA grunts]
[FUNABORI]
Thank goodness!
You don't feel funny
anywhere, do you?
Well that dress is makin' me
feel a little bit funny.
It's weird.
I was tending to
the lump on your head,
and they just put me
on the first-aid team.
Inada said these nurse outfits
make us look more professional.
[KAZAMA] Uh--
You sure do cry a lot.
You okay?
Yeah. Super.
[KAZAMA] The wings're
a bit much, but whatever.
Wait, what'd you say
you were you tending to?
Well, you see...
Takao attacked you
with her boobies!
Wait, rewind!
More like, her tracksuit
launched its zipper
right at your forehead!
Uh! Now I remember!
It was a close-range
rack attack!
Try not to be mad at her.
It really was an accident,
believe me!
She helped us wrap your head!
That's how bad
she felt about it!
Well whadaya' know?
Huh. It seems like she
did a pretty good job.
Uh... I did the
actual wrapping.
[TAKAO whimpers]
You do it.
[FUNABORI]
But, she, um...
She totally stuck a cute
dolphin bandage on your head!
I can't tell if you're
offended on my behalf,
or wish you had done it.
Never mind!
It's not so cute!
Forget I said anything, okay?
C'mon.
I'm just yankin' your chain.
Thanks for the help, Funabori.
Mm! Welcome!
[KAZAMA] Hmm...
Ahhh!
What's up with this guy?!
Let go of my hand already!
[SIOU chuckles]
Would that I could, but we've
got business together!
You see, for the semifinal
round, you and Siou
are gonna face each other
in an old-school thumb-war.
Oh, a thumb-war, huh?
Wait! The semifinals?!
Now we meet on
the field of combat!
We're finally getting
our grand duel!
Right, we're only here
'cause you wanted a duel.
That's how this whole
tournament thing got started.
For the record, we've narrowed
down the field somewhat.
Feast your eyes
on the rankings.
[SAKURAGAOKA whimpers]
[KAZAMA] Aw, what
the hell, you guys?!
So what did I do?
Snore my way to the top?
Kinda. We all agreed
that you deserved
to make the semifinals, whether
you were conscious or not.
[KAZAMA] Seriously?
[SIOU] Heh.
It wouldn't be very
sporting to kick him out.
What say you we let him hop
back into the competition
once he finally comes to?
Okay, I'm cool
with that.
Yeah, you're right.
It would be kind of
a shame to lose him.
I dig it.
He did protect Takao.
Fifty-Fifty was
getting all pervy.
Let's do him a solid.
Yeah, that zipper caught
him right in the melon.
I think that Kazama's gonna need
some time to sleep it off.
[OIMACHI]
No objections.
[ISLE] His disqualification
would lead to an unbalanced
playing field.
I require pitting myself against
Kazama in honest competition!
[TAKAO sighs]
You guys... That's so nice.
It's nothing.
[JIJOU laughs]
No seriously, it's
the least we could do.
[SHINAGAWA chuckles]
It's all good.
But once he's back...
[GROUP] We're gonna give it our
all! No more mister nice guys!
[KAZAMA] Aw, you're
the best, fellas!
And then none of you made
it to the semifinals?
[GROUP]
Go get 'em, tiger!
[KAZAMA]
Yeah, not helpful.
So, who else is still
in the tournament?
[STUDENTS cheer]
[SIOU] Your buxom assailant
and my heart's desire.
[INADA] These girls have
seen some mileage today!
How many tackles
will it take
before one of 'em
finally stays down?
Oh, the wo-manity!
[SAKURAGAOKA, FUNABORI,
and SIOU sigh]
Funabori. What're they
playin' over there?
Uh, musical chairs,
I think?
How do you figure that?!
Musical chairs needs,
oh, I dunno...
Music and chairs?
Okay, yeah, they have a chair,
but they're ignoring
the damn thing!
It's sitting there
all neglected!
At the start, they were playing
it like people're supposed to.
But then it got sorta awkward.
[TAKAO yells]
[ROKA yells]
[KAZAMA]
Man, they're dumb.
It's about time we started our
own match, wouldn't you agree?
First one to pin the other for
ten seconds is the winner!
Huh?
[SIOU] Ready, go!
Hey, what the hell? No fair!
Aahhhh! Aaaaahhhhh!
[ROKA grunts]
[STUDENTS cheer]
Hey, nobody's
even watching us!
Inada! Commentate
on our thumb-war!
[INADA] Why?
Thumb-wrestling's
a snoozefest...
[CHITOSE]
Right in the cleavage!
Can't you spice it
up a little bit?
[KAZAMA] Why are you
doing this to me?
You can talk to me when
your boobies are jiggling.
[KAZAMA]
But I'm a guy!
What is their problem?
I'll show those punks!
I'm gonna win the
whole damn tournament!
[SIOU laughs]
Please excuse the pun,
but my victory this
day is "in the bag!"
[KAZAMA grunts]
[TAKAO] I can do this!
Kazama.
What's up?
If you beat Siou,
who would you rather face
off against in the finals?
Would you pick Takao or Roka?
I don't know.
What does it matter?
[FUNABORI] Uh.
I'm just, making conversation.
That's all.
Uh... Who'd I wanna fight?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Ah! Well,
who would it be?
Whoever wins their match.
So, then you really don't
care which one of them
you have to go up against?
[KAZAMA sighs]
Think about it.
Whichever one's stronger
is going to win.
And if I'm able to beat
whoever the winner is
then I'm totally
king of the hill.
[FUNABORI] I guess
that makes sense,
but earlier you said you
wanted the final match
to be you and Roka.
[KAZAMA] Yeah, if she
even makes it that far.
[FUNABORI whimpers]
[KAZAMA] What?
[TAKAO] He doesn't care
which of us it is?
Does take the pressure off.
[ROKA] Kazama, you're really
starting to tick me off!
[KAZAMA] Far as I'm concerned,
we've got a golden opportunity.
[ROKA] First, you say that
my bag doesn't matter to you.
And now you say that you're
cool with fighting Takao,
even though you told me
you wanted it to be us!
[TAKAO whimpers]
If you hurt my feelings
any worse than that,
who knows what I'll do?
[gasps]
Whoa! Hold onto
your butts, guys!
Roka looks pissed!
Okay, this is getting real.
You need to run!
If she hits you like this
something terrible's
gonna happen!
"Something terrible?"
Well, what are we talking about?
[CHITOSE]
Uh... Hmm...
Her shirt might
explode upon impact
and she'll float away, yeah!
My shirt?
I don't care what the hit does!
I'm not backing down!
Gimme your best shot!
[TAKAO]
I can do this!
Prepare for boob-blivion!
[TAKAO] Uh?
[CHITOSE and INADA]
Huh?
[GROUP] Cheater!
[CHITOSE] Then again,
come to think of it.
I guess that is how you usually
win at musical chairs.
[INADA] Well, yeah, if you
wanna get technical about it.
Still seems like kind
of a chump move, though.
[KAZAMA] Roka, huh?
[FUNABORI giggles]
Fighting Roka was never my plan,
but I presume that's what
the Fates have decreed.
I will face her.
Armed with the power of true
love, I shall carry the day!
Apologies, Kazama.
I'll be defeating you
without delay now.
[SIOU screeches]
You're holding me.
Guys.
That's ten seconds.
It looks like Kazama struck
while Siou was distracted
by the drama in the other match!
He won, but only
by playing dirty!
I guess the two cheats are
headin' to the finals!
They deserve each other!
This is a dark
day for sports.
Yeah, tournaments
are cruel sometimes.
Now then, pull out the
final challenge already.
I got a bad feeling
about this, but here goes.
So, our last match
is going to be...
What the hell?!
[KAZAMA and ROKA grunt]
[INADA] The King's
Game it is, then!
[FATHER 3A laughs]
Didn't think I'd run into
you on the way home, Son.
Lucky, huh?
Hey Dad, can we
have some yakitori?
Sounds delicious!
All right!
Ah!
Dad, look!
What is it, son?
[SON 3A] There's a
big cloud of dark chi
coming from somewhere
over there!
[FATHER 3A] You don't think
it's the high school, do you?
Of course!
It's gotta be from one of those
girls at the school festival!
Awesome!
[FATHER 3A] Incredible!
I don't even sense the chi,
and he can see it!
Attaboy, slugger!
You've surpassed your old man!
Good on ya!
[STUDENTS cheer and applaud]
[ROKA] Hm.
[KAZAMA grunts]
[INADA] So, it's all
come down to this.
One winner-takes-all
round of the King's Game.
Here're the rules, people.
You take a bunch
of popsicle sticks,
number 'em according
to how many players,
and make one the King stick.
Pull the winning stick,
and you're the King.
Everyone else is a commoner.
And the King can boss around
the commoners however he wants!
But, seeing as how we
only have two players,
we'll just skip the whole
bossing 'em around part.
Whoever pulls the King stick
wins the whole thing.
Look at those
game-faces!
These two are out for blood!
He's cracking his knuckles!
Not strictly necessary for
pulling a stick out of a can,
but hey, whatever!
Whoa, and she's
making a rice-ball!
Are you serious?
Food at a time like this?
She's cool as a
cucumber, this one!
Unbelievable!
[BIRDIE 3A chirps]
--[YAMADA] Ah!
--Chill out, Yamada.
It's only a round
of the King's Game.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
I would hunker down
a bit, though,
if it's all the same to you.
No point losing your head.
Uh... But I need my head!
Is this low enough?
Perfect.
You should be safe now.
An' Roka will be able to
reach the sticks easier.
[ROKA] Gulp!
I'm onto you, pal.
You wanted Yamada
to crouch down
just so you could peek
at the can, didn't you?
[BIRDIE 3A chirps]
Wow!
So, who do you think's gonna
walk away as the winner?
Huh? Uh, it's anybody's game.
Skill is not a factor,
it all comes down to luck.
Huh?
There's something
on the ground there.
I think Roka dropped it.
What is that?
Huh?!
It couldn't be!
Nuh-uh! No way!
It can't possibly be a-a...!
Holy crapcakes, it is!
That is the Silver Angel!
What's wrong,
Four-Eyes?
Bad case of candy envy?
[ROKA] Oh yeah.
I won this yesterday
when I happened to buy
some chocolate on a whim.
[INADA] No way!
You're saying you weren't
even trying to win?
Check it. You know
what that means.
Roka must have some
incredible luck!
Yeah. It's not lookin'
so good for Kazama!
[KAZAMA] Hmph. I dunno why
you guys are freaking out.
Think of it this way.
[ROKA] Hm?
Winnin' that angel was
pretty lucky, no doubt.
But doesn't that mean you're
all outta luck right now?
[CHITOSE]
He spun it like a pro!
Hold on.
Good luck can run out?
Sounds like a cliché
that would be used
by someone who's unlucky.
Your logic does not apply to me.
[SHINONOME, JIJOU and ISLE]
Roka's such a bad-ass!
Okay. I'm not denying
the girl is lucky.
Kinda reminds me...
...of something that happened
back at New Year's.
[INADA] He's pulling
a flashback?
[KAZAMA] I was thinkin' about
hittin' the local shrine,
so I was walkin' around
town with my little sister.
Just then!
Hey, that's...!
[SAKURA, CHITOSE, and INADA]
Wait, you found...!
[GROUP] Little Tama's New Year's
money from Grandpa?
Let the record show that there
was 10,000 yen in that envelope!
[INADA]
Wow, little Tama!
Grandpa loves you a crap-ton!
I get it.
You're saying that you were
pretty lucky to have found that
10,000 yen lying on the
sidewalk, is that it, Kazama?
No Roka!
That wasn't the
end of the story.
[ROKA gasps]
C'mon. Losing that much
money would be like
the end of the world
to a little kid, right?
Plus, I wanted to set a
good example for my sister.
So, I brought it to the cops.
Dammit, Kazama!
You're such a good brother,
you, got me right in the feels!
[CHITOSE] Whatever--he's
still a juvenile delinquent.
[KAZAMA] Did you know?
If an item sits in the
lost-and-found for half a year
without anyone coming to get it,
the guy who dropped it off
can claim it as his own?
That fateful day was
six long months ago.
And now!
I swear unto all of you!
I am not gonna go
back for that money!
[INADA] Did he just say
he's gonna pretend that he
never found the 10,000 yen?
And take all that luck back
into his system for this!
[INADA] Little Tama,
if you're out there,
go to the cops and
get your cash!
Things are getting
serious, you guys!
I, I can actually
see their luck!
It's swirling around
them like a cyclone!
[CHITOSE]
Huh, luck is a lot darker
than I thought it would be.
[INADA] Poor Yamada's
at the breaking point!
Stay strong, ya big lug!
I'm glad that I'm
playing someone
who'll give it their all.
Right back atcha.
Hey Kazama.
Do you mind if I
ask you something?
[KAZAMA] Hm?
I want know what you
plan to do with my bag
should you win it today.
[KAZAMA]
I forgot about the bag.
I'd keep it with me as proof
that I won the game, you know?
It'd be a trophy, so
I'd take good care of it.
[TAKAO groans]
[ROKA] In that case, I'm okay
with you having it.
That was easy enough.
Throwing in the towel, huh?
Not that I blame ya,
I am pretty--
[ROKA]
Let's do this.
[SAKURA] The only bag he's
getting today is a body-bag!
Serves him right!
Hey, guys, we're gonna
have to clear out
of the stadium pretty soon.
You wanna do us a favor and pull
the friggin' sticks already?
What is he doing?
[ROKA grunts]
[INADA] He... He's!
He's holding down her
stick with his own!
[KAZAMA] Heh. Yeah, right!
There's no way I'm leaving
it to luck after all this!
If you wanna be the king,
you gotta reach out and take it!
[ROKA gasps]
[KAZAMA] Whoever grabs it first
is the winner, got it?
[SAKURA and CHITOSE gasps]
Sudden death!
Roka, it's a trap!
[ROKA gasps]
[KAZAMA] Heh.
What just happened?
I didn't see anything
but a big blur!
He dodged the bag!
He must have known
it was coming!
If I didn't, I couldn't
have dodged it!
Ah! He's heading for!
[GROUP] Yamada!
[KAZAMA] Heh.
[KAZAMA yells]
[GROUP] He used him
as a springboard?
Well, looks like
I'm the king.
[ROKA grunts]
Wait, he...
Did you just... Huh?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have an upset!
Kazama wins!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[KAZAMA] Hm?
What are you doing?
N-Nothing.
I was just wondering if you were
scowling down there, that's all.
You're being a butthead.
Who talks to their
king like that?
You admit I won the game, right?
[ROKA]
Of course, Your Highness.
I'm the one who wanted to enter
the tournament, and I lost.
I only ask... that you
take good care of my bag,
like you told me you would.
Or else you'll be
in big trouble!
See ya!
[ROKA] Oh, and next time,
let's do something
that doesn't depend on luck.
[KAZAMA] Heh.
Looks like it was a draw.
[SIOU] You were
transcendent, my rival!
[KAZAMA] Uh--
You can hang onto the
bag for the time being.
We have to do
this again?!
[SIOU laughs]
It goes without saying!
We will continue to be
romantic rivals for Roka
and the bag that we cavorted in.
[KAZAMA yells]
[KAZAMA] What the hell?
Again with the hand?
C'mon, dude, I don't wanna
be your romantic anything!
[SIOU] Love triangle!
[24 BALDIES] Story of Fujou
Academy's 24 Nocturnal Baldies!
[NAKASU groans]
[OHORI]
What're you doing?
We're fellow members of
the 24 Nocturnal Baldies!
[OBORI chuckles]
[OBORI]
Word on the street says
you didn't make it to the final
round in that game tournament.
[BALDY 7A] Yeah, we may've been
on different teams an' all,
but that doesn't matter.
It hurts our rep when
you drop the ball!
Heh. Like you're
one to talk!
Yeah!
Wearing that ridiculous
pompadour wig!
I think you're ashamed
of bein' a baldy!
[TENJIN]
They're right, ya know.
[NAKASU] It's him!
Gentlemen.
When I look in this room,
I see a whole lotta
shiny scalps.
[OHORI] Whoa!
It's "I'm Not Bald" Tenjin!
Tenjin doesn't even
believe he's going bald!
Beat it!
[TENJIN] Hmph. I'm sick and
tired of lying to myself.
[OBORI groans]
[TENJIN] Starting now...
I'm Tenjin the Bald,
of the 24 Nocturnal Baldies!
Tenjin, that's so cool!
Now we're the 25
Nocturnal Baldies!
[OHORI and NAKASU]
Tenjin? Tenjin!