‐ [Ruri] There are as many
people as there are stars.
And there are also
as many encounters.
Likewise, there are
as many farewells.
‐ I must be going now, Yurika.
I hope you and Akito are
getting along, Yurika.
(dramatic music)
‐ [Radio Operator] Yamabuki
Platoon, give Blue some backup!
‐ [Yamabuki Pilot]
Roger, will do.
‐ [Radio Operator] The first
and second defense lines,
they’ve been breached!
(screaming)
‐ Orange and Vermilion,
stay at present position!
Red, pull back to
Point Alpha now!
‐ Damn!
(guns firing)
(electronic whirring)
(scientist groaning)
‐ But if you kill us,
then who will be left
to interpret the research?
‐ Hmm, secrecy.
(weapon firing)
(pilot whimpering)
‐ Purple Eye, fall back!
Fall back, fall back!
(pilot screaming)
‐ A belated visit for revenge.
How callow.
Vanish.
(explosion booming)
‐ Shirahime, Shirahime,
please respond!
Shirahime, Shirahime,
please respond, do you copy?
‐ Our first priority
is the injured.
Raise the field and approach.
(alarm blaring)
‐ Bose particles rising!
‐ What?
(electronic warbling)
Change the sensor.
‐ Yes, sir.
(electronic warbling)
‐ What, huh?
What is that?
What is this?
(dramatic music)
‐ The United Earth
has called for
the emergency General Assembly
to be convened in an‐‐
(fighting game characters
yelling and shouting)
‐ Shit!
‐ Did ya hear?
‐ Huh?
‐ Yeah, it’s totally true.
‐ Of course, it’s all just talk.
‐ And then, it cursed them!
(girls screaming)
‐ A ghost?
Robot?
(upbeat operatic music)
‐ [Announcer] The Hisago Plan!
‐ The Hisago Plan Space
Network is in trouble.
Four of its colonies have
been methodically destroyed,
one after another.
Four in a row!
Why?
Who’s doing it and how?
This cannot be tolerated!
‐ We’re not going with Saturn
Lizards this time, are we?
‐ Hmm?
And just what’s that
supposed to mean?
‐ Sources suggest a conspiracy
involving a certain nation.
‐ Our sources suggest
conspiracy too, lizard breath!
‐ What was that?
Meet me outside!
(man growling)
‐ This is war!
(all shouting)
‐ [Man] Gentlemen, order!
‐ And that was the
scene from the floor
of the United Earth
General Assembly.
‐ I saw it clearly.
What I saw was a boson jump.
‐ But we have reports indicating
the explosion of the colony
was wreaking havoc on the
sensors of all nearby ships.
‐ [Jun] You’re saying my
observation was mistaken?
‐ Exactly that.
‐ Think about it.
Neither the Earth nor
the Jovian Federation
has the technology to
build an eight meter Mecha
capable of boson jumping.
‐ [Jun] Damn it!
‐ There’s no need for that.
‐ I don’t think the Accidents
Investigations Committee
has the brainpower to
figure this thing out.
‐ And so the UE Space Fleet
is again left out in the cold,
leaving matters in the hands
of the Investigations Committee
and the United Forces.
‐ [Jun] Admiral?
(laughing)
‐ Well, I suppose
we can’t just sit
and watch everything happen,
so I’ve taken the liberty
of dispatching the Nadesico.
‐ Nadesico?
(heroic music)
‐ [Ruri] Hello there.
‐ [Women] Sabu!
‐ [Woman] I haven’t heard
from you in quite some time.
‐ [Women] Please call me!
(Saburota laughing)
‐ Hey, Sabu!
I don’t know who
you think you are,
but if you’re messing
around with other girls,
I swear to you I will make
you pay in so many ways,
you’ll never be able to
use the bathroom again!
‐ [Woman] This
concludes your messages.
‐ You must think you’re
God’s gift to women.
‐ Ah, were you listening?
‐ The entire crew could hear it.
‐ Ah, well, right.
‐ So tell me, I was
under the impression
that the Jovian
Federation officers
were all very noble and gallant.
‐ Well, I do appreciate
your appreciation of me.
‐ Oh, shut up!
‐ Confirming jump gate
Colony Takiri dead ahead.
(heroic music)
‐ [Saburota] Increasing
distortion field
to maximum power.
‐ [Harry] Confirming route.
Takiri to Sayori to Tagitsu,
arriving, Amaterasu.
Raise optical barrier.
‐ [Ruri] All hands commence
final check procedure.
‐ [Female Technician] Closing
all communications links.
Living quarters ready for jump.
‐ [Female Technician] Energy
systems are clear to go.
‐ [Female Technician] Ship
alert status, pattern B.
‐ [Harry] No abnormalities
in field output.
All else checks out A‐OK.
(dinging)
Fermion to boson conversion
proceeding normally.
All decks, condition green.
Increasing intensity level.
Six, seven, eight, nine.
‐ Okay.
‐ Ladies and gents, welcome
to jump gate Amaterasu.
‐ This is experimental
battleship Nadesico‐B
of United Earth Space Fleet.
We are making request for
navigational assistance
to the Amaterasu.
‐ Acknowledged.
‐ Ah, I guess it’s all work
from here on out.
‐ Shut it, Saburota!
‐ [Ruri] Navigation system,
connect to Amaterasu.
Requesting guidance for
parking and docking.
‐ [Gate Attendant] Acknowledged.
‐ Who the hell are you?
‐ Lieutenant Commander Ruri
Hoshino, United Space Fleet.
‐ Lieutenant Saburota
Takasugi of the UESF as well.
‐ Ah, well, ain’t that
just freakin’ perfect?
Why are you jackasses here?
‐ [Ruri] Sir, I am not aware
of any issues that would arise
from the UESF entering
into any UE properties.
‐ This is the core
of the Hisago Plan!
Did you get permission
from the corporation?
‐ No, we just love you.
‐ What?
‐ Uh, no, that’s just
his foreign tongue.
A dialect. (chuckling)
‐ A highly irregular
increase in bosons
were reported in the
latest Shirahime Incident.
If there are any problems
with the management
of the jump system, any
adjacent navigation routes
and colonies would be affected.
The emergency inspection clause
of Colony Administration law
can be applied here,
so please understand.
‐ Yeah, just think of it as
sort of a plumbing inspection.
‐ Nothing is wrong
with the Plan!
‐ Rear Admiral, sir.
Protecting the peace
of greater space
is the stated mission of
our dear UE Space Fleet.
Let us have faith in
the Commander’s passion
towards fulfilling that duty.
(laughing)
‐ Hello, everyone!
‐ [Children] Hello!
‐ [Mayumi] Welcome to your
tour of the Hisago Plan,
the transportation network
of the future: boson jumping!
I’m Mayumi and
I’ll be your guide,
along with my friend, Hisagon.
‐ Hello!
‐ And today, we have
a special guest.
We will be touring this
facility accompanied by
none other than‐‐
‐ You guessed it!
‐ The youngest ever captain
and beautiful child prodigy,
Lieutenant Commander
Ruri Hoshino
of the United Earth Space Fleet!
‐ I’m thrilled.
(children laughing)
(laughing)
‐ I hope she’s enjoying her
little diaper inspection.
What a shithole!
(both laughing)
‐ I have to say, I
feel a little guilty
making her go
through all of this.
I’m sure Space Fleet Command
feels the need to save face
regarding the latest incidents.
‐ They have no
face left to save,
or any business being here.
‐ It’s public relations,
for Space Fleet, I mean.
She’s nothing more than
a child on an errand.
‐ Well then, let’s get
the runt home soon.
(electronic warbling)
‐ Hmm, all sectors
clear up to 1001.
Are you ready to move on?
Data search, tofu soup pack.
Relay the soups to
me once they’re done
and keep them coming.
I want one after the other and‐‐
‐ Hey!
(Harry screaming)
‐ [Both] Huh?
(giggling)
‐ [Saburota]
(chuckles) Whoa, sorry.
I didn’t mean to scare ya.
‐ [Harry] Please, do
not enter my window bulb
without asking me first!
‐ [Saburota] Oh come
on, we’re not strangers,
we can both fit.
‐ What?
Back off me you sex maniac!
(sighing)
I don’t think I should
be doing this anyway.
‐ Man, you’re just one
mood swing after another.
‐ Hacking into their
system is crazy.
Not to mention
completely unethical.
‐ What else can we do?
Both the Investigations
Committee
and the Unified Forces
are hiding something.
‐ Yeah, but, it isn’t really
very fair to our captain.
‐ Aw, is this
sharp‐tongued little mouth
getting all soft
and squishy on me?
(chuckles) How sweet.
Look, the captain’s
been kind enough
to play the role of
the fool for a while.
Let’s use this opportunity to
find out as much as we can.
‐ Okay.
‐ [Mayumi] And that
should just about cover it
on the subject of super
symmetry and such.
‐ [Hisagon] Uh, any questions?
(children shouting)
‐ Okay, kids, listen carefully.
By going through these Chulips,
we will make traveling,
such as long distances,
like between Earth and
Mars quick as a flash!
(loud popping)
(children oohing and ahhing)
But currently, normal
humans are not able
to use this system.
In fact, in order for a person
like yourselves to use it,
you would have to
undergo a few, well,
genetic alterations,
shall we say?
‐ You mean re‐engineered?
‐ [Children] Huh?
‐ [Mayumi] Well, it’s not
like they do that much.
They just sort of use your DNA‐‐
‐ This was on TV,
saying that it was,
like, inhumane and stuff.
‐ Whoa.
‐ Please don’t be
over‐sensitive on my account.
‐ Oh!
‐ Okay, so at this point,
for a regular person to
boson jump on their own,
they would have to have their
DNA altered a little bit.
‐ [Children] Huh?
‐ So have you been
re‐engineered?
‐ Yes.
‐ Ah!
‐ This is so wicked awesome!
‐ And actually, if
using a powerful enough
distortion field,
a normal person can survive
a boson jump, like on a ship.
(electricity crackling)
‐ [Gate Attendant] Welcome
to jump gate Amaterasu.
(electronic blips ringing)
‐ Okay, h‐here we go.
There are entire sections
not listed in the blueprints.
‐ Guess there’s a reason for
these readings after all.
Okey‐dokey then, what
else you got for me?
(electronic blips ringing)
‐ What?
Human experiments
in boson jumping?
This stuff is all unsanctioned.
‐ Hey, hold on a second.
(alarm ringing)
‐ Huh, are we caught?
Release mode!
Omoikane, data block now!
Guide intruding
program to bypass.
‐ What?
What the hell is this?
‐ Welcome to jump
gate Amaterasu.
Welcome to jump gate Amaterasu.
‐ What’s going on?
Get this under
control, right now!
We are defenseless!
‐ Yes!
Uh, uh, yes sir!
We’re doing the best we can,
we’re trying to get
everything fixed up!
Shit!
Uh, uh, nothing, sir!
‐ [Woman] Remain calm.
Everyone, please, remain calm.
‐ No, the windows are harmless.
‐ Uh, calm down!
Please calm down!
Hey, don’t touch that,
please, children!
‐ Did you blow it, Harry?
‐ I swear it wasn’t me.
Amaterasu’s computers seem
to be fighting themselves.
‐ Fighting?
‐ That’s it exactly,
it’s the strangest thing.
We’ve detected an
unofficial system
embedded within Amaterasu.
And it looks like
this unknown system
is now revealing its presence.
It’s like its
laughing or something.
It’s a huge mess!
(Ruri gasping)
‐ Captain, where are you going?
W‐wait for me!
Captain!
Captain, please
hold on a second!
Where are you going?
‐ Back to the Nadesico.
‐ Huh?
‐ The enemy will be here soon.
‐ Wha?
(dramatic music)
‐ Increased reading
of Bose particles!
Target cannot be identified!
He’s not responding to hails!
(chuckling)
‐ Hey guys, excuse me!
(children shouting)
Coming through!
‐ I do appreciate this.
‐ It’s my pleasure!
Besides, don’t you
love this action stuff?
‐ [Ruri Voiceover] My
premonition was correct.
The enemy came.
Was it a code?
A coincidence?
But he, but they were both‐‐
‐ Ruri!
(Ruri gasping)
(alarm blaring)
(rockets exploding)
(lasers blasting)
‐ [Man] Keep it away
from the Colony.
Lay out some cover fire.
‐ You can’t make an omelet
without breaking some eggs!
‐ Wha‐what are you
talking about, Admiral?
‐ I’m hereby permitting
the use of firepower
in and around the Colony.
‐ What?
But sir, that will put the
Colony in serious jeopardy!
‐ You must lose a small
fish to catch the big one.
Better to swat a mosquito on
your arm than one still in‐‐
‐ Enough!
‐ Huh?
(explosions booming)
(engine roaring)
‐ Time to move, dirtbags!
‐ [Pilots] Aye!
(dramatic music)
‐ Sucker!
‐ [Pilot] You all
right, can you move?
‐ [Pilot] Just go away.
‐ Huh?
‐ Sorry!
‐ Sorry I’m late.
Set the Nadesico into combat
mode and then stand by.
We will monitor the
situation for now.
‐ Then we’re not going
to join the fight?
‐ The Nadesico’s priority
is the orderly evacuation
of the Colony’s personnel.
Besides, it appears they
don’t want our help.
‐ [Harry] I see.
‐ Got that right!
The Unified Forces is now an
invincible military power,
equipped to defeat any enemy
on land, sea, air or space!
Your Fleet is but
an obsolete relic!
So sit back and
enjoy the show, kids!
(laughing)
‐ What’s he so excited about?
‐ Now’s our chance.
Hack into the Amaterasu
one more time.
‐ Huh, we’re going
back in there?
‐ Yes.
The keyword is Akito.
‐ [Harry] Huh?
Akito?
What does that mean?
Captain, answer me.
Captain?
‐ Raise IFS feedback
to level 10.
All stations, stand by at
alert status, pattern A.
Systems control.
Akito...
‐ Stop saying Akito,
Akito all the time!
(engines roaring)
‐ Get your asses out of my way!
He’s mine!
‐ [Male Technician] The
enemy has moved back
to the second Line.
High altitude mobile
units are in pursuit.
(laughing)
‐ How do you like
that, Shinjyuu?
There’s the might of
the Unified Forces!
Bear witness to the new force!
‐ Yeah.
‐ Puke hole Space Fleet scum.
They may have pushed people
around during the war,
but not this time!
This is for the United Earth
unified peacekeeping forces.
This is for the Hisago Plan!
‐ [Male Technician] Increased
reading of Bose particles!
‐ Huh?
(energy blasting)
‐ [Male Technician] Gravity
blast shot from the flank,
heavy losses reported!
‐ [Male Technician]
Estimated total mass.
It’s a battleship!
(dramatic music)
‐ So now a battleship
that can boson jump.
‐ Do you think it’s Nergal?
‐ Don’t know.
So what’d they say?
‐ To be there in five minutes.
‐ Whoo, this is gonna be close.
Emergency orders,
evacuation in five.
‐ Let me welcome all
evacuees onboard.
I’m captain of the
Nadesico, Commander Hoshino.
We are currently moving
away from Amaterasu
out to the second line, where
we are aid with the injured.
‐ [Male Technician]
Nadesico‐B has cleared port
from Amaterasu.
‐ Who cares, as long as
the brat’s out of the way?
Counterattack that battleship!
Bring the Kirutantasu and
the Yoimachizuki about,
and do it now!
‐ [Male Technician] Aye!
(energy blasting)
‐ [Mysterious Voice] Lapis.
Lapis.
Lapis!
(explosions booming)
(groaning)
‐ I got him!
Just get the hell out of my way!
(explosions booming)
There you are!
Eat that!
‐ We’ll cover.
‐ Try and keep up!
(engine roaring)
‐ [Ruri] First, a
sudden attack and raid.
A diversion from an ambush
masked as a counterattack.
All the while yet another raid,
now from a different route.
‐ Whoa, that’s something.
‐ Miss Ryoko’s quite
amazing for catching this.
‐ So now what?
‐ Now we wait a little longer.
‐ Huh?
‐ Their objective, the
enemy’s actual objective,
well, I’m sure you wanna know.
(explosions booming)
(weapons firing)
‐ [Pilot] Jettison!
‐ [Pilot] Jettisoning!
(growling)
(dramatic music)
‐ Damn it, I guess you think
you’re Genkigangar, huh?
‐ Shoot it down!
Fire, fire, fire!
Send everything you’ve got!
Fire!
(guns firing)
That’s it!
(Ryoko screaming)
‐ Ah, crap!
‐ Drop that bastard!
Rip him to shreds!
‐ Dumbasses!
You crazy dipshits are
doing more harm than good!
‐ Listen, pilot, we would
have had that prick by now,
but you keep getting in the way!
‐ It’s you that’s
getting in my way!
(both growling)
‐ Didn’t anyone ever teach you
not to leave the gate open?
‐ Huh?
‐ [Male Technician] Gate
number 13 is opening.
Command from a hacked source.
‐ Gate 13 can’t be
opening, it doesn’t exist.
‐ Sorry Admiral,
wrong on both counts.
‐ [Admiral] What‐what
are you saying?
‐ I am saying the
charade’s over.
You’re no longer needed.
(explosions booming)
(engines roaring)
(Ryoko yelling)
‐ [Ryoko] Here I come, catch me!
(explosion booming)
Ah, crap!
‐ It’s been quite
some time, Miss Ryoko.
‐ Been almost two years now.
You’re still looking good.
‐ And you still never
cease to amaze me.
(Ryoko chuckling)
‐ Hell, knocking
off unmanned drones
don’t really count for nothin’.
‐ [Ruri] It seems
they’re part of a trap
designed for any intruder,
regardless of friend or foe.
‐ [Ryoko] Hmm...
‐ [Ruri] The traps end up ahead.
I’ll guide you from here.
‐ Thank you much.
Wait, you’ve been hacking
into the Unified System,
haven’t you?
‐ And the enemy’s been
doing the same thing.
Oh, and the one actually
doing all the hacking
is Harry here.
‐ Huh?
Why are you doing this to me?
(Ryoko laughing)
(mysterious whirring)
‐ [Male Technician]
The enemy has reached
the fifth isolation partition.
‐ Initiate plan beta.
Dispatch to all branches.
‐ Let me go!
I’m not going anywhere!
‐ Calmly.
‐ Look Admiral, please be quiet.
‐ Lieutenant Colonel
Shinjyuu, what are you doing?
Who the hell do
you think you are?
‐ Enemy of the Earth,
enemy of Jupiter,
and enemy to all other
forms of corruption.
‐ Oh?
‐ Yes, Admiral, I’m
a Martian Successor!
(electronic beeping)
‐ All right, hold
it right there.
That’s a communications tether.
There’s someone who wants
to have a word with you.
‐ Hello there.
I am Lieutenant
Commander Ruri Hoshino
of the UE Space Fleet.
I’m terribly sorry
for the entrance,
but since you’ve locked out
all window communications links,
I’ve asked Miss Ryoko
to act as a relay.
So I’m wondering,
I, uh, who are you?
What is your mission?
‐ Lapis, analyze pass key.
‐ Please enter password, please!
(electronic beeping)
‐ There’s no time.
You can watch if you want.
(dramatic music)
‐ What?
Ruri, are you getting this?
‐ Miss Ryoko.
‐ I don’t believe it!
‐ Miss Ryoko, please stay calm.
‐ What’s going on here?
‐ Miss Ryoko.
‐ Ah, what the hell?
Its shape may have changed,
but it is the ruin.
The very same Martian ruin
that both Earth and Jupiter
spent countless lives
fighting each other for.
The black box of boson jumping.
And now it appears to be at
the heart of the Hisago Plan.
‐ That’s right.
‐ Ruri.
‐ Huh?
‐ They must be turning in
their graves right now.
‐ [Ruri] Miss Ryoko...
‐ [Ryoko] What the hell
is this doing here?
‐ It is here for the sake
of the future of mankind!
(gasping)
‐ Admiral Kusakabe?
‐ Ryoko‐chan, make a hard right!
(Ryoko yelling)
‐ The Hisago Plan now belongs
to the Martian Successors.
(men cheering)
‐ Ladies and gentlemen,
our first course of action
might make some of you
a little uncomfortable,
as we are planning to destroy
and abandon the Amaterasu.
‐ Well, they sure are
a considerate sort.
‐ Did you find what we needed?
‐ Oh, sure did.
‐ I’m back, how are you doing?
‐ Uh, well, I guess
things have looked better.
‐ Can you move?
‐ [Ryoko] Not much‐‐
(explosions booming)
Goddamn it!
(weapons firing)
‐ [Akito] This has
nothing to do with you.
Now go.
‐ [Ryoko] Yeah, right, whatever!
(explosions booming)
What the?
(electricity crackling)
‐ [Hokushin] Twixt a
single dusk and dawn,
the starry spiral
stretching like a snake,
reached the heavens above.
Amatsukuni beckons.
Wishing to die in front
of your woman, are you?
‐ "Your woman?"
(Akito shuddering)
Huh?
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
(explosion booming)
Akito, it’s you!
That’s why you
called me Ryoko‐chan!
‐ [Hokushin] Vanish.
(explosion booming)
‐ Sorry it took
me so long, guys.
‐ Go back, Suba, you don’t
know what you’re doing!
It’s Yurika and Akito, they’re‐‐
‐ Sorry, but the captain’s
orders were very specific.
‐ Ruri, can you hear me?
Come in, damn it!
You saw it, you saw what
I saw, they’re alive!
They’re alive, Ruri, we
can’t leave them again!
Ruri, Ruri, please!
Goddamn it!
‐ All hands, please stand down.
We will leave this sector upon
retrieval of the Aestivalis.
‐ [Crew Member] Aye aye.
‐ [Jun] Haruki Kusakabe.
Former Jovian Vice Admiral.
The Federation’s de facto
number one during the war.
As the anti‐Kusakabe faction
of the young officers
unleashed their coup d’état,
was forefront of the fight.
Eventually, he went
MIA during combat.
‐ [Yoshida] Somehow,
he stayed alive.
‐ Hmm.
As a former member of
the Jovian Federation,
I am much ashamed.
‐ Please.
‐ According to Commander
Hoshino’s data,
there are many supporters
of Kusakabe’s cause.
Military officers, politicians,
and numerous others,
all of whom are closely
tied to the Hisago Plan
are believed to be in his camp.
‐ Are you telling me
that the United Earth
ended up preparing
the Hisago Plan
simply for Kusakabe to
do with as he please?
‐ [Ruri] Yes.
At the core is
the Crimson Group,
who initiated the Hisago‐‐
‐ Commander, you need not
stand in order to respond.
‐ Yes, sir.
It seems the confederacy
of anti‐Nergal industries
and Kusakabe were already
in contact during the war.
They’re seeking to gain total
control of boson jumping,
and thus of the economy
and government as well.
‐ Admiral Kusakabe
was always one
to constantly stress
both the importance
and dangers of boson jumping.
‐ I’m sure he feels
it’s a just cause,
but I doubt those
subjugated will agree.
‐ No doubt.
‐ [Kouichiro] Akiyama.
‐ Sir?
‐ What sort of man is Kusakabe?
What is your impression of him?
After all, you served as a
direct subordinate to him
for quite some time.
‐ Hmm, hot‐blooded and
bent on righteousness.
A man who would die
to realize his ideals.
But what makes him so
dangerous is that he believes
that righteousness in his eyes
should be righteousness in
the eyes of everyone else.
‐ [Saburota] Nadesico‐C?
‐ Yes, third
generation of Nadesico.
C, as in A, B, C.
It’s currently going through
final checking procedures
in the Nergal dock on the moon.
‐ We would like to assign
you the top secret,
and shall we say, independent
mission of retaking the ruin.
‐ If so, then we should
not recruit the services
of any regular enlisted crew.
‐ Exactly.
‐ What are we supposed to do?
(Prospector laughing)
‐ [Prospector] Just leave
that business to me!
‐ [All] Huh?
‐ Hello, from the deep blue sea!
And what that means is that
we will be cooperating fully
with your efforts.
‐ Uh, Prospector?
Is that your real name?
‐ Just a pseudonym.
Right, I suppose
we should split up
to go recruit our crew.
I guess this will be quite a
reunion of sorts, won’t it?
‐ Yes.
‐ [Prospector] I say,
it has been a long time,
hasn’t it, Miss Ruri?
‐ [Ruri] Yes, it has.
‐ Look, we still
have the three of us.
With all of our crew
working together,
we can beat anything!
‐ [Ruri] Hello?
(gasping)
‐ It’s been so
long, my Ruriruri!
‐ Whoa!
‐ Wow!
‐ [Hikaru] What, the Nadesico‐C?
‐ [Ruri] Yeah, and since the
operation is very secretive,
we’re avoiding
enlisted soldiers,
which is why we’ve come to‐‐
‐ [Hikaru] Hmm.
Sure, okay.
‐ Huh?
Now that didn’t take long.
‐ But don’t you have your
serial here to manage?
(Hikaru chuckling)
‐ Oh thank God you’re here!
I’m way behind my
deadlines tonight
and my assistants are
gone with flus and coughs
and engagement parties!
‐ Oh, I see.
(phone ringing)
(upbeat music)
‐ Great, no visual yet.
Uh, how are you
doing, Miss Amano?
‐ Uh, who is this?
I’m Harry.
‐ Huh?
Look here, I need Miss Amano.
It’s her editor, kid.
‐ There’s something wrong
with your telephone.
‐ No, no, don’t hang up!
No, no, wait!
‐ (sighing) They’ll call back.
‐ Oh, thanks so much,
you guys are pros!
Now use tone 61 and
double layer your shadows.
‐ Yeah.
‐ [Hikaru] And Sabu, put
passion into that pointillism.
‐ Will do.
‐ [Hikaru] And Harry, make
that curry extra, extra spicy!
‐ Yeah...
‐ What’s impossible with
one can be done as a team!
All right, just 12 more
pages left, let’s do it!
‐ This way sir, come on in!
(woman giggling)
‐ [Woman] Sweetie,
are you happy with me?
‐ [Man] You know you
make me happy, baby.
You’re the awesomest.
(hiccuping)
♪ One step, two step,
three step, four grand ♪
♪ Please take me with
you when you’re walkin’ ♪
♪ No I won’t fight
you ’cause you’re ♪
♪ Nothin’ but a dirty dog ♪
♪ And you’ll get
hit by a stick ♪
♪ Make money off getting hit ♪
‐ [Bartender] Are you an
acquaintance of our hostess?
‐ I knew her from the war.
♪ Hit it big with a job ♪
♪ Hit it off with shopping ♪
♪ Hit it bit with a job ♪
♪ Money gets around
in this world ♪
♪ So enjoy life while you can ♪
‐ Ruri Hoshino,
systems operator.
I am 11 years old.
‐ Hello.
‐ Hello!
‐ [All] Hello!
‐ Ruri, hello!
‐ You’re so cute, we’re going
to be the best of friends!
‐ [Man] The Nadesico
will go to Mars.
‐ [Ruri] Akito!
Akito!
Oh Akito, listen to me!
‐ Remember that boson jumping
is reverse engineered technology
based purely on what
we’ve discovered on
Mars to this point.
So basically whoever
makes the right
Martian excavation first will
gain more of an advantage
than any technological
innovation.
‐ Is what really
all there is to it?
‐ (chuckles) Suppose so.
But imagine if they
discover something
of far greater significance,
impacting space itself.
(explosion booming)
(plaster cracking)
(screaming)
(gasping)
‐ [Ruri] Oh...
(car horns honking)
‐ Ooh baby!
(men catcalling)
Where’s the fire?
Slow down, mama!
‐ Yeah, right.
I’m so sorry!
I’m home!
I did it, Miss Minato!
I’ve been voted a junior member!
Huh?
‐ Oh, please forgive me,
but something big’s come up.
Ciao!
Oh, please forgive me,
but something big’s come up.
‐ She blew a kiss?
‐ Ciao!
‐ That seems odd.
Well, don’t you think so?
(wind chime ringing)
‐ [Yoshida] I must say, both
the United Earth and the UEAF
seem to be scrambling
after this development.
‐ [Genpachiro] Ah, it
doesn’t surprise me.
‐ [Kouichiro] What
is the latest report?
‐ Aye.
The so‐called Martian Successors
have now managed to
occupy the polar ruin.
Kusakabe sympathizers are
gathering there as we speak,
and it has been
estimated that around 30%
of the United Forces are
now supporting his side.
‐ It appears the marginalized
nations of the UE
are unofficially endorsing this.
‐ And with the Space
Fleet depleted,
it can only add to
that confidence.
‐ We’ve been fortunate.
‐ What?
We are not fortunate, they’re
a bunch of dirty traitors!
How can you be so
nonchalant about this?
‐ Easy, terrorist movements
create a public allure
of glamorized
courage and nobility.
‐ Oh, please!
‐ Outside call
for Commander Aoi.
‐ Oh?
‐ Hey!
How are you doing Jun?
It’s me!
‐ Huh?
‐ What, why’d you
patch her through?
‐ She claimed to be a very
close acquaintance of yours.
And well, who would claim that?
(Jun grumbling)
‐ Miss Minato is heading
your way, isn’t she?
‐ Huh?
(Jun stammering)
‐ Don’t you play stupid with me!
I don’t know if it’s Nergal
or Space Fleet or whatever,
but you’re up to something.
So just tell me.
I know you’re being sneaky
and you know I’m right!
‐ Please, this is
classified information!
‐ Ha, I knew you were
hiding something!
‐ Hmph!
‐ Oh, please tell me!
Pretty please?
‐ Huh?
‐ Mr. Aoi, you’re the only
person I can count on.
If you tell me, I’ll go out
with you and be your girlfriend
and even be seen
in public with you.
I won’t be fussy or high
maintenance, I promise!
‐ Oh, for Christ’s sake,
will you listen to yourself?
Hey, this is serious!
‐ He’s very capable for
sure, but he can be,
how should I say, a
little too nice sometimes?
‐ Too true.
‐ Just look how this
high school girl
has a hold of him
by the short hairs.
‐ Hey, why don’t
you deal with her?
‐ [Genpachiro] Ah,
summer skies above.
Winds of love, the
gust engulfs in Jun.
(insects trilling)
‐ [Ruri] So he’s out right now?
‐ Yes.
He’s gone, to a sort of
neighborhood meeting.
Do you have some
business with him or‐‐
‐ Well, to tell
you the truth, we‐‐
‐ No, ma’am, it’s nothing.
We were simply passing
through the area.
Thank you.
You have a beautiful family.
‐ That’s the 20th one.
Another former brave
warrior bowing out.
Great.
‐ Who ordered the Mars bowl?
‐ Oh, that one’s me.
‐ [Saburota] Knock
if off, Harry.
‐ [Harry] But I only‐‐
‐ [Saburota] But what, Harry?
‐ Is it really that important
to reassemble the old crew?
‐ Yes.
(loud slurping)
‐ I don’t see what’s wrong
with us doing this on our own.
Sure, I can see how we could
use more Aestivalis pilots,
but I have the
experience it takes
to manage the ship’s
navigation system by myself,
and Mr. Saburota can more
than take of combat C and C.
We’re the best team ever
assembled on the UE Space Fleet,
and these people have all
retired to civilian jobs
and have lives of their own!
‐ Harry, shut up, will ya?
‐ Why are they so crucial?
Why do we have to do this?
‐ [Saburota] Harry!
‐ [Harry] Don’t you have
any faith in my abilities?
Captain!
‐ Oh, that’s good.
One more, please.
‐ [Harry] Oh, you
people are impossible!
‐ Harry!
How about paying your
part of the bill, huh?
Crazy little freak boy.
‐ Do you need to go after him?
‐ He’s fine.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ We cannot defeat the
enemy all by ourselves.
Harry is young, but he is
well aware of that fact.
‐ He may be aware of it,
but that doesn’t mean
he has to accept it.
We’re only humans.
He’s probably jealous, you know?
Jealous of your
old crew and, well,
jealous of the galactically
famous Nadesico.
‐ Think so, huh?
(chuckles)
Now where the hell’d that
little buy run off to?
(sniffling)
‐ It’s just so stupid, captain.
Whatever she’s thinking, I’m,
I’m sure this doesn’t
show her my maturity.
That’s just great.
I’m just a‐a big boob.
‐ Okay, where is it?
‐ Oh!
‐ [Minato] Well,
you’re a bold one.
(Harry stammering)
Uh‐‐
‐ Oh, I‐I, uh, didn’t mean to!
I’m so sorry!
‐ Hmm?
‐ Forgive me!
‐ Poor thing,
you’ve been crying.
I guess you’re too shook up
to give me directions, huh?
‐ My lady, you’ve
come to the right man!
Now let’s get moving.
I’m a navigator in
the Space Fleet.
I know this neighborhood
like the back of my hand.
(Harry grunting)
‐ Great.
I’m looking for the restaurant
Everyday Tranquility.
‐ Huh?
‐ Yep.
‐ Howmei’s diner?
‐ Hey, what’s wrong?
‐ Yeah, I know the place.
But I can’t go there right now.
It would be bad.
(loud wailing)
‐ [Minato] Do you
feel better now?
‐ [Harry] Yes, I’m all right.
Thanks for being so nice to
someone you just bumped into.
‐ Harry, right?
‐ Hmm?
‐ Yep, I knew it.
‐ In the letters
Ruriruri wrote me,
she spoke a lot of
her new crew members.
She says you’re great.
‐ Me?
‐ Yep.
"He’s like a younger
brother to me.
"Our backgrounds are very
similar, but unlike me,
"he’s extremely bright
and well‐behaved."
‐ So you were on the Nadesico?
‐ Let her take care of
you, Mr. Younger Brother.
(chuckling)
‐ [Ruri] Let’s go back, Harry.
‐ [Saburota] You owe me
five dollars, wise guy.
‐ So what we toasting to?
‐ To an overdue reunion,
and Harry, I guess.
(both laughing)
‐ So are you going again,
onboard the Nadesico‐C?
‐ When I first heard
from Mr. Prospector,
I was planning on just
catching up with Ruriruri
and then heading back home.
But now that I’ve seen her, I
don’t know if I can do that.
‐ Yeah, I know.
She’s pushing it.
I know she doesn’t show it much,
but the responsibilities
of a captain,
accomplishing a
mission like this,
and the enemy’s no pushover.
‐ It’s too bad she
can’t cut loose
and relax at times like this.
Captain.
(ice clinking)
(train rumbling)
(whistle blowing)
‐ [Harry] Captain...
(train whistle blowing)
(men shouting)
‐ What’s going on?
‐ Everything!
Communication effectiveness
is decreasing!
(men shouting)
(electronic beeping)
‐ Well, it looks like she still
isn’t in the best of moods.
‐ Pleasing a princess
isn’t easy, you know?
‐ Hmm.
‐ Huh?
‐ Oh, oh yes, right, the dress.
Miki and the others
wanted her clothes on.
‐ Oh.
‐ [Scientist] She and the
others kept threatening
sexual harassment charges.
‐ Hmm, well, I’m
glad they spoke up.
(explosion booming)
(lasers blasting)
‐ Pull them back, no
matter what you do!
We need more time!
Help’s on the way!
‐ The enemy’s strength
is now below 50%.
We’ve suffered only 3% losses.
‐ We’re doing well.
‐ I’ve been informed
the Fifth Fleet
has knocked out the Kushinada.
‐ Right, it’s time to
negotiate their surrender.
(explosion booming)
‐ Huh, what’s that?
‐ [Male Technician]
Engineering’s hit,
we’re under attack!
‐ What?
(electronic warbling)
(explosions booming)
(men ahhing)
‐ V!
‐ Congratulations, Professor.
‐ Hmm.
‐ May we call this a dramatic
success, Mr. Yamasaki?
‐ Yes, imaging
communications is 98%.
At this rate, the
navigator’s accuracy
will be high enough to jump
to an almost exact location.
‐ Yes, I see.
‐ And we have this to
thank for our success, sir.
‐ What the?
‐ Huh?
‐ Teenage girl comic
books and boson jumping?
See what you can do to
explain this shit to me.
‐ The stars glimmer as
the hearts of people.
(water splashing)
Tenkawa...
He’s here on Earth.
Kept you long?
‐ Uh, no.
♪ Destined to be a star
in space tomorrow ♪
(both gulping)
‐ Ensign Harry Makibi.
‐ Aye!
‐ I have a special
mission for you.
At 0800, you’re to conduct
a long‐distance boson jump
to Nergal’s lunar factory,
commencing with
final check procedure
at the Nadesico‐C.
‐ A lunar jump?
But we can’t use Chulips.
‐ [Ruri] This will
be a singular jump,
piloted by a Class A jumper.
‐ Huh?
‐ Movement by shuttle will
leave you vulnerable to attack,
making this your
safest means of travel.
I’ll leave the Omoikane to you.
(electronic warbling)
‐ Fruit basket!
‐ Oh yeah, I win!
(Ryoko growling)
‐ One more time!
That was the last time you win!
‐ Hey, sure as much as you want,
since you only know how
do do that one move.
I might start closing my eyes.
(Ryoko growling)
‐ Shut up!
And get ready to eat it!
‐ Okay.
‐ This can’t be a good idea.
‐ Sure.
No matter how talented a pilot
Miss Hikaru may have been,
two years is a long time
away from the cockpit.
And for the purposes of
intensive short‐term,
interactive combat
simulation, it’s perfect.
‐ Lychee Lychee‐ru
Flashing Bright Attack!
(Gekigangar screaming)
(Hikaru laughing)
‐ Oh!
‐ You’re cuttin’ it
pretty close there.
‐ Damn it!
‐ There you go,
forcing it again.
(Ryoko growling)
Oopsies!
Yay!
‐ No!
‐ Wow, Miss Hikaru still
has amazing skills.
‐ This is nothing.
She’s only at about
60% right now.
She’ll need more
practice if she wants
to fight those monsters
on equal footing.
Have you heard anything
about the latest plans?
‐ No, but we do know that
they are currently in Japan.
And of course, we also
know what their goal is.
‐ Hmm.
(ukulele ringing)
‐ Huh?
‐ Hmm?
Well, it looks like the
trio’s back together.
‐ Got ketchup?
Gotta ketchup.
(ukulele ringing)
‐ Oopsies!
‐ Is he the prince in black?
Could it be?
‐ "Are you changing into
someone you don’t know?
‐ "I am changing myself.
‐ [All] "And I don’t like
the way I’m changing.
‐ "It’s a festival day."
‐ Oh, that’s the next issue.
‐ Oh.
‐ But they’ve started
to drift apart.
What do you think happens
in the next installments?
‐ [Men] Hmm.
‐ I think that will be enough.
‐ [Men] Aww.
‐ The source of the
system’s energy outburst
stems directly from dreams.
The human translator
Yurika Misumaru
relays the visualizations
to the jump system.
And her current dreams are
acting as a form of noise,
creating the recent power
surges within the system.
Okay, turn it up.
We are now amplifying
the intensity of the
destination image
in order to override
Captain Misumaru’s dreams,
only this time,
we’ve incorporated
some rather romantic subtext.
‐ That’s the reason for Ururun?
‐ Yes.
We’ve used her adolescent
dreams to our advantage.
Right now she’s only a lovely
date with her boyfriend,
and at the same time, increasing
our imaging effectiveness.
This is truly a
technological victory.
(light gentle music)
‐ Where do you
want to go, Akito?
‐ Chichibu Mountains.
(glass shattering)
(mechanical whirring)
‐ Tomorrow is the day.
(growling)
‐ [Cloaked Man] The accuracy
of this jump acts as proof,
does it not?
‐ Hmm, the information
we gathered
of the specific locations
will greatly help us.
‐ So what is our
mission for now?
‐ Are we to just watch?
‐ [Hokushin] No.
We merely return to
the original mission.
‐ [Cloaked Man] Then?
‐ The little doll
and the test subject.
Lapis.
(elevator dinging)
‐ [Saburota] Did you sleep
well last night, Ensign Makibi?
‐ [Harry] I suppose.
‐ So tell me, how’d it go?
‐ Huh, how’d what go?
‐ Come on, I already know.
You slept in the captain’s
quarters last night.
‐ Wha, how’d you know?
(chuckling)
‐ So, was she all like
nice to you and stuff?
‐ Well, yeah.
‐ Ooh, I’ll bet so.
And?
‐ We both enjoyed a
strawberry milk drink.
‐ Yeah, yeah, then what?
‐ Then we held
hands, then slept.
‐ Huh?
(elevator dinging)
‐ Let’s go, time is short.
(electronic warbling)
‐ [Male Technician]
All systems normal.
‐ [Female Technician]
Jumper’s heart rate
and body temperature, normal.
‐ How are you feeling,
Ensign Makibi?
(Harry chuckling)
‐ [Harry] To tell you the truth,
I feel a bit like a marionette.
(laughing)
‐ Well, that’s all
there so we can measure
your physical and
psychological condition
right up to the point you jump.
Please bear with it.
‐ [Harry] Aye!
‐ Harry, see you on the moon.
‐ [Harry] Okay.
‐ [Male Technician] The
navigator is positioned
at the center of the circle.
‐ [Female Technician] Beginning
activation of the crystals.
‐ My name is Harry.
Nice to meet you.
‐ [Jumper] It’s
nice to meet you.
‐ This, uh, is the first time
I’ve ever met a Class
A jumper before.
‐ I see.
I will be conducting
the visualization
of your destination
so you just close your
eyes and breathe easy.
Think of something
fun and happy,
anything to help you relax.
‐ Just relax, just relax...
‐ Activation of the Chulip
crystals running normal.
‐ Increasing mass levels
of photons and gravitons.
‐ [Male Technician]
Synchronization to
jumper navigator
progressing smoothly.
‐ [Female Technician] Boson
exchange ratio increasing.
‐ Jump in, Harry!
(heroic music)
‐ [Jumper] Let’s go, Harry.
‐ [Harry] Aye.
‐ Huh?
‐ What’s up?
‐ The Princess just moved.
‐ Oh, get real.
‐ [Cleaner] Maybe
there was another jump?
you’re just an idiot.
(birds chirping)
‐ What’s wrong?
‐ It’s Harry’s jump.
It should be
happening about now.
‐ I figured you would have
at least gone to see him off.
‐ I couldn’t handle
a third time.
‐ Hmm?
‐ [Ruri] I know it
sounds superstitious,
but I don’t want
to jinx anything.
‐ Hmm, you’re just stubborn.
(gong ringing)
Akito?
No way.
‐ Today is the second
year anniversary.
I should have realized sooner.
‐ Hmm?
‐ There were many jumpers
other than Mr. Akito,
the Captain and Miss
Inez who either died
or disappeared back then.
Class A boson jumpers,
navigators who can
accurately communicate
to where they wish to jump.
They were all abducted by
the Martian Successors,
weren’t they?
(crows cawing)
‐ [Minato] Abducted?
‐ [Ruri] Mr. Akito, I
cannot begin to imagine
what you’ve been through
the past two years.
‐ Believe me, you don’t want to.
‐ You’re right, I don’t
think I really want to know.
Ever.
But why?
Why couldn’t you tell me
that you were still alive?
‐ [Akito] Because
there was no reason to.
‐ [Ruri] I see.
(Minato gasping)
(loud slapping)
‐ How dare you say such a thing?
Aren’t you the same
person who said
you wanted to take
Ruri into your home?
Apologize to her, Akito!
Apologize!
She has been worried
sick about you
and you do nothing but‐‐
(gun cocking)
Uh, A‐Akito?
‐ You are lax, Akito Tenkawa.
I think you’d better
submit and come with us.
‐ Who on earth is that?
(gun firing)
Ah!
‐ [Hokushin] I say
again, come with us now.
‐ [Minato] Akito?
‐ We may sever his limbs,
but I want him alive.
Slice.
‐ This has nothing
to do with you two,
so you’d best get
someplace safe.
‐ Escape is not an option
at a time like this.
‐ I think you’re right.
‐ And the woman?
‐ Kill her.
‐ What about the girl?
‐ I want her to be captured.
She wears a pair of golden
eyes, like that of Lapis,
the white fairy created
by the technology of man.
It appears the people of Earth
have become infatuated
with genetic alterations.
She shall become the cornerstone
of the glorious research
being conducted at our
society’s laboratories.
‐ You’re the ones, aren’t you?
You have been
intercepting and abducting
all the Class A jumpers.
‐ [Hokushin] Correct.
We are the shadows of
the Martian Successors,
the dregs of men left
to tread the path
humanity dares not travel.
‐ [All] All for the glory of
the rise of the new order.
(Genichiro laughing)
‐ Hmm?
(heroic music)
‐ What?
‐ Talk from you of a new order
is nothing but laughable.
It is true that new order
follows destruction and chaos.
It is natural that
rebirth would accompany
so much death and pain.
But, not here.
Kusakabe has no virtue.
‐ It’s been a long time,
Genichiro Tsukiomi.
The traitor who sold Jupiter
sure has a lot to bark about.
‐ [Genichiro] True, a
traitor to a friend,
traitor to Jupiter,
and now, a dog of Nergal.
(guns cocking)
‐ What now, sir?
‐ Calm yourself.
‐ It appears your ceaseless
attachment to Tenkawa
will be your demise.
‐ Huh, huh?
Ah!
‐ Long time no see, Miss Minato.
‐ I‐I guess so.
(chuckling)
‐ This is a sacred place
reserved for the dead
to rest peacefully.
So please surrender
yourself with grace.
‐ And if we do not?
‐ You’ll be a resident here.
‐ We shall see.
Destroy them.
‐ Right!
(cloaked man roaring)
(cloaked man groaning)
‐ Jovian Federation
swordsmanship
is not the skill of an assassin.
(bones cracking)
(cloaked men yelling)
(cloaked men groaning)
‐ No way!
‐ It’s Jovian‐style Yawara.
‐ [Minato] Huh?
‐ No sword of corruption
can defeat Yawara skills.
Surrender now!
It’s over, Hokushin!
‐ I think not.
(loud whirring)
‐ What the?
How the hell is
he going to jump?
(laughing)
‐ [Hokushin] We’ll meet
again, Akito Tenkawa!
‐ Independent boson jumping?
‐ Yurika is now under
their spell, it seems.
‐ What?
‐ Kusakabe’s offenses will
be coming soon, so I‐‐
‐ Go on.
‐ There is something
very important
that I would like
to give to you.
(engine roaring)
‐ Hey, it’s so great
to see everyone again.
‐ [Male Crewman] We’re gonna
cover for Chief Uribatake
in his absence, right?
‐ Time to show him what the
maintenance crew can do!
‐ Yeah, we got their backs!
‐ [Maintenance Crew] Hoo‐ah!
‐ Seems like Akatsuki doesn’t
quite the punch he used to.
‐ And he’s losing his hair.
It hangs by a hair.
(laughing)
‐ [Pilot] Lunar ETA is
approximately 1400 hours‐‐
‐ [Minato] Ruriruri?
‐ Yes?
‐ So can you tell me what it was
that Akito gave to you?
‐ [Ruri] It’s a recipe.
‐ Recipe?
‐ It’s the Tenkawa
Special Ramen recipe.
‐ [Minato] The one he
offered you out of his yatai?
‐ Yeah.
There’s no way I can accept
this from you, Akito.
When this is all over,
you’ve rescued Miss Yurika,
and everything’s back to normal,
you’re going to need this.
‐ I have no use for it anymore.
The Akito Tenkawa that
you once knew is now dead.
I would like you to hold the
proof that he once existed.
‐ You’re being a bit dramatic.
‐ You don’t understand, Ruri.
While performing all
their experiments on me,
they did something to my brain.
And ever since then‐‐
(gasping)
(dramatic music)
I haven’t been the same.
My sense of taste is gone.
When I get excited,
this stuff can really
start shining on me.
I’m sort of like a comic book.
So I won’t be able to make
ramen for you anymore.
I’m sorry.
‐ [Prospector] I’ll see you
all at the victory celebration!
‐ It’s strange, being on
the side, seeing them off.
‐ [Girl] Mr. Prospector!
‐ Huh?
‐ Hmm?
‐ Hey, Miss Howmei!
‐ [Girls] We made it!
‐ Well, well, but they’ve
already taken off.
‐ No, they have a different
mission to work on.
‐ Okay?
‐ Okay girls, let’s get to it!
‐ [Girls] Aye!
(engine roaring)
(electronic beeping)
‐ [Yukina] So please sit back,
relax, and enjoy the flight.
Would anyone like
some tasty beverages?
‐ [Passengers] Huh?
‐ We’ll be serving
juices, colas, beers,
whiskey, sake, and
lots of snacks as well.
Ah!
(passengers oohing)
‐ Hey, hold on a second.
What are you doing here, Yukina?
My God!
‐ I’d like some hiyahshiame.
‐ Sure.
‐ Double durian juice.
‐ You have got more important
business to deal with.
You should go home right now.
For heaven’s sake,
don’t you have school?
‐ But it’s summer vacation.
‐ What about track and field?
You’ve got intermural
races soon!
‐ That’s the week after next.
Besides, if the mission fails,
then that’ll be
called off anyway.
‐ (growls) You’re a fool!
You should be at home!
(blowing raspberry)
‐ And Jun, where
are your clothes?
‐ No way, please stop!
(girls teasing)
Oh uh, I was just, uh, you know?
‐ I don’t think anyone
can you seriously
dressed up like that, Jun.
(Jun grumbling)
(passengers laughing)
‐ Miss Minato, let’s
talk about this later,
perhaps after we’ve
landed on the moon.
‐ Mmhmm, sure, sure,
later sounds super.
‐ You know, you’re gonna
get burned one day.
‐ Yeah, yeah.
(engine roaring)
‐ Main boosters, full power!
‐ Five G!
No, six G!
‐ Just a little more, Izumi!
(Ikumi humming)
‐ [Male Crewman] What the hell
are those two freaks doing?
‐ [Male Crewman] Supposedly,
they’re reenacting
leaving the Earth’s atmosphere
in the style of old anime.
(Izumi and Hikaru sighing)
‐ Oh.
‐ Just to let you know,
shuttles in the 23rd century
are comfortable and safe,
thanks to the inclusion of
gravity control systems.
‐ [Jun] Huh, ah!
‐ We have reached
stationary satellite orbit.
‐ Well, at least the flight
so far has been relatively‐‐
‐ I would say unpleasant.
‐ What are you talking about?
Is there something wrong?
‐ You knew all along she
would be onboard this shuttle,
didn’t you?
‐ Shiratori’s younger sister?
Yes, I did.
‐ Stupid!
I don’t believe it,
why didn’t you tell me?
‐ Because I wanted to
avoid unnecessary hassles
before takeoff.
‐ What was that?
‐ Just listen.
That girl is the younger sister
of the hero to the
Jovian Federation.
They might be after her
as their next target.
It would be more dangerous
to leave her alone.
‐ Oh?
‐ Approaching escort
fleet, lunar rendezvous.
‐ I am Araragi, commander
of the escort fleet,
at your service.
‐ I’m Ruri Hoshino,
captain of the Nadesico.
We are very grateful
for your contribution.
‐ Please, escorting a
jewel such as yourself,
it is but our pleasure.
‐ [Ruri] Uh?
‐ [Araragi] A white flower
blooming in the black of space,
Ruri Hoshino, the
Cybernetic Fairy.
That’s what the men
call you around here.
Yes, you are truly
a sight to behold.
‐ Uh, well, thank you.
And please send my
greetings and regards
to the rest of
your crew as well.
‐ Cybernetic Fairy, she’s
adorable, isn’t she?
‐ Yes, she is a
treasure in space.
‐ And I recorded the
entire thing, sir.
‐ Great, I’ll show it
to the others later.
(alarm blaring)
‐ Huh?
‐ [Male Technician] Rapid
increase of boson particles
5,000 kilometers ahead!
‐ What?
(dramatic music)
‐ Enemy convoy, 12 o’clock.
‐ Battleship frigate?
‐ Civilian shuttle.
That’s our target.
Behold, as this is truly the
covert operation’s vessel
intelligence discovered.
All units, strike
not the battleship,
but strike the shuttle!
‐ [Pilots] Aye!
‐ Attention all escort
units, full speed ahead,
diamond formation.
‐ The shuttle will
accelerate ahead.
‐ [Technicians] Huh?
‐ Okay everyone, just leave
everything to the specialist.
‐ Passengers and crew,
prepare for thrusters.
Put on your seat belts.
‐ All right!
So you want us to blast right
through the enemy barricade,
or what?
‐ Yes, just do your thing,
and help us get out
of here, please.
‐ Sure!
(engine roaring)
(electronic beeping)
‐ The shuttle’s on point.
These fools must want to die!
(weapons firing)
‐ [Pilot] Field strength
holding steady at 80%.
Push it.
‐ A little more, a little more!
(weapons firing)
‐ The enemy appears to
have lost their target.
We will push through
their front line
and act as the shuttle’s shield.
Life in death’s grasp.
Such a remarkable fairy.
‐ [Male Technician]
Boson readings increasing
in front of the shuttle!
‐ [Araragi] What?
(electronic warbling)
‐ No good, we’ll be
flanked at this rate!
‐ Oh no, this isn’t
what I bargained for!
‐ Well, don’t we
have any weapons?
‐ We took them off to
camouflage the ship.
‐ Just had to be
thorough, didn’t you?
(Minato chuckling)
‐ Ah!
‐ Undoubtedly, this is mutiny!
In the eyes of the
United Earth Charter,
we’re a threat to peace!
They see evil.
However, space‐time transference
ushers the dawn of a new world,
a new strength in space,
a new vision of power and order!
Now, light the way
for our heroes!
‐ Image, image, image.
Destination, Unified
Earth Headquarters.
Destination, Unified Force Base.
‐ [Female Technician]
Navigators,
continue with visualizations.
‐ [Male Technician] Image
transfer rate at 50%.
‐ Initiate transfer
enhancement program now.
Run in multi‐mode.
‐ Multi‐mode input running.
(light gentle music)
(laughing)
‐ Akito!
Just tell me where
you want to go, Akito!
(weapons firing)
‐ Not so fast, pigs!
(groaning)
(vocalizing)
‐ [Male Crewman] What are
those freaks up to now?
‐ [Male Crewman]
Apparently, this time,
they’re reenacting high
stress acceleration G‐force.
‐ [Male Crewman] I don’t
know why they’re having
such a good time.
(explosions booming)
‐ Boson reactions,
50 kilometers.
‐ What?
(electronic warbling)
‐ [Pilot] This one is huge.
‐ This looks like
nothing but trouble.
Eh?
‐ Now firing the
gravity blast cannon!
(gasping)
(heroic music)
(energy blasting)
‐ [Pilot] Emergency!
Leap!
(pilot screaming)
‐ Captain, Miss Minato,
did you just see all that?
(Seiya chuckling)
‐ [Passengers] What?
‐ [Male Crewman] Chief?
‐ Hey, hey, everybody!
How ya doin’?
‐ Mr. Seiya, what
are you doing there?
‐ Yeah, well, you know, I
thought this might happen.
I’m just glad I got
here before you did.
You can laugh this off as
being a little too convenient,
but you can never keep me away
from all these new gizmos!
Behold and long live technology!
‐ His face has been defaced.
Is that from his wife?
‐ That’s the price of a
timely plot twist, I guess.
‐ In any case, Mr. Seiya,
Harry, I’d like to know.
‐ Huh?
‐ Yeah?
‐ [Ruri] I want you to
explain how you got here.
How did you boson jump?
‐ Oh please, let me explain.
(weapons firing)
‐ Sir, they just came out
of nowhere without warning,
and they‐‐
(explosion booming)
(soldier screaming)
‐ [Man] International high
speed communications occupied.
(men gasping)
‐ We’ve all finished this, sire.
‐ Yes, the dawn of a new
order is soon to come.
‐ [Men] Three, two, one, kaboom!
‐ Get to know the Nadesico!
(upbeat music)
Hello, it’s been a while,
and it’s nice to meet you.
I’m Inez Fressange, medical
and science crew officer
of the Nadesico.
The enemy is seeking hegemony
over politics, economics,
entertainment,
morality and chastity
in the new world
order ushered in
with the arrival of the
era of boson jumping.
That is their goal.
So how can boson jumping‐‐
‐ Question.
‐ [Inez] Yes, what is it?
‐ I believe everyone here has
the same thing on their mind.
Didn’t you, I mean, weren’t
you killed or something?
‐ [Hikaru] Yeah, man,
how come you’re not dead?
‐ [Inez] Oh yes,
how rude, I’m sorry.
Why am I alive?
‐ How about I explain this one?
‐ [Hikaru] Hey, it’s
that washed‐up womanizer!
(laughing)
‐ Ouch, low blow.
But first, let me refute the
ugly rumors of me and this war.
(Ryoko growling)
‐ We don’t give a
rat’s ass about you!
Just tell us what’s
going on here!
‐ Hey there little
fella, weren’t you in
the Unified Forces?
‐ Don’t change the
subject, you piece of shit!
(laughing)
‐ Well, in any case, sometimes
to trick your enemies,
you have to trick your friends.
You see, since both Tenkawa
and the captain were abducted,
having her officially listed
as deceased, if you will,
proved to be the most
effective step we could take.
‐ Can I ask you a
personal question?
‐ [Nagare] Shoot.
‐ Mr. Akatsuki, tell me this.
Are you a good guy or bad guy?
(laughing)
‐ You do get straight
to the point, don’t ya?
Oops, I have a call
on the other line.
See ya.
Ooh, my goodness.
‐ This is the front gate!
The enemy has shown no
signs of letting up, sir!
‐ Easy, just leave it to me.
‐ Aye!
‐ All right, the
stage has been set.
Time to go.
(explosions booming)
(weapons firing)
‐ Enemy guard force is gone!
‐ Right, then we attack now!
(men yelling)
‐ Huh?
‐ [Men] Whoa!
‐ Hey boys, what’s the hurry?
‐ Huh?
‐ Hot damn.
‐ [Megumi] Hello everyone out
there, I’m Megumi Reinard!
‐ [Girls] And we’re
the Howmei Girls!
‐ We’d like to
extend a warm welcome
to everyone attending
tonight’s show.
‐ And we hope everyone
has an awesome time!
(crowd cheering)
‐ What is this?
Where in God’s name is
the General Assembly?
‐ Mr. Pros on guitar!
‐ Yeah, baby!
‐ [Megumi] Yoshido
Munetake on the bass!
‐ Far out.
‐ [Howmei Girl] And there’s
Miss Howmei tickling the keys!
(both grunting and shouting)
‐ [Megumi] And on drums,
Kouichiro Misumara and
Genpachiro Akiyama!
‐ And our special guest is‐‐
‐ Nagare Akatsuki!
(crowd cheering)
‐ Dagnabbit!
Hey everybody,
welcome to the show.
(crowd cheering)
‐ Kill him!
(guns firing)
‐ He’s got a distortion field!
‐ Never underestimate
the stinkin’ rich.
‐ Bastards, what is
the meaning of this?
‐ Oh, this?
This means the end to
your foolish undertakings.
‐ [Kawaguchi] What?
‐ Nobody who tries to hold
the General Assembly hostage
will ever take the world.
Come on, there’s no
need for you to die.
‐ [Kawaguchi] Then
we can kill you.
‐ [Pilot] Traitor Nagare
Akatsuki, receive your doom.
(electronic whirring)
(men gasping)
‐ [Genichiro] Your forces
outside have been neutralized.
Surrender.
‐ Boson jumper.
Some new model.
‐ It’s been some
time, eh, Kawaguchi?
‐ Commander?
‐ I just heart Ruri made
it to the Nadesico‐C.
‐ [Akito] Then it’s done.
‐ Yes.
Once she joins and becomes one
with the Omoikane’s system,
they will be utterly invincible.
‐ So the data we collected
was worth all the fighting.
‐ You’re going, aren’t you?
‐ Yes.
‐ Revenge.
It’s a word no one would
have ever associated
with Akito in the past.
‐ [Akito] That was
the past, this is now.
Thanks for the refueling.
‐ It’s nothing.
I’m just here running errands
for the Chairman anyway.
‐ Cancel all hits?
Why is that?
Explain this!
‐ Uh, well sir, the
enemy’s new weapons
and, uh, persuasions‐‐
‐ Persuasions?
(men gasping)
‐ Tsukumo Shiratori
is rolling in his‐‐
‐ Tsukiomi?
‐ He was still alive?
‐ [Man] Boson readings
directly above!
‐ What?
(heroic music)
(electricity crackling)
‐ [Male Technician]
We have a visual, sir.
It’s the Nadesico!
‐ Nadesico?
(all gasping)
‐ [Pilot] All unis are ordered
to stay at their posts!
‐ [Pilot] It’s not our fault,
the machines are moving
on their own, sir!
‐ Doing what?
(pilot gasping)
‐ [Male Technician] We’re
losing control, sir!
We’re losing control!
‐ The system’s been hijacked.
By the Fairy.
‐ [Minato] Phase
transition engine,
no abnormalities reported.
‐ [Hikaru] All stations,
please shift to alert
status pattern B.
‐ [Ruri] Harry, prepare
to take control of
all the Nadesico’s
operating system.
‐ Huh?
All of ’em?
You mean I won’t just
be running the backup?
‐ No.
I will be taking control of
all enemy systems on Mars
and I cannot control
the Nadesico as well.
The Nadesico‐C will
be all yours, Harry.
This is your chance.
‐ B‐but I‐‐
‐ I just know you
can do it, Harry.
‐ [Harry] Huh?
‐ Anyway, you owe Ruri for all
that pampering she gave you.
‐ [Inez] So then Ruri took
control of all of the units
in and around Mars?
She really is something.
‐ How are you feeling after
all that, Miss Fressange?
‐ I’m fine, but
it’s no easy task
to jump an entire battleship
to Mars in a single leap.
‐ I’m sure.
‐ So this is the
new world order?
‐ Good evening to everyone.
I am Ruri Hoshino,
captain of the United Earth
Space Fleet’s Nadesico‐C.
Former Jovian Federation
Vice Admiral Kusakabe,
you are under arrest.
‐ Silence, vile witch!
(men shouting)
‐ We will never,
ever slow down, we will
fight to the death!
‐ I want your word that
all of my subordinates
will be taken care of.
(electronic warbling)
‐ [Hikaru] Boson
readings at seven.
‐ [Minato] Ruriruri?
‐ [Ruri] Don’t bother.
‐ Huh?
‐ Everything’s okay.
We’ll leave it all to him.
‐ [Pilot] Are you sure, sir?
‐ Surprise attacks
involving jumping
are a double‐edged sword.
With the Amaterasu
out of the picture,
our chances of victory
were about 50/50,
but once a Class A jumper was
revealed to be still alive,
our chances suddenly‐‐
(electronic beeping)
The time has come to
put an end to this.
(dramatic music)
(weapons firing)
(explosions booming)
‐ [Ruri] My name is Ruri, and
this is my friend Omoikane.
Who are you?
‐ [Lapis] Lapis.
‐ [Ruri] Lapis?
Lapis Lazuli?
‐ [Lapis] I was born in
the Nergal laboratory.
I am Akito’s eyes, Akito’s ears,
Akito’s hands, Akito’s feet,
Akito’s, Akito’s‐‐
(explosions booming)
(dramatic music)
(energy blasting)
‐ I sense your fear.
No matter how strong
the armor you don,
the weakness within your
heart will always be exposed.
(Akito grunting)
(weapons firing)
‐ [Saburota] Sir!
‐ In comes the cavalry!
Better stay out of
this duel, boys,
or else this horse is
gonna kick your ass
into the River Styx!
‐ I’m the number one horse!
(Hikaru neighing)
‐ And me, number two.
‐ Well, I guess that
makes me a horse too.
‐ That’s right, all settled up!
‐ I think Ryoko
might need a ride.
‐ Hey, that’s good.
‐ Nobody’s riding anybody!
‐ Oops.
Well ladies, I suppose we’ll
just have to wait ’til later
to see who’s riding who.
‐ [Ryoko] Can it, jackass!
‐ [Izumi] Just listen
to those sweet nothings.
‐ Careful, men!
They but they’re crackshots!
(explosion booming)
(pilot screaming)
(explosions booming)
‐ It’s amazing how
far you’ve gotten.
A testament of true persistence.
‐ It’s over.
‐ [Ryoko] Goddamn it,
stop screwing around!
‐ [Hikaru] We’re
fighting, we’re fighting!
‐ [Izumi] Oh, serious fighting?
Then I’ll start fighting.
(pilot screaming)
‐ Let’s see what you’ve got.
(explosions booming)
(electricity crackling)
(gagging)
Remarkable...
(breathing heavily)
(grumbling)
‐ What‐what happened?
You’re all so old.
(all sighing)
‐ [Inez] Oh thank God,
you’re still clueless.
‐ I just had the craziest dream.
Akito?
Where’s Akito?
(dramatic music)
‐ Goodbye!
You sure it’s a good
idea to let ’em go?
‐ If he says he needs to go,
there’s nothing we can do.
‐ Oh.
What do you think he’s
going to do from now on?
‐ He’ll come back.
And if he doesn’t, then
I’ll just go out after him.
‐ [Minato] Ruriruri?
‐ Because Akito...
Because he’s a special
person to all of us.