[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] The Navy triumphed
in the War of the Best
and Luffy, unable to save his
brother Ace, fell into despair.
But this is a story
from another time.
Ten years ago, in the East Blue,
when the brothers ran wild
with dreams of a world
full of adventure.
[LUFFY]
"To Live Up to the Promise!
Departures of Their Own!"
[NARRATOR] The World Noble's
visit to the Goa Kingdom
has come and gone,
but another visitor lingers.
At a small village
in the East Blue,
a group of aspiring swordsmen
chat about the
strange encounter.
[thudding]
Did you see that weird
guy with the big head?
Yeah, his face was
totally crazy, too!
[STUDENT A]
I bet he needs that giant ship
to fit his giant head!
580, 581,
582, 583...
...584... [grunts]
[IVANKOV]
You certainly kept me waiting!
What could possibly be
more important than me?
Sorry.
[gasps] Goodness... is that?
[REVOLUTIONARY B]
Someone get help!
[REVOLUTIONARY C]
This doesn't look good.
Let's prepare treatment!
[REVOLUTIONARY D]
Roger!
[REVOLUTIONARIES chattering]
Honestly!
What in the world have
you been up to all day?
[DRAGON]
I was watching the ceremony
they held for the World Noble.
[gasps]
One, that's some risky business
and two, why didn't you take me?
[DRAGON]
Because you would attract
too much attention, obviously.
[gasps]
[IVANKOV]
Could it be I'm too fabulous?
[DRAGON] At any rate,
we've tarried for long enough.
We've got business to attend to.
Do we have supplies?
The training hall at the village
gave us just enough
food for now.
Very well.
Set sail!
We're heading back to Baltigo!
[NARRATOR] A short time later,
in the nearby Goa Kingdom...
[MAN A]
Ah, finally, some junk!
[NARRATOR] Although the
fire razed Gray Terminal
and its people to the ground,
another sea of trash and another
sea of scavengers appeared.
[LUFFY]
You're in for it this time!
Here it goes!
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Heh.
[yelps]
--[gasps]
--[LUFFY grunting]
[ACE laughing]
Are you kidding me?
You still suck butt!
[ACE] It doesn't matter
how hard you punch
if you can't hit anything!
I told you, rubber's
a crappy power.
It's no good for fighting!
Shut up! You're dumb!
You're the dumb one!
I'm honest, that's all!
I'm trying to save
you from falling
on your stupid
rubber ass all day!
You're just jealous 'cause
you can't do awesome
stuff like me!
All you've got are jerk powers
and I'm working on all
kinds of cool moves!
Luffy! That was great!
Man, that punch of yours flies
further and further every day!
Come on!
If you go easy on him,
he'll get a big head!
I got stronger today
and I'm gonna be even
stronger tomorrow!
[BOTH]
Right, Sabo?
[LUFFY sighs] Sabo was a
nice brother, not like you.
You're trying to say it'd be
better if I'd died, aren't you?
I didn't say anything like that!
Yeah, but that's what
you meant, isn't it?
[LUFFY yells]
That's what I'm talkin' about,
Sabo would never
hit me, you jerk!
[ACE]
So, what?
[LUFFY] Be nice to your
brother! That's what!
[ACE]
Nuh-uh!
[DADAN]
Ow. Huh?
--[DOGRA grunts]
--[MAGRA] Huh?
I'm hereby establishing
my own country.
He's doing what now?
[DOGRA grunts]
Me, too!
[DADAN] What're you
little idiots up to now?
We need to be strong enough
to live on our own!
You're from the Dadan
Kingdom, by the way.
We still need to use
your bath, though.
[LUFFY, ACE]
Hmph!
[DADAN sighs]
[groans, sighs]
--[LUFFY grunting]
--[BEAR growling]
[BEAR snarling]
Ace! This one is way too big.
I need your help!
[ACE] You? The "Mighty
King Luffy" needs help?
[roars]
Here goes!
[LUFFY grunting]
[gasping]
[LUFFY yells]
No!
[ACE panting]
[ACE]
Hey, Dadan Kingdom!
We need help! Luffy got hurt!
He's in trouble!
Magra! Hurry up! This is bad!
Okay, Ace. Hurry,
bring him inside!
[ribbitting]
[ACE sniffling]
Okay, wow.
It's a good thing you brought
him here when you did.
Also, if this cut
had been any deeper,
he probably would've
died on the spot.
I hate to say it, but this is
no good with only two of you.
[ACE crying]
It's all my fault.
I knew better.
Even if you're a captain,
fighting alone doesn't
make you any stronger.
I'm still no good.
I'm still not good enough.
[crying]
Now, now...
[ACE]
I'm sorry, Luffy.
I let you down.
[ACE crying]
[BANDIT C]
Guys, come see!
Makino came to visit
and she brought booze!
[MAKINO] You want to know how
to properly say "thank you"?
[ACE]
Mm-hm.
[MAKINO] And what's this
about "paying respects"?
As a pirate and as
Luffy's big brother,
I need to pay my respects
to this Shanks guy.
Luffy says he owes
the man his life,
so it's kinda
the least I can do.
Uh...
[MAKINO gasps]
Got something to say to me?!
[MAKINO chuckles]
Sorry, sorry.
Okay, I think I can
give you some tips.
For starters, after a meal...
[CHEF A]
It's a dine and dash!
Come back! [pants]
Wait a sec, we almost forgot!
Gotta pay respect!
Oops! Yeah, you're right!
Huh?
[ACE, LUFFY]
Thank you for the meal, sir!
Ah! Keep your thanks. Are you
brats gonna pay me or what?
[LUFFY yelling]
I'm not losin' today! No way!
[yells, groans]
[ACE grunting]
[LUFFY groaning]
[BEAR snarling]
[BEAR growls]
[ACE, LUFFY grunt]
[ACE grunts]
[LUFFY yelling]
[ACE yelling]
[ACE, LUFFY grunt]
[BOTH]
All right!
[ACE]
Now for some bear meat stew!
[inaudible]
[LUFFY]
Take care, Ace! See ya!
Yeah. See you soon!
Keep training hard!
Just gimme three years
and before you know it,
my wanted poster's gonna
be everywhere you go!
[ACE laughing]
Kick some ass! Bon voyage!
Don't catch a cold out there!
Look for me in the papers.
It won't take long, okay?
[NARRATOR] The world did not
know that the son of Gold Roger
had grown up in secret,
nor did they know that
he set sail that day,
determined to make
a name of his own.
[ACE chuckles]
[LUFFY laughs]
Guess that's it, huh?
Honestly! If Garp were here,
think of what he'd say.
[GARP] Gonna need you
to raise this baby for me!
[DADAN]
What? Why? Is it even yours?
So there you are, Boss!
Hey! Believe it
or not, Ace is gone!
[DADAN]
That so?
Well, one less
brat to worry about,
though I'm sure Garp'll
gimme hell for it.
Kid left and he's still
causin' me trouble.
Oh, I almost forgot,
there's a message he
asked us to give to you.
[DADAN]
Yeah, why should I care?
He probably just wants to tell
me my feet smell or somethin'.
[BANDIT A] He said, "thank
you for taking care of me."
[gasps, crying]
How could you do
that to me, you beast?
[BANDIT A]
What's wrong, Boss?
You're not crying, are you?
[DADAN] If you don't
shut up, I'll make you cry!
Three more years,
that's the rule.
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
[gasps]
So close! I just
need a little more.
You almost got it now, Luffy.
Bend your legs a little
and aim straight ahead!
[LUFFY]
Heh.
Now, Gum-Gum... Pistol!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[SABO chuckles]
[LUFFY grunts]
Gotta keep getting stronger!
Hang on, Ace!
I'm comin' for you!
[DOGRA]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[DOGRA]
You gotta see the paper! Look!
Oh? What's up?
[DOGRA]
It's just like he said!
[LUFFY] Whoa, you're
right! Ace made the news!
He's got a ship and
a crew and everything!
Aw, man. I'm so jealous! Wow!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[LUFFY]
But I'm gonna do even better!
Hey, you guys!
I'm leaving now! You're not
gonna see me off? Hey!
[DADAN]
Use your head for once.
The mayor and Makino
wouldn't mind us stopping by,
but as for everyone else
in Windmill Village?
We'd probably scare
the pants right off 'em.
I dunno...
Ugh, don't make it
awkward, just go already!
Okay, well, goodbye, you guys.
Thanks for everything.
I'm sure gonna miss you!
[BANDITS]
Aw, now don't say that,
you're gonna make us blush!
Well, bye. Take it easy!
Heh. I will!
You guys, too, okay?
Oh! One last thing!
[BANDITS]
Huh?
Dadan, I still think mountain
bandits are super lame!
[DADAN]
Shut up and leave, damn it!
But you guys, you're great!
[gasps, crying]
It's not enough to ruin my life,
now you gotta
break my heart, too?
You're awful, I tell ya!
All of you are good
for nothin'! [cries]
[LUFFY]
Sorry I made you cry.
[DADAN]
Shut up or I'll make you cry!
[NARRATOR] Now, to Windmill
Village on Dawn Island
at the edge of the Goa Kingdom.
[MAN B] No offense,
but why don't you take
my old fishing boat
instead, Luffy?
That thing is gonna sink as
soon as you get out to sea!
That's too small, even for you!
I wanna start small,
but I'll get a real big
one soon, don't worry!
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
Sabo!
Here I go!
Watch out for me
out there, okay? [laughs]
[LUFFY] Sabo was first
and Ace was second.
I may be the last to go,
but I'm gonna be the best!
I'm comin' for you, Ace!
And all my special
moves work now, too!
Why are you talking to yourself?
Is this some kind of
pirate ritual I don't get?
No, it's a challenge!
To my brother, Ace!
Ace? Who is that?
[MAN E]
I dunno.
Okay! I'm goin' for real now!
[CROWD shouting]
I knew this day would come,
but I'm still a bit sad.
I'll sure miss him.
Sad is right, like the
world needs another pirate!
[sighs]
[LUFFY]
Perfect weather today! Lucky me!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[gasping]
[CROWD gasping]
Oh, no!
Hey, pal. It's been
a while, huh?
This won't play out
like last time.
I've been practicing this
move for ten whole years!
Now, Gum-Gum...
[roars]
...Pistol!
[SEA MONSTER groans]
Heh.
Been waitin' a long
time to do that.
[CROWD cheering]
[MAGRA, DADAN gasp]
He just... took out that
sea monster in one punch!
I gotta admit... I'm proud.
[LUFFY]
First, I need a crew.
About ten people
should be enough.
After that, pirate flag!
All right! Let's get going!
Someday I'm gonna be...
[LUFFY]
...King of the Pirates!
[NARRATOR]
But time has not been kind,
and after the death of Ace,
Luffy's optimism from that
day is nowhere in sight.
[LUFFY crying]
Please, Luffy...
Me? King of the Pirates?
What a joke!
[LUFFY]
Look at me.
I'm useless.
Ace!
I'm too weak!
[NARRATOR] Garp returns from the
war and visits Luffy's hometown,
only to receive a cold
welcome from Dadan.
Meanwhile, Luffy
is still inconsolable
after the death of his brother.
As Jinbei watches over him,
desperate to ease
his friend's suffering,
he recalls something
that Ace once said.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"I Want to See Them!
Luffy's Mournful Cry!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!