Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of
pirates go to battle
across the seas in search
of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will
cut a path across
the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison Impel Down.
Forming an unlikely alliance
with Buggy the Clown,
Luffy heads to the second
level of the prison:
the Floor of
Wild Beasts from Hell.
There, he encounters Mr. 3,
a former Baroque Works agent
and continues his descent
alongside his unwilling allies.
[CROCODILE laughs]
My, my...
Sounds like there's a lot
of fun going on in the world.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
Jimbei. Ace. Look.
Do you get it?
This world is full of dozens
of second placers.
Silver medalists
who could never defeat
Roger and Whitebeard,
all holding back their tears.
[CROCODILE laughs]
[LUFFY]
"Chief Guard Saldeath's Trap!
Level 3: Starvation Hell!"
[HAIR GUARD] Monitor Room!
We've arrived at Level 2.
Can you see
the image on screen?
We can. Keep us posted on
what you find down there.
[HAIR GUARD]
Roger that.
[CHUBBY GUARD]
What happened here?
Look at the size
of this hole!
It's so big, even the Sphinx
could've fallen through it!
[HAIR GUARD]
What in the hell
is Straw Hat Luffy
looking for?
[gate creaks]
[GUARDS]
Huh?
[footsteps]
[GUARDS]
Huh?
[chains clanking]
[GUARDS]
Huh?!
[PRISONERS growling]
[gasps]
[RIGHT GUARD]
That does not look good!
[LEFT GUARD] I don't
know how they got the keys,
but the prisoners on
Level 2 are out of their cells!
Don't tell me Straw Hat
and his friends did this.
Those guards're
in trouble down there!
[PRISONERS laughing]
Let's hear it for
our savior, Captain Buggy!
[PRISONERS cheer]
Now it's payback time!
[PRISONERS laughing]
Level 2, reporting in!
We need backup here!
[HAIR GUARD]
The prisoners are all free!
I repeat:
the prisoners are all--
Quick! Blugori to Level 2!
[OUTSIDE GUARD]
Hey! Good news, men!
We know what
Straw Hat's doing!
[LEFT GUARD]
Oh yeah? Who told you?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku
himself just sent word to us.
[OUTSIDE GUARD] Little did
we know, Monkey D. Luffy,
and our condemned prisoner
Portgaz D. Ace,
have more in common
than the D in their names.
It turns out they're brothers.
[ALL gasp]
[GUARD]
Hold on.
Are you saying he's trying
to stop the public execution?!
Break in and make it out
with his brother
before we
can transport him?
[OUTSIDE GUARD]
What else could it be?
[UNSEEN GUARD] That would
explain why he keeps going down.
We were so focused on
Whitebeard's attack,
we let him sneak inside.
If he manages
to pull this off,
all hell's
gonna break loose!
We've gotta stop him!
Inform Warden
Magellan immediately!
And get that riot on
Level 2 under control! Now!
[MAN laughing]
Think this is funny, do you?
[laughing]
We're at a crossroads
that could change
the future of the sea.
Yet that troublemaking
grandson of yours
seems to undermine our
efforts at every turn!
Just like at Enies Lobby!
[SPANDAM] This symbol represents
the unity of over 170 nations.
A power that spans the
four seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world itself!
Do you realize how strong
our organization is?
Do you realize how devoted
we are to capturing her?
If that's Robin's enemy,
then I know what to do.
Sniper King.
[USOPP]
Hm?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger.
[USOPP]
This is my new weapon,
a massive slingshot by
the name of Kabuto!
Behold its awesome power!
Special Attack.
Firebird Star!
[gasps]
[ROBIN gasps]
No way.
Then, the Celestial Dragons.
Now you're annoying me, too!
[gunshots]
[CHARLOSS]
Hmm?
[LUFFY yelling]
[SENGOKU growls]
Dammit!
This is unprecedented, I say!
[GARP laughing]
Let this sink in!
We haven't had
a single breakout
in Impel Down in
the past 20 years!
The Golden Lion
was the last.
No one else has
challenged these walls
from the inside
or the outside!
[SENGOKU] Impel Down is
more than a prison.
It's a symbol of
unyielding justice
with an iron-tight
reputation
that Straw Hat
is attempting to tarnish!
And to make it even worse
he's the grandson of a Marine!
Ambitious boy!
I'm so proud of him!
[growls]
Damn that Kuma!
He said he took care
of the Straw Hat crew
at the Sabaody Archipelago.
I should've known better
than to trust that fool.
Man's one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
what do you expect?
What I wanna know is how
he was able to get through
the defenses we've got set up.
You think he flew in?
[SENGOKU growls]
That's enough!
If you weren't known
all over the Grand Line
as the hero of the Navy, Garp.
I'd make you take responsibility
for your family myself!
[laughing]
Go ahead, lock me
up, execute me.
It won't change a thing!
Nothing, you hear me?
[laughing]
It's too late!
[SENGOKU]
Laugh it up while you can.
But a blow like this
to our reputation
will have serious
repercussions.
Tsuru and I have tried to
keep this under wraps.
But there's only
so much we can do!
[GARP]
Hey! Those are mine, dammit!
No fair!
Shut up already!
[GARP yells]
[BUGGY yells]
[BUGGY yelping]
[BUGGY and LUFFY]
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
[LUFFY] This floor feels
like a frying pan!
[LUFFY panting]
So are we in the desert?
It's hot.
Why's it so quiet?
[BUGGY panting]
Level 3.
Oh, how I never
wanted to end up here.
[BUGGY grunting]
Straw Hat! If I have
to go to one more
crappy place with you,
I'll lose my mind!
[LUFFY]
Huh. He's takin' a cat nap.
Oh, that's real funny!
This place is especially
bad for someone like me.
I'm a Wax Man, after all.
Big place!
So where are the stairs down?
Haven't a clue.
Your buddy here's gonna melt
if we don't get moving soon.
Well alright, then off we go.
[LUFFY panting]
On second thought,
maybe we should've
just sat down and died.
Don't waste your
energy complaining.
I won't carry you
if you collapse.
[LUFFY panting]
Hey, look!
It's grilled chicken time!
That is not natural.
A hummingbird fluttered
down from above.
It was grilled
in the open air.
[BOTH]
How hot is it here?
This is good!
You're missin' out!
[MR. 3, BUGGY]
No thank you.
[LUFFY] I wish I could eat
that lion from upstairs.
I bet this heat
could barbeque him.
[BUGGY]
That thing talked like a human!
Are you serious?
[MR. 3]
At this rate.
He's going to eat us next.
Look! You see that?
What, the jail
cells? Who cares?
How thick-headed
can you get, kid?
We can hide from
the sun inside there!
And we might find prisoners
who can lead us to the stairs!
Whoa, I didn't think of that!
Man, you're the smartest!
Damn straight, I am! Hey, Mr.3!
Quick! Make some keys!
[LUFFY giggles]
I'm afraid there's
just no place to hide.
Hey, could you tell
me where the--
[MR. 3] A miserable sight
if I've ever seen one.
You wouldn't think
looking at them now,
but the prisoners on this floor
were all hardened criminals
commanding bounties
of over
50 million berries.
Beneath here is
the Burning Heat Hell,
cooking the ground.
Also, these men are
deprived of food and water,
[MR. 3]
leaving them half dead.
A shell of their
former selves.
[MR. 3] This is Level 3.
The Starvation Hell.
Yes. Now you know
why this floor is covered
with what appears to be sand.
Oh no.
Alas. Yes.
Chances are what you're
standing on are the remains
of prisoners who have
completely dried up.
[BUGGY yells]
[MR. 3] If we remain
in this place too long,
we'll become sand
beneath someone's feet
just like they did.
In other words, let's move
while we have
the sweat to spare.
Okay. Then let's go
to Level 4 already.
[MR. 3, BUGGY]
Seriously?
[BUGGY]
Not that way!
We need to take
the stairs on the left!
[LUFFY]
We do?
[MR. 3] No, we should
take the pass on the right.
[LUFFY]
Are you making this up?
Reporting in, sir.
The targets are
proceeding to the back.
[SALDEATH]
Understood.
Keep an eye on them for now.
Be patient.
All is going
according to plan.
[PRISONERS yelling]
[GUARD]
Oof!
[HAIR GUARD]
Haven't you been able to
contact Warden Magellan yet?
[LEFT SITTING GUARD]
No! Not yet, sir!
[HAIR GUARD]
What about the Blugori?
[RIGHT GUARD] They headed
off to catch the invaders
with their commander, sir!
[HAIR GUARD] Damn it!
The security of Impel Down
shouldn't fall to
pieces this easily!
[BUGGY]
Why?
Why are we back
where we started?
[LUFFY] 'Cause we went
in a circle, I guess.
Quit being so relaxed!
We're having a crisis here!
[MR. 3] I knew we should've
gone to the right.
It's hot here.
I sure hope we get
to Level 4 soon.
[MR. 3, BUGGY] Go by yourself,
I'm getting out of here!
[LUFFY] But you said we were
gonna save Ace together!
You have to show me the way!
That was the deal!
[Mr. 3] I never said that!
Neither of us did!
[BUGGY]
You're just making stuff up
'cause that's what
you wanna hear!
[LUFFY]
I could've sworn you said that.
They've returned
and are in place, sir.
Good. Then draw the net.
[GUARD 431 B]
Yes, sir!
[LUFFY]
Fine! I don't need you!
[LUFFY yells]
[MR. 3 moans]
[LUFFY]
What is this thing?
[BUGGY]
A trap! Obviously!
Damn it, we're done for!
[BUGGY and MR. 3 yelling]
I think it's made of iron!
What's with this?
I should be able to use
my Chop-Chop powers!
Thing must be lined
with Sea Prism Stone!
I fear they'll
give us more than
a slap on the wrist for
our little attempt at escape.
We'll be tortured to death.
[LEVEL 3 GUARD 431A]
We've captured the invader
Straw Hat Luffy
along with two others.
[BUGGY]
What do you mean "two others"?
I got a name!
[MR. 3]
Don't antagonize them, Buggy!
You'll only make it worse.
And it's more than
bad enough already.
[LUFFY]
Crap!
There's gotta be some
way to rip this net!
[BUGGY] The guards and
the Blugoris are coming!
[LEVEL 3 GUARD 431A] Put the Sea
Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
[LEVEL 3 GUARD 431B]
Yes, sir!
[LUFFY growls]
Who's this guy?
[SALDEATH]
"This guy" is called Saldeath.
Saltbreath, huh?
You better change your diet.
[SALDEATH]
No! That's not what I said.
Pay attention.
It's Saldeath. Got it?
Right. Sardine Head.
[SALDEATH]
No! Get it right!
What's wrong with you?
At any rate.
There's no point
in you resisting us.
You're in a highly secure
underwater prison,
so needless to say,
there's nowhere for you to run.
Y'know, you're fortunate
that I was the one
who captured you.
[SALDEATH]
There are four other guards
prowling around on
the floors beyond this one.
And they're demons.
He's right.
This little guy's
downright cute
compared to
what's down there.
If only we'd turned right.
We were so close.
It wouldn't've mattered.
They both circle around
and we were watching
you the entire time,
so if you hadn't
ended up in this trap,
we would've gotten
you with another one.
[MR. 3, BUGGY]
That's how it is.
[SPHINX grunts]
Vongole. Bianco.
Ah! Chief, the Sphinx!
Pasta?
[SPHINX]
Soup spaghetti!
[Level 3 Guard 431B]
He's moved on to pastas now!
[BUGGY yells]
We'll be squashed!
Fettuccini!
[GUARDS]
The Sphinx is awake!
[SALDEATH] Oh, no.
He's gonna break the net!
Be careful, men!
They can't escape,
especially not Straw Hat!
[SPHINX roars]
Deep fried noodles!
Did he say that one yet?
I don't even care anymore!
Yay! I'm free!
[GUARDS yell]
It's still hot,
but at least I can run away!
After them!
[BLUGORI grunt]
Gum-Gum. Gatling!
[LUFFY panting]
Hey. Where'd they go?
[BUGGY]
Come on, Mr 3! Hurry up!
[MR. 3 groans] I can't move
quickly in this heat.
[LUFFY]
They climbed up the net!
Good thinking!
[BUGGY laughing]
So long, Straw Hat!
Tell your brother
I said "hello"!
If he's still alive,
I'll buy him a drink!
[MR. 3 laughing]
And by the way,
thanks for being
our live bait you
little imbecile!
Whew, glad to see they're safe.
Well okay! See ya!
Thanks a lot for
your help, you guys!
[BUGGY and MR 3 groan]
He's so sweet!
My heart. It's breaking.
Stay sharp, men!
He's got a 300
million berry bounty!
[BLUGORI grunting]
[BUGGY]
This is our chance! Run for it!
[MR. 3]
Right! Let's go!
Look, I don't have time to
fight all you guys right now.
Soba!
Oh, great!
He's on a rampage!
[LUFFY yells]
He's on the run! After him!
[LUFFY]
Where are the stairs to go down?
[sighs]
[MAGELLAN]
We're close. Only a bit further,
and we'll arrive at the floor
where Ace is being held.
Took long enough.
It feels like we've been
riding in this elevator forever.
It just makes sense.
The area we're headed
to must be isolated.
It's filled with the
most dangerous criminals
from all over the world,
not just "Fire Fist".
With inmates like these,
we can't afford to
take any chances.
We wouldn't be going
to all this trouble
if you weren't
a Warlord, you know.
Then it's fortunate that I am.
So you're more than happy
to help me, aren't you?
Oh, but of course!
[MAGELLAN coughing]
Incidentally, there's
a prisoner down here
who was once
a Warlord, just like you.
Well, I have no
interest in him.
I only came here to
see "Fire Fist" Ace.
I promise to behave.
And I intend to
hold you to that.
[BUGGY and MR. 3 panting]
[MR. 3]
So hot.
I think we're safe up here.
Their attention's on
Straw Hat, like we planned.
They've sealed off the
staircases leading up.
And it's getting far too hot
for me to remain
here any longer.
[BON CLAY]
♪ Un. Deux. Krah!
♪ Un. Deux. Ora!
Hey. Who's that singing?
[BON CLAY]
♪ Un. Deux. Ora!
♪ Un. Deux. Krah!
[MR. 3 screams]
[BON CLAY] ♪ They always
say it's all about ♪
♪ The ways of
boys and girls ♪
♪ But I'm special, 'cause
♪ I take the best
from both worlds! ♪
♪ That's why we
♪ Are always free!
[PRISONERS]
♪ So free
[BON CLAY]
♪ Always free!
[PRISONERS]
♪ So free
[BON CLAY]
♪ When you're queer
♪ You never fear!
[PRISONERS]
♪ Never fear!
[BON CLAY]
♪ No, never fear!
♪ Oh, come my way!
Oh, come my way! ♪
[NARRATOR]
After much tribulation,
Impel Down is put on lockdown
and its only exit is sealed,
leaving Luffy's chance of
success even lower than before.
Unaware of this, Luffy
continues to Ace's floor
only to have another
unexpected reunion.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"The Unleashed Swan!
A Reunion with Bon Clay."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!