Mwell, Hello there, Pirate Boy.
Were you looking for me?
All I want to hear is
your side of the story!
Last night I saw Nico Robin
here, without a doubt.
And mind you. I have
nothing against any of you.
I have no reason to lie.
Are you sure it wasn't
someone who looked like her?
[ICEBERG]
Shut up and listen, boy.
I didn't call you in here
to bicker about who did what.
I have a favor to ask
and it would be in your
best interest to grant it.
No matter what it takes.
I have to see
Nico Robin again!
[NEWSPAPER GUY A] Extra!
Extra! Read all about it!
The Straw Hat Pirates
were the culprits
in the attack
against Mr. Iceberg!
We know that the culprits
are still here on the island,
so be sure to
stay on the lookout.
We must band
together to hunt down
the Straw Hats and
send them to the gallows!
[ICEBERG]
I'll say it once again.
Let me see Nico Robin!
[LUFFY]
Sorry, that's not possible.
We have no
idea where she is.
[loud gunshot]
[CRAFTSMAN A]
Gunfire!
It came from the bedroom!
[CRAFTSMAN A]
Iceberg, we heard a...?!
Are... Are you all right?
Yes.
I'd hoped to come
closer to the truth
but that foolish
hope has been in vain.
Arrest all of the
Straw Hat Pirates.
[CRAFTSMAN B]
Yes, sir!
[NAMI]
Hey, Luffy.
Were you able to
speak with Iceberg?
What did he say? Is it true?
Yeah he said it was
Robin, no doubt of it.
No way! Why would...?
Why would she do
something like that?
I refuse to believe it!
♪ opening song ♪
[LUFFY]
[CHIMNEY]
We're here! We're here!
Come on, Granny, Hurry! Hurry!
[KOKORO] Calm down,
get a hold of yourself.
Aaah...
Water 7, it's been a while.
[CHIMNEY]
Granny! Hurry! Hurry!
Okay, okay.
[STATION AGENT A]
Attention, all passengers!
Wearing a mask on the sea train
today is strictly prohibited!
Look, ma'am, just cooperate
and show me your face.
This is my face, see?
Huh?
[KOKORO]
Hey, you!
Oh... Uh, Ms. Kokoro!
So nice to see you again!
What's going on here? Trouble?
[STATION AGENT C]
Yes, yes, ma'am.
Everyone is on the lookout
for the Straw Hat pirates.
The culprits in the attempted
assassination of Iceberg.
Iceberg's assassins?
What is it, Granny? Huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
[NAMI]
Huh?
Waaaaaahhhh!!!
I'm falling! I'm falling!
[LUFFY]
Whew!
Good! Safe and sound!
Man that wore me out. I'm...
"Safe and sound" my butt!
I thought I was gonna die!
What was I supposed to do?
You were the one that said
we couldn't use the elevator
'cause we'd get caught!
I didn't have a choice!
That doesn't mean
"Hey, let's jump down," idiot!
You can't glide around like
that square-nosed
shipwright, got it?!
Right, sorry about that.
[NAMI] Whatever. It's fine
since we're safe now.
Then stop hitting me!
However, we might
not be safe for long.
[LUFFY] We won't?
Why not? What's wrong?
[NAMI] This island's
topography and climate.
With this much wind blowing,
and the atmospheric
pressure falling so rapidly,
there's likely going to
be a typhoon here tonight.
This place is called
"The City of Water."
Think about it:
Its greatest weakness
would have to be flooding.
Okay, so it floods. So what?
[NAMI]
Well, it worries me, that's all.
I'll check into it later.
Come on, let's head back to
the inn for the time being.
[squeaking door hinges]
Eh heh heh heh...
Hey there!
Welcome! How are you?
Ow! How's everything
going, Blueno?
Feeling super?
Eh heh heh heh...
Yeah, well, I suppose
you could say that.
[FRANKY]
What do you mean "suppose"?
You're not a very
decisive guy, are you?
I'll take the usual.
Fill 'er up, please!
Do you got any money?
Just fill 'em up,
will ya?! Cola!
Gah! To think that you run
an establishment like this
with the greedy notion of taking
money from your customers!
We do have
a little money.
About a million berries
left from our shopping spree.
What?!
We have that much left?!
How disgraceful!
How totally uncool!
To think that I didn't
spend it all in one night!
Here! Gimme that!
Ow! Listen up! This is
your lucky day, customers!
All of your drinks are on me!
Knock back as much
booze as you like!
Complements of me,
your pal, Franky!
[CUSTOMER A] That's our
Franky! You're the best!
[CUSTOMER B] The face of
Water Seven's underworld!
What a guy!
[CUSTOMER C] Whoa!
That's awesome!
[CUSTOMER D] Look over here!
It's piled up on the floor!
[FRANKY]
So, Blueno! Where's my cola?
Come on! Hurry it up, already!
[KOKORO] Looks like business
has been good for you, Franky.
Huh?
Ahh!
Old hag Kokoro?!
That was you I sat next to?!
I thought it was a
statue of a sea monster.
Ahhh... Ahahahaha!
[CHIMNEY]
Granny, is it okay
for me to get a refill
on my juice then?
Hey, kid, this is a bar.
It's no place for
little shrimps like you.
[KOKORO]
Business has been good, right?
Huh? Fine. Whatever.
Suit yourself.
[CHIMNEY]
Hurray! Juice!
Yeah, business has
been outstanding.
But I feel terrible.
In fact, this entire week
has been a total downer.
And it's all because
of that stupid pirate!
[BLUENO]
Here you go! A full tank!
[FRANKY]
Good! Took you long enough!
Fuel, fuel, fuel, fuel!
Mmmmmmm...
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Super!
There! Completely restored!
That bastard, wait 'til
I get my hands on him!
Hey! Hag! Why are you here?
Aqua Laguna is on its way.
Oh? Is that right.
No wonder the wind's
blowing so strong today.
You need to get your house
prepped up for the storm.
Well there's nothing
much to prep really,
seeing as how I don't actually
have a house anymore.
Hahahaha.
[KOKORO] I was going to
have a drink with Iceberg,
but it seems he was shot.
[FRANKY]
Yeah, I heard about that.
They say pirates
are responsible.
Galley-La and the
townspeople are raging pissed.
So a pirate did it, huh?
Hahahaha!
Do you honestly think
that's what happened?
Hey, you sound like
you know something.
If you really do, then
spit it out, you old hag.
Iceberg's constantly being
hounded by the World Government.
You ever notice that?
So? Wait, are you trying to say
that government lap dog
Corgy pulled the trigger?
Hahaha!
That little troll isn't cut out
to try something like that.
[KOKORO]
You're right.
An assassination plot falls more
in line with the work of CP-9.
Isn't that right, Blueno?
Ever heard of 'em?
[BLUENO] Eh...
Only rumors, really.
Geez, you village
simpletons sure put
a lot of stock
into stories about
imaginary boogeyman-
shadow-organizations.
[KOKORO] Don't be an idiot.
Of course they exist.
They just never show themselves.
Can't really work undercover
if everyone knows who you are.
You seem pretty
sure of yourself.
Got some kind of
proof about this?
Nope. Just rumors.
Nyahahaha!
Stop screwing around, hag!
Look, rumors are
superstitious nonsen--
Strange they've remained a
rumor for such a long time, huh?
They're good at eliminating
people without anyone noticing.
If you mess with them,
you're dead meat.
Nyah! Hahahaha!
[SAHDOWED FIGURE]
Impressive work.
The assignment we had to
do yesterday went very well.
Excellent job, Nico Robin.
Thanks. It was a cakewalk.
[SAHDOWED FIGURE]
Though, naturally,
you're now being pursued
by every last
person in the city.
[ROBIN]
Indeed, I am.
[SHADOWED FIGURE]
Merely a temporary setback.
Tonight is what's
important. Understand?
We'll infiltrate Iceberg's
residence one more time.
If it becomes a
worst-case scenario,
you're free to eliminate
all of the evidence.
Among Tom's apprentices
who could've had it
from the very beginning,
Iceberg is the only
one that remains alive.
No matter how much
he denies having it,
in the name of CP9,
we will take it tonight.
Never forget--this is
a mission of justice.
[ELEVATOR GIRL A]
In compliance with
the Aqua Laguna warning
that was issued for the
entire island earlier today:
all docks on the
shipbuilding island are now
to be considered public
shelter and evacuation centers.
Large crowds are expected,
so please take shelter
as quickly as possible.
Additionally, keep
in mind that Dock 1
is currently in
a dangerous state.
[CITIZEN A] All right,
I'll put the iron board on.
Hey Honey, you sure we
have everything we'll need?
Yes... Now, come on.
We need to take
shelter in the shipyard.
Yeah, Dad!
Let's get going!
C'mon! Hurry!
[CITIZEN A]
Patience, patience!
You gotta be careful
sealing this board.
If the inside of our
house gets flooded,
everything will be ruined.
[CITIZEN C] Tie that
side down, too! Move it!
[CITIZEN B] Hey! The wind
is starting to pick up!
The waves will be
here anytime now!
Hurry! If we take too long,
those assassin pirates
are gonna show up, too!
What?
Where'd he disappear to?
[CRAFTSMAN B]
I'm sure he went this way!
[CRAFTSMAN C]
He's gotta be around here!
[CRAFTSMAN A] Okay.
You guys look over there!
[CRAFTSMAN B]
Right!
[thinking]
What the hell is going on?
Why're they chasing me?
I don't understand!
Wait a sec! Is this why
everybody's after me?
"Culprits in the
assassination plot"?
Well that sucks.
Can't go back to the inn now...
I'll be out in the open.
Hey! Who goes
there? Who are you?
Over here! There's a suspicious
guy hiding in the alley!
You sure about this?
There's no mistake?
I'm certain!
They've been
staying here at the inn
since they
checked in last night!
They took off just
a little while ago.
They're staying here?!
Yes, that's right!
They still have lots of
luggage left in their room.
I'm sure they'll be
back for it sometime.
Right! You guys
stay here, okay?
The rest of you, search the
surrounding area with me.
Look sharp!
Leave no stone unturned.
Does everybody got it?
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[CRAFTSMAN F]
Huh. No one's here.
Are you one hundred percent
certain that this is their ship?
There's no mistaking it!
Look up there!
That's the flag of
the Straw Hat pirates!
They probably
already abandoned her.
She's all worn out.
[CRAFTSMAN I]
Did you find them?
[CRAFTSMAN J]
No. They're gone.
[CRAFTSMAN F] There's
not much left on board.
I'm pretty sure she was
abandoned and left to sink.
Let's keep looking around.
[thinking]
Who were those guys?
Is there something
going on in the city?
[CRAFTSMAN K]
Find anything?
[CRAFTSMAN L]
Not a trace of them.
[CRAFTSMAN K]
Dammit! Where are they?
They sure are persistent.
Hey, Luffy?
Huh? What is it, Nami?
Do you think
everybody's okay?
These guys are
all over the place!
Chopper and Sanji
are probably safe
because no one knows
their faces yet, but still.
Come on, we need to hurry!
[NAMI]
Right!
It looks like the sea
train's still in operation.
I guess the noon
departure has already left.
There's another one
scheduled for tonight,
even in all this bad weather.
The 11 PM, leaving
for Enies Lobby.
That sea train is
pretty impressive.
[CRAFTSMAN M] Hey!
Any news on those pirates?
[CRAFTSMAN N]
We've got nothing!
[CRAFTSMAN O] If we can
capture just one of those three
from the wanted posters,
we'll make 'em cough
up who the others are.
[CRAFTSMAN M] Hurry!
Before the waves get too high!
[CHOPPER]
Maybe we can't find Robin
because she got
on the sea train.
Well, if she did that
would make things
worse than they already are.
Water 7's too big an
area to cover on its own.
What if...
What if I did something to upset
her back at the bookstore?
[SANJI] Don't be ridiculous.
No way that's the reason.
Hey! Excuse me!
Have you seen a
beautiful woman
who kind of looks like this?
[CITIZEN D]
You mean the one who's
about 20 years older
than that picture?
If I had, I would've
told the newspapers
or the Galley-La
Company about it.
[CITIZEN D] To think
she's an assassin.
Kind of shocking, huh?
I admire you for trying to
track down that criminal,
but I suggest you find
yourself some shelter soon.
Aqua Laguna is on its way!
Take care!
Things are getting
dangerous around here.
What about the others?
Think they're okay?
I'm sure Luffy's fine.
Nami's the one that I'm
really worried about right now.
[SANJI] At any rate, this city's
becoming quite the ghost town.
[CHOPPER]
The wind's really picking up.
I'm sure most people
are already in the shelter.
Where could she be?!
Hey! Robin!
Where are you?!
[thinking]
That scent! Is it?
Huh? Chopper! What is it?
Chopper?
Hey! Wait for me!
[thinking]
I'm close!
Chopper! Wait up!
What's going on, dammit?
[thinking]
This way!
Hey, Chopper!
Chopper!
Oo... Waaah!!
[tumbling sounds
followed by a thud]
Are you all right?
[SANJI]
Chopper! Did you hurt yourself?
There you are!
You can't just go
running off like that!
What in the hell is
the matter with you?
One second, you're
right beside me.
I knew it! Look!
[CHOPPER] Robin!
[SANJI] It's Robin!
Robin! Where in the
world have you been?
Everyone's worried!
We've been looking
for you everywhere!
Come on! Let's head
back to the inn!
A lot's happened
while you were gone.
I'll explain
everything on the way.
This damn
water's split us up.
Hold on! I'll find
another way over there!
Don't bother. It's all right.
Stay where you are.
There's no need.
Because I won't be coming
back to you and your crew.
We're parting ways
here in this city.
What the?
What in the world
are you talking about?
Oh wait, you mean
that stuff they said
about you in the newspaper?
Don't worry about it!
None of us believes it.
Pirates are falsely accused
of crimes all the time.
We're easy targets.
[ROBIN]
About that.
I apologize for pinning such
an unreasonable
crime on all of you.
But as far as my involvement...
Everything that was said
in the newspaper is true.
Late last night, I broke
into the mayor's place
of residence and shot him.
No way.
Inside me, I carry a darkness
that none of you know about.
One day, that darkness
will be the end of all of you.
[AOKIJI] Every organization
that she's had something
to do with in the past
has been annihilated.
Not one single, solitary
member escaped, except for her.
[ROBIN] I'm afraid you'll
be taking the fall
for last night's attack
while I escape.
And let me warn you.
The situation
will only get worse.
What are you talking about?!
I don't understand!
[ROBIN]
Why I'm doing it?
There's no need for
you to understand.
Robin! What happened?
You're not making any sense!
This isn't like you at all!
Please! We'll work
this out together!
Although I only spent
a short time with you,
from this day forward.
We will never see
each other again.
Thank you for all of the
kindness you've shown me.
Know that I'll never forget it.
Goodbye.
[SANJI]
Wait...
No... please...
This can't...
This can't be happening.
Hey!
Come back!
[SANJI] Stop! You don't know
what you're saying! Robin!
Wait! Please! Come back!
Robin!
♪ ending song ♪
[ZORO] We need to settle
this once and for all.
Is Robin our friend,
or is she our enemy?
[NAMI] Wait! Hold on!
It's that masked man!
I bet he's responsible
for what's come over her!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, that's it!
He's forcing her to do
bad things against her will!
[ZORO] That's a
positive way to look at it.
But if this guy is
really Robin's friend,
then we've got a problem.
[LUFFY] On the next One
Piece : "Capture Robin!
The Determination
of the Straw Hats!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!