[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in intrigue and danger,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed
to Navy Headquarters
to rescue his brother,
Ace, from execution.
[LUFFY]
Ace.
[NARRATOR]
Three hours remain.
The Navy has gathered every
possible force at Marineford
in anticipation of an attack
by the Whitebeard Pirates.
[SENGOKU]
Ace.
I would like you to tell them
the name of your father.
The name of my father
is Whitebeard.
Not true!
[SENGOKU]
And your mother's name?
Portgas D. Rouge.
And thus, a full
year and three months
after the death of his father,
a child was born with the blood
of the world's most odious
villain in his veins.
That child was you.
[SENGOKU]
Your true father...
...is Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates!
Then it survived.
His bloodline.
[REUDER]
Roger's bloodline lives!
[LUFFY]
"A Vast Fleet Appears!
Here Come the
Whitebeard Pirates!"
That monster had a kid?
I can't believe it.
That means the legend of
Gold Roger, it never ended!
[WOMAN A] Why haven't
they killed him already?
If he's the son of the
King of the Pirates,
then he's too dangerous to live.
[MAN C] If only I'd caught him
and put him up for auction,
I could've made a fortune.
[MAN D chuckles]
So many twists
A fine execution!
[MAN E] Does that mean he
got his "fire fist" powers
from his father?
[MAN F] Better yet, ya think
he's got the One Piece?
[MAN G] What's it matter,
he's as good as dead.
That bloodline's about to get
wiped off the face
of the planet.
Then Ace isn't Luffy's
real brother after all.
Gold Roger?
He's his son?
[DOFLAMINGO]
Huh.
A miracle the little
bastard survived this long!
We know the story.
The Navy executed every
person they could find
who was connected
to Roger in any way.
But I always thought
his father was Dragon.
That's Luffy's father, right?
And they're brothers.
Yeah, that's what
I thought, too.
What's the deal here?
Does Luffy know about this
and he never told anyone?
[GOLD ROGER]
Garp.
Come here.
You're never gonna believe this,
but I've got a baby on the way!
A boy, I bet.
[GOLD ROGER]
For obvious reasons,
I sadly won't be there
for the kid's birth.
[GARP] Why the hell are you
telling this to a Navy officer?
What're you thinking?
You realize what'll happen?
Are you trying to get the mother
of your own damn child executed?
[GOLD ROGER] I'm telling
you so that doesn't happen.
[gasps]
[GOLD ROGER] There's no doubt
the Government'll manage
to dig up my whereabouts
for the past year,
and when they do, they'll
find her and kill her.
[GOLD ROGER] Would you approve
of them punishing a child
who hasn't even been born?
Garp!
You and I have tried
to kill each other
more times than I can count.
That aside, I know
you're an honorable man,
one that I can trust.
Look after my child.
Why me, you selfish bastard?
Because... I know
that you'll do it.
[GOLD ROGER]
Keep him safe for me.
Please, Garp.
I don't know.
Are you sure this is this
island we're looking for?
It's gotta be.
There've been a lot of Roger
sightings reported here.
They say he wasn't
acting like a pirate,
but instead, like a man in love.
The Navy's put
Roger's era to an end.
And we've gotta cut the
bloodline to keep it that way.
Check for pregnancy tests.
If they happened within
ten months of his capture,
I wanna know about it.
[INVESTIGATOR]
Round up any pregnant women.
[INVESTIGATOR] And kill any
suspicious mothers on the spot.
This month, five were born.
[ROUGE humming]
There're several due next month.
[ROUGE]
Not yet.
[INVESTIGATOR]
Take in married women, too.
The marriage could be a ruse.
[ASSISTANT] You'll get her back
when we've cleared her.
[ROUGE]
No. Not yet.
[ROUGE] You have to
hold on a while longer.
[ROUGE]
I'm sorry.
Not yet.
[ROUGE]
[MARINE C]
No more pregnant women, sir.
[ASSISTANT] It's been ten
months since he went to jail.
I don't think Roger
sired a child.
[INVESTIGATOR]
So, that really is the end
for the King of
the Pirates, huh?
[ROUGE'S FATHER]
Get away!
Your name is Portgas
D. Rouge, correct?
[BABY ACE crying]
[ROUGE]
If it's a girl, Ann.
And if it's a boy, Ace.
Those names, he picked them.
So his name is Gol D. Ace.
[ACE crying]
Our son. Our little boy.
Oh, Ace.
[ROUGE'S FATHER]
Rouge!
[ROUGE'S MOTHER]
Rouge! Stay with us!
[ACE crying]
[GARP] I'm gonna need you
to raise this child, Dadan.
[DADAN]
Oh, hell no!
[ACE crying]
[DADAN]
Whose baby is this?
What? Why?
I said so.
Starting today,
you're with Dadan.
[LUFFY]
No!
You're staying with her family
and that's the end of it.
And be nice to 'em.
[ACE] We've both got
the blood of criminals
flowing through our veins,
and that was only gift
those bastards ever gave us.
I took the name
"Portgas" from my mother
because I owe her so much.
But I don't owe my
father a damned thing.
He can keep his name.
Whitebeard is my only father.
Got it, old man?
Oh, Garp.
[SENGOKU]
Two years ago,
you took your mother's
maiden name as your own.
And with your exquisite
speed and strength,
you quickly gained notoriety
throughout the world
as the unrelenting captain
of the Spade Pirates.
And that's when we put
the pieces together.
There was no doubt that Roger's
blood had been passed on.
But Whitebeard came to
the same realization
and got to you before we did.
In order to secure your mantle
as the next King of the Pirates,
he warmly accepted the son of
his old rival aboard his ship.
That's not true!
I joined my father's crew in
order to make him the next King!
Nobody believes that except you.
Why do you think it took us
so long to finally catch you?
You were under
Whitebeard's protection.
So today, we know that
if you were to go free,
you'd use your abilities
to become the next King.
The only recourse we have
to avoid this inevitable risk
is to execute you.
Even if it means we face
the prospect of war
with Whitebeard!
[MARINES yelling]
We have a situation.
Fleet Admiral.
The Gate of Justice!
It's opening without
any order from us, sir!
And we can't make contact
with the control room!
What did you say?
[JIMBEI]
Hmm.
Maybe if I give it a good hit.
Sure, maybe if we knocked.
Do you really think a
punch is going to open it?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, it worked!
Now that's unexpected.
[PRISONER B] It's opening!
Are they actually letting us in?
[PRISONER C]
But that Navy guy said
they were gonna leave us
on the tub current to rot.
It's not the control room.
That's in Marineford.
So who's behind this then?
[PRISONER D]
Huh?
[BUGGY] Keep opening!
Just a little more now!
You will open all
the way! I can feel it!
My bones are dancing
in total harmony
with your whirling gadgets
and gears! We move as one!
Yes, keep going!
There we go, there
we go! A little further!
Hey, wait, Captain
Buggy, are you--?
[BUGGY yells]
[BUGGY]
Almost there!
[PRISONER F]
You're really opening it?
[PRISONER G] He's our savior!
He's the chosen one!
Buggy? No way!
Oh, would you stop milking it?
This is clearly a trick!
[BUGGY] Seriously,
who is opening the gate?
Maybe the universe
really does want me
to be King of the Pirates.
[CREW yelping]
Who cares why?
It's open! Let's go!
[BUGGY yelping]
It's so quiet.
Heh. Yeah, you could cut
the tension with a knife, eh?
[MCGUY]
Right. Let's do this.
[MARINE E]
Uh!
They're here!
[MARINE F]
Ready battle stations! Now!
They appeared out of nowhere.
But how did they get in here?
[MARINE G] It's an entire
fleet of pirate ships!
[MARINE H]
Keep an eye out for Whitebeard.
He must be there.
Bohemian Knight Doma!
Thunder Lord McGuy!
The DeCalvan Brothers!
Whirl Spider Squard!
It's worse than we expected.
They've got just about
every big-time captain
from the New World with them!
We've counted 43 ships in total,
and there's no sign of
Whitebeard or the Commanders.
But every single one of them
is a sworn ally of Whitebeard!
All right, Ace, we're here.
We've got your back, bro.
[MARINES gasping]
Listen to those children
panic. It's pathetic.
They actually came?
[MARINE I]
Should we attack?
[MARINE J]
Not yet.
Whitebeard's gotta be
around here somewhere.
He's planning somethin' big,
so keep your eyes on the sea.
[DOFLAMINGO chuckles]
Now this is fun!
I'm ready for some war!
Now come on,
Whitebeard, I'm hungry.
It's him.
[MARINES whispering]
Where is he?
Go figure. It's a surprise
attack. Whitebeard is no fool.
Oh, don't act like
you're so smart.
[MARINE M] There's a shadow
in the middle of the bay.
[MARINE N]
What's happening?
[SENGOKU] It's just as I feared.
Why didn't we plan for this?
They got their ships coated
to ambush us from underwater.
[MARINES gasping, whispering]
[MARINE O] It's Whitebeard's
ship, the Moby Dick!
[MARINES yelling]
[NARRATOR] Much to the
surprise of the Navy,
the Moby Dick surfaces in
the middle of Marineford.
On the deck stands Whitebeard,
the man who Ace calls father,
and his 14 Commanders,
the pirates he calls family,
who share Luffy's determination
to stop the execution.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Beginning of the War!
Ace and Whitebeard's Past!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!