[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
The Whitebeard Pirates have
successfully
pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines
still block the path to Ace.
The battle is heating up!
[MIHAWK]
Apologies, Shanks.
[LUFFY panting]
[MIHAWK] But I will not
hold back against him.
Hey, I know him!
"Hawk-Eye"!
[MIHAWK]
I wonder, what is written?
Will my hand wipe
his name from history?
Or perhaps...
His fortune shall spare him
the fury of this
Black Sword I wield.
[panting]
[LUFFY]
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
Luffy Comes Under the Attack
of the Black Sword!"
[LUFFY] I don't have
time to get in a fight
with such a strong guy!
All I'm here to do is save Ace!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Go! Second Gear!
[MIHAWK grunts]
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
Death Wink!
[IVANKOV]
Galaxy Wink!
[LUFFY panting]
[IVANKOV]
That's it, Straw Boy, well done.
Just keep your eyes on the prize
and keep moving forward.
You let us handle the rest.
[IVANKOV yells]
[PIRATE A] Don't worry,
we'll deal with fancy pants!
Yee-hee-haw!
[PIRATE A]
Yeah!
Hey, "Hawk-Eye"! Remember the
time we challenged you?
Well, here comes a blast from
the past to kick your smug ass!
We're powered up now as New
Kamas and you're gonna feel it!
[PIRATE A, PIRATE B yell]
[MIHAWK]
I don't remember you.
You're worms
in a long line of them.
[MARINES, PIRATES shouting]
[pants]
Almost there! Keep running
and don't look back!
[MIHAWK shouts]
[LUFFY groans]
You're still in range.
[LUFFY yells]
Ow. Man. He got me.
[grunts]
[JIMBEI] Only Ace's brother
could survive that attack.
Anyone else would've been
sliced clean in half.
The turncoat, Jimbei.
I'm going to make sure
that's the last time
you so much as touch Luffy.
Even if it costs me my life!
[gasps] Why are you doing this?
For one, I don't want to
see Ace get murdered.
And I'd like to have
a peaceful sea for a change.
It may be too late
to avoid the war
we've gotten ourselves into now,
but there is still hope.
Namely, in that
daring kid over there.
[LUFFY grunting]
"Hope," you say?
We'll see what fate
lies in store for him.
But, as for you, I'd step back.
Fishman Karate!
[JIMBEI]
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
[JIMBEI]
Shark Brick Fist!
[JIMBEI grunting]
That guy's a monster. Aw, crap.
[IVANKOV groaning]
[IVANKOV pants]
Huh?
He's going in for the kill!
[LUFFY gasps]
Bastard!
Now, Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY]
...Jet Bazoo--!
[LUFFY gasping]
[pants]
Too close.
He'd've sliced my arms
right off if I'd attacked.
So, you're smarter
than you look.
[LUFFY gasps]
[MARINES, PIRATES gasping]
[MARINE AA] Okay,
a sword should not do that.
Can we please call that thing
something other than a sword?
[COBY]
Uh, he's definitely earned
that world's strongest
swordsman title.
[HELMEPPO whimpering]
He's stronger than
a mountain of ice?
There's no way
Straw Hat's gonna survive.
Not if he's fighting him.
[VISTA]
Hmm?
That's why you
don't slice icebergs!
[BUGGY] Stealthy footsteps,
no one sees me.
[BUGGY] All right, you guys
ready? Time to put operation:
"Make Captain Buggy
Look Like a Bad Ass
In Front of The World"
into action.
[whispering] The Navy
loves propaganda,
so I'm sure they're
broadcasting the war.
We just gotta find us
a Video Transponder Snail.
Let's go.
[PRISONERS whispering]
Yeah.
It's shocking how easy
it is to encourage them
with such vague directions.
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
So, you wanna team up? Nonsense.
Why not? The reign of these
antiquated, geriatric pirates
like Whitebeard
is coming to an end.
He's the last of them.
We're on the brink of
a new era and it belongs to us.
An era where all that matters
is the power you yield.
Sounds appealing, right?
You know you want a piece of it.
[CROCODILE]
Hmm.
Oh, come on, now. I can tell
that you're intrigued.
Sure, technically, you've
been stripped of your title,
but when you get down to it,
we're both Warlords
at heart, aren't we?
Stop looking at me
like you're my equal.
'Cause you're far from it.
If anything, you should
be begging to work for me.
[DOFLAMINGO]
Heh. Well then,
and here I thought
you'd been humbled by prison.
But not even Impel Down
could make a dent in you.
Damn straight.
I've heard enough talk.
Sables!
Get lost! You jackal!
I assumed you
could be reasoned with,
but I was obviously mistaken.
These dumb jarheads
don't notice you
if you don't try to fight 'em.
We can just breeze through!
[laughing]
[BUGGY]
Hm?
[BUGGY screaming]
[BUGGY]
Th-That's not a breeze!
[PRISONER AA]
Captain Buggy!
Whoa! He literally got sucked
into someone else's fight!
Are you gonna move,
or do I have to make you?
What'll it be?
[HANCOCK]
You're welcome to try,
but you will perish before I
let you touch my future husband.
Husband?
Yes, my betrothed.
[HANCOCK]
After the ceremony,
we'll embark upon an
enchanted honeymoon.
[gasps]
[HANCOCK]
Luffy, my love,
let us abscond into the
depths of amorous euphoria.
[HANCOCK]
But then, what if...
[LUFFY] Our bliss has
left me famished, my dear.
[HANCOCK] I'm afraid the
food storage is empty, darling.
[LUFFY] But the world is full
of meals waiting to be cooked.
My darling, cook for me,
so I can taste your love.
[HANCOCK]
Of course! Anything for you.
Just give me
one moment, darling.
[HANCOCK] I must be prepared
for this possibility.
Luffy's appetite
is truly voracious.
If I want to satisfy him,
I must be capable of producing
a truly colossal feast!
[AMAZONS]
Please, Snake Princess!
We'll be happy
to make it for you!
[HANCOCK]
I'll have nothing of it!
Luffy wants to savor the
labors of my love, not yours!
[LUFFY] Darling!
How much longer must I wait?
[HANCOCK panting]
Coming, my love!
[AMAZONS]
Such undying devotion!
[HANCOCK]
I'll gladly embrace any trouble
that life throws our way,
because it's worth it!
Anything's worth it
to be his wife!
"His wife"? [giggles]
What the...? I can't tell if
she wants to fight me or not.
Straw Hat! Got you!
Are you deaf,
you ridiculous fool?
The only way you're getting
past me is in a coffin!
Perfume Femur!
You're kidding me! Really?
[LUFFY grunts]
Stop now!
[LUFFY grunting]
You'll never make it
to your brother in time.
[LUFFY]
Damn!
You shall perish after all.
[LUFFY yelling]
[BUGGY] Just breezing through,
nothing strange here!
[MIHAWK] There's no denying his
fighting skills have improved,
but I've already
seen all his moves.
There's no chance
that I'll miss again.
Not from such a close distance.
[LUFFY yelling]
[BUGGY] Don't mind me!
Just passing through!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Oh! Nice save!
[BUGGY screams]
...Jet Human Shield!
Hey! What's wrong
with you?! I'll die!
What? I didn't slice you!
Besides, I just heard you say,
"Don't mind me,
I'm here to save you!"
There is no way your hearing
is that selfishly selective!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum... Human Shield!
[BUGGY]
Cut it out!
[BUGGY yelling]
[MIHAWK]
Hmm?
All right! Enough!
Your sword's not working!
Suffer the Special
Muggy Ball! And blow off!
Or maybe not!
Do you wanna hear
a joke instead?
How's the Muggy Ball like
a robust financial market?
[MR. 3]
I don't know, how is it?
[BUGGY] Say it together
everyone. Because it goes...
[BUGGY, PRISONERS]
...boom!
[MR. 3] I've never
heard that one before!
[PRISONER BB]
Nice, Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER CC]
Good one!
[LUFFY]
Thank you, Buggy!
See you in the
afterlife, I guess!
We're not done!
[LUFFY yells]
Vista!
Pops said to make sure Ace's
brother doesn't get killed!
Now go! Back him up!
Certainly! I shall make haste!
[LUFFY screaming]
We meet at last.
Your reputation precedes you,
Flower Sword Vista.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, too.
I'm thrilled you've heard of me.
[MIHAWK]
You can drop the false modesty.
[LUFFY grunts]
Ah, well that sucked!
That mustache guy, who is he?
[MIHAWK]
I see Straw Hat's true strength.
[LUFFY]
Well, thanks, whoever you are!
[LUFFY panting]
[MIHAWK] It's nothing
to do with physical strength.
His power is to
rally those around him.
[LUFFY panting]
That's the spirit,
Straw Boy! Keep running!
[LUFFY panting]
Least he got past Mihawk.
Luffy! Save your brother,
you can do it!
[MARINES grunting]
[LUFFY]
Outta my way!
[MIHAWK] Of all the people
seeking to conquer the sea...
[LUFFY panting]
[MIHAWK] ...he may possess
the greatest talent of all!
Ace!
[BUGGY, MR. 3, PRISONERS
yelling]
That--That damn Straw Hat!
You'll pay for this!
Once again, you've proven
how amazing you are!
You let Hawk-Eye
think he'd beaten you,
but in reality, you got
exactly what you wanted!
Huh? What do you mean?
Don't be so coy.
Ya did it, Captain!
[BUGGY]
A Video Transponder Snail?!
Uh, yeah! That w-was
definitely my plan.
But did you expect
anything less from the man
who's gonna rule
the world? [laughs]
[PRISONER D] I'll follow you to
the end of time, Captain Buggy!
[BUGGY]
Shh.
[PRISONERS whispering]
Yeah.
Now, this is where
the important part starts.
I wish that the universe
would stop encouraging him.
[NARRATOR] In the looming shadow
of Ace's impending execution,
the world has been rocked
by one revelation after another.
[NARRATOR] It all began
when more than 200 inmates
managed to escape from the
iron-tight prison of Impel Down,
and the most notorious
of those prisoners
have now taken a lead role
in this epic battle.
[NARRATOR]
The blood soaked expanse
of the ghastly battlefield
is an unearthly sight.
And with a single
glance at its horrors,
it's clear that this
showdown will change history.
[NARRATOR] The populace
of the world has no choice
but to helplessly observe
the events of this war with the
knowledge that its outcome will
determine their very future.
[MARINE FF] Fleet Admiral,
everything has been arranged.
[SENGOKU] The bay is
fully prepared as well.
[MARINE FF]
Yes, sir, we're all set.
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN C]
What?
They're already
preparing for the execution?
[WALLEM]
Those bastards!
They're pushing up
the schedule, are they?
Damn! We don't have much time!
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN A] Hold on. Is it
really about to happen?
[MAN B]
That's ridiculous!
Why would they announce the time
and then change it
at the last minute?
Cut the feed!
Kill every single video
broadcast outta this place!
As representatives of the Navy
and the World Government,
we're fighting to
preserve the righteous cause
of absolute justice,
and we must prevail.
Even if that means
stepping over the line.
But it's too much for this
naive world to understand,
let alone see.
There's no reason to
submit innocent citizens
to the horrific imagery
about to unfold.
[MARCO]
Pops...
[PIRATE AA]
Run faster!
Dammit, looks like
they really are
gonna execute Ace ahead of time!
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[SENGOKU]
The only news that
should spread throughout
the world after this war
is of our victory.
And the details are irrelevant!
[PIRATE D] Huh? They're
attacking our ships!
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATE BB]
Look at the bay head!
There's something out there!
[PALMS] Pretty sure
they're not on our side!
The Navy must've found a way
to get some reinforcements
around the ice wall somehow!
But are they admirals? I mean,
these guys are blowing up ships!
Shouldn't they be up front?
[PIRATE CC]
Is that...?
[PIRATE DD]
What--What the hell are they?
Of course. I wondered
when I'd get a glimpse
of the Government's
human weapons.
It's that big bear guy,
or I guess I mean guys.
There're so many!
[IVANKOV]
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
I'm confused.
[NARRATOR] A mere hour
and a half has passed since
the war began, but the Navy
aims to end it in one strike.
With this critical push,
the tide of the war
has once again changed course,
flowing into its final stage.
I'm tired of waiting!
Let's get this done!
Go out there and make me proud!
[NARRATOR] The Whitebeard
Pirates and Navy forces
appear to be in a deadlock, as
powerful fighters from each side
clash again and again.
However, when an army
of human weapons
encircle the battlefield,
Luffy and his allies find
themselves overwhelmed
by their explosive attacks.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Extermination
Strategy in Action!
The Power of the Pacifistas!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!