[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Still, that's how he feels.
So trying to reason with him
would be a waste of time.
If you really want
him to go with you,
then your only choice
is to use force.
Since he's not willing
to break that chain,
you'll have to do it for him!
[LUFFY]
Goodbye My Dear Underlings!
Franky Departs!
[CITIZENS complaining]
[MAN 322A] Put some pants on!
[WOMAN 322A] My eyes!
I'm gonna sue you
for mental anguish!
Think of the children!
[MAN 322B] Get outta town!
Gimme back my briefs, Straw Hat.
Sure. Join my crew.
[FRANKY] What, are you stupid?
I'm not gonna be a pirate.
You know? You can keep
those briefs, brother.
[TILESTONE] Hm?
[FRANKY] Ow!
[FRANKY] Standing before
the crashing waves,
naked and proud,
you wouldn't ask a lion
to put on underwear,
so why a man?
[screaming]
He's showing off that bare
bottom loud and proud!
Don't look! No!
Try as I might,
I can't unsee it!
I was a fool!
His determination is too great!
He's a true man! A hero!
C'mon! He's obviously
just a pervert!
It might get a little rough,
but shall I lend a hand?
Actually, Ice Pops
said before,
if we want Franky to join,
we're gonna have to use
force to get our way.
But what were you planning?
Try Dos Fleurs.
[ROBIN] Grab.
[screaming in pain]
Robin! What did you do?
Oh man!
Ow!
You're gonna crush them, Robin!
Don't do it!
[screaming]
She'll tear 'em off!
She's gonna crush 'em to bits!
--Like little oranges!
[FRANKY]
They're called "tangerines!"
[screaming]
[pained whimpering]
Robin!
I still want him to be
a man when he joins us!
Lay off!
Just looking at him hurts!
[FRANKY whimpering]
What's going on?
They're not fighting,
but Franky's in a lotta pain!
That scream.
It almost sounds like someone
is choking a chicken to death!
I know he's a pervert...
But gosh.
Everyone knows
pirates won't give up
on treasure once they've
set their sights on it.
And now that we have
this one in our palms,
so to speak, I won't
let go without a fight.
[FRANKY]
C'mon, I already told you!
[choked yelling]
I couldn't leave this
island even if I wanted to.
[choked yelling]
[FRANKY] I appreciate
the offer, really,
but it just ain't
in the cards for me.
Sailing the seas
would be great and all,
but there's still a lot of stuff
I have left to
take care of here.
That's why I
gave the ship to you.
[FRANKY] I quit being
a shipwright a long time ago,
and I'm not going back.
This is the last
ship I'm building
for the rest of my life.
I only had one goal
as a shipwright,
and now I've fulfilled it.
I made my ship of dreams!
[ICEBERG] That's a lie, Franky.
You can say what you like,
but I know the truth.
This isn't the ship of dreams
that you talked about before.
[ICEBERG] Ship of dreams?
[FRANKY] That's right!
And my dream doesn't end
with blueprints, either.
It's much bigger than that!
[FRANKY] A ship that will
sail with pride and courage
over uncharted waters fighting
its way through every battle,
over every wave!
And when it finally reaches
the ends of the earth,
then it will be
my ship of dreams.
One day, I'll design that ship
and hammer the nails
with my own two hands.
And when its crew sails,
I'll join as their shipwright.
That way, I'll be there when
the ship reaches its goal.
At the ends of the world,
even if it's beat up
and worn out,
I know that my ship will shine
brighter than anything
the ocean's ever seen!
[FRANKY]
What do you think?
Pretty awesome, right, Tom?
Ha! You bet!
And if you ride that sucker
down the Grand Line yourself,
then you'll surpass your master!
[laughing]
[KOKORO] It's that
pirate blood of yours!
Gimme a break.
You're all talk.
A thug like you
can't surpass Tom!
[FRANKY] "Thug", huh?
[ICEBERG] See? You're
resorting to violence already!
Gero, gero, gero!
If you're a man,
you do it with gusto!
Yeah, well my dream
is different now!
[ICEBERG] Your dream?
That's not what
this is about at all.
You're not on this island
because of something
you have to accomplish.
You're here...
...because of guilt.
[ICEBERG] Ever since that
day that Tom was taken away
by the government,
you've blamed yourself
for what happened.
It's obvious.
[ICEBERG] But even before
Tom left this island,
he'd already forgiven you.
He had shown you a new path.
[FRANKY] Ships that would
do such a horrible thing
are no longer my ships!
[CROWD exclaiming]
He just hit him.
Tom has never hit Franky before.
What'd you do that for?
They're no longer
your ships, huh?
Don't you ever say that again!
What's wrong with saying that?
I wish I'd never made 'em!
If those ships didn't exist,
then nobody
would've gotten hurt!
When a ship is built,
no matter what type...
[groans]
It's neither good nor evil.
I don't care what kind of
ships you choose to make
for the rest of your life.
Remember...
[TOM] Even if the ships
you build hurt someone,
even if they
destroy the world...
Even if no one else does,
their creator must
love them unconditionally.
The one who made them
must never deny them!
Don't place the
blame on the ships!
You must be proud of every
ship you've ever created!
For years,
you've taken punks
from the inner city
streets under your wing.
You've taught them
to be dismantlers.
You've worked as bounty hunters,
and you've protected this
island from attacking pirates.
[ICEBERG] All of this
to atone for your sins.
To look after the
city that Tom loved,
that Tom was forced
to leave behind.
Although, I don't imagine
most people saw it that way.
No, of course not!
'Cause that's not
what I was doing!
Not at all!
[groaning]
You loved shipbuilding
and you gave it up.
You suppressed your dream
for years and years.
Are you going to do that
for the rest of your life?
[ICEBERG]
Tom has already forgiven you.
I've already forgiven you.
Nothing you do will change that.
This has gone on long enough.
[ICEBERG] It's time to
forgive yourself, Franky.
Live.
And follow the dream
you've buried for so long.
[sobbing]
[laughing]
[FRANKY] What the heck?
[FRANKY] A bag?
[ZAMBAI] It's luggage
for your trip, Bro!
[FRANKY FAMILY BEARDFACE]
Move it! We're comin' through!
[MAN 322B]
Ah! It's the Franky Family!
--[FRANKY FAMILY] Big Bro!
--[FRANKY FAMILY] We love you!
Now you, too?
Big Bro! Forgive us!
We didn't want to trick you!
Really, we're sorry!
We're sorry!
We'll take any punishment
you throw at us!
We aren't smart like you,
but we thought
long and hard about this
and even we know
that it's the only way!
Only way, huh?
You guys aren't
making any sense to me.
You think I'm better off
without my only pair of briefs?
Huh?
Think I'll be better off
with a bunch of pirates?
Well, I don't care
what you think!
This is my life!
And I decide what's best for me!
[FRANKY] I'm the boss, damn it!
You think I'd be happy
living out the life
my underlings planned for me?
You say you thought
long and hard, huh?
If you'd really
thought about this,
you wouldn't have
done it in the first place!
I--I know we're a pain, but--
Is it wrong for us to worry
about you, even a little?
You turned our lives around!
We just want
what's best for you!
We just want our
big bro to be happy!
Can't you see?
[screaming]
Ain't that sweet?
Damn it, you guys!
[groaning in pain]
--Ah, Big Bro!
Hey! Stop!
You're going too far!
Come on! He's gonna be a woman!
Can't you hear him crying?
She'll tear 'em off!
She's gonna crush 'em to bits!
--Like little red grapes!
[FRANKY] I thought
they were tangerines!
Damn it, Robin! Stop it!
You'll pay for this!
She'll tear 'em off!
She's gonna crush 'em to bits!
--Like a little apple!
[FRANKY] That's more like it!
[FRANKY] It hurts so much!
I can't stop crying!
Robin!
[LUFFY] Wait, you're
not doing anything?
I only did it one time.
He's just being a big baby.
How convenient.
Now he has an excuse
to cry all he wants.
Huh?
He's faking it?
[FRANKY]
Owwww!
It hurts so much!
I can't stop crying!
[CAPTAIN 322A] What do you mean
you haven't found them yet?
Keep searching!
Don't let them get away!
[groaning in pain]
It hurts! Oh, the pain!
Still can't stop crying!
Big Bro!
I feel your pain, Bro!
You ain't got a clue
how this feels!
[ZAMBAI]
Well, what do we have here?
Some freakjob in his underpants!
I think you just stepped into
the wrong part of town, buddy!
Get him, men!
[ZAMBAI] What the hell?
You won't make a fool of me!
You got a pretty
strong arm, huh?
You're too good to be a thug.
It's a waste.
Wha--What're you trying to say?
Zambai!
I'm Franky. Hey.
From now on,
the backstreets of Water 7
will be ruled
by me, and only me.
Got that?
[ZAMBAI] Y-Yes, sir!
[sobbing]
--Big Bro!
[KIWI and MOZU laughing]
[MOZU] Ah, good stuff.
[KIWI]
Let's hit up the next place.
Wow, this guy thinks
he's too good for pants!
I like it-- Let's have
a drink together, pal!
We'll show you the way
to the bar. Just follow us!
[MOZU] Hey, what're you doing?
[KIWI] Let go of us!
It's too early in the day,
and you're too young
to be drinking like that!
Take it easy!
If you're really thirsty,
I can show you where
to get some cola!
So? That sound good to you?
Big Bro! Big Bro!
Food... I need... food...
[FRANKY] Anyone who's hungry,
get up and come with me!
[FRANKY] Let's run wild!
This is the beginning
of the Franky Family!
Yeah!
Leave your tears behind!
'Cause we're gonna
have a super time!
That's right!
[cheering]
[CROWD]
Franky! Franky! Franky!
[cheering continues]
[FRANKY] You guys.
Are you--
Are you really gonna
be okay without me?
Bro!
[ZAMBAI] You taught us
how to work together!
We'll make you proud
for as long as we live!
Water 7 will never
forget your name!
[FRANKY FAMILY BEARDFACE]
Yeah, we'll be fine!
[FRANKY FAMILY BUBBLEMAN]
Don't cry, Bro!
[FRANKY FAMILY SILVERHAIR]
We love you!
[ZAMBAI] No matter
how far away you are,
you'll always be our boss,
and you'll always be our bro!
[FRANKY FAMILY] That's right!
[sobbing]
I can't stop!
Hurry!
Yeah, I know!
[ZORO, SANJI]
Luffy!
Hey. What's up?
We got bad news, Captain!
That stupid Grandpa of yours
came back for us, Luffy!
He's got a whole
bunch of Marines
on the other side of the island
getting ready to hunt
us down and take us out!
[LUFFY] Huh? Why?
I thought he said
he was leaving!
[SANJI] We don't have time
to figure that out!
Just set sail!
What the--
Damn it, Franky,
put your underwear on already!
Jeez!
Catch!
[LUFFY] Well? Come on!
Get on my ship!
Captain's orders.
"Your" ship already, huh?
An amateur like you
will probably sink her
in less than a week.
You got the finest
vessel on the sea,
and no shipwright?
That's a real pity...
For the ship, I mean.
What can I say?
You don't leave me much choice.
I gotta take care of my
masterpiece, after all!
So set sail.
I'm joining the crew!
Yeah!
We got us a shipwright!
Ah! All right!
[KIWI, MOZU] Big Bro.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
I know Straw Hat's gonna
take good care of him!
[FRANKY] Tom, this is it.
I'm leaving the island.
Will ya teach me how
to draw up blueprints
for one, too?
[laughing]
What's so funny, huh?
[FRANKY] You sure are
working late tonight.
What're ya drawin'?
[TOM] This here
is hope for our island.
It is?
[FRANKY]
I know I was a bad student.
I know I only
caused you trouble.
[ISLANDER 248J] Hey!
Did you guys hear?
Big news from Scrap Heap Island!
[ISLANDER 248H]
Did Tom's workers
actually finish
the sea train?
[FRANKY] But all the same,
thank you for looking after me.
[train whistle]
[FRANKY] You put together a fine
team of shipwrights, Iceberg.
I'm sure they'll
take good care of you.
I'm sorry I've been such
a pain over the years.
[FRANKY] Granny Kokoro.
Shorty and the rabbit.
Yokozuna.
Pervert!
[FRANKY]
All the lively townspeople.
My little sisters.
[sobbing]
[FRANKY] Sodom. Gomorrah.
[FRANKY]
And all my bros.
I love you guys so much.
[FRANKY]
I'm gonna super miss you all!
[SANJI] Put on some pants.
[LUFFY]
What? Usopp is coming back?
[CHOPPER] Really? Awesome!
[LUFFY]
Hey, turn the ship around!
We're going back!
[ZORO] Hold on, both of you.
If you let him join the crew
again, I won't forgive you.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Departing the City of Water!
Usopp Mans Up and Brings
Closure to the Duel!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!