Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] While on their
journey to Fishman Island,
The Straw Hat crew was ambushed
by the Flying Fish Riders
and their leader, Duval,
resulting in a desperate battle.
Straw Hats,
I'm gonna murder you!
[NARRATOR] Blaming Sanji
for his misfortunes,
Duval swore to destroy the Straw
Hats, even if it killed him.
[SANJI]
Oeil! Nez! Joue!
Bouche! Dents! Menton!
Parage Shot!
Now eat this.
[LUFFY] Disembarking with
Sights Set on Fishman Island!
The Sabaody Archipelago!
Hey, Head! Where are you?
Talk to us!
[FISH RIDER 386A]
There he is!
--Are you okay, Head? Are you?
Oh, man. This is awful.
He really messed him up.
[FISH RIDER 387A] Head?
Are you still alive?
Look, he's moving!
Damn it.
[DUVAL]
It's not fair.
Ah finally track down Black Leg
and look at what he does to me.
[DUVAL]
What?
I know we got our asses kicked,
but you don't need
to look that surprised.
But Head,
this ass-kicking's
a little different.
[DUVAL]
What...
M-My face...
What... What the hell
happened to my face?!
[LUFFY]
So good!
[CAMIE]
Yep!
Hatchin's octopus fritters
are the best in the world!
[LUFFY] I can't stop eating
and you can't make me!
This stuff is amazing!
[screaming]
They're great! Wow!
That flavor.
It's a brilliant idea turnin'
your ship into a food stall.
This is the first time
I've had the pleasure
of eating octopus fritters.
They really are delectable.
My stomach is about to burst,
or it would, if I had
one in the first place.
Nyuu!
You can eat as much as
you want. It's on the house!
It's the very least we can do
to show a little
gratitude for saving us.
These have rice cakes in 'em,
and these were
made with soup stock.
Be careful now,
they're really hot.
So, Nami,
what do you think?
Are... they good?
Um... Is it...
Uh, does it taste okay?
Listen. Don't think
I'm going to forgive you
'cause of something
silly like this.
No! No, of course not!
That's not what I meant!
I just wanted to know if ya
think it tastes good, honestly!
That's all, I swear!
So, uh...
It's really delicious!
Nyuuuuu!
You think so?
Do you mean that?
That's such a relief!
I'm so happy you like it!
[HACHI]
Now go ahead and eat up!
Don't hold back!
There's plenty more
where that came from!
[LUFFY]
Yeah! Keep it comin'!
I'm nowhere near full!
[DUVAL]
Heyyyyy!
Hey, you guys!
[DUVAL]
Heyyyy, you guys!
Young masterrrrr!
[ZORO]
Who's that?
It's those guys.
[DUVAL]
Wait, don't go!
You can't leave before
I get to say thank you!
Who is this clown, anyway?
I'm eating here.
[laughing]
Handsome!
Well, obviously,
but it's me, Duval!
[DUVAL laughing]
[LUFFY]
Wait...
Didn't his face look different?
I rearranged his bone structure.
Now the creep's got nothin'
to gripe and moan about.
[DUVAL]
Why, young master Black Leg!
I was surprised after
you kicked my face,
but I can't deny
the results are amazing!
Look!
Look how ravishing and
handsome you've made me!
I'm a different person!
Wow! The ladies are
gonna go nuts over me.
I must say,
life's starting to look rosy.
I love it!
[laughing]
[DUVAL] All I want to do now
is head back to the countryside
and take it easy.
But there's no way I could
leave without thanking you.
I'd be paralyzed
with guilt if I did.
It's your first time
in this part of the sea,
so if there's anything
we can do to help you out,
do not hesitate to call on us.
[SANJI] Don't wink
until your face is settled.
Well as long as you're happy,
that's more than enough.
If you really wanna pay me back,
don't bother us anymore.
So handsome. I'm beautiful.
Are you even listening to me?
[DUVAL]
I belong atop a white stallion.
[SANJI]
Hey! Listen!
[FISH RIDER 386B]
Head!
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Hey, Head!
Listen to the guy, will ya?
[DUVAL]
Did he say...
...I'm handsome?
[SANJI] I didn't say
anything remotely like that!
You want me to turn your face
back into the wanted poster?
[snaps]
Blowing me a kiss
is a bit forward,
but nonetheless...
I accept.
[FISH RIDER 386B]
Woo-hoo!
[NAMI]
I didn't blow you a kiss!
I was just wiping
all this sauce off my lips!
[NAMI] You're so
overconfident you're delusional!
[DUVAL]
Mirror, mirror, in my hand,
I'm the handsomest in the land.
[FISH RIDERS]
You didn't give it a choice!
[DUVAL laughing]
You know,
it doesn't really matter
how handsome you are
if you're still an idiot.
Oh! You're jealous!
No, I'm not!
Give it up, Usopp!
You can't talk him
out of being crazy.
[DUVAL]
Well, young master and friends--
Here's my
transponder snail number.
Call me any time.
You can count on my
assistance day or night.
I owe it to you after
all I've put you through.
I do apologize for
all the trouble. Sorry.
[USOPP, LUFFY, SANJI]
Just stop winking already.
Ciao for now!
All right!
Rosy Life Riders, ho!
[FISH RIDERS]
Aye-aye, handsome!
[USOPP, LUFFY, SANJI]
Hurry up and leave.
[LUFFY]
I'm finally full!
Ah! That was some good eatin'.
Every bite of it.
That was amazing.
I'm about to burst.
Nyuu!
I'm worn out.
They sure know how to eat.
They must've broken
some kind of record.
I really could've
used six more arms.
Awesome work, Hatchin.
It looks like
they're all satisfied.
Nyuu. Oh, yeah?
Then I'm satisfied, too.
[BROOK]
What a truly splendid afternoon.
My first taste
of octopus fritters
and hopefully not my last.
Uh-oh, do excuse me.
[farts, burps]
Everything about you is nasty!
[SANJI] Hey! Octopus,
Starfish! You too, Camie!
Come take a break up on deck,
I'll make you a cup of tea!
[CAMIE]
Sure!
That's some good tea.
It looks like you guys
are on the right course.
First stop, Sabaody Archipelago.
And we've gotta go there first
if we wanna get
to Fishman Island?
We fishmen and mermaids
could dive right down
and get there in no time at all.
It's not quite
so easy for humans.
The water pressure would
crush you to bits if you tried.
Yeah. No joke.
It was too much for the
Shark Submerge to handle.
That's odd.
I don't imagine it's supposed to
make that horrid creaking noise.
Oh, no. That's bad.
I'm afraid we already
passed 5000 meters.
Ah. That makes sense.
Wait, that is bad!
The water pressure is going
to crush the submarine
like a tin can!
So then how the hell
are we 'sposed
to get down there?
Ahem! Folks.
Attention please.
It's clear to me that
you're downright clueless,
so allow me to
enlighten you about the sea
around these parts.
Wait...
Who will enlighten them?
Well, I suppose
that would be this guy!
[HACHI] Yeah.
That sounds pretty good to me.
[PAPPAGU] Um, will
you please listen to me?
[clears throat]
First off--
There are actually two
separate routes one can travel
to reach the New World.
But for outlaws
such as yourselves,
only one of them
is a viable option.
[LUFFY]
Why's that?
Oh, I'll tell you.
You see, the first route
passes over the Red Line
and directly through the
sacred land of Mariejois,
which is protected
by the World Government
and requires their
permission to enter.
Huh?
[PAPPAGU] The World Government's
not exactly fond of pirates,
so I doubt you'd get through.
[CHOPPER] You've gotta cross
the Red Line on foot that way?
How do people get
their ships across?
[PAPPAGU]
The common practice is
for people to leave
their ships behind
and buy a new one
on the other side.
[FRANKY]
They abandon their ships?
Yep.
You've gotta apply
to get permission,
so it takes time and money,
but it is the safest way
to get across.
Good news for you, though.
The passage you'll be taking,
ya don't have
to get rid of your ship.
And that passage is
the great Sea Floor Route.
Straight through Fishman Island!
[CAMIE]
The thing is,
the Sea Floor Route
is pretty dangerous.
[PAPPAGU]
Excuse me, Camie?
--How dangerous we talkin'?
--[PAPPAGU] Camie? I wasn't
--Well, dangerous like it's
--finished talking yet. Hey!
full of sea kings that eat
ships and people and stuff
all the time.
[USOPP and CHOPPER]
Huh?
--Yeah, that counts.
--[PAPPAGU] Hey, Camie!
--definitely dangerous.
--I'll take it from here.
Uh-huh.
Y'know, I don't wanna
go to Fishman Island after all.
Yeah, me neither.
Hey, wait, Camie.
Did you say their
ships get eaten?
Huh? Yeah.
What kind of ship will
get us across the sea floor?
[CAMIE]
This one's fine.
[ALL]
Huh?
No. This ship's not equipped
to travel underwater.
Sure, but it will be.
Huh?
The thing is,
the Red Line may be the most
massive wall in the whole world,
but it's not totally solid.
And there's one small hole
that passes through it.
Well, small in the big picture.
To us, it's super huge.
And inside that hole
is Fishman Island!
Nyuu!
It's actually right beneath
the sacred land of Mariejois.
All you do is dive down
about thirty thousand feet
and there it is,
in all its glory!
That far?
[HACHI] Trust me,
it's worth the trip.
Then again, I guess we went
about thirty thousand feet
in the air to get to Skypeia.
But taking this ship underwater?
How is that possible?
Oh, we're gonna
get the ship coated
when we reach the island
we're headed to.
Coated with what?
You'll find out
when we get there.
Hey, look up ahead!
We're here, everybody!
It's beautiful!
It sure is. Wow!
What's all that
stuff floating around?
Oh, my.
It's like a dream.
Bubbles?
[PAPPAGU]
This is it!
The Sabaody Archipelago!
[LUFFY]
So cool!
[LUFFY] I've never seen
so many bubbles in my life!
So pretty.
Yow!
It's just an
endless barrage of 'em.
Where the heck
are they coming from?
[LUFFY] And who's
blowing all of them?
[CAMIE] No one.
The island makes them.
Wait, what?
Yeah, explain.
[ROBIN]
Mind if I interrupt?
Sorry.
I'm not trying to be rude.
But what does the Log Pose say?
Oh. Right, just one sec.
The needle's still pointing
toward Fishman Island.
Let's just hope that this island
isn't gonna rewrite
the log on us.
Nyuu. It's fine.
The Sabaody Archipelago's
just a cluster of trees.
There's no magnetic field.
So then it's not
actually a real island?
Right.
Are you guys familiar
with mangrove trees?
Mangroves?
[SANJI] Trees with roots
above or under the water,
depending on the tides, right?
[HACHI]
Yep, you got it,
but the tide never
rises high enough here
for the roots
to be submerged.
The Sabaody Archipelago
is home to the largest
mangrove trees in the world.
These colossal giants are
the Hustle Muscle Mangroves.
The largest
mangroves in the world?
Those are some manly mangroves.
This place is great!
[HACHI]
There's a total of 79 trees.
And each one serves
as its own little island
complete with tiny
towns and facilities.
The cluster of all
these trees is known as
the Sabaody Archipelago.
Huh?
[CHOPPER] Look.
They've got numbers on them.
Yeah.
All the trees are
designated by number,
so it's pretty easy
to find your way around.
Grove 44 up here is
the private residence entrance,
so before we land, we'll need
to go a little further in.
Wow, when you
see 'em up close,
these roots are huge!
[CHOPPER] Look how dark
it is beneath them.
[BROOK]
It is quite fascinating.
Is that a man-made bridge?
[HACHI]
It is.
Bridges connect
each one of the islands.
[BROOK]
I see. That makes sense.
[HACHI]
All right! We're here.
This is a good spot
to drop anchor.
Welcome to Grove 41.
First one off the ship!
[LUFFY laughing]
Hey!
Make sure you all remember
the grove number, okay?
Like I said earlier--
The whole archipelago
is connected
by a series of bridges,
so you won't get lost
if you remember
the number you're docked at.
There's one guy
that'll still get lost.
Yep.
[ZORO]
Huh? What's goin' on?
Hey, what was that for?
A bubble popped
out of the ground!
How weird is that?
--Awesome!
[LUFFY]
I'm riding it!
That is one strong bubble!
Wow!
These soap bubbles...
I'm curious. How exactly
do they get produced?
I got this one.
It's a chemical reaction
from the Hustle
Muscle Mangrove roots.
They secrete a unique
resin that causes it.
Ugh. It's really sticky.
Hey, stop that!
[PAPPAGU] You see, when the
roots of the trees breathe,
the air inflates the resin
as it rises out of the ground.
Interesting.
I never would've thought
tree sap could float.
[USOPP] Wow, so this is all
one hundred percent natural.
[LUFFY]
Hey!
[USOPP]
Huh? Luffy!
When did you get
all the way up there?
[LUFFY] There's an
amusement park over there!
Let's go! I wanna
ride the Ferris wheel!
Oh my gosh! Really?
Yeah, that's Sabaody Park.
Oh, wow. I'm so jealous.
See, I've always dreamed
of riding that Ferris wheel.
You have?
Why don't you just ride it?
Not a chance!
Don't you even think about it!
Yeah. I know, don't remind me.
If she can't ride it,
does that mean I can't, either?
So high!
Why are they popping?
[screaming]
[CAMIE]
Luffychin!
Oh, no! This is awful!
[SANJI]
Calm down, he's okay.
Trust me, he's the last guy
you've gotta worry about.
Man! That took it outta me!
See?
So, Hachi.
What's our objective
on this island, anyway?
Didn't you say something before
about getting
the ship coated here?
Nyuu! We'll meet up
with one of the island's
coating specialists and have
him slap a coat of this resin
on your ship.
[HACHI]
That's all it takes.
After that, your ship
will be fully equipped
for underwater travel.
Seriously?
[HACHI] Yep,
the process works wonders,
and it's the only way I know of
that humans can
reach Fishman Island.
But you don't want
an amateur to do it.
If it's not done right,
the water pressure
will crush the ship
and everyone on it.
I've got one specialist
that I really trust, though,
so you'll be in good hands.
Thank you for your help.
You really are a good man.
Wait. Good octopus.
Yohohohoho!
But first...
[HACHI] In exchange for my help,
promise me one thing.
Sure. What is it?
[HACHI] Once we cross
the bridge into town,
there's a chance we might
run into the World Nobles.
Okay. Who?
Yeah, who're they?
The World Nobles.
They're from the
Holy Land Mariejois.
Cool.
So what's the big deal?
This is difficult to ask,
but no matter what
happens in the town,
you must promise
that you'll do nothing
to defy the World Nobles.
No matter what happens?
Just ignore it?
[HACHI]
Exactly.
Even if they kill someone
in front of you,
just look the other way.
Try to pretend
like nothing happened.
I'll say it one more time.
[HACHI] No matter what, you act
like you didn't see a thing.
[LUFFY] Man, the Sabaody
Archipelago sure is fun!
They've got tons of stuff
here I've never seen before!
[CHOPPER] Here come some people
with bubbles on their heads!
[LUFFY] Even their dog
is wearing a bubble!
[HACHI]
Crap! Quick!
Get on your knees, guys!
And don't look them in the eye!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Tyranny!
The Rulers of Sabaody,
the Celestial Dragons!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!