[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from the
rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed
to Navy Headquarters
to rescue his brother,
Ace, from execution.
Also determined
to keep Ace alive
is the notorious
pirate Whitebeard,
who launches a surprise
attack with his massive crew.
[MARINE C]
Did he crack the air?
[MARINES yelling]
A seaquake!
He's turning the ocean
waters against us!
[ACE]
I... I won't lose.
[chuckles]
Ya got some fight left?
Look, I'm not gonna kill
you today, all right?
Don't fight it.
You're too valuable to die
in a place like this.
Run wild with us and
our flag will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
[ACE]
Screw you, you old fart!
Tell me.
Why does everyone on
this ship call him "Pops"?
You don't get it?
Because he calls us "sons."
None of us have any family left,
hell, the whole world hates
us, so it's nice, right?
I know it's just a word.
But it still feels nice.
[LUFFY] "The Force That
Could Destroy the World!
The Power of the
Tremor-Tremor Fruit!"
That's a lie! You
know the damn truth!
You told me not to go after
him, but I wouldn't listen--
[WHITEBEARD] I'm your Captain
and I told you to go.
[WHITEBEARD] Ace was
only following my orders.
Isn't that right, Marco?
Yep. I heard it myself.
Then you left.
Sorry for all the
trouble. Really.
Teach broke the
rules of our ship
and you had to seek justice.
Everyone in the world
knows what happens
if you mess with one
of our crewmates.
If you do, you're
gonna pay the price.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE A] That means
if anyone lays a finger on you,
Ace, they're gonna
have to deal with us!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE BB]
Don't worry, Ace!
We'll get you outta here!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yelling]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE AA] Get ready
to make hell your new home,
Navy bastards!
Have to admit,
we asked for this.
That had better not
be regret I hear.
This is a real mess.
[MORIA cackling]
All right, what do you
say we tally up the odds?
On this side, we've
got us Warlords,
the Navy's most ferocious
weapons, the Admirals,
and a 100 thousand soldiers!
On that side they've got
the Whitebeard Pirates,
an entire fleet of more
than 40 allied ships.
Okay, it's your move,
Whitebeard, let's go!
[chuckles]
Oh, I like it.
Looks like you are gonna
watch from the sideline.
I know, you're just
here to kill some time.
[DOFLAMINGO]
More for me, then.
[DOFLAMINGO chuckling]
[HANCOCK] This is oppressive.
I can hardly stand it.
These men are all the same.
Disgusting, bloodthirsty beasts.
In all my travels, I've
only met one exception.
Please stay safe, Luffy, for me.
[MARINE A]
Huh?
The.... water.
What's wrong?
It's receding.
What's causing it?
[PRISONERS yelling]
[PRISONER AA]
What the hell is going on?
[PRISONER BB]
What's happening?
Why is the ship
moving backwards?
Aw, c'mon, we had
this! What gives?
It was nothin' but smooth
sailing two minutes ago!
I'm as confused as you.
[MR. 3 screams]
[BUGGY] Careful! You've got
some of my favorite parts there!
[PRISONERS yelling]
Stupid ocean, we don't
have time to go backward!
What's making this happen?
[JIMBEI]
He's here.
[BUGGY yelps]
What? And now it's over?
I'm not complaining, but weird.
It pushed us...
a good distance back.
Well, great
At this rate, by the time we
get there, the fight'll be over.
[PRISONERS groaning]
[ALL]
Uh?
What was that?
[LUFFY]
Jimbei, c'mon!
Can we go faster?
We're already late!
We can't let them kill Ace!
Ace will be safe, for
now. We'll get there.
Okay.
[BUGGY]
Gimme a break!
[LUFFY]
Uh.
What? You know
something that we don't?
Is your fishman karate
gonna get us there on time?
Or better yet,
are ya gonna get your pals the
whale sharks to give us a ride?
[JIMBEI] My powers don't
have much to offer here.
[BUGGY] Yeah? Then where's
that confidence coming from?
He says we'll make it, 'kay?
So we're gonna make it!
"He says we'll make it"!
It's that simple, huh? Tch.
Fine! You keep believing.
I'm taking a nap.
Heh.
Wake me when we get there.
[PRISONER A]
Uh, Captain Buggy?
I really don't see this workin'
out if we don't move any faster.
You're not givin' up
on your dream, are you?
To become the King?
It's destiny, right?
[BUGGY]
Oh, uh, yeah.
Well, when the timing's right,
I'm sure some kind of
miracle will happen.
But this obviously
ain't the right time,
so all I can really do is wait.
[PRISONER A]
So, you are giving up?
How can you let
us down like that?
What's wrong with you?
Can't you see?
[PRISONER B, PRISONER C]
Uh?
[PRISONER A]
Just look at 'im!
That's not surrender,
it's not laziness,
that's confidence.
No. It's not. Not at all.
See? Cool as can be.
He's perfectly composed!
So regal, he's like
a king already.
How could I be so
blind? You're right.
[PRISONER A]
He's amazing!
So wrong. All of it.
[BUGGY]
I know miracles ain't exactly
the most common of occurrences,
but what the hell else can
I do except wait for one?
Dammit.
[rumbling]
[ALL]
Hm?
[PRISONER C]
The tide is changing course.
We're moving forward again!
Did you do something?
Not me. All I've been doing
is keeping us on course.
[PRISONER CC] It feels like
it's starting to pick up speed!
It-It's happening! He's right!
[BUGGY]
Ah! Ow!
What is it? What's going on?
[PRISONERS]
Hey, Captain Buggy!
It's happening,
just like you said.
Look, the miracle
you prophesied.
[BUGGY]
Heh?
[MR. 3]
Hmm.
It's just a coincidence.
I don't know what's going on,
but it's our chance! Go!
[BUGGY]
What did I tell you, guys?!
All ya gotta do is wait
for the right time,
and now that time is callin'
me to become the King!
[BUGGY laughing]
[PRISONER A] You're incredible,
Captain Buggy! One of a kind!
[PRISONERS]
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Yeah! At this rate,
we'll make it for sure!
[PRISONER F]
Uh?
Hey! Behind us!
[PRISONER E, PRISONER G]
Uh? Ah!
[BUGGY]
Heh? Gah!
Oh, hell no!
I don't get it.
Nobody is moving.
Maybe they're just waiting
for Whitebeard's command.
I'm choking on the tension.
What the--? It reversed.
The tide is rising again.
[MARINE B]
Uh?
Look! The horizon!
What the--? That's not right.
And here comes the final payoff.
That harmless seaquake he
threatened us with earlier
was just the prelude
to a massive tsunami!
"Quake Man" is
what they call him!
He wields the power of
the Tremor-Tremor Fruit!
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINE BB]
A tsunami! Run for it!
Our forces may be many,
but that won't
guarantee our victory.
Not against Whitebeard at least.
Before him, his crew,
no one is safe!
He has the power to destroy
the world in his veins!
It's happening! The great war.
[ALL]
Let's go!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR]
The invaders:
47 pirate ships from the New
World led by Whitebeard.
The defenders:
The two greatest forces
of the government,
Navy HQ and the Seven Warlords.
No matter who wins,
no matter who loses,
the world will be
forever changed.
[MARINE CC]
It's a tsunami!
[BOTH screaming]
[MARINES gasping]
[BOTH whimpering]
Now that is power! Heh!
He's straight outta hell!
[DOFLAMINGO chuckling]
[laughing]
[AOKIJI]
Ice Age.
[WHITEBEARD]
Aokiji.
You little squirt.
[FULLBODY]
He-He froze it!
That was too close!
Kuzan saved our butts!
[AOKIJI]
Partisan!
Uh-oh.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE CC]
The whole bay is iced over.
The ship's locked in.
We can't even move.
Hey. C'mon, guys. We've
got the admirals on our side.
They're the Navy's
greatest warriors, right?
Yeah, you're right.
There's nothin' to be
scared of. Screw Whitebeard.
[MARINES]
Yeah!
All cannons, open fire!
Sink the Moby Dick!
Well, let's move.
We got something
to stand on now.
Let's show them what
we can do, gentlemen!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yelling]
We've got the Commanders
backin' us up, too!
Open fire and give 'em
everything ya got!
[SMOKER]
Mount a counter-offensive.
[TASHIGI]
Right!
If I'm not mistaken,
that's the Fifth Division
Commander, Flower Sword Vista.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE E yelling]
Keep on your toes, Tashigi.
The Commanders
aren't the only ones
we've gotta worry about here.
Every single one of these
S.O.B.s is a mighty soldier
in his own right.
Yes. Yes, thank you, sir.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE F laughing]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE F] This ice
in the water ain't half bad!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE F]
Nice of him to set up
some stationary targets for us!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE G]
Let's finish these ships off
so we can invade the island!
Yeah, I'm not sure
it's gonna be that easy.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE DD] They're
sending out the Vice Admirals
of Navy HQ.
It's a rare sight to see them
all lined up in a row like that.
Ain't that cute?
[ZODIA laughing]
It's like they rolled out
a Buster Call to greet us.
Too bad.
Because this time we're
the ones doin' the bustin'
as they're all
about to find out.
Hey, Tsuru, why don't
you stand back some?
Yeah, please. Just leave
this nonsense up to us.
Have a nice cup
of tea. Stay safe.
Don't give me that, ya
condescending pricks. I'm fine.
Besides, there's
no place safe now,
even if I swam all the way
to the end of the sea.
[SQUARD] We're settin' anchor
here on the ice, boys!
It's time to trounce
those Navy sissies!
Now push for solid ground! Go!
[SQUARD PIRATES]
Yeah!
We're happy to give our lives
for Pops. It'd be an honor.
Bring it on, Navy. My men
got nothing to fear!
Enough talk. Let's go,
Squard Pirates!
[SQUARD PIRATES]
Yeah!
And now, it all begins.
[DOFLAMINGO]
Huh?
Oh, man. Look!
Is Dracule Mihawk
gonna make a move?
Well, what do you know.
That is mighty strange.
So, piqued his
interest, did they?
Hawkeye finally
willing to fight.
[DOFLAMINGO] You gonna grace
them with your sword for once?
[HANCOCK] That icy gaze would
leave even a seasoned warrior
frozen dead in his tracks.
Even with his blade
resting upon his back,
who has the courage
to stare him down?
[VISTA]
Hawkeye.
Every swordsman worth their salt
longs to cross blades with him.
How else are we to find
our worth, but to duel?
Climbing the steps of glory
with death nipping at our heels.
Hey, that's the black
sword. Quite famous.
To be precise,
it's named Night.
There are only twelve
like it in the world.
They bear the highest grade.
See the dark edge of the blade?
The temper line?
Its clove pattern?
An ornate design suitable for
only the greatest swordsman.
It's Hawkeye.
[NARRATOR]
Mihawke and Kizaru
launch an attack
against Whitebeard.
Unfazed, his Commanders
leap into the fray,
showing off their fearsome
Devil Fruit powers.
As the struggle rages on,
Admiral Akainu unleashes
a living hell
that transforms the battlefield.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"An All-Consuming Inferno!!
Admiral Akainu's Power!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!