Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy was sent flying
from the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring
through the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom
inhabited entirely by women.
Its name was Amazon Lily.
[LUFFY] Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock!
[LUFFY struggling]
Sorry I can't pay you back
for saving my life and stuff,
but I got places to go and
a crew that's waiting for me.
And that means
bye-bye lady land.
[MARGARET]
Men truly are mysterious.
Their arms stretch,
they grow fat without warning,
their chests are flat, and
between their legs they have--
Hate to ask you
for your help again,
but could you
take these off for me?
[MARGARET] Your family jewels?
Would you drop it?
I mean these things!
I said I was going to
see my friends, remember?
If I show up looking like this,
they're all gonna laugh at me!
I think they look nice,
but I suppose.
[MARGARET] There.
[LUFFY] Hey, thanks lady!
You're the best!
[MARGARET] I can't
imagine anyone hating frills.
You men are just too strange.
Yeah? Well...
Whatever you say.
Either way,
thanks for taking them off.
Okay. Bye for real this time.
I gotta hurry.
[MARGARET]
Are all men so hasty?
[LUFFY] I can't rest 'til I know
my friends survived like I did.
That's all that matters.
'Cause as long as they're alive,
we can get back up
and keep fighting!
I'm gonna get stronger
than all those guys!
[yelling]
[LUFFY] Let's do this!
I'll walk all the way back
to Sabaody on my hands!
That'll toughen me up for sure!
[LUFFY]
Think you could give me a ship?
[MARGARET]
Wow. You really are hasty.
[LUFFY] You don't have any
ships? We're in a Calm Belt?
[MARGARET] That's right.
This island lies in an
area known as a Calm Belt.
And it's surrounded
by a giant Den of Sea Kings.
That's another reason
sailors never dare
to come near this place.
Castaways do sometimes
make their way to our shores,
but they almost always
do so as corpses.
Wait, but you said your leader
was part of a
pirate crew, right?
The ship of our
Snake Princess, the Yuda,
is pulled by two
giant poisonous sea snakes,
so even Sea Kings
don't dare to attack it.
And it's the only ship
on Amazon Lily.
This sucks. And there's no wind.
Should I just build a raft
and paddle all the way there?
[MARGARET] That's a joke, right?
Hey!
I'll just build a raft
and paddle all the way there!
Wait, you weren't joking?
Yeah! It's done!
[MARGARET]
But it's already falling apart!
[LUFFY yelling]
What's wrong?
He said he was a pirate,
but he can't even swim?
[LUFFY coughing]
I had no obligation to save you.
Do all men sink like a rock
even if they're sailors?
That was close!
Damn it!
If only Franky was here!
I'm screwed!
[MARGARET] You're not
the only one with problems!
Why did you have to cling to me
when you should've
been running away from here?
If this keeps up much longer,
I'll end up
growing attached to you!
Hold on! Just stop!
[LUFFY]
Why do you wanna shoot me?
You know...
Come to think of it,
these arrows are crazy strong.
When those girls
were chasing me earlier,
they were busting up
stone walls with those things.
Doesn't look like
there's anything special
about them, though.
Well, of course
these arrows are strong.
They're imbued with our haki.
You're mocking me, aren't you?
Haki? I never heard of it.
[YAMABUKI] There she is!
Margaret, are you safe?
You made it!
The man's with her!
Strike him down!
[LUFFY]
Uh-oh!
[KIKYO]
Coward!
[MARGARET] Come back!
[SWEETPEA] Forgive me if
you were injured, Margaret,
but our situation is quite dire.
The Snake Princess has returned,
so we must vanquish
this fiend post haste!
You're quite bold
to lay your anchor
in Sea King-infested waters...
Unless you're just fools.
[MOMONGA] Yes. We did notice
the Sea Kings, thank you.
The Sea Prism Stone
on this battleship
may conceal our presence
from the beasts for a while.
But after waiting here
for so long,
they eventually caught on
and attacked us.
We would prefer
to avoid such encounters,
but as you know,
the agreement between
the Kuja and the government
forbids us from getting
closer than three kilometers
from your island.
So, like "fools",
here we are waiting
in a monster's nest
while you ladies
take your sweet time.
Hey, have you heard?
They say that
the ruler of the Kuja
is a monster that
can turn people to stone!
That's stupid!
You killed that Sea King?
Well, you can
color me impressed.
[MARINES muttering]
Those of us who
travel on the Grand Line
are no strangers
to these creatures.
But the ones
here in the Calm Belt
are certainly larger
and decidedly more ferocious.
[MOMONGA]
Any sign of the Kuja ship?
Uh, no, not yet, Vice-Admiral!
No approaching ships
anywhere in sight!
[MOMONGA] How long does
she intend to keep us waiting?
Or perhaps the empress
has changed her mind.
[MARINE 410B]
It's a Sea King!
[MARINE 410C]
Fire! Fire!
No way!
Our cannons didn't even
leave a mark on that thing!
[MARINES]
Ahh!
The whole ship's
gonna be smashed to pieces
if we don't do something quick!
Yeah, but what can we do?
We gave it all we had!
[SEA KING screeching]
That thing isn't gonna
eat the whole ship, is it?
I had hoped for a
greeting from the empress,
not this monster.
However, I shall
meet it all the same!
[SEA KING choking]
Look, guys!
He's alive!
[MOMONGA]
Monster though it may be,
if I allowed that beast
to devour a Marine vessel,
how could I call
myself a Vice-Admiral?
[MARINES cheering]
What strange marks.
Did you cut from
the inside of its stomach?
[MOMONGA] I am not here to hunt
Sea Kings or to chat about them.
Let us conduct
our business quickly
so that I may
leave these waters.
[RAN] Your words
are as sharp as your blade.
Then hear them well,
Kuja Pirates.
I tire of waiting here.
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters!
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock.
I have come for you!
Reveal yourself!
The Snake Princess does not
cater to your beck and call.
There's your answer.
You might as well go home now!
Look at those ugly men!
Unsophisticated boors!
I haven't seen a
live one in a long time!
Whenever pirates or
merchants see the Kuja flag
flying above the island,
they flee in terror!
[laughing]
That laugh isn't very lady-like.
We received a message
from your princess.
She claimed that she
would reply to our summons,
but now it appears
she was not quite sincere.
[MOMONGA] This morning's paper.
A place and date
has been decided
for the public execution
of Portgas D. Ace,
the 2nd Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
There is no turning back now!
[MOMONGA] The World Government
has issued strict orders
that the Seven Warlords
of the Sea assemble.
Refuse and our
agreement will become void.
And your princess' title
as Warlord will be revoked.
Think about that for a moment.
Until now,
you have done as you pleased
because of your position.
But if you are unwilling
to grant us this favor,
you will be reduced to
nothing but ordinary pirates.
Which means
you'll be adversaries
of the Marines and
World Government alike.
Do you hear me? Boa Hancock!
[footsteps approaching]
[footsteps continue]
[KITTEN meows]
[HANCOCK] Which one of you...
...had the audacity...
...to place this
kitten in my path?
My deepest apologies, empress!
I accept full responsibility!
[HANCOCK]
You should be more careful.
Yes. Of course!
Stop it!
At long last. Boa Hancock!
Careful men, keep your guard up!
The Vice-Admiral is right.
I'm still not
convinced those women
aren't really
monsters in disguise!
There's no telling
how frightening
their leader could be!
Brace yourselves!
[MARINE 410F]
That's the Pirate Empress?
[MARINE 410G] She's the most
beautiful woman in the world!
Crap! Crap! Crap!
Halt, man! Face me!
Ah jeez, the girls from
this island are scary as heck!
I'll take Nami
over them any day!
Well, maybe not.
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY] One hit from those
crazy arrows, and I'm done for!
All right, here goes!
This fiend behaves
more like a monkey
than a human man.
Damn it,
what are we going to do?
We cannot allow
him to run free here,
not with the empress coming.
We have no choice
but to hunt him down
and kill him
as quickly as possible!
Our time is short.
We must split up!
[KIKYO] Very well!
May your arrows find
their target, my sisters!
[ALL] They shall!
[LUFFY] Maybe it's not
a good idea to go this way.
I mean, this is where
I was running away from before.
It'll work out.
I can always run back
to the jungle if I have to.
[YAMABUKI] Up there!
Oh no!
I won't miss
my mark this time!
[LUFFY yelling]
Is he dead?
Not yet.
The man just slipped
and fell into the jungle.
So you've come for me at last.
Stubborn and meddlesome, I see.
[HANCOCK] I shall be frank.
I have no intention
of keeping my promise.
In other words,
I refuse to go to war for you.
Still, I rather like
my position as a Warlord.
So I think I shall keep it.
Also...
You shall give me
all the cargo on your ship,
quickly, without complaint.
[MOMONGA] That's enough!
I won't stand for you
acting like a spoiled child!
Do you honestly
think we'll accept
such unreasonable demands?
[MARINE 410C]
Haul it over, men!
I'll do anything you want!
Order me around some more!
Put that cargo
down this instant
or I'll throw you overboard!
Sorry!
I couldn't resist her, sir!
[MOMONGA] Portgas D. Ace's
public execution
will be exactly
one week from today!
The event will be held in
the town square of Marineford.
In other words,
we're doing this inside
of Navy Headquarters itself.
[MOMONGA] There is
no doubt that Whitebeard
will attempt to rescue him
in the next few days.
Likely with the strength
of his entire crew behind him.
Under the leadership
of three admirals,
and with the aid of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
Navy Headquarters is determined
to stop him at any cost.
Will you give up the title of
Warlord, or accept your orders?
Make your decision quickly.
You've kept us
waiting long enough!
[HANCOCK] I already told you,
I like being a warlord.
However, I loathe
the World Government.
I have no interest
in following their orders.
Surely I can find
a better solution.
Oh, I know--
How does this sound?
"The Marines who came to escort
me had a mysterious accident.
When they were discovered,
they had all been
transformed into stone
and were promptly disposed of."
She's planning to do something!
Don't let your guard down!
I've heard about
Hancock doing this before!
A merchant ship was
attacked by the Kuja Pirates,
and when it was
discovered later,
there weren't any
crew members onboard.
Just a bunch of weird statues!
[SAILOR 410A]
Hey! Look at that!
[SAILOR 410B] Those aren't...
people, are they?
You mean they
were all turned to stone?
I've had enough
of these threats.
Your temper tantrums will not
be tolerated, do you hear me?
[SANDERSONIA giggles]
Our big sister has
a rotten personality.
But in the end,
she always gets her way.
[MARIGOLD] Indeed. And there
is a very good reason for that.
[HANCOCK]
Would you like to know why?
Because no matter what I do.
Even if I kick a kitten.
Even if I yank off your ears.
[growls]
[HANCOCK] Why, even
if I were to commit murder,
the world would forgive me.
And that is because... yes.
It is because
I am beautiful!
[screaming]
[AMAZONS] Your highness!
[MARINE 410K] You're right!
You can abuse me all
you want, your highness!
Stop that, you fools!
[HANCOCK] The guilty thoughts
swimming in your hearts
shall turn your flesh to stone!
Love-Love Beam!
Hancock!
Oh, I'd expect no less
from a Navy vice-admiral.
[HANCOCK] Clever.
Forcing the wicked thoughts
from your mind with pain.
I do applaud your conviction.
Though...
I can't extend that
compliment to your men.
They should be ashamed.
[HANCOCK]
Now you're the only one left.
[MOMONGA] But one...
...is not...
...zero.
[AMAZONS laughing]
We shall return to our
peaceful home of Amazon Lily!
Aye-Aye, Snake Princess!
[MOMONGA]
Listen up, Boa Hancock!
I won't turn away!
I refuse to return empty-handed!
Unless you reappear
in two days...
Your position will be revoked!
[HANCOCK] Do as you wish.
[NARRATOR]
Luffy storms the Kuja village
in hopes of acquiring a boat,
but accidentally lands in a bath
where Empress Hancock
is bathing.
As he peers through the steam
rising from its waters,
he sees a forbidden secret
etched upon her back.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
The Secret Hidden on the Backs!
Luffy and the
Snake Princess Meet!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!