[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from the
rest of his crew, Luffy has
finally arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
The Whitebeard Pirates have
successfully
pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines
still block the path to Ace.
The battle is spreading
to the bay head,
where allies of Whitebeard
are under attack from
the Navy's human weapons,
the Pacifistas!
Oh, Squard.
Good to see you're alive.
[SQUARD]
Yeah, barely.
[WHITEBEARD]
Is that so?
I was trying to
reach you earlier.
How're things lookin'
at the bay head now?
I'm sorry to say, but your
allies were beaten pretty badly.
As for me, I only managed to get
out of there through sheer luck.
[WHITEBEARD] Sengoku is
one merciless bastard.
He's pulling out every
dirty trick he can think of.
Judging by your shift in tactic,
I'm guessing you picked up
on the Navy's plan.
[WHITEBEARD]
I've known Sengoku
and what he's capable
of for a long time.
[MARCO] Huh?
What's Squard doing up there?
You have 43 allied captains
willing to die for you.
We're all in your debt,
for now and for always.
We consider it a privilege to
risk our lives for
you and your crew.
[SQUARD yelling]
[WHITEBEARD gasps]
[LUFFY] "Akainu's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped!"
[heart beating]
[heart continues beating]
[panting]
[BUGGY, PRISONER A gasping]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL humming]
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN A]
I-I can't believe it.
It's impossible!
No, it can't be!
[MAN A]
Whitebeard has been stabbed!
[CROWD shouting]
The old guy?
[MAN AA]
Why? No, who stabbed him?
[MAN BB]
They'll be torn apart!
[MAN AA]
Wait, look!
It was one of Whitebeard's
allies who did it!
A captain from the New World!
The Whirl Spider!
How dare you, Squard!
[SQUARD grunts]
Why the hell did you
attack Pops, huh?
Answer me now,
or I'll kill ya!
Yeah? Then do it! This whole
mess is his fault anyway!
What do ya mean?
Do you even realize what
you've just done, you--! Huh?
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARCO]
Don't move, Pops!
You'll make things worse
if you keep squirmin'.
Whitebeard!
[panting]
I'm serious,
this battle is a fake!
Just ask him!
[MARCO gasps]
[SQUARD] I know about your
treacherous deal with the Navy!
You have their
assurance that Ace
and all of your pirates
won't even get scratched!
They'll just go
after your allies!
[BLONDIE]
Hm?
Wait, what's he saying?
Is it true that they're...
just targeting us?
[SQUARD]
Everybody! Listen up!
Whitebeard's been
playing us all for fools!
[panting]
All this time you've
kept it a secret.
You didn't have
the guts to tell me
that Ace is actually the son
of that wretched pirate,
Gold Roger!
[SQUARD panting]
When you first found me,
I was alone in this world,
a complete wreck.
[thudding]
[MAN CC]
Squard is outta his mind again!
[MAN DD] He's dangerous
when he's like this! Stay away!
[OLD LADY A]
Come on! This again?
[MAN EE] Once he starts, we just
gotta sit back and ride it out.
[yelling]
[SQUARD] Isn't there anyone
strong enough to face me?
I'm right here! Bring it on!
How's about Gold Roger,
where's he at?
[MAN FF, MAN GG gasping]
[SQUARD] What's a matter?
Are you all scared?
[SQUARD laughs]
Gimme your best shot!
[SQUARD gasps]
[SQUARD] You knew why
I was all alone that day.
[SQUARD gasping]
[SQUARD] My precious crew,
who had fought alongside me
in so many battles,
was killed by Gold Roger.
You know this, and you know
that I despise Roger.
More than anything!
Yet you still kept
these secrets from me,
that Ace was Roger's son,
that you were helping him become
the next King of the Pirates!
How could I trust
someone like you?
[MAN HH]
Never mind the Whitebeards,
take care of yourselves!
Get back down to the plaza!
The old guy, he wants
Ace to be the King?
'Cause, ya see, Whitebeard's
the greatest pirate
I've ever met.
That's why I'm going to help
him become King of the Pirates.
[PIRATES screaming]
[SQUARD]
You've been betraying me
and playing me for a fool
since the very beginning!
I didn't have a damn clue!
I bet you laughed your ass off
when I became friends with Ace!
Then your favorite
son got caught,
and you showed your true colors!
All of the Whitebeard
Pirates are inside the bay,
while us allied pirates
are stuck outside.
Forty-three captains
fight beside you,
and you handed us
all to the Navy!
Just to protect Roger's son!
We allied pirates
will be obliterated,
whereas Ace and your men
will be completely safe.
That's your underhanded
deal with Sengoku, isn't it?
[SQUARD] What?
Fire Fist Ace is Roger's son?
That's right. And our superiors
already have an agreement
regarding how this
war's going to end.
[SQUARD]
Go to hell!
I don't believe
a word of that crap!
Whether you believe it
or not doesn't matter.
You're gonna end up dead anyway.
That's enough! We'll see who
ends up dead, you wretch! Ahh!
[SQUARD groans]
[AKAINU]
You're a stubborn brat,
but you'll learn what
I'm talking about soon enough.
Stand up and look for yourself!
[panting]
We plan to converge
our forces soon.
Then attack the allied
pirates. Only them.
Huh?
And Whitebeard?
The Navy isn't even gonna lay
a finger on his gang of pirates.
[SQUARD grunts]
Not one of us knew the truth,
and so, we followed you,
risking our lives
to help rescue Ace,
only to find out we were nothing
more than sacrifices to you!
We're the ones bearing
the brunt of the Navy's attacks!
It's as clear as day!
[PIRATES yelling]
[SQUARD] Those monsters
approach from the back,
and the ice blocks
us on both sides.
There's no way we can escape!
[KARMA panting] Whitebeard, old
buddy, is he tellin' the truth?
[DECALVAN BROS] He's lying
his teeth off! He's gotta be!
It's a miracle I was
able to stab you.
Well, now it's
your turn. Kill me!
The ice wall is in the way!
We're blocked off on every side!
Oh, no. Is this the end?
[PIRATES yelling]
He was right, look!
The Navy's only goin' after us!
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE AA]
Run away!
[PIRATES yelling]
Old buddy, please tell me we're
not throwin' our lives away.
Just so you can save Ace?
[PIRATE BB]
Please say somethin'! Anything!
[PIRATE DD]
Whitebeard!
[gasps]
[WOMAN A gasps]
[MAN II] It can't be true!
It's impossible!
[MAN JJ] Whitebeard wouldn't
sell out fellow pirates!
[MAN KK]
He did that to his allies?
[MAN LL] No way,
he'd fight the Navy head-on!
[MAN MM] Whitebeard and
the Navy are in cahoots?
[MAN NN] All those
New World pirates who trusted
and followed Whitebeard.
[MAN OO]
I know, I can't believe it!
They're all rushing to their
doom thanks to his betrayal!
I didn't wanna believe it.
We're all sons to you,
but I guess some kids are
just worth more than others!
You're a damn fool!
The Navy is
deceiving you, Squard!
Why trust them instead of Pops?
I know you're in on the deal,
don't you play dumb with me!
You're the first
division commander!
You're basically
Whitebeard's right-hand man!
If anyone knows about his
deal with the Navy, it's you!
[WHITEBEARD]
It ain't Ace's fault his old man
killed Squard's crew,
but it is what it is.
And I can only blame
myself for keeping it
a secret all these years.
The Navy made the right move.
That doesn't make you
any less of a bastard, though,
Sengoku, even if you
are a crafty one.
It's time to end this.
Go, Aokiji!
Hell no! Don't target us!
[MAN PP]
This entire war's a setup?
[MAN QQ]
It can't seriously be fake!
I've wasted my whole day
watching this stuff!
[MAN RR]
It shut off!
[WOMAN BB]
What's wrong?
[MAN SS]
Is it broken?
Now activate the walls!
[MARINE AA]
Right!
[CROCODILE]
The pirate who defeated me
would never be
struck down so easily.
Especially by his own ally!
You're not worth
my time anymore, old man!
If this is how the
great Whitebeard dies,
you'll make a fool of us both!
Oh, boy, that was harsh.
Then it was a matter of pride.
[MARCO]
It's true.
He coulda easily blocked that
if he was as tough
as he used to be.
It wouldn't have mattered
that it was a surprise attack,
or that it came from
one of his allies.
Has Pops gotten weaker
than we thought and
I just didn't notice?
I don't want no sympathy.
There's no way I'm wearing this
crap in front of my enemies!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES]
But Pops!
[MARCO] He's letting his
health get worse and worse!
[SQUARD]
Huh?
I don't know if you realize
the magnitude of what
you've just done, Squard.
You thrust a sword into
your father's body,
trying to kill him.
You've lost your way,
my poor, stupid son!
[SQUARD gasps]
[gasping]
But I still love you.
Even if you are a damn fool.
[SQUARD] Cut the crap. You sold
our lives out. All of us.
Who took your loyal and
steadfast heart away from your
father and delivered it
into the hands of our enemies?
Now you tell me his name.
Akainu.
Admiral Akainu.
[AKAINU] I'm opposed to
such an underhanded plan.
Most people don't
know the truth,
so they call Whitebeard a hero.
They don't think twice
about praising the man.
But you know better.
He's a scumbag who
came to us with a deal.
One that protects his
and his pirates' interests,
but betrays his New World allies
without so much
as a second thought.
All those stories and
legends are made up.
[SQUARD grunts]
The one we should kill
in this war is Whitebeard.
Letting him live would be
a great disservice to the world.
If you can help me, I'll save
all of the New World Pirates.
[gasps]
Whitebeard. Kill him.
[gasping]
[SQUARD]
He said if I killed you
he would save your
New World allies.
Akainu. So, that's
what he told you.
I completely understand
how much you hate Gold Roger.
So much so that
I can feel your pain.
But listen to me.
It's ridiculous to lay
the blame on a child
for the sins of his father.
Did Ace ever do
a thing to hurt you?
[SQUARD gasps]
[WHITEBEARD] The two of you have
been through so much together.
Some of it happy,
some of it painful.
But you've weathered it all,
good times and bad,
with our brothers in arms.
I never gave a damn
about who Ace's father is,
and I still don't.
We all crossed paths on
these seas by chance!
And wherever the
hell we came from
doesn't mean a thing anymore.
We're together now.
So, Squard,
please treat him kindly.
I don't love Ace more than
any other son of mine.
On that, you have my word.
Every single one of you
is part of my family!
[SQUARD gasping]
[WHITEBEARD]
Now, moving on...
That Sengoku...
He hasn't changed
one bit. The bastard!
But that crafty old snake
gave us a pretty
good shakeup, didn't he?
[WHITEBEARD]
But to even suggest that
I'd sell out my sons
is ridiculous!
They can leave now.
He destroyed the ice wall.
He's a sharp one.
[PIRATE EE] There's nothing
blocking our path.
[PIRATE FF]
You're right!
We can take these Navy ships
and sail away whenever we want!
If you're a true pirate,
then you choose which
path to take on your own!
[SQUARD crying]
I knew it was a lie! The Navy's
just trying to tear us apart!
Come on, guys!
Let's take it to 'em!
Of course they were lying,
old buddy would never betray us!
Hear that?
We'll die before we ever lose
trust in you, old buddy!
[PIRATE HH] Please
forgive me! We were wrong!
[PIRATE II] I'll follow you to
the end, Whitebeard, old buddy!
[WHITEBEARD]
Think I'm going soft, do you?
Give it a rest, Croco bum.
I'm only human,
and every human has a heart,
no matter how large or small.
People can call me
a monster all they want,
but the reality is I can't be
the strongest pirate forever.
If I can save this
one young man's life,
I'll have earned the right
to retire from this
world once and for all.
Those of you who'll
still follow me,
put your lives on the line!
[PIRATES shouting]
Get ready, men!
He's coming this way!
The strongest
pirate in the world!
Let's attack!
[NARRATOR] At last the
world's most powerful pirate,
Whitebeard, leaps into the fray.
The Navy cowers in fear
before the power of his
Tremor Tremor Fruit,
as it literally changes
the landscape of the battle.
However, Sengoku has a plan
that may yet turn the tide.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Encircling Walls Activated!
The Whitebeard Pirates
Backed Into a Corner!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!