[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope,
and others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era in
the country's history
that will forever be
overshadowed by sadness.
Crocodile does his best
to get information
on the whereabouts
of the Poneglyph.
Panic spreads as he
announces that a bomb
will be shot into
the Palace Square.
Will this mark the
end of Alabasta?
Or is there still time to
establish a lasting peace?
Once again, the hourglass
of fate resumes
its dreaded countdown
to annihilation.
[LUFFY] "The Battle is Over!
Koza Raises the White Flag!"
[swords clanging]
[CLAW SOLDIER A] Move it!
Get out of our way! Step aside!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
Hey! Isn't that‐‐?
[CLAW SOLDIER A yells]
[CLAW SOLDIER A]
No, Chaka! Please wait!
[CROCODILE]
Hm?
So who are they?
The Guardians!
The Kicking Claw Force!
Don't attack, men.
You'll only be throwing
your lives away!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
They broke the door down!
[ROYAL SOLDIER B]
A daring move!
[ROYAL SOLDIER C] Please! Save
His Majesty and Princess Vivi!
[CLAW SOLDIER B]
Your Majesty!
Defending you to the death
is not only our mission,
it is the highest
honor and privilege!
Therefore, we can't
simply avoid him.
He is one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea.
The only way to beat
him is to fight dirty.
[ALL]
We four are as one!
We fight for your honor!
To set things right!
It seems that you have
quite the reputation.
Therefore, I will
spare your lives.
Leave now and go home.
[CLAW SOLDIER A]
We can't do that.
There is another reason
we will not withdraw.
Reason?
If the rumors are true and you
really are the ringleader,
the architect of this
whole rebellion...
[grunts]
[gasps] Those bruises!
What have you men done?
Shall I?
You needn't waste your
time on these cretins.
[gasps] They didn't!
Chaka, what's happening
to their bodies?
I fear... to temporarily
increase their power,
they drank the fatal elixir.
It grants incredible strength,
but then kills the host.
They're dead men!
Oh, no!
[chuckles]
You bulked up to challenge
me. I'm flattered.
But what good is victory if
you're not around to enjoy it?
[CLAW SOLDIER B]
Chaka, please!
Forgive us for doing this
without consulting you,
but we had to take
drastic measures
to end this country's suffering!
Those idiots! How could they?
[CLAW SOLDIER B]
We have to make him realize...
...the fury of...
[CLAW SOLDIERS yelling]
[CROCODILE]
Huh.
...this country!
[CLAW SOLDIER A]
Huh?
[CROCODILE] That wasn't
the smartest decision.
A person should value
his life above all else.
But it's too late
for regrets, yes?
[CROCODILE laughing]
And if you're all
going to die anyway,
I don't have to bother
killing you myself, right?
You don't even have
the decency to fight?
[gasps]
Chaka, I'm sorry.
[CROCODILE laughing]
Behold, the very
definition of stupidity!
[growls]
You bastard!
[growling]
[VIVI]
Chaka!
Chaka! This is senseless!
You'll just be following
them to their deaths!
Ah. You're a Zoan type.
[CHAKA]
Dog Dog Fruit. Model: Jackal!
Howling Fangs!
[CROCODILE] I see you share
the same flaw as these fools.
You'll die for others.
[ZORO grunts]
Dammit! Lost too much blood.
Guess I should be thankful
the cuts aren't that deep.
But it does hurt like hell.
[ZORO]
Wonder how the others are doing.
Wanna know what's goin' on.
Idiots better not be dead!
[USOPP]
What?
What do ya mean I have
to pair with Eyelash?
[crying]
Look! He's a camel!
I'm very fragile, so I need
someone who can back me up!
[EYELASH grunts]
Man up. The raffle was fair.
You got Eyelash,
and that's that.
Fine! But you better
promise me one thing.
When me and this stupid camel
are standing at the
doorway of death,
please come to our rescue!
Sorry. I only save the
damsels. You're on your own.
[ZORO]
Usopp.
[SANJI]
Hey, what's wrong?
Usopp! Why're you crying?
Who's crying? I'm not crying!
You're crying! Yeah!
"He who smelt it dealt it."
Yeah, that's it...
[SANJI]
That doesn't even make sense.
You're a dealter.
A dealter‐smealter.
That old hag said... Luffy...
She said Luffy's dead, so I...
I wonder if it's true.
Come on! You guys
really believe that?
Of course not! Luffy's alive!
What do ya think we are, stupid?
That's right! I don't believe
it either! Luffy is alive!
[EYELASH grunts]
Yeah, all right, I get it.
You're preaching to
the choir here.
What we have to do now
is get to the palace ASAP.
Now, if ya don't mind,
try to plug your snot,
at least until the rumbling
from the battle stops.
[USOPP snorts]
[SANJI]
Don't swallow it!
Thank you, everyone.
You're welcome, but it's
too early to thank us.
He's right.
Besides, if you really
wanna thank pirates,
you have to let us
see some goods.
Nami, what is it you're trying
to leach out of this
country, anyway?
[ZORO] Is Nami okay?
Did she manage to get away?
[NAMI sighs]
[NAMI]
They finally came off.
Calling it a powerful
one‐shot attack?
Think that's a bit of
an understatement.
The fighting's come far.
They're right there,
just around the corner.
[NAMI]
Guess the situation's changed.
Anyway, I better
get to the palace.
[ZORO] Sounds like
the battle's started.
What about Vivi?
[SANJI]
Oh, yeah.
One more thing, and this is an
important fact to remember.
After a battle, these guys
put down a ton of food.
'Kay.
We'll be waiting for you!
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
[SANJI]
This is absolutely crucial.
[DUCK A squawks]
[DUCK B squawks]
[ZORO]
Don't screw this up!
[SANJI]
Let's go! See you at the palace!
Chaka!
[CROCODILE chuckles]
Weakness is a crime...
...punishable by death.
[KOZA]
Vivi!
No. Koza.
[CROCODILE]
Huh?
It's you.
I see you came through the
shortcut you used to use.
This can't be.
What am I seeing here?
[KOZA] I came in hope of
persuading the royal army,
but...
[KOZA]
Chaka...
And the king is...
He's about to be killed
by this country's hero.
I can't believe my eyes.
[laughing]
Now things are starting
to get interesting!
Here we are in the
midst of an epic war,
and yet, the leaders of both
sides aren't on the battlefield.
Fate has placed them
squabbling at my feet!
A battle to the death
between two broken titans
bleeding out the last
remnants of their power!
You seem lost and confused.
Don't worry. It's a natural
reaction. Let me help you.
Relax and open your mind.
Then imagine being faced with
the worst possible scenario.
[TOTO] Koza, purge your
heart of all suspicion.
Do you love this country?
This is my home!
[COBRA]
Mine as well!
Koza, listen!
[KOZA]
Vivi!
Who is responsible for the
drought ravaging this country?
Tell me!
It was‐‐!
[CROCODILE]
That honor belongs to me.
Over the past two years,
each and every malicious
deed you attributed
to the king's doing was in fact
perpetrated by my company.
A trap that saw you playing
right into our hands.
It was a flawless,
systematic plot of deception.
I must say, it was entertaining
watching as the royal family
and its mighty army
desperately chased our shadows.
[CROCODILE laughs]
[CROCODILE]
Pity.
You probably would've
died in ignorant bliss
not knowing these brutal facts.
[CROCODILE laughs]
Koza! Listen!
Majesty!
There's still some time
if you have the courage!
You must act now. Save as
many citizens as you can.
[CHAKA]
In less than half an hour,
the whole Palace Square will
be blown to kingdom come!
What do ya mean?!
So, you're still alive, are you?
Hurry!
[CROCODILE]
Hm?
[VIVI]
Stop!
[gasps] Vivi!
Get off of me!
What're you doing?
There's no time!
The battle is about to
spill into the Square!
If it's really set to
blow up, get off!
You have to listen to me!
[VIVI]
Think this through. Please.
What will happen if
you tell the armies
the Square is set to explode?
The men will panic.
It would only add more
chaos to the battle.
And even if you stop the bomb,
it won't stop the fighting!
Either way, people are
still going to die!
You won't save anyone!
Understand?
[chuckles] Well, well,
what a perceptive girl.
Our only hope is to do
what should've been done
from the start.
We have to stop the rebellion
and end this bloodshed!
And you...
You're the only one
who can do it!
Vivi.
Did you really think
I was going to sit back
and watch passively while
you tried to ruin my plans?
[yells]
Chaka!
[CROCODILE]
Huh?
[CHAKA]
I am...
...Alabasta's guardian deity.
Destroyer of all who
threaten the royal family.
I am...
...the Jackal!
I'll fight as long as there
is breath left in my body.
Some call that brave,
I call it stupid.
[CHAKA]
Do what you must, both of you!
I will hold him back
for a few more minutes!
[KOZA]
Chaka.
[CHAKA] Such a shame the
leader of the Sand‐Sand Clan
is so weak.
Boy? What's the matter?
[KOZA growls]
[KOZA]
Ah!
What's wrong with
you?! I'm a child!
You can't treat me like this!
You're a pain in the neck, kid.
Koza, you asked me to train you.
Have you forgotten that already?
[ROYAL SOLDIER A] Report from
Guard Unit 2 to Headquarters!
Report from Unit 2
to Headquarters!
Line 4 has been breached!
Enemy has broken through!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A] The rebel
army is currently passing
through the Central Plaza,
heading to the North Block!
They will reach the palace!
Raise the flag to surrender!
Royal army! You will
surrender immediately!
Princess Vivi! Is she serious?
But why?
That's absurd!
If we do as she says,
that would mean the
end of this country!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
Hey, look! That's‐‐!
It's Koza!
What is the rebel army's leader
doing here in the palace?
Hear me! The princess
speaks the truth!
We no longer desire victory,
only to end this conflict!
Both sides have
spilled enough blood!
[ROYAL SOLDIERS chattering]
I will make each and
every rebel understand
the pointlessness
of this civil war!
They will see as I do that we
no longer have reason to fight!
In the interest of restoring
peace and preserving life,
I ask you, wave the white flag!
Please!
[REBEL SOLDIER A] The king's
head will roll this day!
[REBEL SOLDIER B] Ah! I can see
the clock tower up ahead!
[REBEL SOLDIER A] We're
approaching the Palace Square!
Prepare to attack!
[yelling]
[REBEL SOLDIER D]
Wait, stop!
White flags?
The royal army is
waving white flags!
We did it! They surrender!
It's Koza!
[REBEL SOLDIER E]
What's going on?
[REBEL SOLDIER F]
What's Koza doing here?
[KOZA]
The battle is over!
Everyone! Quiet your anger
and lower your weapons!
The Royal Army will stand down!
Let no more blood
stain the streets!
[VIVI]
Please listen to him.
Is this the truth, Koza?
Yes. The battle's finally over.
[gunshots]
[VIVI]
Koza!
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[CROCODILE]
Wake up, Princess.
You cannot save this country.
[VIVI] My voice no longer
reaches anyone.
If nothing is done,
the country will...
[LUFFY]
Don't worry, Vivi!
We hear your voice
loud and clear!
[VIVI]
Luffy!
[LUFFY] I'm gonna put
an end to all of this!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Where Vivi's Voice Gets Heard!
The Hero Descends!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!