[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[ZABO]
No!
[GEDATZ] Yet another
group of illegal entrants
have already
infiltrated Skypeia.
Old lady Amazon informed us
that it's a ship with seven
Blue Sea dwellers on board.
[NAMI]
Seven Blue Sea dwellers?
That's probably us!
[gasps]
[MCKINLEY]
White Berets, halt!
[WHITE BERETS]
Heso!
[CONIS]
Heso.
[PAGAYA]
Heso, gentlemen.
[SUU]
Suu-suu.
Speak our language!
We can't understand you.
Well, look what we have here.
You must be the
Blue Sea dwellers
who have illegally entered the
sovereign land of Skypiea!
Prepare to have the weight
of Heaven's Judgment
brought down upon you!
You're calling them criminals?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[LUFFY] "Already Criminals?!
Skypiea's Upholder of the Law!"
Illegal entry? What's that?
Let's just say it's not good.
[MCKINLEY] Don't waste your
breath making excuses.
Amazon, the woman who
stands at Heaven's Gate,
captured these very images
using her vision dial.
No, wait. That can't be!
I think this is all
a big misunderstanding,
Captain McKinley.
They're not the criminals
you're making them out to be.
What do you mean
by illegal entry?
Does this have to do
with that ridiculous
one billion extol entrance fee?
Because we didn't
pay her a thing.
But didn't that old lady say
we didn't have to pay it?
It's not like she
tried to stop us.
Yeah, that's true!
Enough! There's no sense
trying to deny it.
Now, fess up!
Don't worry, you need not
become panicked just yet.
According to Heaven's Judgment,
Illegal Entry is only
an 11th degree crime!
Once you accept
your punishment--
which will be minimal--
you become legal
tourists on the spot
and may go about your business.
Well, you shoulda
told us that sooner,
but before we accept,
what exactly do you have
planned as far as punishment?
A mere slap on the wrist.
All you need to do is pay
ten times the entrance fee.
Of course, if you
pay immediately,
we'll pretend this little
episode never happened.
So, ten billion per person,
times seven people
makes your total
70 billion extols.
Cash only.
Wait, 70 billion extols?
That sounds like an
awful lotta money!
How much is that in Berries?
That's the currency used
in the Blue Sea World, right?
Today's exchange rates are
10,000 extols per Berry.
Let's see now,
there's, uh, 10,000,
and you gotta carry
the one, and, uh,
is there a decimal in there?
Five?
Seventy billion extols is seven
million Berries, genius.
Get real! Do you realize
how expensive that is?!
After risking our lives
coming to this place,
why should we have
to pay a stupid fee
just to enter your
precious city?
We can't agree to that!
[MCKINLEY]
You brought this on yourselves.
If you had just paid the 700,000
Berries in the first place,
we wouldn't be having this talk.
[SANJI]
That's still way too expensive!
This is your first warning.
The White Berets serve under
the vassals of almighty Eneru.
Arguing with us will only raise
the level of your crime.
[SANJI]
Oh, whatever, man.
Let's forget these idiots.
We need to start looking for
Nami. I'm getting worried.
She may need my tender
affections right about now.
[CHOPPER]
Is she in trouble?
[LUFFY]
I doubt it.
[NAMI] Those weird guys
from earlier somehow knew
about us coming to Skypiea.
That means Luffy and the
others may be in trouble.
Better hurry back!
Soon as the wind
changes direction,
we can head out for
another adventure.
I mean, to look for Nami.
[USOPP yelps]
Listen to me!
Usopp, are you doin' okay?
[USOPP]
Wait, keep your cool, Usopp.
Try and talk some
sense into him.
You know, Cap'n.
If Nami's just taking a joy
ride around the island,
she may be back any minute.
If we leave now,
we could miss her.
We don't want that, now do we?
You think so?
She's taking way
too long for that!
Shut up!
The reason Luffy's here
in the first place
is to prove he can go where
he was told he can't go,
not chase after Nami, stupid!
[CHOPPER]
Okay!
That's true.
Let's just go.
Yeah, guys, Conis warned us
about that, remember?
If we go, we'll incur
Eneru's wrath,
then who knows how
much trouble we'll be in?
So what now?
Our best bet is to
wait here for Nami,
and try not to upset
the White Berets.
I mean, it's Nami
we're talkin' about!
She's gotta have
a secret stash
of a few trillion
Berries somewhere!
She can pay up, and
then we're outta here!
All right, what are you all
blabbing about over there?
And where's your
seventh crewmate?
I only count six!
Do I need to add "suspicion
of fleeing the island" to...
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
let's not get carried away here!
She's just takin' the waver
out for a quick spin.
Soon as she gets back she can
pay the fine in its entirety.
You can trust us, sir.
We're good for it!
Heh.
[USOPP] Okay, I think
I bought us some time.
Now, Luffy, don't do anything
stupid to make Nami angry.
You know how she can get.
[LUFFY]
Aww. Okay.
[USOPP]
Sanji, you, too.
[SANJI]
Yeah, yeah.
Great! That's the plan.
We'll meet back here later!
[SANJI] So, Robin, can I treat
you to a cup of tea?
[ROBIN]
Sure.
[sighs] Boy, that
was a close one.
Hey, Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[USOPP] You wanna go
fishin' or somethin'?
[CHOPPER]
Totally! Let's do it!
[USOPP] Conis, are there
any good fishin' spots
you know of around here?
[CONIS] I know of one about five
minutes from here. Follow me.
[LUFFY]
I can't wait to ride this thing!
I hope you can fix it.
[MCKINLEY] This waver
looks downright abused!
If I find out you're responsible
for this damage,
you're looking at a
tenth degree crime:
"Destruction of Sky
Island Property
by a Blue Sea Dweller."
I'm sorry, Captain McKinley,
this is my fault.
I crashed the waver, not him.
[LUFFY] Yeah, besides,
this thing's mine.
[MCKINLEY] Is that right?
Sounds suspicious to me.
I was under the impression
wavers didn't exist
in the Blue Sea World.
If this one was stolen
from Skypiea,
the degree of your
crime will increase!
It's not stolen!
Wanna fight about it?
[MCKINLEY]
Excuse me?
[USOPP screams]
Don't mind him!
He was just kidding!
Right this way, Luffy!
[MCKINLEY] Who do these Blue
Sea dwellers think they are,
insulting a senior member
of the White Berets?
They'll pay for this.
This's the life.
Gorgeous girl and
a view. Not bad.
I'm losing it!
Don't let it get away!
Hands are slipping!
Luffy, help!
[LUFFY]
Hm? Ah!
[USOPP]
We got 'im!
[CHOPPER]
It's a big one!
[ALL scream]
[gasping]
[CONIS screams]
What did we catch?
A fish or a monster?
[CHOPPER]
It tried to eat Conis.
[ZORO]
Take it this is a sky fish.
[PAGAYA]
You're heroes!
[ALL]
Hm?
Mere words cannot express
how grateful I am
that you saved my daughter.
[CONIS]
Father, look.
[PAGAYA]
We're in trouble.
[MCKINLEY]
Why am I not surprised?
This species of sky
fish is so rare
that it's forbidden to catch it.
Your incompetence has
once again earned you
a violation of the law.
This time it's a
ninth degree crime.
[CHOPPER]
Why is that a crime?!
That thing was gonna eat
Conis! Zoro saved her life!
[chuckles]
Wait! Zoro, you didn't
kill it, did you?
Don't think so.
Well, if it's not dead,
then we didn't commit a crime!
[roars]
[USOPP] See? What'd I
tell ya? It's alive!
Yum!
Don't eat it, Luffy! Stop!
You just dug your
own grave, son.
Eating an endangered species
is an eighth degree crime.
[LUFFY] Little on the tough
side, and it tastes kinda fishy!
[USOPP]
Get off of him, Luffy!
Hey, sky fish,
go back to your home.
And if you see any bait
on a hook, don't bite it!
You know, I've been biting
my tongue for the last day
listening to all the bogus
crimes you're accusing us of.
If you don't cut it out, I'll--
[USOPP] Zoro! Wait!
Think about what you're saying!
[MCKINLEY]
This has become ridiculous.
Your behavior is obviously
an attempt at extortion.
Congratulations,
seventh degree crime.
[USOPP] Zoro wasn't
trying to extort you!
Uh, he was about to say,
"If you don't cut it out,
I will have a good laugh!"
It's kinda like his
catchphrase. Asilly gag!
This isn't fair!
He's trying to get us
in trouble on purpose!
Ah! Chopper!
Shut up. You're only gonna
make things worse!
The only way to not get
in trouble is do nothing!
Do nothing, huh? That's it!
Now we just have to hope
that we don't get
charged for loitering.
Okay! Nap time!
[snoring]
[MCKINLEY] How dare they make
such a racket on Angel Beach.
Listen up, you're
all in violation
of Skypiea's noise
pollution statutes,
which are sixth degree crimes.
[USOPP]
You mean we can't even snore?
Agh! Enough already!
Let's put a beating on
this beret-wearing freak!
--[ZORO] Yes, let's.
--Stop it!
[USOPP]
Guys! Cool down!
[NAMI] Oh, no, there's
a whole group of people!
I hope they're not
those guys from before.
Whoever they are,
I hope Luffy's not pulling
any of his usual stunts.
Let's sit down and take
a breather, okay?
Zoro, Luffy, Chopper,
there's no reason for us--
[NAMI]
I'm back!
Nami, baby! I missed you!
[NAMI] Luffy! Promise you won't
start any trouble, okay?!
[LUFFY] Don't know if I
can keep that promise!
Hey! Nami!
We need you to fork up seven
million Berries from your stash
to pay for all the fines we got!
Oh, good! So we pay the
fine and we're clear?
Did he say seven million?
[MCKINLEY]
Hm? What?!
[NAMI]
You're ripping us off!!
[gasps] Oh, crap!
I was so worked up I forgot
to hit the brakes!
[BOTH]
Ouch.
[WHITE BERETS]
Captain!
[NAMI] Hey, thanks for letting
me use your waver.
I love the way it handles.
[PAGAYA]
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
But more importantly,
do you realize how much
trouble you're in now?
[WHITE BERET A]
Captain...
[NAMI] Guys, let's make
ourselves scarce.
[LUFFY]
Aww. Aren't you gonna finish
the fight you just started?
[NAMI] Trust me, this
Eneru is not someone
we wanna mess with.
I assume that's another
crime on our records.
Oh, yes, quite.
And knocking out an official
is a crime of the fifth degree.
Fifth, huh? Could be worse.
[CONIS]
That's not good at all.
Once you're found guilty of
committing a fifth degree crime,
almighty Eneru will banish you
to the land of the
drifting clouds.
How's that bad?
[LUFFY]
Land of the drifting clouds?
That sounds like fun!
It's a death sentence. You die!
[ALL]
We-We die?
[ZORO]
You really got him good, Nami.
But come on, a death
sentence in God's land?
That's quite a contradiction.
But it's the truth!
This is very serious!
They'll put you and your
ship on a small cloud
and set you adrift in the sea
with no chance of
rescue or escape.
You'll eventually die a very
slow and painful death.
It's terrible!
Interesting.
That must be why we saw
that ship fall from the sky.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
Don't you remember that
galleon we saw falling?
The St. Briss,
I think it was called.
For all we know,
that crew could've been
punished over 200 years ago.
[gulps]
[WHITE BERETS]
You! Criminals!
[WHITE BERET B] Do you scum know
what you've done to our Captain?
Who cares?
Sanji, let me handle this.
Anything for you!
Don't take it so personally.
It was a lucky shot!
[WHITE BERET B]
A lucky shot?
[NAMI]
Completely unintentional!
You're lying!
[NAMI]
No, I'm telling you the truth.
It was an accident. I swear!
An accident?
Uh. Okay, guys.
Look, try wrapping
your heads around this.
It was an accident
because those wavers
are really hard to control,
and it was only my first
time to ever pilot one.
So I made a little mistake
while I was turning.
Yeah, I'll admit that
makes me clumsy,
but can you blame a
beginner for messing up
and nearly killing your boss?
[LUFFY] That's weird,
seemed like you had
a pretty good handle
on it to me.
[NAMI]
Shuddup!
Quiet, Luffy!
Nami's trying to trick them into
thinking it was an accident.
Don't blow it, okay?
All right!
[PAGAYA]
Gentlemen.
As important as your
investigation is,
perhaps it would be best to get
the captain to a doctor first.
Just a thought.
Oh. Right! The captain!
[PAGAYA]
Now, there's no reason to panic.
Let's take him to my house.
We'll get right on that.
[WHITE BERETS]
Heso!
[WHITE BERET B]
Consider yourselves under
preliminary arrest.
Don't go anywhere! Got it?
The poor captain's bleeding!
[SANJI]
Why are they crawling again?
Can't they just carry him
like normal people?
You guys saved my life,
so I know you're not as bad
as they claim you are.
So take this chance
and get out of here!
Wait!
[NAMI] I think we'd
better take her advice.
When I was on the waver,
I saw it for myself.
An island filled with monsters!
Great, so you did
exactly what everyone
was hoping you wouldn't do.
You mean the place we were
told to never ever set foot on?
And there's monsters?
Whoa! Don't give 'im any ideas!
It's nothing to get
excited about, Luffy.
The last thing we need is
to get involved with this.
Regardless, we're
leaving, now let's go!
[SANJI] Ah, it'll break my
heart to be away from Conis,
but if that's what
Nami wants, so be it.
[NAMI]
If we stick around any longer,
Conis and Pagaya may get
in trouble because of us.
[USOPP]
That's true.
Those White Berets will charge
them as our accomplices!
If we can escape now on our own,
then it shouldn't cause
them any trouble, right?
After all, how can
they be helping us
when they're with that captain?
Okay, that's the plan. Let's go!
Luffy, what are you doing?
Why are we running away?
Because we're in trouble!
So what? We're
always in trouble.
It's not about just us anymore!
If we don't leave, Conis and
Pagaya could get arrested, too!
[LUFFY]
They haven't done anything.
Whoever arrests
them is an idiot.
I know that, but--
[CONIS]
Please. Please hurry.
The Blue Sea dwellers
will never escape!
[MCKINLEY laughs]
Can't you two argue on
the boat? Come on!
How many times do
I have to tell you?!
Staying here equals more
trouble for everybody!
We're in trouble no matter what.
[gasps]
[CONIS]
Save yourselves!
Please, go!
Ugh. Just great.
[MCKINLEY]
Be careful, miss.
If you say anything to
defend these criminals,
I will consider you and
your father accomplices.
These people must be punished
to the full extent of the law
for all the abusive language
and deplorable violence.
I find them guilty of
fifth degree crimes.
In the name of almighty Eneru,
you are banished to drift
in the clouds for eternity.
I told you, it was an accident!
Oh. Forget it.
Arrest them!
Just run! You can't win!
[MCKINLEY]
Fire the milky arrows!
[yelps]
Go, Nami! Run!
[NAMI]
Ya think?
What the heck?
Clouds?
[screams]
[MCKINLEY]
White Berets! Attack!
[WHITE BERETS chuckling]
Cool trick! Mind if I try?
[chuckles]
Attack!
These clouds are too fluffy!
I can barely run on 'em!
[yells]
Watch out!
Those fools. They think
they can get away from us?
Awesome. Are those cloud skates?
Nice!
[LUFFY]
I gotta get a pair of those!
Whoa!
You see his arm?
[CONIS]
Look! He's all stretchy!
I hope he's okay!
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
No way! Devil Fruit!
[LUFFY]
...Fireworks!
[WHITE BERETS yell]
[ZORO]
Piece of cake.
Nami! How's the money
situation looking?
[NAMI]
Fifty thousand Berries left!
[ZORO] Fifty thousand?
We're that broke?
[NAMI] Normally that'd last
us a day or two at most.
What's the deal?
Why are we so poor?
Listen up, everybody! Your
captain has something to say!
Everyone on my ship
needs to be more good
with money from now on!
So lead by example!
Huh?!
[USOPP sighs]
In any case,
the Fighting Formation B
I taught them to use
was successful.
There's that.
Really?
They defeated the White Berets.
Unbelievable!
At this altitude,
the athletic ability
of Blue Sea dwellers
usually decreases.
[laughs]
[MCKINLEY]
Those poor deluded fools.
[MCKINLEY] Sorry, criminals!
You have no chance of escape!
[SANJI]
Hm?
[MCKINLEY]
You should have behaved
and done what I told you to do.
Of all the upholders
of Law here in Skypiea,
we White Berets are
the most lenient.
However, they are not
nearly as forgiving!
[MCKINLEY laughs]
[MCKINLEY]
Congratulations!
You are now considered
second degree criminals.
You can try to cry for mercy...
[MCKINLEY laughs]
[MCKINLEY]
...but you will all be judged...
...by the Priests of Upper Yard!
Heso!
Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear-blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...
[NAMI]
That old lady ratted us out!
[LUFFY] You're not used to
that kinda thing by now?
Come on. Now, let's get
this adventure crackin'!
[NAMI] You still wanna
go to the Upper Yard.
[USOPP] Uh, hey, something's
wrong with the ship!
[ROBIN]
Our punishment has begun.
We can't stop what's
been set in motion.
[ZORO]
You mean Heaven's Judgment.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Is Escape Possible? God's
Challenge is Set in Motion."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!