[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[rumbling]
[LUFFY laughing]
[ZORO screaming]
[LUFFY]
Hey, Zoro!
[ZORO]
What...
...were you doing?!
What do you mean?
We're here to
pick up Nami. Duh!
Oh, yeah. And what about
Usopp and Johnny?
[ZORO]
Usopp! Oh, no!
C'mon, we gotta hurry!
[LUFFY]
Why, what's wrong?!
[ZORO] That dumbass has
been caught by Arlong!
We gotta hurry
before they kill him!
[JOHNNY]
He's already dead!
[ZORO]
What?!
[JOHNNY]
We're too late!
Big Bro Usopp is dead!
[grunts]
Nami... murdered him!
[LUFFY]
"Everyone's Gathered!
Usopp Speaks the
Truth About Nami!"
[YOSAKU]
You can't be serious!
[JOHNNY]
Yeah. It's true.
She was a traitor all along.
She's been winning
Arlong's favor
so she could
have the treasure buried
in Cocoyashi Village
all to herself!
That woman is just
a cold‐blooded killer.
She won't stop until
she gets what she wants.
Nami had us fooled the entire‐‐
[LUFFY]
Quiet!
Say another word
and you'll regret it!
Easy, Luffy.
This has nothing
to do with Johnny.
Go on, believe
whatever you want.
But I know what I saw!
Nami killed Big Bro Usopp!
[LUFFY] Shut your mouth!
Never in a million years
would Nami kill Usopp!
She wouldn't do that
to her friends!
[JOHNNY]
But‐But I saw it!
[NAMI] What was that
about friends, Luffy?
‐‐Nami!
‐‐What are you doing here?
[LUFFY]
What are we doing here?
You're our friend!
We came to get you.
‐‐[NAMI] What a pest.
‐‐[LUFFY] Nami?
Friends, huh?
Don't make me laugh.
You're just pathetic enough
to deserve each other.
Damn you!
You killed him!
I watched you do it!
And now...
Big Bro Usopp is gone!
Yep, that's right.
So why don't you kill me
and get your revenge?
[JOHNNY]
Eh‐‐ What?
[NAMI]
Word to the wise, fellas.
Because of your
"friend's" stupidity,
Arlong is preparing to kill Zoro
along with his entire crew.
And I don't care
how monstrously strong
you guys think you are,
you're no match
for the real monsters.
I promise you,
if you stay on this island,
you will die.
So, you have a choice to make
between life and death.
[ZORO grunts]
Her "heartless" face is so hot!
Hi, Nami! It's me Sanji!
Let's run away together!
Can it, Romeo! This isn't
the time or place for that!
Excuse me.
Love is like a hurricane,
so back off.
Hey, look at me
when I'm talking to you!
Nami, where is Usopp?
‐‐[NAMI] With the fishes.
‐‐[ZORO] Damn it! Cut the crap!
‐‐[SANJI grunts]
‐‐[ZORO grunts]
[SANJI] How sad,
a swordsman striking a lady.
Idiot! Can't you see
what's happening here?
Your starting to piss me off.
Heh. If someone had
stopped me that easily,
I'd be mad, too.
What?
You... should watch your mouth.
I'll say whatever
I want, bastard.
[YOSAKU]
Big Bros!
We're all in this
together, okay?
This is no time to fight!
Your pal's right.
Now quit your bickering
and leave while you still can.
You outsiders have no right
to butt into
this island's affairs.
Don't you get it yet?
The only reason
I got close to you idiots
was so that I could rob you
of everything you had.
But now that you're broke,
it looks like the dreams dead.
So go, take your ship.
Go on. Find a navigator
dumb enough to join you
and go to the Grand Line.
Continue on your quest to find
the One Piece or whatever.
Just leave here!
You're an eyesore!
[grunts]
[NAMI]
Goodbye now.
Nami...
[JOHNNY]
Big Bro Luffy!
‐‐Sleepy.
‐‐[JOHNNY] Sleep?!
[YOSAKU]
At a time like this?!
In the middle of the road?!
Well, I'm pretty tired.
I'm not gonna
butt into their affairs.
I'm not interested.
But I'm not leaving either.
‐‐[LUFFY] Night.
‐‐Huh?!
Uh‐‐ Big Bro?
[snoring]
[NAMI]
Fine.
Whatever!
Just go ahead and die!
Na‐‐!
‐‐[CHABO] C'mon! Hurry up!
‐‐[NOJIKO] What's the deal?!
[CHABO] The Marines
are here! We're saved!
Some survivors from Gosa managed
to contact the government
and they told 'em what happened!
Now the Marines
are here to rescue us all!
See?!
Finally! It's over!
Now we get to leave
this horrible place!
[PURINPURIN] So this is
the infamous Arlong Park!
What is the world coming to
when pirate scum
can set up
such an opulent base?!
[PURINPURIN]
Listen up, men!
Our noble mission today
is one of extraction!
We must rescue the survivors
of the town of Gosa,
which was savagely destroyed
by the Arlong Pirates!
But I am left to wonder...
Would our brand of
swift and terrible justice
allow us to simply overlook
the decadent fortress
of these unchecked brutes?!
[MARINES]
Sir, no sir!
[PURINPURIN] Correct!
Our unit must annihilate Arlong
and his men!
Prepare for battle at once!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
Is that right?
Marine branch 77?
That's right.
That's what I said.
A newcomer.
We'll have someone negotiate
with the man in charge.
If two million isn't enough
to keep them from
trying anything funny, then kill
every last one of them.
‐‐[distant thud]
‐‐[gasps]
[FISHMAN M] Oh, no!
The Marines have opened fire!
Arlong! Watch out!
Whoa. He crushed a cannonball.
Those jaws are terrifying!
So what now?
Are the talks...?
‐‐Canceled.
‐‐[FISHMEN cheer]
[FISHMAN M]
All right! Let's do it!
[FISHMAN I] I've been
waitin' for a good fight!
[FISHMAN E]
It's gonna be a bloodbath!
Choo. Hold on guys, not so fast.
There's no need
to expend so much energy
just to take out
the trash. Choo.
Just leave it to us!
What foolish humans they are
to pick a fight with us.
In our own waters, too.
Those Marines
don't stand a chance
against three of our leaders.
[laughs]
I doubt that ship will make it
a full three minutes!
[laughs]
[PURINPURIN]
That's odd.
[MARINE A] Commodore.
Seems that cannonball was a dud.
[PURINPURIN]
Fire another!
This is a signal
of open hostility!
Never drop your guard when
you're dealing with fishmen!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[MARINE A]
Man down!
[MARINE B]
It's one of them! Attack!
[PURINPURIN]
Stand down, right now!
One of Arlong's men, yes?
I am Commodore Purinpurin
of Marines branch number 77.
Allow me to elaborate.
You see we are a somewhat
well‐known elite marine unit.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you, fishman?
If you wish to live,
surrender immediately and‐‐
[MARINES]
Commodore!
‐‐What have you done to him?!
‐‐You killed him!
[MARINE B]
What's all this shaking?!
[MARINE D]
Don't tell me there are
fishmen under the ship!
[CHOO] I really am sorry to
inconvenience you like this,
but we just took the liberty
of removing your rudder.
Is that okay?
‐‐Uh! You what?
‐‐Commodore!
[CHOO]
Choo. Don't worry,
I didn't hit any
of his vital organs.
Commodore, I have a question.
It's just hypothetical
of course.
If one were to
move a large reef
directly into a strong current,
what do you suppose
would happen to the ocean?
[PURINPURIN]
What?!
No. Moving a whole reef?
That can't be done,
it's just not possible!
[KUROOBI]
Put it down over there, Hachi.
[HATCHAN]
Right!
[MARINE C]
Uh‐‐! Commodore!
[MARINE C] A giant whirlpool
has just appeared!
[MARINE D]
The rudder isn't working!
What?!
[CHOO] I told you.
We removed the rudder.
So now this rudderless ship
is headed straight... choo...
...to the sea floor.
[MARINES screaming]
They're dead.
That's right. And so is hope.
Time to face the truth.
There's no way to escape
Arlong's control.
I'll bet you're tired.
No, I didn't even
break a sweat.
We know everything
about these waters,
from the winds to the depths.
It was quite easy.
With our expert knowledge
of these waters,
no one can beat us.
True, but let's not
forget Nami's charts.
I checked those
before I moved the reef.
It even tells the flow
of current and everything!
Indeed. They are
excellent charts.
If we could persuade
Nami to do this
for all the world's oceans,
we would be the undisputed
rulers of the sea forever.
[ARLONG sighs]
I know. Nami's brilliant.
In fact, she could be
critical in the creation
of the Arlong Empire.
It's just a shame!
A shame?
[CHOO] He promised to let Nami
and Cocoyashi Village go
once she saves up
100 million berries.
Oh, no! Seriously?!
Whatever you do,
you can't let her leave!
You can't!
Say it ain't so, boss!
I have to!
That's was what we
agreed upon eight years ago!
I'm the kind of man
who will always
keeps my promises
when it comes to money.
Always.
[JOHNNY]
Hey! Big Bro Zoro!
What on Earth
are you thinking?! C'mon!
Did you forget that
Arlong is out to kill us?
We should be running away!
Now that we know
what Nami's really like,
there isn't a single
good reason why
we should stay on this island.
My reason for
staying here is there.
I'm staying 'cause he's staying.
[YOSAKU chuckles]
Don't be stupid, Big Bro Zoro!
Are you saying you want
to bring her back, too?
[ZORO] What I want
has nothing to do with this.
I don't decide who
the navigator is, he does.
Big Bro.
Right. Understood.
You're not leaving.
Sorry to cut our reunion short,
but I won't stay.
My role as guide ends here.
Yeah, I'm with him.
I don't want to deliberately
get myself killed.
Fine. I'll see ya around.
[JOHNNY]
Until we meet again, Big Bro!
[YOSAKU]
Take care you guys!
[ZORO]
You, too!
[snoring]
[SANJI]
Hey.
Well. What do you think it is?
Why was she crying?
[ZORO]
I don't know. Was she crying?
[SANJI]
She was in her heart.
Tch! If there were,
they were tears of guilt
for killing Usopp.
[SANJI]
Yeah, right. Are you serious?
You really are dense.
[ZORO]
Hm?
Do you still honestly believe
that Nami could've killed Usopp?
[USOPP]
When she did that...
[NAMI]
It's for my business.
This was my only choice.
[USOPP]
When she did that...
...Nami stabbed
her own hand
to make it look
like she stabbed me!
I can't believe
she did that for me!
But it's a good thing she did,
otherwise I'd be fish food
right now for sure!
But, what do I do?!
A manly man like me
can't just turn tail
and run after being saved!
One step at a time!
Right now I gotta hurry
and find Zoro!
Is that him up ahead?
It is! It's Zoro!
So Nami didn't kill him.
Is that what you're saying?
[SANJI]
Am I wrong?
Huh. Well who knows?
I always thought of her as
kind of a small time crook
who wouldn't even watch
a guy die, let alone kill him.
But maybe she just snapped.
Wait. What'd you say?
She's not small time!
[ZORO]
Is she all you think about?!
[USOPP groans]
‐‐[USOPP groans]
‐‐[SANJI] He's alive.
‐‐[ZORO] Well, he was.
I hope he still is.
Usopp!
Did Nami do all this to you?!
Sorry. Zoro and I did that.
No, you did!
Luffy. You're here now.
Yep. Sure am.
I'm here, too. Hi there.
[USOPP] One of
these days I'll kill you.
Oh! You just made
a full recovery!
[USOPP]
Shut up!
Oh, and by the way,
we kinda heard you were dead.
Killed by Nami.
‐‐[USOPP] Huh?
‐‐Stupid Johnny!
He was spouting nonsense
that entire time!
Well, in a way...
it is the truth.
But, I'm alive...
'cause you see,
she actually saved my life.
[sighs]
[distant clanging]
Jeez, Nami. You sure know
how to trash a place.
Hey. What's wrong?
[NAMI] Nothing. I'm just
resting a little, that's all.
You mean to tell me that
pouring over a treasure map
after wrecking a house
is how you relax?
You're not fooling me.
Now fess up already.
What's bothering you?
[NAMI] Something happened
to make me mad. It's nothing.
[NOJIKO exhales]
Those guys? Who are they?
You know?
Yeah. I met some captain guy.
He seemed kind of
liar‐ish though.
Nami, I heard that
you smiled with them.
We both know
that's rare for you.
As a matter of fact,
I haven't seen you
smile in years.
C'mon. Tell me
who these guys are!
It's okay. You can
tell me anything, remember?
[NAMI] I had planned...
to forget about them.
♪
[NAMI] I thought I could
just erase them from my mind.
And I'm out!
Aw, man! You gotta be kidding!
How did you win again?
And Luffy, how come you have
so many cards in your hand?
I don't know.
Seems like more is better.
Idiot! Learn the rules
like everybody else!
[LUFFY]
All right, here's the rules!
The one with the most wins!
[NAMI] But the more I tried to
erase them...
...the more I remembered.
[LUFFY screaming]
Holy crap! We sprung a leak!
[NAMI]
Hurry up and fix it!
[LUFFY]
Leave it to me guys!
[USOPP]
No! Stop flailing around!
[USOPP yells]
[NAMI screaming]
[NAMI] The truth is,
when I was with them,
the only thing I forgot about
was the pain that I bear.
Don't you have any honor?!
Those men are your friends!
[NAMI] If it were possible,
I'd join up with those guys
and sail around the world.
Now I see.
Yeah, that would hit her hard.
To think that someone
actually showed up for her.
[NAMI]
Friends.
That word... means pain.
It breaks her heart.
So that's it. That's how
Nami pretended to kill me
and make sure I could
escape from Arlong Park.
Looks to me like she's got
some sorta hidden motive
for hangin' out with
a bunch of renegade fishmen.
‐‐Obviously.
‐‐Fine. What next?
We gonna destroy Arlong Park?
[USOPP]
Whoa! Hang on just a second!
Don't you think
we'd better find out
what's going on with Nami first?
[NOJIKO]
It's no use either way.
No matter what you guys do,
Arlong's rule
won't come to an end.
[USOPP]
Nojiko.
[LUFFY]
Who's she?
Nami's big sister.
What?! Nami's sister.
No wonder she's so hot!
What do you mean that
"it's no use"?
Just trust me.
Don't get yourselves involved
in what's going on here.
And leave poor Nami alone.
I'll explain the situation.
‐‐Situation?
‐‐Do you mean that you can
tell us why she joined up
with Arlong's group?
[NOJIKO] Yeah. And if that
doesn't get you to leave,
I don't know what will.
'Kay. So tell us all about it.
I gotta admit, I'm curious.
‐‐I'll pass.
‐‐Hey, wait!
[LUFFY]
I don't care about her past.
[SANJI]
Where are you going, Luffy?
[LUFFY]
For a walk.
[USOPP]
A walk?!
Do you mean you're not
gonna listen to this?!
[LUFFY]
Nope.
Who's he?
[ZORO] Don't mind him.
That's just how he is.
We'll hear you out.
Though I can tell you right now,
I don't think it's
gonna change anything.
Well, I'll listen too.
It might help me make
some sense out of everything
that's going on around here.
Me too! I wanna know
all about her!
[snoring]
Now    h asleep.
Hey, you said
you'd hear her out!
Mm. I see.
This is why it was hard for her.
[VILLAGER A] Look, there's
a Marine ship at the shore!
[VILLAGER B]
It's branch 16's ship!
Maybe headquarters
is finally taking action
after what happened
to branch 77!
[NEZUMI chuckles]
I'm Colonel Nezumi of branch 16.
Now then. Genzo please step up.
And make it snappy.
[GENZO] Yes, Colonel.
I'm the one you're looking for.
[NEZUMI] You, huh?
Take me to Nami's house at once!
[GENZO]
Nami? But why?
I don't understand
what's going on, colonel.
Lead the way. That is
all you'll need to do.
[NOJIKO]
From the beginning then.
[running footsteps]
[NOJIKO] It all goes back
to eight years ago.
[BOTH laughing]
[NOJIKO]
Up until that day,
when we were still
little children.
She lived here in the village.
Nami and I will never forget her
as long as we live.
Her name is Bellemere.
All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way
[SANJI] Bellemere!
What a beautiful girl's name!
How I'd love to meet her!
[LUFFY] Hey, are Bellemeres
yummy or what?
[SANJI]
It's not food!
It's the person
Nami will never forget!
Meaning she could be Nami's...
[ZORO]
Shut up! I can't sleep!
[USOPP]
Are you guys even serious
about listening to Nojiko?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Untold Past!
Female Warrior Bellemere!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!