Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison Impel Down,
Now at Level 4,
the Burning Heat Hell,
Warden Magellan
has ambushed him.
[MAGELLAN]
And one final thing,
I will find out exactly how
you broke into my prison.
You will spill every last,
juicy detail to me.
[LUFFY]
I'll die before I say a word.
Don't do it!
[BON CLAY groaning]
You can't!
Why did you--?
[BOTH grunting]
Don't get in my way!
Didn't you hear me?
You can't fight him!
Listen, if you touch
that poison anywhere,
it'll be the last thing you do!
Down the Venom Road!
Try as you might.
You won't escape from me!
--[LUFFY sneezes]
--[MAGELLAN grunts]
[BON CLAY]
Warden Magellan guards
the most dangerous criminals
in the most infamous prison
in the entire world!
He's the lord and
master of hell itself!
You're not going to let Straw
Boy face him all alone, are you?
[whimpering]
Forgive me!
[BON CLAY] I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen!
Running is the only answer!
I'm sorry, Straw Boy!
I'm a coward! Forgive me!
[MAGELLAN]
I suggest you put an end
to this nonsense and submit.
[LUFFY] And I'm not gonna let
you execute him, you hear me?
[LUFFY]
I'm not getting anywhere.
I can't win
without touching you.
I'll make a sacrifice.
You can take my arms,
but I won't lose!
Now Gum-Gum!
Jet Bazooka!
[groaning]
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY]
"The Showdown Has Come!
Luffy's Desperate Last Attack!"
[GUARDS groaning]
[sighs]
Morons.
What's wrong with you two?
[HANNYABAL] If you had just
slipped away when I told you to,
I could'ave blamed
this mess on the warden!
We're at the staircase
to Level 3.
There was a raid
by two of the escapees.
We've got some casualties here.
Yes, that's right, we have Buggy
the Clown and Mr. 3 in custody.
[MR. 3, BUGGY groaning]
[HANNYABAL] You wanted
to go through the gate,
I said "fine," but
you wouldn't believe me!
Ruin my plan!
Ugh. Ow. He's a hell of a lot
stronger than he looks.
Damn Hannyabal!
I don't wanna be tortured.
If that's what's
in store for me,
I'm gonna bite off my tongue.
I'm serious. Here I go.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm really gonna do it.
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY screaming]
[MAGELLAN growling]
[BON CLAY yelling]
Oh, he's coming!
[BON CLAY] Get out of my way!
I said move it, you fools!
[GUARDS yelping]
[BON CLAY]
If you don't wanna get hurt,
then move! Let me through!
Mr. 2 is about to attack!
Get him!
I'm not pulling your tail!
You asked for it!
[GUARDS gasping]
[BON CLAY]
Drunken Swan Soiree!
[GUARDS screaming]
[footsteps]
[crying]
[BON CLAY] There's no way
we can beat Magellan!
I'm not gonna dream
an impossible dream!
If I'd remained
there any longer,
I'm 200% sure
he would have killed me!
Don't look back!
Just keep running!
[BON CLAY]
The only thing I can do is run!
Straw Boy!
[panting]
It would seem you have
brought me to my knees, boy.
Even a cornered rabbit
will fight with teeth and claws.
[LUFFY groaning]
But now, your hands and arms
are covered in my poison.
That's enough to affect
your entire body.
[MAGELLAN]
You're feeling the pain.
I know you are.
[LUFFY yelling]
Give up already.
Now, Gum-Gum!
Twin Jet Pistol!
Venom!
Blowfish!
Hm?
[LUFFY grunts]
See how you like this!
Gum-Gum!
Hydra!
[LUFFY]
Jet Pistol!
Not even a scratch.
[groaning]
[hissing]
[LUFFY gasps]
Fog?
Venom Cloud.
[gasps]
[coughing]
Damn!
It's no use. That poison fog
is a part of me.
[coughing]
It lives and breathes.
[LUFFY coughing]
[MAGELLAN laughing]
[MAGELLAN]
Vision getting blurry?
Are your ears ringing?
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum.
Balloon!
I said, it's no use.
Why can't you see that?
[LUFFY groaning]
There's no escape.
You have already been condemned.
[MAGELLAN] Your hands have
become useless, haven't they?
[LUFFY groaning]
In time, my poison...
will take everything from you.
[LUFFY groaning]
[groaning]
'Kay! I'm about to do it!
I'm gonna bite my tongue off,
and none of you can stop me.
[whimpering]
I just can't do it!
Damn it all!
[BUGGY, MR. 3 crying]
Take them away.
Sir!
[HANNYABAL sighs]
[HANNYABAL]
What a waste.
Please, stop it!
--Have mercy!
--[MR. 3] No fair!
Torture stinks!
[BUGGY]
It stinks like ass!
[MR. 3]
Yeah, like that!
Hold it right there, chumps!
[ALL]
Huh?
Hey,
who's that?
I know that voice. He's here!
[GUARDS]
Huh?
Now, Swan Arabesque!
[GUARDS yelping]
[BUGGY, MR. 3 screaming]
Hey! Just who are you?
That guy!
It's Mister 2!
That man's the other escapee!
[GUARDS yelling]
[GUARDS yelping]
I've had enough!
[grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
Take this, and this, and this,
and this, and this, and this.
[BON CLAY] Un, deux, trois! Un,
deux, trois! Un, deux, trois!
And that, and that,
and that, and that!
[BON CLAY] Deux, trois!
Un, deux, trois! Un!
[growls]
[HANNYABAL] I admit,
you're quick on your feet,
but I think you'll find
I'm quite persistent.
[yelps]
[HANNYABAL]
What?
[NAMI]
Hey, big boy.
Aren't you a cutie!
What're you doing
way over there?
[LUFFY groaning]
[MAGELLAN] You just
don't know when to quit.
Rescuing your brother
really means that much to you?
[groaning]
--[LUFFY groaning]
--[thudding]
[LUFFY groaning]
The sooner you stop
this nonsense,
the sooner I end your suffering.
[LUFFY]
Now, Gum-Gum Pistol!
[gasps]
[yells]
[groaning]
Hey, jailer!
Wanna do a condemned
man a favor?
Tell me, is something happening
on the upper levels?
No, not a thing.
[inaudible]
[ACE grunts]
[LUFFY groaning]
This is pointless. Hopeless!
You have no right!
Your brother is
a notorious criminal
who will face his execution,
and rightfully so.
You are an intruder
who has waged open war
on the World Government.
You've wronged this world
and you must pay.
The law demands
Ace's death in Marineford,
and so it shall have it.
Do not mistake
your misguided attempt
at rescuing him for justice!
[LUFFY growling]
That's enough!
[ACE]
Luffy, please... stay away.
It's not worth it!
[LUFFY yelling]
[yelling continues]
This is sad to watch.
[panting]
Now Gum-Gum Stamp!
[LUFFY groaning]
Are you finally done?
[LUFFY growling]
[LUFFY panting]
[MAGELLAN]
Hm?
[LUFFY panting]
Now, Second Gear!
[LUFFY yelling]
[MAGELLAN]
Hmm.
Hydra!
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY grunts]
[yelling]
[LUFFY]
I want... my brother!
[LUFFY yells]
Consider this
your punishment, child.
There's no way to neutralize
the amount of poison
your body has absorbed.
You will suffer
in agonizing pain for 24 hours,
and then you will die.
This is true hell.
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY]
A...
A-Ace...
[NARRATOR]
After losing to Magellan,
Luffy's imprisoned on Level 5.
Even though he knows
the warden's poison has no cure.
Bon Clay rushes to his friend's
aid, betting on a distant hope.
However, before
he can reach him,
a pack of Army Wolves
blocks his advance.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"For His Friend! Bon Clay's
Deadly Rescue Attempt."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!