Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
The Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
seeking a coating mechanic to
help them reach Fishman Island.
But the man they met,
Silvers Rayleigh,
was also the former Vice-Captain
of the Roger Pirates.
Luffy and his crew
went into town to hide
while Rayleigh coated the Sunny.
Meanwhile, Admiral Kizaru,
an operative dispatched
from Navy Headquarters,
had already arrived
at the archipelago in
search of those responsible
for threatening the
Celestial Dragons.
[KIZARU]
Hello?
This is Admiral Kizaru.
Hm. That's odd.
Hello?
Now. Take this!
No, wait! Stop!
[KIZARU]
Hello?
[NARRATOR]
Fierce battles between the Navy
and the rookie pirates
erupted all over Sabaody.
Whoa, it grew!
[MARINES scream]
What the hell just happened?
He didn't even have
to lift a finger!
[KIZARU] Well, if I can't
find him, that leaves me
with a bit of
spare time, you see.
And if I have some spare
time, I obviously can't
let a wanted man escape.
Especially one with a
249 million berry bounty,
"Magician" Basil Hawkins.
Speed is weight. Observe.
This is what it feels like to be
kicked at the speed of light.
[HAWKINS PIRATES gasp]
Captain!
Huh?
What was that?
[HAWKINS]
Impressive.
You far surpassed
what I imagined.
[NARRATOR] And then, yet
another "Bartholomew Kuma"
appeared before Luffy
and the others.
[USOPP]
Get back, Luffy!
[NAMI] He's one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
He is? How do you
guys know that?
Luffy! Don't let that attack
hit you! It's a shockwave!
[LUFFY gasps]
Damn!
[NAMI] What is this?
[USOPP] Great!
So he can do this crap too?
Hey! You lied! That
wasn't a shockwave!
[LUFFY]
All right. Second Gear!
We know he's
strong, no question.
So let's go all-out
from the very start!
[ZORO]
Something's off here.
He seems different from
the last time we met.
[SENTOMARU]
It's chaos already.
He'd better hurry.
[LUFFY yelling]
Or there won't be
any rookies left.
Well, certainly not
at this rate, I'd think.
[LUFFY]
Overwhelming!
The Navy's Fighting
Weapons, the Pacifistas!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY panting]
[FRANKY]
Damn, this guy is unreal.
[USOPP] He can shoot those beams
from his hand and his mouth!
[BROOK whimpers]
[USOPP]
Here it comes again! Crap!
Run!
[ALL yelling]
[ALL panting]
Son of a-- the hell is he
shooting us with anyway?
[USOPP]
They're beams, obviously!
[FRANKY] That would be pretty
kickass if it were true,
but that tech
doesn't even exist!
It's just fantasy!
Wait. What are you
doing over there?
[BROOK]
I'm playing dead. See?
[FRANKY, USOPP] He already
knows that's not true!
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY grunts]
[ZORO]
Three-Sword Style!
Alright! Now, Gum-Gum...
How about some Diable?
[SANJI] Mouton!
[LUFFY] Jet!
[ZORO]
600 Caliber!
[ALL yell]
[SANJI yells]
[ZORO growls]
[LUFFY growls]
[ALL yelling, grunting]
[panting]
Yes! Way to go!
They took him down!
Those three are
just too awesome!
Don't forget, he's
one of the Warlords.
It'll take a lot more
than that to beat him.
And judging by their faces,
they know that, too.
So he's different now?
Well, then maybe he's
a twin or something.
It's possible, but
that's a scary thought.
They look the same,
but they're different.
The real one would have
teleported to dodge our attacks.
[ZORO] And he doesn't use
that shockwave attack.
He doesn't have
those paws, either.
[SANJI]
Well, he's plenty strong as-is.
And what's worse...
The real one might
be after us as well.
Well done. You gave
me quite a beating.
Heh. But I'm not just bigger
now, I'm much stronger, too!
Retribution!
[UROUGE grunting]
I bet you felt that
one, didn'tcha?
The Mad Monk Urouge
may have escaped death
countless times before reaching
this place, but no matter
how strong he grows,
he cannot escape his fate.
[UROUGE groans]
[DRAKE growls]
[UROUGE]
It burns!
[UROUGE groaning]
That was Kizaru's laser!
[DRAKE] So, he recreated
Kizaru's attacks while using
Bartholomew Kuma's body?
Damn that Vegapunk.
I had no idea the
Pacifista technology
had advanced so quickly.
[DRAKE]
It's one hell of a show.
You've gotta admit that.
Indeed. But a Warlord
and an Admiral, friend?
Not even three pirates
with bounties over
100 million can handle that!
[UROUGE groans]
Is that Rear Admiral Drake?
Sorry, former Rear Admiral.
Not here for your old
job back, I take it.
[KIZARU] Or perhaps you'd
like to test the Pacifista?
I'm afraid your inside
knowledge will only
make your despair
all the greater.
Also, I suggest
you little chickies
exercise a level of caution.
After all, you have me
to contend with too.
[ALL grunt]
Hot damn, this fight just
delivers one crazy thing
after another! It's a
rare ancient Zoan type!
I've never seen one before!
[DINOSAUR roars]
[DINOSAUR roaring]
[DRAKE groans]
[DRAKE chuckles]
[DRAKE]
Imagine that.
You bleed red blood
just like the rest of us.
I'm surprised.
[UROUGE] A truly rare
sight! I'm speechless.
[KIZARU]
As I was just saying:
you have to contend
with me, too.
[UROUGE grunts]
Now ain't that something. You
Supernovas are a strange bunch.
Every one of you turns
into some scary monster.
Demon Face!
[HAWKINS]
He's gone!
[HAWKINS gasps]
[HAWKINS groans]
My eyes!
Captain Hawkins, run!
Get out of there!
[HAWKINS]
I... I can't see!
[HAWKINS grunting]
[KIZARU] I don't know
what your power is,
but I do know you
have a physical form.
It doesn't seem like
you're a Logia type.
[HAWKINS grunting]
Captain Hawkins!
He doesn't have any more
voodoo dolls to protect him!
He can't take any more of this!
[KIZARU] Looks like
you're the first to go.
[HAWKINS grunts]
[KIZARU] You did well to journey
all this way and for that,
you have my compliments.
[cymbols crashing]
Huh?
[jazz music playing]
[APOO]
Yo, people!
Who might this be?
And what is he doing?
[cymbols crashing]
Huh?
[jazz music playing]
[APOO]
Yo, people!
Yo!, Yo-yo-yo! Yeah!
Yo! Is this music reaching you?
If you can hear it, stay tuned!
Navy Admiral Kizaru!
[APOO]
Yeah. Yo-yo-yo.
So he's the one.
He's the "Sea Roar".
[APOO]
Fighting music, kickin' it live!
C'mon. Scratch!
[KIZARU]
Huh?
What is this all about?
[APOO]
Here we go!
[KIZARU]
Huh...
Check it out!
[BOTH grunt]
[APOO laughs]
Gotcha!
Though, knowing you
Navy Admirals, you'll probably
be right back up in a second.
Glad I hung
around for a bit--
this was a sight to see.
I guess it's time for me
to scram. Peace out!
Hoo! How terrible.
[KIZARU sighs]
That one was quite the shock!
[APOO]
Po-po-po-po-pow!
[KIZARU]
I'll use the Yata Mirror.
[APOO]
What the--?
[APOO gasps]
[DRAKE gasps]
[HAWKINS gasps]
[HAWKINS groans]
[HAWKINS grunting]
[HAWKINS PIRATES gasping]
[HAWKINS grunts]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[KIZARU] Hello?
[TRASPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[KIZARU] That's odd. Hello?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[HAWKINS pants, groans]
[KIZARU]
Ah, here it is.
This is Borsalino.
[SENTOMARU]
What the heck, Uncle?
You do have a baby
transponder snail!
Why didn't you contact me?
[KIZARU]
Huh? Oh! Is that you, Sentomaru?
[SENTOMARU] Don't give me that
"Is that you?" business!
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I tried contacting you before,
but I couldn't get
a hold of you.
Don't tell me you
were trying to talk
into the black
transponder snail again.
Huh?
[SENTOMARU] I've told you
before: the black one
on your wrist is for
eavesdropping! Remember?
[KIZARU]
Oh, that's right.
[SENTOMARU]
Ugh. It's fine, forget it.
It's time to get to work now.
It seems the culprits
have split up.
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain
Eustass Kid, and Trafalgar Law.
Which one do we start with?
Huh. Split up.
In that case, well...
[LUFFY panting]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
108-Caliber Phoenix!
[SANJI]
Concasser!
[ZORO]
108-Caliber...
[ZORO gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO groaning]
[ZORO groanig]
What the hell are you
doing? Snap out of it!
[ZORO grunting]
Zoro!
Hey, Zoro! What's the
matter with you?
How are you already hurt
so bad? We just started!
Look, just forget about
him for now, Luffy.
We're all screwed if we
can't beat this thing.
Yeah, right.
[ZORO grunting, coughing]
[SANJI] He hasn't had the chance
to recover from last time.
Standing up to him at all must
be pretty damned painful.
That look on his face tells me
everything I need to know.
This bastard wants us
dead, but if he's not
Bartholomew Kuma,
who the hell is he?
Either way, we don't
have time for this crap.
If we don't get out of here,
we're gonna be even
worse off than we are now.
[ZORO panting]
[SENTOMARU]
I am the most well-guarded
and tight-lipped man alive.
Nobody can break down
my impenetrable defenses.
[USOPP]
Who are you?
[SENTOMARU]
Ha!
A secret I shall take to the
grave with me, if I must!
But if you really must
know, you may call me...
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
"An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle
Axe-Carrying Sentomaru."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!