[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other instead.
Meanwhile, to reach Yuba,
the location of the rebel army,
Luffy's group set out
into the desert,
where they faced numerous
unimaginable hardships!
[LUFFY]
"Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely!"
Ugh... So hot. Water.
[CHOPPER] Thanks, Zoro.
This heat is too much for me.
[ZORO] Don't blame
yourself. It's stifling.
[SANJI]
Nami! Where have you gone?
I even love you when you
abandon me in the desert!
[USOPP]
Huh?
What's wrong, Luffy?
[USOPP]
Eh?
[NAMI] This is a lot easier
thanks to you, Eyelash!
[VIVI] But are the others
going to be all right?
Of course, all they have to
do is follow our footprints!
Tsunami! A tsunami is coming!
[SANJI]
What is it now?
[ZORO]
What's the matter, Luffy?
Maybe it wasn't really
such a good idea.
[CHOPPER]
What wasn't a good idea?
I warned him,
but he didn't listen.
He said he was so thirsty
he couldn't stand it anymore,
so he chomped down on some of
that cactus growing back there
to suck out the moisture.
[ZORO]
Cactus?
Yep, right there.
Those round things.
[LUFFY]
A tsunami!
Ah! You gotta be kidding!
Those are mezcal cacti;
they're used to make
hallucinogenic drugs!
What?
[LUFFY screaming]
Look out! We're gonna drown!
Right! Bring it on
if you got the guts!
I'll beat you all up!
[LUFFY yelling]
Oh, crap.
Gum‐Gum...
[USOPP, CHOPPER screaming]
Heh. Knock‐out!
[SANJI]
Way to go, Chopper.
Luffy. Hey, do you
see Nami anywhere?
[ACE]
What the‐‐?!
[USOPP] Damn! They must
be miles away by now!
[SANJI] Yeah, and their
footprints are disappearing.
[ZORO]
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Ace
for a while either.
[USOPP] Oh, great.
When did he disappear?
I betcha he got
separated from us.
Sorry. My big brother's
kind of a flake.
[ZORO, SANJI, USOPP shouting]
[SANJI]
What is it, Usopp?
Did you guys hear something?
[SANJI, ZORO]
Hm?
[rumbling]
[ALL]
A pirate ship?
Hey, guys! Bad news!
Nami and Vivi have
been captured!
Oh, and the camel too.
What?!
[LUFFY yelling]
[ZORO]
Are you crazy?!
[USOPP]
Hey! Luffy!
Damn! We better go after him!
[USOPP, SANJI]
Right!
[ALL yelling]
Gum‐Gum...
...give me water!
[USOPP]
He was just after water?
I'm exhausted.
[SAND PIRATES scream]
Strange, I thought
I heard something.
You asked for it.
[LUFFY]
Okay, that was my bad.
I was just so thirsty,
I must've miscalculated.
By the way, do you
have some water?
Hold on a sec,
are you saying you didn't
come here to rescue us?
Hey, I was really thirsty,
what can I tell ya?
Well, you've got
to do something!
They're going to eat Eyelash!
You're kidding.
You can eat him?
Huh?
[BARBAROSSA] We, the Barbar
Sand Pirates, have a saying!
Saying?
With the exception of friends,
there's nothing alive in the
desert that can't be eaten!
Ha‐ha! Right on!
I even eat stuff
straight off the ground!
[BARBAROSSA]
Ugh.
You'll get sick!
Hey, I'm careful!
[laughs]
You're a funny little squirt!
You're pretty funny yourself!
Okay, let's eat!
How's that?!
[BARBAROSSA laughs]
[BARBAROSSA]
I am Barbarossa,
captain of the
Barbar Sand Pirates!
And your name's Luffy, huh?
Please let me apologize
for being so rough
with your friends here.
It's just that we're all so
hungry, we got carried away.
[LUFFY laughs]
Aw, I don't mind at all!
Thanks for your concern!
There's a problem, Captain.
I've searched the ship's
stores from top to bottom,
and there just isn't enough
spare lumber on board
for us to repair the main mast.
And without a main mast,
this ship isn't gonna
be going anywhere.
[SAND PIRATES]
Yeah! Yeah! What do we do?
If we don't do something soon,
we're gonna wind up
dying like dogs
in the middle of this desert!
[SAND PIRATES] We're gonna die
like dogs! This is the end!
The Barbar Sand Pirates
are gonna die!
We sand pirates are born
right here on our ships,
and we'll die here as well!
A true sand pirate would never
think of abandoning ship!
[SAND PIRATES]
Yeah! Yay us!
We'll die right
here in our ship!
We'll die like dogs in our ship!
[SAND PIRATES laughing]
[USOPP]
Who are these guys?
The mast's destruction
was an act of fate!
And we sand pirates
will never do anything
to defy the flow of the sand!
You can't say I didn't warn you.
Hm?
[BARBAROSSA] Fate aside, there
is timber at the Meriyasu Oasis.
[LUFFY]
Huh? And where's that?
I'll be glad to dash
over and get it!
[BARBAROSSA]
Hmm... Bad idea.
The sands have changed lately.
It's too dangerous
for outsiders.
[LUFFY] I caused this.
I'll take care of it!
[BARBAROSSA laughs]
All right! You're on!
You can use this sand sled
to bring back the lumber.
[NAMI] It looks more like
a canoe than a sled to me.
Zaba and Rasa will
show you the oasis.
They'll be your guides.
Huh?
[BARBAROSSA] Rasa is the best
sand‐sledder on the ship.
These sleds carry two.
Who'll you take?
Hey, don't worry,
I'll be fine alone!
[USOPP]
Oh, come on now!
This is no time to get cocky!
[SANJI] It looks like
it might be tough going.
You want me to come along?
[screams]
[ALL]
Huh?
[BARBAROSSA]
Very impressive, Rasa.
[RASA] These others,
they seem like outlanders,
but you're from here.
Whoa. How could she tell?
[RASA] I'll wager you've
had some experience
with a sand sled.
Which means you'll
come along with us.
No way! It's much too
dangerous for Vivi to go!
Yeah! She stays!
All right. I'll be glad to go.
[LUFFY]
Huh, so these travel on sand?
How does it work?
[VIVI] I'll pilot the sled.
I did it once long ago.
[LUFFY] It's not too
different from a ship.
This goes here, right?
[LUFFY screams]
[BARBAROSSA]
Huh?
Okay, I'm back!
[SANJI, USOPP, NAMI] Will you
let Vivi handle the sled
from now on?
You take it easy there,
Luffy, all right?
Now, let's see...
[VIVI screams]
Zaba! Let's go!
Ready, Rasa!
Yahoo‐ee! Ha!
This is loads of fun!
We should borrow one of these;
we'd get to Yuba real fast!
[VIVI] I don't know.
Sand sleds are hard to control.
Believe me, they're
not easily mastered!
Then how is it you got
so good at it so quick?
I used to have one.
I got it way back when
I was just a little girl!
I'd ride it all the time.
Oh.
[CHOPPER]
But what are we supposed to do
while we're waiting for them?
We can always eat the camel.
[SAND PIRATES]
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
[SANJI, USOPP]
Second!
I'm just kidding!
[SAND PIRATES]
Aww...
Didn't sound like you
were kidding to me.
[LUFFY, VIVI scream]
[LUFFY]
You guys! What's the big idea?
Hey, Rasa! What are you doing?
[BOTH yelling]
[LUFFY]
Hey, Vivi!
We're getting pulled
even farther in!
[VIVI]
It's quicksand!
If we get pulled in all the way,
we'll never get back out!
Rasa, wasn't that going too far?
[RASA]
If she's lucky,
that spoiled little
princess will be fine.
Huh? It sounds as if
you know that girl!
Yeah. I'll never forget her.
[LUFFY]
Can you bring her around, Vivi?
I can't! It looks like
we're done for!
[VIVI]
This is it, Luffy!
No! Watch out!
Gum‐Gum...
[NAMI]
Despite how he seems,
you can always count
on Luffy in a pinch.
Well, I'm more concerned about
the fickleness of the desert.
The fickleness of the desert?
Yeah.
The desert can shift
moods in an instant.
A slight change in the weather
or people's hearts
will affect it greatly.
A change in people's hearts?
Huh? What's that?
Captain, it's them!
They've found us!
Off the starboard side!
Battle stations, everyone!
[SAND PIRATES shouting]
Do you wanna get
in my way, too, pal?
There must be hundreds!
Who are they?
[BARBAROSSA]
They're desert bandits!
A desperate band of vermin
who are always attacking us!
Conflict seems to be
in the air today.
Everyone in the desert
seems to be on edge.
[laughing]
Now that you can't run away,
we've finally got you
where we want you!
Hear me, men!
Don't let a single one of
these desert rats escape!
[SAND PIRATES]
Yeah!
Go pirates!
Yes, hooray. Go pirates.
[BARBAROSSA] The desert has
pitted us against each other!
Now we will see who
the desert will favor.
At last, we will end this.
Let the desert decide
who will be victorious!
[laughs]
Fool! Fool!
The desert will never
choose one such as you!
[USOPP]
Hm?
What's that?
[SAND PIRATE H]
Grand Dung Beetle!
[SAND PIRATE I]
It's a Grand Dung Beetle!
What's a Grand Dung Beetle?
Beats the hell outta me.
[BARBAROSSA]
They're desert bugs that haul
enormous balls of dung.
Over a hundred people
a year are squished
by their rolling
balls of manure.
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[BANDIT LEADER laughs]
Captain!
That huge ball of excrement
is headed right for us!
[growls]
[BARBAROSSA]
Leave it to me!
[yells]
[ALL scream]
[SAND PIRATES yelling]
[ZORO]
I'll take this!
Thank you, my friends.
[laughs]
[BANDIT LEADER] We'll let
you off easy this time!
Your lives are spared for now!
What a screwball.
[ZABA] Rasa! If that was
a joke, it wasn't funny!
They're not following!
[RASA]
Fine by me!
I'm not gonna wait
around for her.
If she can't keep up, it's not
our job to look for her!
Hope you weren't waiting long!
[laughing]
[LUFFY] This whole oasis
is covered in sand.
[VIVI] Once it was a
flourishing city, but now...
[LUFFY]
Have you been here before?
[VIVI]
Yes.
The people of this city gave me
a small sand sled as a memento.
[VIVI] It was a very long
time ago, though.
I stopped here once with
my father when I was little,
when he was traveling
around the country.
[RASA] And I've been
waiting all this time.
Back then, the king made
this town a promise.
"If anything should
happen to this oasis,
I will come rushing to help.
The kingdom won't ignore any
voice, no matter how small."
[VIVI]
Then, you were that girl!
[RASA] Eventually, this
oasis was buried in sand
and abandoned.
Every last person in
town left... but not me.
I stayed behind and
waited for you.
I believed in you.
But... the king never came.
And neither did you.
But that's‐‐ The same
thing was happening
to towns and cities
all over the country,
and the king was busy every day
trying to deal with
a nation‐wide crisis!
I don't wanna
hear your excuses!
For years, I waited for you all
alone in an abandoned city
in the middle of
a trackless desert!
Finally, I couldn't even
tell the difference
between dawn and dusk.
By the time Barbarossa took me
in, I couldn't feel anything.
Not the scorching heat
of the midday sun,
or the freezing cold of night.
The fact that I was
still alive baffled me.
But the king's promise continued
to ring inside my head.
[RASA] To this day,
I don't understand it.
Life was so difficult,
and I was all by myself,
so what exactly
was I waiting for?
Just what was it that kept me
going for all those hard years?
Was it hatred? Anger?
Was I too stubborn or
stupid to give up hope?
Why did I stay here?
Somebody tell me!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I made you wait.
[BARBAROSSA]
They sure ran off in a hurry.
It's really too bad.
It would've been nice
to steal all of their
food and water first.
[NAMI] I guess sand pirates
have it rough too.
[BARBAROSSA] Every living
thing in this desert
has it the same way.
You know, long ago,
I used to feel that the desert
belonged to everybody,
but when I think
about it nowadays,
I've begun to think that that
was somewhat conceited.
When I look at the desert now,
I wonder if perhaps it doesn't
really belong to anybody at all.
That's why we can
live here freely.
It belongs to no one,
and so is free itself.
Like the ocean?
[BARBAROSSA]
That's a good question.
I suspect that's something
you'll have to find
out yourselves.
There it is! We're here!
[ACE]
Luffy!
Where are you?
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[NAMI] Hey, Luffy!
Where's your brother?
[LUFFY]
Beats me!
[SANJI] You mean he's worse
at directions than this guy?
[ZORO] Shut up! Don't you
have cooking to do, pervert?
[SANJI]
If the shoe fits, blade boy.
[ACE]
Hey! I got food and water!
[USOPP]
You do? How?
[ACE]
Got it from the rebel army!
[VIVI]
What did you say?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"False Fortitude! Camu,
Rebel Soldier at Heart!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!