Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] After leading
the Straw Hat Pirates
into their trap,
the bounty hunters
began to make their move.
[laughing]
A total bounty
of over 600 million.
Hurry up and show them to me!
Don't get a chance
like this every day.
[CAMPACINO] A toast!
To our beloved Papa, Don Accino,
and to the rest of the
Accino Family, as well!
May fortune bless us all!
And to the present
for our Papa...
...the bounty of the Straw Hats!
[ALL] Cheers!
[LUFFY] The Dream
Sinking in the New World!
The Disillusioned
Pirate, Puzzle!
[USOPP] The icebergs
are moving on their own?
[ZORO]
Come on! Don't be ridiculous.
There's no way
that could happen.
Ridiculous or not,
something strange
is going on here.
[sneezes]
[NAMI] She's right.
They are moving,
and not in the same direction
as the sea current.
Whatever's making it
happen isn't natural.
How is something
like that even possible?
Come on!
You don't really expect
us to believe this crap.
Fine! See for yourselves!
Sanji? Demonstrate.
Sure!
[USOPP] What's going on here?
And again!
Well, would you look at that.
Cheeky little bastards!
[ZORO] Hm...
Nothing but ice, top to bottom.
[USOPP] If I hadn't seen it,
I wouldn't believe it!
It's almost like
they're making a path.
And yet, they're
normal icebergs.
Very strange, indeed.
Ever since that run-in
we had with the Marines,
it's like there's
some sort of force
trying to guide us
to a specific place.
[FRANKY] I don't know who's
responsible for this crap,
but they've got some nerve!
Whoever it is,
I ain't scared! Bring it!
Well, first,
before you fight them,
we have to figure out
who "they" are.
[snoring]
[PUZZLE] Vigaro! Wait!
Captain?
Vigaro... No...
Vigaro!
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
It's Captain Puzzle!
He's starting to wake up!
[JIRO]
Captain! Thank goodness!
Thank you so much!
You're an amazing doctor!
Sure. Glad I was
able to help him out,
but saying I'm amazing doesn't
make me happy, you jerk!
Jiro...
What happened? Why am I here?
[JIRO] You don't remember?
We were attacked by some really
strong guys in the New World.
It was terrible.
[GUYLE]
This can't be happening...
[STANSEN] Who in the
hell were those guys?
[SUTTON] Hurry!
We gotta put out that fire!
[RACE] Do something!
[GUYLE] Why'd they attack us?
[RACE] Come on!
We have to see to the injured!
We're retreating!
Get moving, full speed!
The New World is
too much for us to handle.
We're nothing here!
Come, now...
What would people think
of the fearless Puzzle, The
Phoenix, talking like that?
I'm no phoenix, dammit!
I'm nothing but a daydreamer!
Captain, listen.
We follow you because
all of us believe in you.
--Because you have--
--[STANSEN] It's no use, sir!
They're too fast!
Don't worry about it, Captain.
I'll buy us some time.
Stansen! I need a boat!
Vice-Captain...
[VIGARO] Hurry!
[STANSEN] Right!
[PUZZLE] Vigaro, wait!
I'm going with you!
Don't be an idiot!
The Captain can't abandon
his ship, you know that!
But...
Listen.
I believe in you, Puzzle.
You're the man who'll
be King of the Pirates!
Vigaro, no! Don't do this!
They're coming back around!
[SUTTON] Meteorites?
[yelling]
No!
But Vigaro couldn't
defeat them, either.
It was no contest.
They took him out
in a matter of seconds.
Still, it was those few seconds
that allowed us to escape.
We managed to break their rudder
so they couldn't catch us.
I'm not sure how we did it,
but I'm grateful either way.
Vigaro saved us.
Later on, the rest
of the crew and I
made a solemn promise
to each other.
[RACE, LAGO, TROFF sobbing]
[JIRO] Just like Vigaro,
we must all be willing
to protect the
captain with our lives!
I feel the same way. Yes.
If it's to save Captain Puzzle,
I would gladly lay down my life.
[TROFF] Me, too!
[JIRO]
We'll protect the Captain!
[LAGO] No doubt!
[GUYLE] Let's do it!
[BASIL] We'll go back
to the New World!
Nothing's gonna stop us!
But Stansen
didn't agree with us.
[STANSEN] Vigaro went so far
as to sacrifice himself
to protect you!
He gave his life for you!
I won't let that
sacrifice be in vain!
You had a fight with
bounty hunters, huh?
[JIRO]
Yeah. They were super strong.
It took everything
we had to escape.
We were completely worn out.
We knew if we fought them,
we'd lose, but--
We didn't care.
We weren't going to
let them steal the pride
of the Phoenix Pirates.
But he--
[JIRO] He wouldn't let us do it!
Stansen is a coward!
But now, since you're awake,
we can put those
awful times behind us!
Captain Puzzle The Phoenix
has risen from the ashes!
[JIRO] Whoa! Easy!
[CHOPPER] Don't exert yourself!
You need to rest!
I'm fine.
My body has rested enough.
Gather the crew. Get everyone
together on the deck.
You got it!
[RACE]
Really? The Captain's better?
[TROFF] You mean it?
Hahahaha, oh, yeah!
The day we've been
waiting for is finally here!
[GUYLE] The return
of the Phoenix Pirates.
Sucks for you, Stansen.
You deserve whatever you get.
[BASIL laughing]
--[RACE] Captain!
--[TROFF, LAGO] Captain Puzzle!
[SUTTON] Captain!
I'm sorry.
Seems I've been trouble.
No big deal.
[SUTTON]
None of that matters anymore.
[TROFF] I'm so glad!
Our Captain's back!
C'mon. Let's get going.
[JIRO] Doctor Chopper! Luffy!
Thank you for helping us out.
Aw, don't mention it.
I'm a doctor, so I
was just doing my job.
It's no big deal. Really!
Either way,
we'll definitely
repay the favor someday.
And I'm sure we'll be in
the New World when it happens.
I see!
So you guys are headed
to the New World, too?
Same as us!
If that's the case, then,
when we meet,
we'll be rivals.
Hahaha! I can't wait!
Captain.
As soon as we have
a chance to regroup,
I'm sure we'll be
stronger than ever!
What is it?
What's wrong, Captain?
Listen to me.
We're--We're not going
back to the New World.
What'd you say?
Stansen's decision was right.
I stand by it.
From this point forward,
we'll remain in the
bounty hunter crew.
[RACE] But I thought--
[BASIL] Captain Puzzle,
have you lost your mind?
[GUYLE] We're all ready
to lay down our lives for you!
Just like Vigaro did!
[PUZZLE] That's right.
Vigaro died for me. To save me.
Listen.
I believe in you, Puzzle.
You're the man who'll
be King of the Pirates!
But why?
You're back now!
Nothing can stop us!
We were waiting
for you all this time!
For the Phoenix to
rise from the ashes!
What happened to you?
Where is our fearless
Captain Puzzle?
[PUZZLE]
Phoenix, huh?
They're nothing but a myth.
They don't exist in this world.
[PUZZLE] And someone like me,
who can't even protect
his friends and his crew,
has no right to set
foot in the New World.
[JIRO] Why? I don't understand.
I refuse.
I won't accept this, Captain.
Our flag!
Are you telling me
you're not even
going to try
to get it back?
We're not pirates anymore.
We no longer have
the right to that flag.
Dammit!
How can you just throw away
your pride like that?
Luffy, wait!
[PUZZLE] You have my thanks.
I'd really like to repay
you for taking care of me,
but unfortunately,
almost everything I had
was taken away from me
in the New World.
I'm sorry.
[PUZZLE]
I know you're determined,
but the New World
isn't to be taken lightly.
It's dangerous out there.
It's fine. We can handle it.
See, we're really strong.
[VIGARO] Don't underestimate
the New World, Captain.
[PUZZLE] Come on, Vigaro! Relax!
I'm The Phoenix, remember?
[PUZZLE]
I see. Best of luck, then.
[sobbing]
Jiro...
--[LUFFY] Let's get going.
--[CHOPPER] But we--
Their captain's
given up on their flag.
It's over for them.
They're no longer pirates.
[CHOPPER] I--I guess so.
[yelling]
[screaming]
Luffy! Chopper!
[NAMI]
They'll be fine on their own!
We need to take care
of the ship!
Leave it to me!
We're being surrounded by them!
Hard to starboard now!
Aye-Aye! Hard to starboard!
It's no use!
They're still coming!
Hard to port!
Whoaaa! Careful!
[ROBIN]
They're all gathering together!
[USOPP] Dammit, Sanji!
Watch where you're going!
Aw, crap!
The rudder's not responding!
It's not the rudder.
Take a look over there!
Since those icebergs
have blocked the current,
they're causing
whirlpools to form!
Whirlpools, too?
What the hell
is wrong with this sea?
[LUFFY] Whoa, it looks like--
We just found the
world's biggest snow cone!
We did?
[CHOPPER] It's gigantic!
--Yummy!
--Luffy!
This isn't the time
to be thinking about food!
Sorry, what's that?
All I heard was "food"!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
[LUFFY yelling]
Devil Fruit powers?
[LUFFY]
And now...
It's pointless.
...Axe!
[LUFFY] My snow cone is sinking!
The Sunny! It disappeared!
This is the Frozen Highway.
Once a ship loses its way here,
it will never again
return to the open sea.
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 328A]
There's no doubt!
A 100 million Berry bounty!
The Phoenix, Puzzle!
But I thought that guy
was killed in battle.
That sneaky Stansen!
He tricked us!
He was just protecting him!
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 328B]
Straw Hat Luffy,
worth 300 million,
is there, too.
Making a total of 400 million.
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 328A]
Not a bad haul!
We need to report
this to Brindo ASAP!
Hahaha! So The Phoenix
Captain Puzzle is alive.
I can't believe
those pitiful pirates
thought they could actually pull
one over on the Accino family.
Why, the nerve of those people!
[BRINDO] My brothers!
It seems our present
for Papa will be even better!
For now, I will
leave this to you.
I shall return shortly.
[SANJI] I can't believe you!
Sneaking a peek at Nami's
butt during all the commotion!
[FRANKY] You switched
over to the paddles.
Is something wrong?
Franky!
Where have you been?
[FRANKY] I was refilling
our supply of cola
in the energy room.
I got a feelin', if I'm right,
it'll definitely
come in handy soon.
That's great and all,
but with all these moving
icebergs, it doesn't matter.
We're stuck here!
We're gonna be trapped
in this stupid place
for the rest of our lives!
Don't worry.
We'll figure it out soon.
[FRANKY] Come on!
You make it sound like those
icebergs are a big deal!
What are you talking about?
We just need to
get outta here, right?
It doesn't matter how.
Oh, yeah!
Looks like we
finally found you!
Going somewhere?
Don't you know
that when a ship is lost
on the Frozen Highway,
it's destined to wander
for all eternity?
Just give up already!
Couldn't have
said it better myself.
Indeed! Indeed! Indeed!
You'll never get away from us!
That's rather tasteless.
[SANJI] I can't believe
such a beautiful woman
is with that man-troll!
Hey! You!
I challenge you
to a duel for her honor!
Unfortunately, we can't
stick around for games,
right, Franky?
[FRANKY]
Mm-hmm.
Excuse us, but I'm
afraid we'll be leaving now.
Have you gone daft?
I already told you,
escaping from the Frozen
Highway is impossible.
Understand? Impossible!
Right! Couldn't
have said it better!
Indeed! Indeed! Indeed!
You'll never get away from us!
Whenever you're ready, Franky!
Aye-Aye! Leave it to me!
[FRANKY] Coup de...
[FRANKY] ...Burst!
[confused yelling]
No! But how? It's flying!
Well... Look at that.
[SALCHOW yelling in pain]
[CAMPACINO]
What's wrong, Salchow?
[SALCHOW] The ship, it--
It flew through the sky!
They got away!
[CAMPACINO] What insane
drivel are you babbling about?
--[SALCHOW] But I swear I--
--[ARBELL] Give me that thing!
[ARBELL]
It's true, brother!
They flew away!
I saw it with my own two eyes!
[CAMPACINO] Papa.
Something unfortunate
has happened.
They won't leave
without their flag.
[CAMPACINO] Of course!
What a devious idea, Papa!
We are to steal
their flag. Understand?
Perfectly, my honey!
[kissing noises]
[SALCHOW] Oh, Lil!
Might I ask a favor of you
to help us catch them?
I don't wanna.
What? I mean...
I was just hoping that--
I'll handle this.
Lil, dear.
It's not just us asking.
Didn't you hear?
It's a request
from our beloved Papa.
Go! Flying fish!
[FLYING FISH cooing]
What a strange fish.
[USOPP] I can finally relax!
I could sure get used to this!
Blue sky, white clouds,
and a big beautiful sun
shimmering behind
a pirate fla--fla--
What the hell?
[NAMI] Our flag! It's gone!
Come to think of it,
Zoro's gone, too.
[ZORO] I can't believe them!
They got lost again!
Buncha idiots.
[ZORO]
Brrr! I'm not cold!
And I'm not lost, either!
If the icebergs and the Sunny
can move around as
they please, why can't I?
So what if the rest of the crew
is eating something
nice and warm without me...
[ZORO sneezes]
What's up with
that weird building?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
The Assassins Attack!
The Great Battle on Ice Begins!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!