Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] In an effort
to save his brother Ace,
who had been
captured by the Navy,
Luffy journeys to the great
prison known as Impel Down.
Meanwhile, the other Straw Hats,
scattered around the globe
by Bartholomew Kuma,
face struggles of their own.
[LUFFY]
The Friends' Whereabouts!
An Island of Giant Birds
and a Pink Paradise!
[HANCOCK] How many times
must I repeat myself?
[yells]
[MARINES] Huh?
[whimpers]
[HANCOCK] Are my instructions
too complicated to penetrate
that thick head of yours?
I require at least
100 kilos of food per meal.
Anything less than that
is completely insufficient.
[HANCOCK] Do you want
to be turned to stone again?
No! Please! We're very sorry!
[MARINE 419B]
We'll be more careful next time!
Bring her another meal
to her specifications
to replace this one!
Here you are, Luffy!
Open wide for me okay?
[LUFFY] Simply delectable.
And when you're the one
feeding it to me, why,
it makes it all the sweeter.
Oh? Go on.
[giggles]
Clearly that's
exactly what he would say!
[giggles]
[LUFFY]
What are you doing over there?
Who're you talking to?
[gasps, giggles]
[LUFFY] Aren't you
gonna eat something?
This Sea King Ham
is unbelievable!
[HANCOCK] No, no, it's fine.
Please, help yourself!
I'm more than satisfied
just as I am!
[giggles]
[MARINE 419C]
Dammit! I can't see anything!
Huh?
[MARINE 419D]
I know! The curtain's closed!
[MARINE 419C] Hold on a minute!
There's an open space
right over here.
[MARINE 419D] Ooh!
[BOTH] Uh... Aaah...!
Love-Love Beam!
[thud]
[LUFFY]
Who was it? Something wrong?
[HANCOCK] It was just
two bad-mannered rats,
so I taught them a lesson.
It's nothing for
you to worry about!
[LUFFY] Okay.
Whoa! Look at that!
It's a warning!
If anyone ever tries
to peek into her room,
[MARINE 419F]
this is what will happen!
[MARINE 419F] She's so scary!
[giggling]
[NARRATOR] A few days earlier...
on an island somewhere
in the South Blue...
[CHOPPER] Luffy... Guys...?
Why isn't anybody else here?
[CHOPPER] Did they kill them?
That's ridiculous--
don't even think it!
It's not true.
It can't be! Guys!
[LUFFY] Hey, Chopper!
Huh?
[chuckles]
Luffy!
[gasps]
You're here!
[wailing]
[birds cawing]
[CHOPPER] When I woke up
and I was all alone, I wasn't...
scared at all! Really!
[chuckles]
Luffy, Usopp, come on!
Knock it off.
[CHOPPER] Ouch!
I said "stop," you big dummy!
You guys are gonna
regret this, you hear me?
[screams]
[CHOPPER] Hey. Where the heck
did these birds come from?!
They're huge!
Ah! Don't even think
about trying to eat me!
No! My body's too stiff
to get up and run!
I gotta move!
[CHOPPER]
Ow! Stop it! Leave me alone!
I'm getting dizzy!
[gasping quickly]
[yells]
[BIRDIE BIRD 419A] Mmm!
[CHOPPER] No! Let me go!
Bastard!
Uh. Uh. Uh...?
Uhhh...
[CHOPPER] This island is weird!
This is a dream, right?
Please let it be a dream!
I wanna wake up!
[BIRDIE BIRD 419A grunts]
[hollers]
[CHOPPER]
Stop, I'm gonna hurl!
No! You birds are mean!
I'm a reindeer, not a toy!
[sobs]
[BIRDIE BIRDS grunt]
[CHOPPER yells]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[CHOPPER yells]
[BOTH cawing]
[CHOPPER panting]
It's over now. I think.
[frogs ribbit]
[crickets chirp]
[CHOPPER] There aren't
any people here? Just birds?
Hey! Luffy! Everybody!
[sighs]
[CHOPPER] I'm the
only one on this island.
What am I gonna do?
I'm so thirsty. And hungry, too.
If only Luffy
and the others were here.
Even on a deserted island...
[CHOPPER] they'd still
throw an awesome party!
[laughing]
[CHOPPER] A party! A party...
[CHOPPER] Who am I kidding?
I'm lost, and they
could be dead, for all I know.
I can't take it!
[CHOPPER sobs]
Where is everybody?
Guys. Luffy...
Oh, yeah!
This!
[CHOPPER] We promised that
no matter what happened,
we'd meet up wherever
this Vivre Card leads us!
Luffy and the others
will be waiting!
I just know it!
Nothing can stop them!
They won't ever give up!
[CHOPPER]
And that goes for me too!
This is no time to
sit around and do nothing!
That's why I gotta
eat and get stronger!
This fruit is
pretty bitter, though. Ugh.
But I need nutrients! Bluh!
This one is super sour! Puhhh!
[CHOPPER] Gotcha! I'll need
meat to survive, too.
This guy... doesn't look
too yummy, though, I guess.
[CHOPPER] But what can you
expect on an island like this?
Gotta make do.
Whoa! You come
back here, dinner!
[laughs]
[CHOPPER]
Can't get away from me!
[CHOPPER] Huh? Uh--
[thonk]
[drum beat plays]
[groans]
What the--? I wonder
who the heck hit me?
Ow! Ugh...
[CHOPPER]
And why is it so hot?
[gasps]
Uh. Uh...
[BIRDIE TRIBESMEN chant]
[CHOPPER screams]
I was supposed to
catch dinner, not be it!
It rare to get
raccoon on island.
Raccoon Hot Pot!
Raccoon nice,
but me rather have chicken
and make Chicken Hot Pot.
That good idea, but no chicken.
Raccoon will have to do for now.
Stop it! Shut up!
I'm a reindeer!
[BIRDIE TRIBESMEN grunting]
[CHOPPER gasps]
Ah. Guess we have
Reindeer Hot Pot then.
Hey. Wait. Did reindeer
just say something?
Me not know
reindeers could speak.
[CHOPPER]
Good, you're finally listening!
Now let me down!
--[BIRDIE BIRDS cawing]
--[BIRDIE TRIBESMEN] Huh?
Bad! We got crisis on hands!
We try to sneak up
into bird's nest,
but bird caught us!
[BIRDIE BIRDS] Mmm!
[BIRDIE TRIBESMAN 419B]
And now bunch of birds
are coming right for us!
[BIRDIE TRIBESMAN 419C]
Maybe we can shoo away?
[BIRDIE TRIBESMAN GOATEE]
Me say we run for it.
[SHANBA] We go now!
[CHOPPER] Come on, guys!
Don't leave your
reindeer hot pot
behind for the birds!
[BIRDIE BIRD 419C grunts]
[BIRDIE BIRD 419D grunts]
[BIRDIE TRIBESMEN groan]
Those birds are
really strong, huh?
[gasps] Oh, crap!
[CHOPPER screams]
[CHOPPER shrieks, yelps]
[panting]
[CHOPPER] The birds
rolled me around like a toy.
And those humans
tried to eat me in a hot pot!
What the hell's wrong
with this crazy island?
[BIRDIE BIRDS cawing]
[NARRATOR] This island
is known as Birdie Kingdom.
A place where
birds reign supreme.
One legend suggests
that its lands
are filled with hidden treasure,
but all Chopper
has found is danger.
[NARRATOR]
Behold, Peachy Island!
A dreamy, beautiful
destination on the Grand Line.
[WOMEN giggling]
[SANJI] My dearest Nami.
My sweet Robin.
It's been a while.
How are the two of you doing?
As for me, I'm--
[birds cawing]
Where the hell... am I?
[SANJI] Bastard. This is all
'cause of that damn Warlord!
[gasping]
[WOMAN]
Oh, my goodness! Excuse me!
Mister, are you all right--
can you hear me?
[WOMAN] Please!
Say something! Anything!
[SANJI groaning lightly]
[SANJI]
I can feel a tender touch.
And I smell something sweet.
I'm in the lap
of a beautiful woman!
Is it... Nami? Maybe Robin?
No, I must be dreaming.
It doesn't matter.
All I know is
I wanna stay here forever.
[gasps]
[WOMAN sobbing]
Hey! Wait a minute! Come back!
[SANJI] What's this?
You forgot your handkerchief!
[SANJI]
I guess it wasn't a dream.
[SANJI] Elizabeth.
[angelic music plays]
Uh. I still don't
have a clue where I'm at.
Beautiful.
Maybe I ended up in heaven.
[SANJI] Her name is Elizabeth.
[heart beating]
If this place really is heaven,
then, is she an angel?
[SANJI]
Oh, my heart is pounding.
What is this feeling?
So warm. This...
must be... love!
I sense... romance in the air!
[ELIZABETH giggling]
--[SANJI laughing]
--[ELIZABETH] Sanji! Wait!
--[ELIZABETH] Come back!
[BOTH laughing]
No, I can't think about
such things right now.
[SANJI] Nami and Robin
are out there waiting for me.
But...
Well, the least I can do
is thank her for her kindness.
Through thick and thin
a gentlemen must always
be courteous to a lady!
[SANJI] Aaah! Nami and Robin!
Please forgive me
for being unfaithful!
Elizabeth!
[laughs] Uh--
[birds chirping]
It's the same design
as the handkerchief.
Then this must be
Elizabeth's place, I presume?
[SANJI]
Hello! Lady Elizabeth?
My name's Sanji.
You were looking
after me not too long ago?
I came here to
return your handkerchief!
[footsteps]
Uh. Aaah...
Hey, you didn't give me
a chance to say "thanks"!
No. Hold on. Shouldn't rush it.
[SANJI] She's obviously
a shy and innocent girl.
I need to be cool.
Have a little patience.
[clears throat]
Pardon my manners.
Didn't mean to be rude!
Your hand was--
it was so lovely,
I couldn't help myself!
I just wanted to thank its
beautiful owner face-to-face!
But here I am
being too forward again!
[SANJI] Perhaps you would
allow me to apologize
and say thanks, as well,
by giving me the honor
of cooking for you?
Whatever you'd like,
I'll make it!
Believe it or not,
I'm a world-class chef!
Or not.
[ELIZABETH] So you...
you really like to cook?
Oh, yes! I love cooking!
[ELIZABETH] Then...
do you like clothes, too?
[SANJI]
Clothes? Like, fashion?
Yeah! U-Unlike some
stupid swordsman I know,
I actually care a lot
about the way I look!
[ELIZABETH] Really?
You're not just saying that?
[SANJI] Oh, no!
[ELIZABETH]
Then what about... dresses?
Dresses? Uh...
[SANJI] Oh, I get it! She keeps
asking me about stuff like that
because she wants
to know what I'm into!
She's making a love connection!
What do you think
of dresses like this?
Like them?
Like them? I love them!
They're beautiful!
Oh! You have no idea how much!
[ELIZABETH]
And what about flower prints?
Hell yes! Nothing in life
beats a gorgeous flower print!
[SANJI]
Ooh! They're so adorable!
[ELIZABETH giggles]
All right, then.
Finally! Sweet Elizabeth is
opening up to me, after all!
[SANJI] Ahhh...
Oh, you have
exquisite taste, my dear!
[SANJI] Don't be shy.
You've already opened the door
to your home, now open
the door to your heart.
[ELIZABETH] Oh, Sanji!
[laughs]
No need to hold
anything back, my love,
just leap into my arms!
Oh, Elizabeth!
[ELIZABETH chuckles]
I think this dress...
...would look amazing on you!
Uh...
[groans]
[SANJI]
Ouch! Wasn't ready for that.
Heh-heh.
You're a lot stronger
than I thought you would be,
my dear Elizabeth--
[SANJI] Auuuggghhh..
[heart beating]
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI groans]
[ELIZABETH (MAN) chuckles]
[SANJI] No. I was right.
I must be dreaming after all.
[SANJI]
But this is a nightmare!
[groans]
Aaah...
[ALL chuckle]
[SANJI screams]
We like the same things!
That makes you one of us!
This is a safe place!
You don't have to pretend to be
something you're not anymore!
Yes! It's a free country
where you can be yourself!
[SANJI groans, yells]
Huh?!
[ELIZABETH (MAN)]
Now. Put on this dress.
And open up
the door to your heart!
[SANJI] No!
I'm... not gonna open anything!
--[QUEENS] No, don't go!
--[SANJI yells]
[NARRATOR] This island is known
as the second Maiden Island.
Everything here is pink.
All of the animals and
people who come to this land
share a common bond.
No matter what forms
their bodies take,
they still have girlish hearts.
[SANJI] How did I
think this was heaven?
[commotion]
Uaahhh...!
Leave me alone you weirdos!
I already told you
I'm not into that kinda crap!
[SANJI] My dearest Nami.
My sweet Robin.
It's been a while.
How are the two of you doing?
As for me, I'm--well... Uh...
How to put this...?
[yells]
[LIME DRESS QUEEN]
Don't run, sugar!
[RED DRESS QUEEN]
You can't fight it!
[BLONDE SCHOOLGIRL QUEEN]
You're one of us now!
Oh yeah, fat chance!
[QUEENS]
Welcome to Kamabakka Kingdom!
[SANJI] No. It's obvious.
I'm in hell.
[NARRATOR] Robin finds herself
in a far away land
with inhabitants that have
been forced to work
for 700 years, days and night.
She must either help them
or become enslaved herself!
Meanwhile, Usopp awakens
in a land full of
mysterious and
deadly plant life.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece,
The Friends' Whereabouts!
Bridging the Islands
and Vicious Vegetation!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!