[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind
of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from the
rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed to
Navy Headquarters
in order to rescue
his brother from death.
However, there are
only three hours left
before the public execution
of Portgas D. Ace.
[LUFFY] "Ticking Down
to the Time of Battle!
The Navy's Strongest
Lineup in Position!"
[GUARD A]
Stand up.
Start climbing.
[MERCHANT A] You think
Whitebeard's gotten there yet?
There're only three
hours left now.
Eh. I'm starting to wonder
if he's gonna show up at all.
I know the guy's serious news,
but isn't he a little
bit too old for a war?
You really think so?
He's been tearing up the seas
since before the
Great Pirate Era.
Do the math, he's
gotta be senile.
And it's been a few years now
since his name
made any headlines.
[OLD WOMAN] You're all fools
for taking this so lightly.
You need some proof
of how serious this is?
They've manned Navy HQ
with their entire fleet
and brought in their
elites as a precaution.
I would bet my life savings
Whitebeard's gonna show.
Just you watch.
So, whaddya think is gonna
go down when he does?
[OLD WOMAN] No idea. How the
hell am I supposed to know?
[MAN A] Whitebeard's living in
a completely different era now.
Does he stand a chance?
Taking on the entire Navy?
He's bound to fail if he does.
No pirate can attack Marineford.
It just isn't possible.
[MAN B]
It's happened before.
I wanna say it was
about 20 years ago now.
But a pirate called
Shiki the Golden Lion
invaded Marineford and
managed to leave at least half
of the Navy
Headquarters in ruins.
This time, though, I can promise
you it's gonna be much worse.
It's bound to be a colossal
massacre no matter who wins.
[MAN B]
Let's just hope he doesn't show.
The execution would happen,
but one death is
better than thousands.
[BARKEEP] You want me to open
the bar on a day like this?
The whole world's about to
go to war any minute now!
Just go back home!
I'll open up tomorrow if
we're all still alive!
Then sell us some bottles to go!
There's no reason
for ya to treat us
like we're on the
execution block!
You expect us to live
without drinking?
[MAN IN BAR] Everyone talks
like he's just some old man,
but we all know it ain't true.
How long's it been now?
Couldn't have been
more than a year
since he walked in here and
sat right there across from me.
We all thought we were dead men.
[MAN C] Is Whitebeard
really as nefarious
as everyone makes him out to be?
[MAN D]
Heh. You kidding?
Even those kids know. Just
listen to their little song.
[KIDS]
Whitebeard, Whitebeard,
he's so mean,
he's so feared.
[KIDS laughing]
[NUN]
Oh, Lord, I'm so afraid.
Where is this world headed?
Please help us through
these awful times.
[NARRATOR]
On the island of Marineford,
home of Navy headquarters,
there lies a large city
primarily populated
by Navy families.
But not today.
[NARRATOR]
For their safety,
an evacuation order has been
issued to all residents.
[NARRATOR] At the evacuation
site on the Sabaody Archipelago,
the displaced residents
anxiously wait
to view the execution
on giant monitors.
[NARRATOR] Journalists and
cameramen from across the world
have also gathered here to break
the news of the proceedings
as quickly as they unfold.
Jeez. The Navy's really
not messing around.
That's the best they've got.
Yeah.
Whitebeard's gotta
know what's in store.
So the question is,
does he wanna risk it?
[NARRATOR] Every look-out
ship the Navy has sent out
in search of Whitebeard
has been swiftly sunk.
And yet, there have been no
sightings of the pirate himself.
The tension looming
over Marineford
rises with each passing second.
And with less than three hours
left until the execution,
the sickening suspense is
soon to grow unbearable.
Damn. It ain't right.
And I don't see
why it's necessary.
I understand your reservations,
but this isn't some simple
execution of a pirate.
You have to think about
what's at stake here.
The significance it has
on the future of the world.
That's why it's necessary.
I know it's difficult for you,
but you are deeply
involved in this matter.
The responsibility lies
on your shoulders.
[SENGOKU] And you better
not forget it, Garp.
[MARINES shouting]
Get those in place!
You! Pick up the pace, now!
[LACROIX]
Don't let your guard down!
No matter what we face,
it'll only last three hours!
After that, it's all over!
[MARINES]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR] The Navy has summoned
its most elite soldiers
from all over the world,
totaling almost 100 thousand.
With a focus on the
crescent-shaped bay area,
the island is protected
by 50 Navy warships.
On top of that,
the surrounding walls
have been armed with a
countless number of cannons.
And positioned front and center
before the vast throng
of marshaled forces...
...stand five of the Navy's
most ferocious allies,
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
[MARINES gasp]
They're here.
It's the Admirals.
Is it just me, or are they even
scarier than the Warlords?
[NARRATOR]
Closely guarding the scaffold
from the foot of the structure,
both revered and feared,
the three Marine Admirals.
[MARINES cheering]
[NARRATOR] On this day,
every force of order
the World Government can gather
has been unified to stand
against the Whitebeard Pirates
in the imminent battle
over the life of one man.
[ACE]
Luffy, listen.
There's only one
way to live life,
and that's without any regrets.
[LUFFY]
Uh-huh.
[ACE] Someday, we're
gonna head out to sea
and live the way we wanna live.
More free than anyone else.
[grunts]
I can see it!
Hey! Jimbei!
It's the Gate of Justice!
We made it!
That was really fast!
It should've been faster!
We would've arrived a lot sooner
if the winds had been right.
We're here, but...
Now let me explain your future.
Your fates depend on whether
we open the Gate of Justice.
As long as we leave it closed,
you can't get to Marineford.
You can't even get out
of the Tub Current.
You will be completely stranded.
There is no sea for
you to escape to.
The question now
is how we're supposed
to get through the gate?
Well, men, y'know
what time it is?
Huh? Let me hear it now!
[PRISONERS]
It's time for Captain Buggy
to conquer the entire world!
And lemme hear the rest!
[PRISONERS]
Navy HQ's goin' down!
And Whitebeard's goin' down!
And who is the next
King of the Pirates?
[PRISONERS]
Captain Buggy!
[laughing]
And don't you forget it!
--[PRISONERS] Buggy! Buggy!
--[BUGGY laughing]
Ace.
[CROWD gasping, whispering]
Hey, look. They're bringing
out Fire Fist Ace.
Wow, so that's him.
He looks like just anyone else,
but every step he takes
could throw all of us
into an unthinkable war.
Alive or dead,
he's responsible for our fates,
and the whole world's.
Okay, Garp, I'll
do the talking.
Go ahead. I'll be
waiting downstairs.
[SENGOKU]
Step aside for a minute.
[GUARDS]
Yes, sir.
It's the Fleet Admiral.
What's he doing?
Pass me a Snail.
[GUARD A]
Sir.
[SENGOKU]
I have some information
you all need to hear.
This man is Portgas D. Ace,
and the significance
of his impending demise
is more profound
than you may realize.
None of this is
your fault, Garp.
[GARP laughing]
Can't hold back those
motherly feelings
during dark times, Tsuru?
Ace.
I would like you to tell them
the name of your father.
[grunts]
[JOURNALIST B]
His father?
What's that have
to do with anything?
The name of my father
is Whitebeard.
Not true!
Yes, it is!
Whitebeard is my father!
My only father!
[SENGOKU]
We launched a painstaking
and exhaustive search for you
around the time of your birth.
When we heard rumors that
your father had a child,
we took them very seriously.
Thanks to Cipher Pol,
a small but reliable amount of
information was presented to us.
Based on this, we
checked all newborns,
as well as all preborn children.
We spoke to many mothers,
but no matter how far
and wide we searched,
we couldn't find you.
No surprise, though.
Especially when you
consider the lengths
your mother went to to hide you.
She performed a miracle
that could only come
from the love of a mother.
As a result, she
misled the Navy.
No. She managed to
mislead the world.
You come from an island in
the South Blue called Batelira.
And your mother's name?
Portgas D. Rouge.
She pulled off a feat
that completely defied
the laws of nature,
all to protect her child.
She kept her baby inside her
womb for an entire 20 months.
No, that's impossible.
[SENGOKU] And once she
finally gave birth to you,
she lost all of her strength
and passed away
right then and there.
And thus, a year
and three months
after the death of his father,
a child was born with the blood
of the world's most odious
villain in his veins.
That child was you.
[SENGOKU]
Surely, you must know the truth.
[ACE'S FATHER]
They can't persecute someone
who's yet to be born.
Right, Garp?
So please look after my child.
[SENGOKU]
Your true father...
...is Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates!
So, for all these years,
Gold Roger had a son?
[CROWD gasping, chattering]
This is massive news.
Call the head office!
Issue an extra!
Then it survived.
His bloodline.
[REUDER]
Roger's bloodline lives!
[NARRATOR] The secret of
Ace's birth is revealed.
Saved by the determination
of his father, Roger,
the hope of his mother, Rouge,
and the mercy of Garp,
he entered an unwelcoming world.
Now, he must rely on the help
of his loved ones once more.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Vast Fleet Appears!
Here Come the
Whitebeard Pirates!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!