[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[SATORI]
Ha, ha!
[ALL gasp]
[SATORI]
Impact!
[SANJI groans]
[USOPP, LUFFY]
Sanji!
[SANJI groans]
[LUFFY]
Sanji!
Like they say, "Life
is pain"! [chuckles]
Now, who wants to go next?
[NAMI] Okay! Here's
how we're gonna do this!
Center of the ship!
We leave the whistle
on the main mast here,
so if any of us
gets into trouble,
all we have to do is run
over here and blow it.
Now it's fair to everyone.
There. Good.
I'm sure glad thing
this was still here.
Just one?
Surely you're not the only
sacrifice I get to kill?
[gasps]
[whistle blows]
[LUFFY] "Chopper in Danger!
Former God vs. Priest Shura!"
[GAN FALL] I'd call this one of
the finest batches in years.
Wouldn't you agree, Pagaya?
[PAGAYA]
Huh?
[GAN FALL]
I'm referring to the pumpkins.
I don't think I've ever
grown them quite as sweet.
[PAGAYA]
Hm.
Of course. I'm sorry, but my
mind is wandering elsewhere.
It's very kind of
you to take us in.
I dislike putting you
in this position.
[GAN FALL]
Not at all.
If they believe
that your daughter
let the Straw Hats escape,
they'll consider
you an accomplice.
The only safe place
for you is here.
You can consider this
one on the house.
We're all lucky that Eneru's
Mantra doesn't reach this far.
[GAN FALL] How are things
back on the island?
I'm sorry?
The crops.
Are they coming in
hardy this year?
From what I know of it, yes.
Quite well, indeed.
Well, that's good to hear.
I prepared us
some pumpkin juice
made from the very ones
that grow here in my field.
Wonderful flavor.
Try some.
[PAGAYA]
Thank you.
It looks refreshing.
Conis, dear.
You should try this.
[GAN FALL] Young lady,
I'm curious if you've ever
heard tale of those from the
Blue Sea World called 'pirates.'
Never.
They are basically
just criminals
who travel on the water.
And though each ship
may vary somewhat,
these pirates are usually
recognized by their flag
with a skull and
crossbones on it.
[gasps]
[GAN FALL]
I have my suspicions
that your new friends
fall in line with this kind.
[PAGAYA]
That's absurd!
You mean that these
people were criminals
before they set
foot on our shore?
[GAN FALL chuckles]
[GAN FALL] They may not live
by the rules of their world,
but I can't necessarily
call that criminal.
There are those who
fall out of grace
with the rule of law
in any society.
I don't see you two as
any different from them.
[CONIS gasps]
Whose says that those
who don't fit in are wrong
and others are right?
Sometimes the way of the world
is backwards and blurred
and it can change in an instant.
For example, you kill a man in
war and you're branded a hero.
Kill the same man in peacetime
and you're prosecuted
as a murderer.
I, myself, had a pirate
friend at long time ago.
He came here with his band
more than 20 years ago,
while I was still
God of Skypiea.
They were funny, all of them.
Boisterous people with
lots to laugh about
and a general air of freedom.
I hated to say goodbye.
The beauty of this land
masks a truth as old as time.
Skypiea is entangled
in endless war.
We, the people of the sky,
wage this battle with
those we call guerillas.
The Shandorians.
Even now they move
against Eneru constantly,
trying to siege the sky.
I worry for all those
I could not protect.
When you were God, you did
all that you could to coexist.
Even the Shandorians
were convinced of this.
You gave all of us hope
that the several-hundred-year
war would end
and leave us with lasting peace.
[sighs] I didn't
have near enough time.
Eneru dethroned me before I
could solidify the treaty.
Wasted efforts.
I'm sorry for failing my people.
Stop that.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
[GAN FALL] A legend is passed
down through the generations
in Skypiea about its beginnings.
[GAN FALL] It is said that
the day the Upper Yard,
the sacred grounds, was created,
the voice of the island sung
forth a beautiful song
that echoed through the skies.
It was after that moment
that the tragedy
between the people of the sky
and the Shandorians began...
As if on cue.
And so the legend says,
when we next hear the
singing voice of the island,
this war will finally
come to an end.
The... voice...
[GAN FALL]
That's right.
And our sacred land
will sing again someday.
Someday she must.
[whistle blows]
[PIERRE gasps, squawks]
[GAN FALL]
Hm?
[PAGAYA]
Huh? Is something happening?
[GAN FALL]
Nothing you need worry about.
I've got a job to do.
You'll be safe here.
[SUU THE FOX]
Suu?
[giggles] He's right.
This pumpkin juice is fantastic.
Yes. He's quite good
at cultivating things.
[SUU THE FOX]
Suu, suu!
Suu!
[whistle blowing]
[CHOPPER whimpers]
So.
You offer your life to
the Almighty God Eneru,
and I will oblige!
[CHOPPER screams]
[CHOPPER grunts]
A fire?
Why are you resisting?
You can't escaped
the sacrifical altar.
Try to die with some dignity!
[FUZA squawks]
[screams]
[CHOPPER grunts, gasps]
[CHOPPER]
No! Not the ship!
[SHURA]
Hmph. He's going to grow.
[gasps, grunts]
[CHOPPER grunts]
[CHOPPER]
Go out! Go out already! Come on!
[SHURA] I don't see why you
care so much about a ship
that no one is going
to sail on again.
Death will find you as surely
as it will find your friends
who left you here alone.
I don't even know who you are!
Stop it! And stay away
from my friends!
[CHOPPER grunts]
You wanna help your friends?
Then hold still! [grunts]
[CHOPPER groaning]
[gasps, yells]
[gasps]
[CHOPPER gasps]
[screams]
[CHOPPER]
Not the mast! Stop it! Please!
[yells] Just stop
burning the ship!
I'm serious, I don't wanna die!
[CHOPPER whining]
Heh.
[CHOPPER]
This is gonna hurt!
[CHOPPER grunting]
[CHOPPER yells]
[CHOPPER panting]
Oh, no. Oh, no!
If you want me, that's fine!
But you can't have the ship!
They put me in charge of it,
and I'm not letting them down,
so you back off now,
mister! [whimpers]
[SHURA] What do you think
we should do, Fuza?
He's so impassioned.
[squawks]
[SHURA] He doesn't want us
to hurt any of his friends,
he's begging us not
to torch his ship,
and he says, of course,
that he doesn't want to die.
I'm at a loss here.
[groans] You're a greedy
little hairball, aren't you?
And you get under my skin.
[AISA panting]
[AISA grunts]
It's Gan Fall.
[PIERRE screeching]
[ZORO] Nami, would you
pick up the pace?
I'm growin' grey
hairs back here.
[NAMI] Shut up! Stop it!
You're distracting me!
What if I slip and fall, huh?
I'll be dead! And then
how would you feel?
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI screams]
[ZORO grunts]
Nami. You all right down there?
[NAMI]
Yeah...
But I have no idea how.
[NAMI pants]
[NAMI]
Sorry for being such a pain.
Thanks for grabbing me.
No problem.
[ZORO]
What is it?
No more monsters, I hope.
It looks like... a well.
A well?
[SHURA]
Let me get this straight.
Your friends, this ship,
and your life--
You don't want to
lose any of that.
[CHOPPER gasps]
Then...
...why don't you try
putting up a fight?!
[CHOPPER gasps]
Your spear!
It's burning through the metal!
[CHOPPER screaming]
Hot! Hot!
Why's he burning
everything?! [screams]
[CHOPPER]
You creep!
[yells, gasps]
[SHURA] Are you trying
to survive this...
...without sacrificing
anything of yourself?
[CHOPPER] There's more to
this guy than he's showing me.
He's not just a fighter.
It's like he can predict
all of my moves!
[SHURA] For one to live,
another must die.
That is the way of the world.
This is a sacrificial altar.
[SHURA] What did you
think was going to happen
by you being up here?
[CHOPPER]
I was supposed to fix the ship
and wait until my
crewmates came back.
[SHURA] Be assured, your friends
are trying their hardest
to get back here.
Of course, they're going to
find it incredibly difficult.
On this island
there are four areas,
each of which is governed
by a different priest.
Our first rule is that when
the targets are in one area,
the other priests are not
supposed to interfere with them
in any way.
But this sacrificial altar
doesn't sit inside the
perimeter of any of the areas.
Here, we are in a free zone.
Which means that any one of us
can attack those we find here.
And proper etiquette would not
have those at the altar killed
until after the targets fail
at a challenge and die.
What?! Luffy and the
others are dead?!
Calm yourself.
The fact that I am here
does not necessarily mean
your friends are
dead at this point.
It's unfortunate but true.
I stand before you now
with a different purpose
than sacrifice.
[CHOPPER]
What's different about it?
Wait. You mean if my friends
get back here and rescue me,
then we're free to go.
But you won't let
that happen, will you?
Well, that depends on you
and whether you and your
crew can make your escape
from the free zone fast enough.
[CHOPPER]
What?
[SHURA]
But hold that thought.
The reason I'm here is because
those are the judgment rules
under normal conditions.
However, when there is
an exceptional situation,
the rules are set
to change a little.
Exceptional?
Yes. Exceptional.
Say, for example,
three sacrifices were
to escape the altar
and swing to the main
island using vines.
[CHOPPER]
Oh, that kind of situation.
[ZORO]
I say we should cross over
and see what's on the
other side of the river.
[ZORO yelling]
[CHOPPER]
It's all his fault!
[ZORO yelling]
[ZORO] I wonder what
crawled into her knapsack,
wandering off ahead like that.
It's immature is what it is.
If this is a thinly veiled
attempt to call me childish,
at least have the courtesy
to do it to my face.
Huh?
[NAMI]
You know, when I think about it,
most of the times I've ended
up in situations like this
are your fault.
You're losin' it.
[SHURA]
Someone has to lose their life
to bring balance back
after your friends' escape.
It's atonement.
And sacrifice is part of life.
I want them to see it
when they come back--
their good friend lying on deck,
the life drained from him.
Then they will realize the
severity of their mistakes.
And now...
...I offer your life to God!
[CHOPPER yells]
No!
[CHOPPER groaning]
[gasps, groans]
Now die.
[CHOPPER groaning]
[gasps]
[SHURA growls]
--[GAN FALL yells]
--[SHURA grunts]
[GAN FALL]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's Gan Fall the Sky Knight!
[grunts] I wasn't
expecting company.
[SHURA grunts]
[SHURA]
Gan Fal!l
[CHOPPER] I knew you wouldn't
let me down, Sky Knight!
[GAN FALL] We're not dealing
with an amateur here, Pierre.
I wouldn't want to disappoint
a worthy opponent
with anything but our best.
[squawks]
What could that decrepit old
relic possibly be doing here?
Do you feel like putting
him in his place?
[squawks]
[GAN FALL]
Enough stalling!
[SHURA] We don't need
two Gods on this island!
[SHURA groans, grunts]
[CHOPPER]
Go, Sky Knight!
[SHURA growls]
[SHURA grunts]
[SHURA gasps]
[SHURA groans]
[gasps]
[CHOPPER]
Sky Knight, you're my hero!
[CHOPPER squealing]
[GAN FALL]
One more hit in the right spot
should do it for
him, eh, Pierre?
[PIERRE squawks]
I've had enough.
[CHOPPER gasps]
You're nothing but a pathetic
shell of your former self.
And I'm through playing
games with a fool.
You showed up to this
fight a criminal,
which leaves me
only one option--
take you out.
[GAN FALL]
Hm?
[SHURA]
Ordeal of String!
[FUZA screeches]
[LUFFY groaning]
[SATORI]
Aha! You're still alive!
I'm impressed!
And as a reward
for good behavior,
we're going to finish
our little fun today
with a move I've received
several awards for.
[laughs]
[LUFFY groans]
[SATORI]
Ha, ha, ha!
My super secret surprise!
Sphere Dragon! [laughs]
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[CHOPPER]
Now that's an incredible fight!
[GAN FALL]
You scum!
What did you do to me?
I can't move!
[CHOPPER]
Sky Knight Gan Fall!
[LUFFY]
That doesn't look good.
[SATORI laughs]
[LUFFY laughs] Looks like
I'll get him this time.
Sanji, give this guy a good hard
pounding when you catch him.
On the next One Piece!
"Profound Mystery!
Ordeal of String and
Ordeal of Love?!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!