[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
"Luffy Gets Angry!
A Dirty Trick Violates
the Sacred Duel!"
[BROGGY yells]
[DORRY, BROGGY yell]
[growls]
[rumbling, thudding]
[DORRY, BROGGY growling]
[DORRY growls]
[BROGGY yells]
[yells]
[yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[whimpers]
He...
He blocked that hit
with his helmet.
That's incredible!
A couple of inches left or right
and it would've killed him!
[BROGGY growls]
[DORRY, BROGGY grunting]
What an incredible fight, huh?
Every one of those
attacks is aimed
at some vital spot.
Just one slip from either
of them, and that's it‐‐
they're dead!
[NAMI] These guys have really
been fighting to the death
for 100 years?
That's gotta get old.
This is a good thing.
This is our chance
to get away. Let's go.
[NAMI]
Usopp?
Amazing...
[BROGGY]
Why?
I don't remember!
[BROGGY laughs]
They fight so seriously...
And they don't even know why.
This fight's getting
really annoying.
[USOPP]
Don't you see?!
This is an example
of a real battle
between real men.
Say what?
[USOPP]
Maybe an analogy will help.
It's as if they have each
planted a flag in their hearts
that says, "I am a warrior."
This flag is more
important than anything,
more than their lives, even.
They can never allow the flag
to be destroyed by someone else.
That's why they've both
continued this fight
for 100 years.
[DORRY, BROGGY yell]
[USOPP] Do you see it now?
This is a proud duel‐‐
a legendary fight‐‐between
two dedicated warriors.
Yeah, whatever.
That warrior stuff
doesn't really interest me
in the slightest.
You coming?
[USOPP]
No, I'm still watching this.
This is my ultimate goal.
This right here.
To be a brave warrior
like each of these titans.
Really, though, someday...
...I will be a proud
warrior of the sea!
[NAMI]
So what you're saying then,
is that you wanna be a giant?
[USOPP]
Huh?
Moron! You haven't
listened to a single word
I've said, have you?
Hey, Usopp...
Isn't there something that
you're supposed to be watching?
[DORRY, BROGGY grunting]
If there's a village full of
warriors like these two,
then I really wanna
go there someday!
[laughs] I've got a great
view from up here!
They're gonna see ya,
Miss Valentine.
Now get down here!
Oh, don't be so
jittery, Mr. 5.
You see...
They're completely absorbed
in the fight down there.
They won't notice me.
[MR. 5]
Just come down already.
[MISS VALENTINE]
Okay, okay.
Now, behave yourself.
This is a 200,000,000
berry job here.
[MISS VALENTINE]
Of course.
Though I'm not really
crazy about this.
What Mr. 3 wants us to do.
I know.
Come on now.
Okay.
[rumbling]
[DORRY, BROGGY groan]
[panting]
It's safe to say...
...that we're both starting to
get homesick here... huh, Dorry?
That's why I intend to
end this duel of ours.
I'm going to beat you
and go home to Elbaf.
Got that, Broggy?
[yells]
Seventy‐three thousand...
...four hundred sixty‐six duels.
Seventy‐three thousand,
four hundred and
sixty‐six draws.
[rumbling]
[DORRY chuckles]
[BROGGY chuckles]
[DORRY, BROGGY laughing]
Hey, Dorry.
A couple guests of mine
gave me some alcohol.
Drinks? It's been a long while,
eh, Broggy?
[laughs]
[BROGGY, DORRY laughing]
What was that? Laughing?
First that long,
strange earthquake,
and now this creepy
laughing sound?
What's goin' on in this place?
What kind of
creatures live here?
Well...
That damn cook's still
hunting out there.
Maybe he'll run into
one of those monsters.
Were those bird cries?
'Cause the birds here
don't look appetizing.
I'll find somethin' else.
We may be competing
for big prey,
but a chef has
to have standards.
Doesn't matter how big it is,
it still has to taste good.
Something I'm sure
that lousy swordsman
doesn't understand.
[DORRY laughing]
That's interesting‐‐
so Broggy's guests
are friends of yours, then?
I saw a goofy‐looking guy
with a long nose
and a woman there.
That's Usopp and Nami.
They said they weren't even
gonna get off the ship.
I guess they wanted to have
an adventure after all.
If they're your
friends, then I guess
I can thank you, too,
for these yummy refreshments.
[pterodactyl screeches]
So, Dorry, tell us...
Does it really take a year for
the log to reset on this island?
Yes.
Didn't you notice all the
mounds of human skeletons
that are lying around here?
I guess it's hard not to.
The people who come
to this island tend to die
before their logs are reset.
Some become dinosaur food,
some die from heat or
thirst or starvation.
Others are killed because
they stupidly attack us.
Whatever the case,
they all die here somehow.
An entire year on
this island just seems
to be too long. So far,
no humans have been able
to survive here
for the full year.
[VIVI]
What are we going to do?
Even if we could manage
to last here for a year,
who knows what could
happen by then?
My country could be lost.
She's right.
Plus, I'd get bored
here after a year.
Isn't there anything else
we can do about it, old man?
[DORRY] Hm... We do have
an Eternal Pose here,
but it's magnetic link is
to our home village, Elbaf.
Basically, that Eternal Pose
is what Broggy and I
have been fighting for with
our duels this whole time.
Of course, you can try
to take it by force.
No, that's not gonna work.
Elbaf isn't the place that
we're trying to get to.
We just wanna get to the island
that's right after this one.
Right?
[VIVI]
Yes.
We must stay on the route
that's going to lead us
to my home, or else
there's no point.
Yeah.
Maybe you can try
sailing forward randomly.
You may get there eventually,
if you're real lucky.
[LUFFY laughs]
Maybe so.
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
We may actually get there!
[laughs]
[DORRY] Now that I think
about it, someone did
leave the island once
before his log was reset.
[LUFFY]
And what happened to him?
[DORRY]
How should I know that?
[LUFFY] I'm sure he was able
to get to the next island.
[DORRY]
That must be it!
[DORRY, LUFFY laughing]
[VIVI]
What is so funny?
[DORRY, LUFFY laughing]
[VIVI] I don't understand
what these two idiots
are laughing about
at a time like this!
[BROGGY] A brave warrior
of the seas, you said?
What's that exactly?
I'm talking about you guys!
What I really want is to be
like the two of you someday!
Huh? You wanna be a giant?
[NAMI]
You hear that?
[USOPP]
That's not what I mean!
I wanna be a great warrior.
I wanna be brave
and proud like you
and the others from Elbaf.
[laughs]
I see.
You know, in Elbaf,
even though our lifespans
are longer than yours are,
we still think about
how we will die.
We know everything
we have and everything
we are will one day cease
to exist, like everything else.
But it is worth it to die
a true warrior of Elbaf,
without sacrificing
your pride.
That is what we call
dying with honor.
To die such a great death
would be an
everlasting treasure.
It's what we seek in Elbaf.
So pride is your treasure.
That's great!
I've decided to learn from you!
From now on,
I'll call you Master!
[BROGGY]
Huh?
[DORRY groans]
[gasps]
[screams]
[DORRY groans]
[LUFFY, VIVI gasp]
Old giant guy!
[LUFFY]
What's going on?
Why did it explode?
That was the same
alcohol we had with us
on the ship, wasn't it?
[DORRY groans]
[VIVI]
It exploded in his stomach!
The other giant must
have booby trapped it!
Hold it! Were you
even watching them?!
They fight their
duels honorably!
No way he'd do that!
All right, then who did do it?
You strangers.
[DORRY growls]
It wasn't Broggy.
No way...
No warrior of Elbaf
would dare. So...
Who else is there to suspect
on this island then...
...besides you?
[KAROO screams]
Let's get out of here!
There's no use talking
to him right now.
I doubt running
would do us any good.
Hold on to this and stay back.
You're going to... fight Dorry?
[panting]
[knuckles crack]
Yeah. I don't want to,
but we have to settle this.
Don't do it, you guys! Stop it!
Dorry, please just listen to me!
We don't know anything about
the explosives in the barrels,
I promise! We wouldn't do that.
You can't be in any shape to
fight right now, so please stop!
Right.
Why should I believe you liars?!
[yells]
[gasps]
[groans]
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
All right, then, Gum‐Gum...
[LUFFY grunts]
[yells]
[groans]
Gum‐Gum...
[DORRY panting]
[LUFFY]
Sorry.
...Rocket!
[DORRY groans]
[LUFFY growls]
[screams]
‐‐[DORRY groans]
‐‐[LUFFY yells]
[DORRY growls]
[LUFFY gasps]
[gasps]
[DORRY gags, coughs]
[VIVI]
No! Luffy!
I see now.
He has some power from...
[coughs]
...one of the Devil Fruits!
[DORRY] It seems...
I underestimated...
‐‐...him.
‐‐[gasps]
[panting]
[VIVI]
Luffy! Are you all right?
How is he?
[VIVI]
He should be okay.
I guess you were
right about fighting.
He's certainly a lot calmer now.
[LUFFY]
Well, I'm not!
The old guy was right
about one thing, anyway.
The other giant would never
do anything like this.
But I know that our friends
wouldn't do it either.
They aren't like that.
Yeah. Then who?
[LUFFY] There must be
somebody else on this island.
[MR. 3]
The key to winning any game
is to know your opponent's
state of mind.
For now, we have succeeded
in confusing our enemy.
They are no doubt wondering
about the mysterious bomb
that we delivered.
And about the identity
of their invisible enemy.
Our first target
was the long‐bearded
giant, Dorry.
I knew, of course, that it
would be nearly impossible
to finish him off,
but the damage done to
his stomach by the bomb
must have been considerable.
Now...
We can sit here enjoying
our tea while relaxing...
...and wait for the
next duel to start.
So we stay in the
background and let the giant
kill off the injured one?
[MR. 3 chuckles]
Yes, that's exactly right.
That's certainly
an indirect method.
[MR. 3] Again, you have
to consider your enemy.
Warriors like these two
operate in much the same way
as wild boars.
They can be intimidating
in a head‐on fight,
but they don't have
the brains to think beyond
their immediate circumstance.
So why bother going
after them directly
when you have the intelligence
to destroy them indirectly?
[MR. 3 chuckles]
[MR. 3]
Hm...
[MR. 3] Why can't you
just get the tea yourself,
Miss Golden Week?
[MR. 5] And just what
are we supposed to do
with the Straw Hat Gang?
Straw Hat Gang...?
Oh, you're talking
about the little brats
who found out
the Boss's secrets.
We can start by luring
them out one by one.
The order doesn't matter really.
Let's start with the one
closest to my tea set.
I have a personal
motto, you know:
And that is, "Big crimes
via cheap tricks."
[laughs]
There are plenty of good
ways to defeat any enemy‐‐
all without fighting.
Hey, Mr. 3, refill.
Yeah. While you're up.
[MR. 3]
Can't you savages take some time
to actually savor your tea?!
[rumbling, explosions]
[gasps]
That's their signal... isn't it?
[rumbling, explosions]
Well, damn. Guess my time is up.
[BABY DINOSAUR whines]
Oh! Sorry, buddy.
[ZORO]
Ow! God, let go!
I said I'm sorry, come on!
I don't have time to
mess around with this!
Cut it out, you little brute!
Seriously, I do not
have time for this!
I don't have any
big game to bring back
and that was the signal.
Dammit. Guess my time's up.
[BROGGY]
Well, there's the signal.
It's really been active today.
You're really going?
But your wounds from the
last battle haven't healed!
Please!
Dorry can't be doing
any better than me!
[BROGGY laughs]
A few scratches won't
take me out of a duel!
That would sure make me a poor
excuse for a brave warrior.
[laughs]
[panting]
[LUFFY]
Wait, giant guy!
Don't!
[VIVI] You can't fight,
Dorry! You need to rest!
You'll die if you
push yourself too hard!
I will fight... I am Dorry...
I will‐‐ [sputters]
...fight... for Elbaf's
pride and die as a warrior.
[panting]
[DORRY panting]
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[ZORO]
Ah, great! I'm lost again.
[USOPP]
Nami's disappeared!
What am I gonna do?! Luffy?
[LUFFY] Someone's interfered
with the giants' duel,
and that just isn't right!
Who is it? Show yourself!
[USOPP]
Hey, who are they?
[VIVI]
Baroque Works!
[LUFFY]
It was you!
[USOPP] How dare you violate
the warriors' battle,
you scoundrels!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Broggy's Bitter
Tears of Victory!
The Conclusion of Elbaf!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!