Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Third Gear!
It's open.
All right! Time to head out!
No way! How'd you
make yourself all tiny?
All right! Back to normal!
Hang on, Robin!
Stupid pigeon guy!
I can't wait to kick your ass!
Secret Technique.
Owl Thrashing!
Chapapapapapapa!
Beans Left!
You call that an attack?
This is terrible!
He's right--He's
fighting on our side now.
I better help him.
There it is! The real stuff!
That's cola, for sure!
Come to papa!
Super!
Chapapapa. Oh, come on!
It's not like
anything's gonna change
'cause you drank some cola.
Get ready.
Chapa? For what?
Another round of
your flimsy punches?
Gimme a break.
Strong Hammer!
Dobeba!
Amazing!
Oh, you were right.
My punches were pretty flimsy.
But don't worry--that's
all gonna change.
"Zoro Busts Out a New Technique!
The Sword's Name
is Sniper King?"
Oh, hey, Franky.
I've gotta tell you something
while there's still time.
Zoro and Sniper King got
their wrists cuffed together
with those Sea
Prism Stone Handcuffs!
They what?
You're tellin' me we're on
the hunt for two keys now?
One for Robin and
those two bozos?
Yeah, exactly.
How stupid can this get?
Alright. At least I know
how deep of a hole we're in.
Chapa!
You've really
got me fired up now!
Chapapapapapapapa!
Oh, boy. He just
won't stay down.
Talk about tough.
Oh, I'll show you tough.
Franky.
Destroyer canon!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I've gotta dislocate
my shoulders to do this.
Maybe you shouldn't do it then!
Chapapapa. Moron.
That won't work.
I'm a Six Powers master.
No bullet can move
as quickly as I can!
It doesn't matter how much
you run around or how fast.
It's practically
impossible for anyone
to escape my
Franky Destroyer Canon.
These aren't just any canons.
They're loaded with
tracking cannonballs!
Tracking cannonballs?
Does he mean they're cannonballs
that can sense their
target and track it down?
I've never even heard
of technology like that!
This guy's amazing!
Hey, wait!
You mean all the
"tracking" is done by you?
How can you still
run that damn fast?
Chapapa, why am I letting
this idiot chase
me around like this?
Aw, man, he disappeared again.
Come out!
Searching for me is pointless.
I'm a master of
the Shave technique.
With its power,
not only am I faster
than the speed of lightning,
I'm also completely silent.
Just like an owl
patiently hunting his prey.
I always carry out a
flawless assassination.
Just like an owl, huh?
Precisely.
My target doesn't
realize I'm upon them
until the moment of their death.
He was hiding over here.
Yeah, all that bragging
was real stealthy of you.
Cocky jerk. How dare you
humiliate me like this!
No one humiliates CP9 and lives!
Shave!
Iron ball!
Whoa! Be careful!
Dammit! We're over the ocean!
Franky!
This is bad!
The current's too strong.
It'll drag him
straight to the waterfall.
And there's nothing I can
do to help him in the sea.
Franky! Swim
with all your might!
Chapapa. No matter
what, I'll be fine.
I'll just use my
moonwalk if I go over.
Not good. I can hardly move.
Talk about a
damn strong current.
And I'm gonna run out of air.
I'm doubly screwed, here.
Chapapa!
Just hurry up and drown!
Yoyoi!
There's no way.
He busted out of the fridge?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you! I am so full!
Holy crap, he got fat!
You cannot be serious!
Did you eat every
piece of food in there?
I really don't have
any desire to die today!
I'm already at the basin!
Don't fall!
Don't fall! Don't go over!
Franky Butterfly!
Chapapapa! You are
going over that waterfall!
Moon Walk!
Solid Beast!
Ugly bastard!
Chapa!
Weapons Left! Eat this!
Paper Art!
Slime!
Chapapapapapapapa!
Come on! What the hell was that?
So close! Too bad!
Dammit. This is serious.
I've gotta get to shore, pronto!
One Liter Cola Cannon!
Coup de Boo!
Chapa!
Didn't learn your lesson, huh?
It takes more than strength
to defeat a Six Powers Master!
Strong Hammer!
Paper Art!
Now fall over the edge!
Strong Right!
Let's go!
Chapa!
Lemme go, you jerk!
I can't do the
Moon Walk with one foot
when I'm carrying someone else!
You're gonna make us fall!
Yeah, I realize that.
Tell ya what,
I'll let go of your leg.
After you've taken
me back to shore.
We could fight it out on land.
Or you could put all your energy
into fighting me right now
and see where that gets us.
I prefer the first option.
But if I'm goin' down those
falls, you're comin' to.
You and me. We're in
the same boat here.
So why don't we
just go back to shore?
Good job, that's
some fine kickin'.
Good, good. We're
almost there. Keep at it.
Chapapa. Just so you know.
This battle is gonna end
as soon as we're there.
Oh? Is that a fact?
Chapapapapapa!
Your damn right it's a fact.
'Cause I just remembered
a little technique of mine
that's sure to finish
you off in a single blow!
How funny. That makes
two of us, Fukurou.
Chapa?
Robin! I'm comin' for ya, Robin!
Shout if you can hear me!
We'll save you! No matter what!
I made you a promise, Robin.
We're not gonna leave
this island without you!
I don't care what happens, I'm
gonna get you back from them.
Robin!
Where the hell is
that number 2 key?
Zoro! I'm finished!
I'm too tired!
Gimme a piggyback!
No way!
Tempest Kick!
Finger Pistol!
What was that for?
Don't play innocent with me!
You were just pretending
to fire that kick at them.
You were aiming
for me, weren't you?
That's the most paranoid
accusation I've ever heard.
But I will admit you have
been getting in my way,
so if you wanna
fight, I'm ready.
What'd you say?
You've been getting in
my way, you stupid herbivore!
What are you talking about?
I like meat just as
much as the next guy.
Don't lie to me,
you long-necked freak!
You're a giraffe!
Now why don't you run along
and eat some tree leaves?
I can tell you're pretty
insistent on fighting me.
So why don't you just sit
tight and wait for me here.
I'll finish off
the prey on my own
and then we can settle this.
Hold it!
We're gonna fight alright,
but you're not taking my prey!
Wow! I've always
wondered about this!
You too, Zoro!
Didn't you just
ask me the other day
who you think is stronger,
a giraffe or a wolf?
I bet you're just
dying to find out.
Not really.
I see! Yep, I guess
we're both really curious
to see who'd win in
a fight between them!
No, I said I--
Just leave this
one to me, alright?
So the prediction of the world's
most feared pirate hunter
and the notorious swordsman of
the Straw Hat Pirates is-- oh!
He gets the feeling the wolf has
the greater edge strength wise!
Of course I do!
What's that you say? Really?
You don't think we should
overlook the giraffe though?
Very true, that is a good point!
That Sky Slicer of his was
pretty impressive indeed!
Yeah, it was powerful.
The fact is that wolves
aren't much more than cunning.
But beyond that,
they aren't exactly the
most capable of creatures.
You bastard!
That's the final straw!
So you wanna do this right now?
Excellent. Alright.
Now's our chance, Zoro.
I get it!
You're trying to get them to
stop paying attention to us
and start fighting each other,
and then we'll make our escape
while they're distracted, right?
Are you for real?
That just occurred to you?
And why are you sharing
that information with them?
I'm kind of embarrassed,
but you actually had us
going for a minute there.
The prey is always
the first priority.
Geez, Zoro! What am
I supposed to do with you?
We almost got away
and you completely
ruined the plan!
Big deal, it was a
pretty terrible plan
in the first place.
I've got an even
better survival plan!
Just do me a favor, Zoro,
and please keep your
mouth sealed shut this time.
Hmm, a giraffe or a wolf,
I wonder which one is cooler?
There's more to
life than just strength!
There are the
truly important things.
For example!
Being known as the
most stylish and hip!
Hm, which one is it?
Well, I'm having a
little trouble arguing
with his logic on this one.
Nothing to argue about.
Everyone knows that wolves
are both stronger
and cooler than giraffes.
You are so full of it!
All you have to do
is go to any zoo to see
that giraffes are a
million times more popular
with kids than wolves are!
Which obviously means
that giraffes are cooler!
Just the kind of stupid point
I'd expect a tall horse to make.
Don't you ever call me a horse.
I'm a giraffe, dammit.
It's working! Let's go!
That kind of distraction
won't last long enough
for us to get away.
What? Well, I sure hope you have
some sort of backup plan then.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You and me.
These cuffs are
the real problem.
But I've thought of a way
we can get them off of us.
Really?
What's it have to do with
playing rock, paper, scissors?
Whoever loses has to
chop off his own hand.
That is the most terrifying
idea I've ever heard!
I'm not done explaining,
just listen!
The first thing
we do once we've got
these cuffs off us is run
like hell until we find Chopper.
With his medical expertise,
he'll be able to
sew the hand back on
in no time at
all, understand?
We're not rag dolls!
Don't be ridiculous!
Wait.
I've got another plan
to get us out of this mess.
I don't even wanna hear it!
We won't be able to settle
this with words alone.
I'm ready to go when you are.
And let's up the stakes,
the winner gets to keep
the prey all to himself.
What the--?
Shing!
Alright, Sniper King.
Just hold that posture.
You are now a sword.
Someone get me a lawyer!
There is no way I am not
gonna sue your ass off for this!
So, what's your plan now?
Just take me to shore already.
I wanna hurry up and knock
you out and get this over with.
That's it. I'm sick
of your talking.
Sick of it.
I'm gonna shut you up
right here and now!
Super Cartwheel Iron Ball!
I'm gonna slam you into the
tower and smash you to pieces!
That's your plan?
Well that would pulverize
me, gotta give you that.
Franky Centaur!
Chapa?
I've got both your legs.
As long as I've got
you bound like this,
you can't move around!
That doesn't mean anything.
At the speed we're going.
There's nothing you can do
to slow us down now!
Well, let's just see about that.
70 mm Caliber Cola Cannon!
Just a little Coup de Vent!
He stopped our momentum!
We're not even
rotating anymore! Damn you!
That's far enough.
We're right above the shore.
Now, take this. 70 mm Caliber.
1 point 5 Max
Cola Power! Coup de--
Stop it! What're
you trying to do?
Just give up already,
you bastard!
Coup de--
Vent!
Super!
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
I can't keep my word.
Maybe I am just like
the doctor after all.
If he put his life on the
line to save his country,
then I want to put my life
on the line to save my friends.
Everyone, please stay away.
I'm about to lose control.
On the next One Piece:
"Uncontrollable!
Chopper's Forbidden Rumble!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!