[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me
my head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really, really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til
I get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[cheering]
[TOWNSPERSON A]
Welcome to the Grand Line!
[TOWNSPERSON B] Greetings and
good tidings, brave travelers!
[TOWNSPERSON C] We're happy to
have you here in Whisky Peak!
[USOPP]
They seem happy we're here...
[LUFFY laughs]
What the hell's
wrong with 'em...?
[TOWNSPERSON D] You're
always welcome in our town!
[IGARAPPOI] It contains
all the flavorful benefits
of a fine wine but zero alcohol.
Yeah, you're right!
It's delicious!
You quitin' already Zoro?
This is a new feeling;
I think it's full...
It's all mine...
Now go! I want them alive.
[ZORO] I count a hundred
of you scumbags, give or take.
One of them escaped from the
room when we weren't looking.
And I'll fight all of you,
you hear me... Baroque Works?!
Ugh! How do you know our name?
That's some secret.
[IGARAPPOI]
If you know all of our secrets,
then we are left with no
other choice but to kill you.
[IGARAPPOI]
And another gravestone...
...shall be added to
the cactus rocks tonight...
[chuckles]
Kill him!
[gasping]
He... disappeared!
[LUFFY] "Explosion!
The Three Swords Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!"
[MR. 9]
He's gone!
[IGARAPPOI] What?! But how
the hell can he just disappear?
‐‐[MAN A] Ahh!
‐‐[MAN B] Huh?!
[ALL gasp]
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasping]
[ZORO]
Hmm.
[MAN D]
Who do you think you are?
[MAN E]
Fire!
Incompetent morons!
They just shot each other!
Yeah, and the pirate got away!
Ugh! Just kill him!
He's only one man!
Hmm? Hmm?!
Ask yourself, will one
gravestone really be enough?
[gasps]
There he is! Now!
No! Don't shoot! Wait!
You're going to shoot me!
Stop!
Igarappa!
[IGARAPPOI]
All right, you idiots...
Where did he
escape to this time?
So that thing's a weapon, huh?
Dangerous...
I better watch it.
It seems as though this
guy might actually be able
to put up a fight,
even against us...
Can he possibly be
so arrogantly stupid
that he thinks he can
fight all of us by himself?
What kind of a man would
even consider challenging us
after knowing that we're
all with Baroque Works?
[snoring]
[SANJI] Ladies, please...
Come a bit closer.
And now it's time for...
...Usopp cheer
number 721. Now, go!
[NAMI] So... Whiskey
Peak is really home
to a whole nest
of bounty hunters?
You know, I had a feeling
that might just be the case.
[MAN 1]
He couldn't have gone far!
Let's find him, men!
[ZORO] Ah, yes... my new
recruits from Loguetown,
Yubashiri and Kitestsu the 3rd.
Now's as good a
time as any to see
what you two are made of,
and with these thugs,
we don't need to hold back!
[MAN E]
Hahaha! I got you now!
Huh?!
Die!
Damn!
Up first... Yubashiri.
Light... Well‐balanced...
There's the sneaky rat!
This way, guys! Hold it!
Well, I guess they found me.
[MAN H]
He's coming your way!
He's mine!
No way!
[MAN J chuckles]
Time to die!
[roars]
[MEN]
Miss Monday!
Awww! And that wine
must have cost a fortune.
What a waste, huh?
Huh?! What the
hell is it doing...?
Well, Kitestsu the 3rd,
you're quite sharp,
but you're also a bit of
a troublemaker, aren't you?
A good sword only cuts
when its master directs it to.
Cursed or not, you're going
to listen to me now.
[CHILD]
Die!
No! Please have mercy on
the little boy! I beg you!
Please, kind sir,
have mercy on us!
Or, try some blinding powder!
[ZORO] You'd be better off
trying that cheap trick
on someone who's more
likely to fall for it.
[ZORO]
The flat of the blade is mercy.
Agh! He just keeps on climbing!
Corner the guy!
[PERSON A]
Over there!
[PERSON B]
Cut him off!
[PERSON C]
Around the back!
[PERSON A, PERSON B]
Right!
I dreamed someone stepped on me.
My darling, you look lovely.
Would you share
this dance with me?
[snoring]
[NAMI] Oh, seriously?! This is
all the treasure they have?
This is a pathetic excuse
for a bounty hunters' nest!
Whiskey Peak is a
thoroughly useless town.
[MAN M] Hahaha!
There's nowhere to run now!
Huh?
[ZORO]
Well, that was fun. See ya...
Oh no! Look out for the ladder!
[PERSON D] Look out!
He's coming right for us!
Shoot him!
Two sword style...
...Hawk Wave!
I wouldn't be standing
there if I were you.
All right, that was too close...
[MISS MONDAY]
It was a good effort,
but there is no man
who can best my strength.
Now you die, swordsman.
[MISS MONDAY] Taste my
Superhuman Brass Knuckles!
Well, we've wasted‐‐ [coughs]
Ma‐ma! Well, we've
wasted a lot of time,
but at least we've
finally put an end to him.
Now, let's go.
[MISS MONDAY screams]
[MR. 9]
Miss Monday?!
[MISS MONDAY cries]
[ZORO]
What's the matter, muscle woman?
Didn't you want to pit
your strength against mine?
[ZORO]
Well, I guess you lost...
Is that all you can offer,
Baroque Works?
'Cause your gonna need
to do a lot better than that.
It can't be...!
He really beat Miss Monday!
No! It's just not possible!
[gasps]
Now it all makes sense!
The Marines must have made
a mistake on that poster.
It does make sense!
I can understand why
this guy would have
a thirty‐million berry
bounty put on his head.
He must be the real
captain of those pirates!
Yeah. He must be...
It seemed strange
that that weakling would
fetch such a high price.
[IGARAPPOI] Even if this
guy is the real captain,
this is getting disgraceful.
The Boss put us
in charge of this town,
and he's not going
to be very pleased
if we lose to one measly pirate.
Well, then, looks as
if we finally get to fight.
[MR. 9]
Something you may not know,
in Baroque Works, the
smaller an agent's number is,
the greater their power, as well
as their rank in the company.
Take the two of us,
Mr. 9 and Mr. 8,
we're single‐digit agents.
And don't forget Miss Wednesday.
Our abilities are much greater
than the riffraff you've been
fighting against so far tonight.
Hmph! I've found that
fancy titles mean nothing
when it comes to fighting.
The strongest wins,
and that's it.
[IGARAPPOI]
Igarappa!
Let's go, Miss Wednesday!
Of course, Mr. 9!
[whistles]
Come here, Karoo!
Quaaaaaaack!
No, not shake! Now, come here!
Come on, Karoo.
Show them how fast you are!
Leave them in the dust...
Quaaack!
I didn't tell you
to sit, now did I?!
You kidding...? A duck?
[MR. 9 laughs]
You get distracted so easily.
How can you hope
to follow my acrobatics?
You better prepare for...
my Bloody Bat!
Hahaha!
You'd better be careful not
to chip your precious blades!
[MR. 9]
What's the matter?
Are you too afraid to fight me?
What happened to
your fancy acrobatics, huh?
Watch really carefully, now!
Aaaaah!
[crash]
[ZORO] Is this really
the best they can do?
There's better. I'm still here.
Are you ready... Mister Bushido?
Take a look at this.
What do you think, bad boy?
Hm?
Now enjoy my perfume dance...
[coughs]
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Good boy.
And now... Peacock Slasher!
Go, Karoo!
Quaaaack!
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
You ran right past him!
Man, these guys are so pathetic,
fighting them is starting
to get embarrassing.
[IGARAPPOI] He slipped
down through that hole.
That won't keep him safe...
[IGARAPPOI]
Come back here, swordsman,
and get a taste of
just how dangerous I am.
That horn of his
complicates things...
How do I get close
enough to fight?
Aaaaugh!
[MR. 9] You may
have won the first fight,
but you won't get away with it.
No tricks from you this time!
[ZORO] I didn't trick you;
you jumped off a building!
Now for my Home Run Sneaky Bat!
[MR. 9] Hahaha! What'cha
gonna do now, tough guy?
Kick your ass.
Hmph! Excellent work
[chuckles] Come on...
Do it Mr. 8! Kill him, now!
Hahaha! You won't get away!
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
That's right. Don't move.
If you even think about doing
anything foolish, Mr. Bushido,
your friend here will
be paying the price...
[snores]
Hahahah! Well done,
Miss Wednesday.
It looks like there
will be no escape
for the swordsman this time,
unless he wants
his friend to die.
You idiot!
Can't he at least wake up
when he's being held hostage...?
[IGARAPPOI]
Preparing to fire.
Firing squad... ready!
[ZORO]
What?!
Igarappappa!
Oh great, more guns!
[gasps]
Aaaaaah!
[IGARAPPOI]
Igarappappa!
[ZORO] Gotta borrow
your stomach, Luffy.
All right... Done.
[ZORO] Now maybe I can
get some peace and quiet.
Where am I? How did
I get outside? That's weird.
[MAN 1] Three single‐digit
agents lost to one man.
I never thought I'd see
the day that would happen.
[MAN 2]
We've got to escape from here,
but where do we go?
We're just gonna
have to find some place
to hide until
this all blows over.
The Unluckies are here...! No!
Now hold on a second.
I know it looks like
we're running away,
but we're not, I promise!
Please spare us...!
Please don't report us
to the Boss, okay?
Aaaaaah!
[MR. 5]
Hold it!
[MISS VALENTINE]
There's a lot of action tonight
for such a sleepy town.
Shouldn't everyone be in bed?
[MR. 5] Heh! The Boss sends us
all the way to the front lines,
and this is what we find...?
What a pathetic little group...
[explosion]
[screams]
Hmm?
[IGARAPPOI pants]
Can't die here...
I have an important
mission to complete.
I must keep going...
[MR. 5] Three of you lost
against a single pirate...?
Now that's just sad.
[gasps]
[IGARAPPOI]
Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Really...
Can't do your jobs...? Hm.
[laughs]
Well...
That's clearly the difference
between our rank and yours...
Ugh... You came here...
just to laugh at us?
Nah... That's a bonus...
Ahahaha! We're here
under the Boss's orders.
Hahaha! With you
guys here to fight,
we can finally defeat him.
He doesn't stand a
chance against you...
[MISS WEDNESDAY] That's right!
Let's track him down
and show him what
Baroque Works can really do!
[MR. 5] Seriously, Miss
Wednesday, stop with the jokes.
We didn't come here
to clean up your mess.
[MISS VALENTINE] You really
think that we'd come all the way
to the end of the Grand Line,
to hold your hands?
Ha! You're even more
pitiful than you look.
[MR. 9] But... But then what
mission are you here for?
You mean you
haven't figured it out?
There are people here whose
crimes against the company
are grave enough that the Boss
has sent us to deal with 'em.
[MR. 9]
Huh?
[MR. 5] He said someone
had learned his secrets...
I don't know
what secrets exactly,
and I don't wanna know.
Obviously, someone else did...
But knowing them is
against company rules...
Our motto is mystery.
Everyone's identity is
to be kept strictly secret,
no matter who they are.
And if someone's dumb enough to
nose around the Boss's business,
well then, that's a crime
punishable by death.
So, while we were conducting
our search to find out
who had uncovered
the Boss's secrets,
we learned something. Hahaha!
It turns out...
A rather high ranking individual
from a certain kingdom
has somehow managed to
infiltrate Baroque Works.
[MR. 9] A kingdom...?!
Wait, wait, hold on a second!
I may be wearing a crown,
but I'm not a king or
anything like that, I swear.
It's just an
innocent little hobby.
Shut up you idiot...
You still don't get it.
We need the people
from Alabasta.
They're the ones
who angered the Boss.
[IGARAPPOI]
They know...! It's all over now.
Die...! Igarappappa!
You will not lay a
hand upon our princess!
Not while the captain of
Alabasta security still stands!
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Igaram!
[MR. 5] Igaram,
Captain of Alabasta security
and Princess Vivi Nefertari,
of Alabasta Kingdom,
we have come here in the name
of the Boss of Baroque Works,
to see that you are
both eliminated.
[gasps]
This could be good...
I left Luffy down
there with them.
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with you
'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts invade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're
watching it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be
with you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[ZORO] Why do I have
to help Nami make money?
Can't she do it herself?
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
[ZORO] What's wrong, Luffy?
I have to fight you, too?
[LUFFY] I'm gonna beat
you up, you ungrateful jerk!
[ZORO]
What are you talking about?
[LUFFY]
Don't give me that!
I'm not gonna forgive you!
Now, fight me!
[ZORO]
You can't be serious...
[LUFFY] On the next
One Piece: "All Out Battle!
Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!