Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[DOGGUIN] If any of you
so much as touch this lady,
you'll regret it!
What the heck is going on here?
Isn't that penguin
one of the zombies?
Did you notice
his fighting style?
It can't be.
Hey! Dumbass!
You're really starting
to piss me off, chum!
You're fighting the
wrong enemy, idiot!
The girl is one of our targets!
[DOGGUIN] Anyone who
mistreats a lady is gonna get
a crash course in table
manners from yours truly.
You got that?
You crappy zombies!
That dog-penguin is--
It's him. I'm sure of it!
They're stubborn,
huh? What a pain.
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
[JIGORO] One-Sword Style!
36 Caliber Phoenix!
That move! Zoro!
Zoro! What's your problem?
That's dangerous!
Scars on the back are the
shame of a swordsman, but...
[FRANKY] What the--?
[LUFFY]
Arrrggh!!
This sucks! Stop it!
Lemme outta here!
Is that a coffin?
[LUFFY] Open up this box and
let me out! You hear me?
[ROBIN] That voice.
What are you doing
in that box, dumbass?
Why'd you go and get
yourself caught like that?
Hey! Straw Hat!
[TARARAN] That's far enough.
[TARARAN] Hey! Hey!
Monkey! Monkey! Monkey!
All those stories you've
heard about Spider Monkeys?
You're looking
at one! That's me!
A giant spider!
Even for a monkey, that's
damn big. It's a monster!
[LUFFY] I'm warning you!
Lemme outta this box or else!
[TARARAN] Ah! Looks like
we've got another one!
It sounds like it hit the floor!
Damn it! What are you
punks gonna do to him?
Oh, don't worry.
You'll find out soon enough,
since you're gonna be next.
But I'd be more worried
about myself, if I were you!
You've got me
in front of you,
and armored warrior zombies
closing in from behind.
There's no escape!
Prepare for annihilation!
[LUFFY] "Chivalry Remains!
The Traitorous
Zombie Protects Nami."
Hey! What're you trying
to pull here, Newbie?
[RANDOM WILD ZOMBIE 347A] Our
Master's orders are absolute!
We zombies couldn't oppose
them even if we tried!
But that doesn't
affect him at all!
What makes him different?
And wait, why is he
as strong as a General?
[DOGGUIN] My power is one
that is not bound by logic.
It makes the
impossible possible.
This unstoppable
force that rages
like a hurricane is
none other--than love.
I'm not exactly
sure how this works,
but if he's saying stupid things
like that, that must be Sanji.
[CHOPPER] You're right!
Hey Sanji, is that
really you in there?
Or maybe you're just
friends with Sanji?
Either way, he's our friend,
so maybe we should--
[DOGGUIN] Shut your trap,
you damn dirty pirates!
Whoa!
I guess that means we're
still his enemy after all.
[loud crashing]
What's that?
[CHOPPER] I don't know,
but it sounds big.
[USOPP]
Haven't we suffered enough?
[ABSALOM] Lola! Stop!
[CHOPPER and USOPP]
A warthog in a wedding dress?
[ABSALOM]
Don't be hasty! Please!
Listen to your Commander, Lola!
Catch me if you can,
you little cutie!
Listen, you beast,
I'm ordering you to stop!
Well, if you insist,
then I guess I can!
If you want me that bad, then--
[LOLA] Bridal Martial Arts.
Embrace of your Princess!
Oh, please no!
[CHOPPER and USOPP]
Uh okay.
[LOLA] Now that I have
you where I want you.
I want a taste of
your sweet sugar.
[ABSALOM]
This isn't right, Lola!
I'm engaged! Remember?
I already told you I found
the woman I'm going to marry!
Sorry, I can't hear you.
Did you say that
you want to marry me?
You monster!
Are you trying to kiss me
or gnaw my face off?
Well! Don't mind if I do!
[ABSALOM] You're not
listening to me at all!
Mark of the Queen!
[USOPP] So are they
friends, or enemies?
[CHOPPER] Frienemies?
You don't give up.
Same to you.
Then let's get married.
Could you be any more dense?
Surprise kiss!
All right, that's enough!
You've made me mad!
What?
[LOLA] You wicked cat burglar.
You'll pay for stealing
Master Ab's greatest treasure!
[CHOPPER and USOPP]
Nami!
Ah! She found her!
[NAMI] Me? Treasure?
Hold on, I know
I'm a pirate and all
but I haven't
stolen anything yet.
[LOLA] You stole his heart!
And now I'm going to tear
yours out of your chest!
Watch out!
No, it's too late!
You won't lay a
hand on this lady!
Shut your mouth,
and get out of my way!
Dogguin!
Pendog!
That looks bad!
Are you okay?
[USOPP] Why didn't
he try to fight back?
I already told you,
even if it kills me,
I'll never kick a woman!
[CHOPPER] Awesome speech!
[USOPP] And I gotta admit,
you're a true gentleman
to see that thing as a woman.
What did you say?
[NAMI] Aaah! Guys, help me!
[ABSALOM] I'll be taking
my bride, thank you!
[USOPP and CHOPPER]
Nami, you can fly? Awesome!
Idiots! I'm being abducted here!
Huh? By who?
Hey, come back!
[ABSALOM] We'll hold the
wedding ceremony immediately.
All the preparations
have already been made.
[NAMI]
You're that invisible pervert
from the shower, aren't you?
Let me go!
Whoa. I guess he
really is invisible, huh?
Nami!
[NAMI thinking] Just like
last time. Who is this guy?
[ABSALOM] I was sizing you up.
In short, I've determined
that you're fit to be my bride.
[ABSALOM] You may
call me. Absalom.
It's the name of your future
husband, so remember it well!
You've got a
lot of nerve looking
at me naked and
acting like you own me!
I don't keep myself in shape
so some sick voyeur
can drool over me!
So don't treat me like a
piece of meat, you animal!
[NAMI] Thunder Charge!
[USOPP] Nami!
[USOPP]
Great job!
Now keep running! Don't stop!
[USOPP] We gotta
get out of this forest!
What happened?
Even after that,
he's still standing up?
That guy is not normal!
Just look at him!
[ABSALOM] What is this feeling?
Every nerve in my body
is dancing! I'm on fire!
I can feel it coursing
through my veins,
as if I've been
struck by lightning!
I see! There can
be only one answer!
This must be--Love!
[LOLA] You're not getting away!
[ZOMBIE HORSE] We gotta stop
staring and start moving!
Even if Absalom's here, it's
still our job to catch them!
[ZOMBIE PANDA] You're right,
and if we fail,
Perona's gonna punish us!
[ZOMBIE HORSE] We can't
mess this up again!
[ZOMBIE PANDA]
Yeah, we need a game plan!
Not good. At this rate,
they're going to hurt her.
I don't know why it is,
but I feel like I have
to protect that
lady no matter what.
Why is this body so weak?
I can't even take a single step!
[ZOMBIE KOALA] High-tail it
you guys, we gotta catch up!
Stop and heed my words,
Wild Zombies!
The woman is mine--
don't harm her.
Shut up!
Screw you, Perv-salom!
[ZOMBIE HIPPO]
You can't boss us around--
we only answer
to Mistress Perona.
This is out of
your jurisdiction!
Stay out of our way!
[ZOMBIE KOALA]
We don't need you, loser!
Go look at your girly mags!
[ZOMBIE HIPPO]
We can handle this!
I said stop, damn it!
[ABSALOM] I'm not a fool.
I know you're under
Perona's command.
[ABSALOM] But if you have
the sense to fear her,
you should know how
frightful I can be as well.
In other words, mind your
tongue when you speak to me.
You understand?
[ABSALOM] What the
hell do you want?
I won't let you
touch that lady.
What did you say?
Hey, newbie, cut it out, man.
Absalom's mad enough already!
No, not that!
Here it comes.
I warned you, didn't I?
Mind your tongue.
[LOLA] Get back here,
Cat Burglar!
Uh, hey Nami, I think
she's only chasing after you!
You're right!
What the heck is going
on here? What a pain!
[USOPP]
So I was thinking...
Maybe we could just
sorta split up?
Selling me out,
you heartless bastard?
[LOLA] Get back here
and die already!
Women are scary!
You'll have to
run faster than that!
Slow down, Nami!
[USOPP] You're using us as
a shield, aren't you? No fair!
[thinking] That's it!
I'm done for!
[thinking] So long, everyone.
It was nice knowing you.
Spread my ashes in the
East Blue for me, okay?
[LOLA] I'll brutalize you!
Huh? We're not dead after all.
You mean she's gone?
[USOPP] I guess she
really did just want Nami.
[BOTH] Wow, that's great.
What a relief.
Oh crap! Nami!
Okay, Chopper,
full speed ahead!
[CHOPPER] Right!
Talley-ho!
Give back my husband!
What does that even mean?
[USOPP] Nami!
You big pink eyesore!
Leave her alone!
[USOPP] Get out of here, Nami!
[LOLA] Love stops for nothing!
[USOPP and CHOPPER]
Damn it! She's too strong!
[FRANKY] I see. So that's
what happened to 'em.
[LUFFY] I'm warning you!
Lemme outta this box
or else! You hear me?
You captured our
crewmates, didn't you?
And carried them behind that
wall, like with Straw Hat.
Monkey monkey! Ah-ah-ah-ah!
That's correct.
And just wait,
because any second now
you'll be suffering
the same fate!
Zombie Generals in the front.
Zombie Generals behind.
I'd give up if I were you!
Whether you're a dumbass
monkey or a dumbass spider,
it looks like that big sticky
web that caught the Sunny
when we came here was your
work. If I'm not mistaken.
[FRANKY] In other words,
you were after us
from the beginning.
That must mean you
had us under watch, huh?
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
Yep! Once on Thriller Bark,
there's no hiding!
Mistress Perona's
Ghost Network sees all,
knows all, and tells all!
Frankly, you were
doomed from the start!
Those big ears
of yours must be useful
for gathering information, too.
And you certainly
like to run your mouth.
Huh? Sorry, what was that?
You mean they're just for show?
Franky.
Yeah. I got it.
We're completely surrounded.
"Worst-case scenario"
they call it, right?
What we need is a
last-second miracle plan.
Heh. You think I can handle it?
I'd love to see you try.
Put on a good show for me.
You got it.
Just follow my lead!
What's he doing?
Check this one out.
Hey! Don't do that--
have you lost your mind?
Coup de Vent!
[TARARAN] Aw, crap!
Aaaah!
You can't break the
friggin' bridge, man!
That's cheating!
[FRANKY] So? My plan
super enough for you?
[ROBIN] Well,
it certainly is violent.
Now, Cien Fleurs...
...Wing!
What?
[FRANKY] You... You can fly?
[ROBIN] Yes. For five seconds.
[FRANKY] Lame! But actually,
that's all we need.
Strong Right!
Sweet! I got the ledge!
That's the building where
they took Straw Hat.
If we can make it up
there, we can save him.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold it.
[FRANKY] Arm Return!
Just a little more. Hey!
[ROBIN] A fall like
that won't stop a zombie,
but at least they're trapped
in the courtyard for now.
That should buy us some time.
Excellent work, Franky.
Yeah, thanks a lot!
How generous of you
to pay a compliment
to your stepping stone!
How 'bout an apology?
[ROBIN] We should hurry
while they're still down.
[FRANKY] Hey! Don't pretend
like you didn't hear me!
You could try helping
me up at least!
Hm? See something?
Damn. I guess that's
the undead for you.
Now I'm angry.
You are gonna pay for this!
You realize
I'm a spider, right?
Gimme two seconds and
I'll be right up there!
I'd start running if I were you!
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
Hm? What is that?
Looks like something's
falling up there.
Aaaaaaaaah!
No, someone is falling!
Huh?
Aaaaaaaaah!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE GENERAL 347A]
You guys see that?
[BROOK] What do you
call a flying skeleton?
Air bone!
[FRANKY] Whoa, look! Who is
that falling from the sky?
[ROBIN] Take a closer
look and you'll see.
[FRANKY] Oh yeah! That afro.
[ROBIN] And that cane as well.
[FRANKY] I guess it's
fro-tally obvious, huh?
[ROBIN] Yes. You might
say you cane'nt miss him.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Appearing from the Sky!
That Man is the
Humming Swordsman!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!