[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
The Whitebeard Pirates
have successfully
pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines
still block the path to Ace.
The battle is heating up!
[MARINE N yelling]
[LUFFY grunts]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[ACE]
Why do any of them care?
I deserve to die like this.
Why can't they see I'm not
worth risking their lives for?
Please don't do this.
Just stop! Just let me die
like I'm supposed to!
Ace! You're my brother!
[PRISONERS shouting]
[IVANKOV]
Please listen! That's enough!
Kuma! Look, it's me!
Have you forgotten my face?
If you don't stop, friendship
be damned! I will fight back!
[DOFLAMINGO laughs] I don't
know what kind of a history
you two have,
but it doesn't matter.
Trust me, Emporio Ivankov.
There's really no use in
talking to him as he is now!
Doflamingo...
What're you saying?
Is something wrong with him?
[DOFLAMINGO] You're clearly
a friend of Bartholomew Kuma's,
so I doubt you'll
take this well.
The man you knew
as "The Tyrant Kuma"
is not the man you
see before you now.
Because that man is dead.
Hate to tell you though,
you're still not strong
enough to beat me.
Dammit! Ya cheap jerk!
Move that thing!
[HANCOCK]
Get your filthy hands off him!
[SMOKER groans]
My body's smoke.
How'd she hit me?
[MARINE JJ]
Wait a sec!
Why did the Pirate Empress
just save Straw Hat?
Hey, Hancock! What the
hell's wrong with you?
Don't tell me you're
resigning from the Warlords?
Shut your mouth!
The screaming fury in my heart
has rendered me
deaf to your words!
How dare you pin
my beloved down
with your boorish club
and threaten him?
You will die for your actions.
I've never felt this angry
in my entire life!
I'll feed you piece by
piece to wild animals!
Hah. The Kuja's Haki
is overwhelming.
[MARINES gasping]
[MARINE AA]
What the hell just happened?
I thought Hancock was
supposed to be on our side!
No! Look!
She's not saving him.
She's about to turn
Straw Hat into stone!
[HANCOCK]
I never stopped believing that
you'd make it here alive,
and now, here you are.
[HANCOCK]
Take this.
[HANCOCK] It's the key
to your brother's handcuffs.
[gasps]
[MARINE BB] Wow, she's really
doin' a number on him!
[MARINE CC]
Straw Hat's frozen in place,
he hasn't moved an inch!
Did she turn him to stone?
Thanks, Hancock!
[gasps] He said my name!
[HANCOCK gasping]
The touch of his hands...
They're strong, yet so kind!
[LUFFY]
Hancock.
Yay! You're so awesome!
I could hug ya forever!
I'll never forget this,
what a pal!
[MARINES shouting]
[HANCOCK gasping]
[MARINES gasping]
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you!
Oh, um, well...
it's really no trouble at all!
I'm just glad I could help out.
Never mind me though, Luffy,
just go and save Ace!
Oh, yeah, right!
Thanks again!
[HANCOCK gasps]
[SALOME hisses]
No way! He managed
to defeat the Pirate Empress!
Unreal! The stare
did nothing! He's a beast!
[HANCOCK panting]
[MARINE GG] He smothered her
into submission!
[MARINE HH] I can't believe
how easy he made it look!
Straw Hat Luffy's unstoppable!
Ah. Oh, Luffy. Oh, Luffy!
Oh, Luffy!
My love, you're too much.
Hold me like that again!
[HANCOCK]
The warmth of his embrace still
reverberates within my breast--
no, my entire body!
Could it be?
Perhaps...
This is... what people call...
[HANCOCK]
What they call marriage.
[bells tolling]
[CROWD]
Snake Princess, oh my gosh!
[MARIGOLD, SANDERSONIA]
Congratulations, sister!
[CROWD cheering]
Ah, there she is!
She's so pretty!
[FEMALE C]
Best wishes, Princess!
Oh. Oh, Luffy.
My darling.
You're beautiful.
[gasps]
I'm so happy!
Oh, yeah? Better get
used to it, baby.
Ah, yes.
[LUFFY]
Hancock...
Baby...
[HANCOCK]
Luffy...
Honey.
Baby!
[gasps] Luffy! Yes.
This union was meant to be!
Between us lies a thread
that links us together!
An unbreakable bond
that can't be cut.
It's a long and strong
red string of fate,
a mighty red serpent!
[giggles]
[SMOKER] You ain't
getting away, Straw Hat!
[growls]
[HANCOCK grunts]
Perfume Femur!
[SMOKER grunts]
[SMOKER]
Huh?
[SMOKER grunts]
[HANCOCK]
Stay back, you fool!
You shall not pass on my watch!
Jeez! The Empress is
really looking down on him!
Looking down so far,
she's started looking up!
Get out of my way, pirate!
You know what happens
to people who betray the Navy?
Well, do you, woman?
[HANCOCK]
I'll do whatever I like!
And you will allow it.
Because I'm beautiful!
[MARINES]
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
[LUFFY panting]
This is great.
It's the exact thing I needed.
Hold on, Ace. I'm coming!
Impossible! Kuma is dead?
Then who's that big guy
standing behind you?
Stop spouting nonsense!
You can't deceive me!
[MARINES grunting]
It's Iva!
[gasps]
And that big guy from before.
Hey, Iva! Be careful!
Don't let him get his paws
on you! They're dangerous!
[IVANKOV] I'm all right.
Kuma! Get out of my way!
[gasps]
[LUFFY] So, uh, are you guys
friends or something?
[IVANKOV] We were, but he's
not acting like himself.
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
I'm sure this is a lovely trip
down memory lane for you,
but I'm afraid the Kuma
you know is no longer with us.
This is the new model.
"New model"? Whaddya
think he's talking about?
He wants to get under my skin!
Yeah, okay. He's acting pretty
different than usual right now.
But he's still Kuma!
Wake up, buddy! Hey!
[IVANKOV grunts]
Damn it all!
Then again, he's always
been the quiet type.
[DOFLAMINGO]
Are you deaf or just stupid?
Trust me, it's no use
trying to talk to him.
It happened just a few days ago.
Dr. Vegapunk,
the Government scientist,
finally finished his
modifications on Kuma.
Now he's the ruthless
weapon of death
he should've been
from the start!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the former Bartholomew Kuma!
Doc Vegapunk? Mods?
What the hell are
you talking about?
[DOFLAMINGO] Kuma here
volunteered to be a guinea pig
in a study to build
the ultimate human weapon
run by the Government,
of course!
[DOFLAMINGO]
First, they modified his hands,
then his legs.
Although his mind was still
intact, they modified his body,
piece by piece,
until he was no longer
the same Kuma you know and love.
But that's nonsense!
Kuma always hated the
Government, you jerk!
As if he'd ever sacrifice
himself for their stupid plan!
Hey, Kuma!
Snap out of it! It's me!
[DOFLAMINGO]
Stop yelling.
It's starting to
get on my nerves.
I don't know what kind of deal
he had with the Government.
He was just fine a few days ago.
It's funny, but tragic.
Before you know it,
someone's gone.
[DOFLAMINGO]
In Kuma's case,
he doesn't even realize
he was ever human,
so the poor sap
might as well be dead.
Now he's just a monster
who the Government
has do their dirty work.
It's the latest, the greatest,
Pacifista PX-0!
Your new, old friend!
--[LUFFY grunts]
--[IVANKOV] Ahh!
[LUFFY, IVANKOV yelling]
[LUFFY grunts]
--[LUFFY grunts]
--[IVANKOV] Ahh!
[LUFFY, IVANKOV yelling]
[LUFFY grunts]
[IVANKOV growls]
Kuma! What's the big idea?!
Ya better stop shooting that
laser crap at me right now!
[LUFFY panting]
Yeah, I remember.
We will never meet again.
Farewell.
Even then, he knew.
What's wrong, Kuma?
Surely you recognize me!
[gasps] That was spooky!
Now where is he?
[PRISONERS shouting]
Huh?
[gasps]
[PRISONERS yelling]
Hey! Watch out,
you guys! Get away!
[PRISONERS gasping]
Pad Cannon.
[PRISONERS shouting]
[IVANKOV growling]
[IVANKOV]
Damn it Kuma, that's enough!
You forgot me!
But how about my Face Spectrum?!
Hah, hah!
[IVANKOV yelling]
[IVANKOV laughing]
[IVANKOV]
Hah! This ring a bell?
How about this? Galaxy Wink!
[IVANKOV grunts, sighs]
[IVANKOV chuckles]
Hee-haw!
Ah! How dare you attack
my sweet, succulent crew
of candy boys? You cad!
I don't take unfashionable
gestures lightly,
you conniving minx!
Vengeful Kick!
[PRISONERS gasping]
Work it, boss!
I have met a lot of people...
[PRISONERS]
Huh?
...but no one forgets my face!
No one has ever forgotten
my face in my entire life!
This mug is damn memorable!
[PRISONERS]
Oh. Uh, hmm.
[IVANKOV]
Kuma!
If you wanna forget who
you are, that's your business.
But, If you can't remember how
dangerous the great Ivankov is,
then I will beat it into you!
So, get ready, hon'!
[PRISONERS]
Uh, he is pissed.
[IVANKOV]
I'll take it from here!
All right, my battling beauties.
Keep going and back
Straw Boy up, okay?
[PRISONERS]
Roger!
[PIRATE AA]
'Kay Straw Boy, let's get 'em!
Thanks. Good luck!
[PIRATE BB] Come on ladies,
get to the scaffold!
[PRISONERS yelling]
[LUFFY grunts]
[MARINES grunting]
[MARINE I]
Huh?
[MARINE J] All of a sudden, they
just disappeared into the ice!
That doesn't make any sense,
unless Admiral Aokiji
used Ice Age again,
and I don't remember seeing
him do that, do you guys?
[MARINE K]
Where'd they go?
Uh, that's weird. This is warm.
The ice?
All clear. Okay.
Men! Listen up.
Blah-blah, blah-blah.
Buggy is the greatest.
Yada-yada-yada,
Buggy is amazing.
These are all things you guys
have heard plenty of times.
[PRISONER A]
Totally!
[BUGGY] But I want to get
the entire world chanting
those words when
their new, pirate savior
makes his appearance.
[PRISONERS] Ah...
Excellent plan, your Buggy-ness!
[PRISONERS laugh]
Ugh, really?
[BUGGY]
Let's go, men!
[PRISONERS, BUGGY shouting]
[laughing]
[BUGGY] Eh? Gah! Straw Hat's
gonna steal all my thunder!
Now commence operation:
"Make Captain Buggy
The King of the Pirates"!
Anything is possible
with me at the helm!
[PRISONERS]
Yeah!
The whole world
will be taken aback
with my onslaught
of awesomeness!
All of you, follow my lead
and don't mess anything up!
Forward, you fools!
[PRISONERS]
Yeah!
[MR. 3] I question the efficacy
of your latest strategy!
[MR. 3 panting]
[PIRATE CC groans]
[PIRATES]
Crocodile!
They're too many.
[CROCODILE]
I won't reach him like this.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE A]
Don't you even dream
of touchin' our Pops!
Get outta my way.
--[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yelling]
--[CROCODILE] Peons!
What a pain in the ass.
He's gonna mess up
our rescue mission.
[CROCODILE grunts]
I call this "Brilliant Punk"!
[CROCODILE gasps]
[JOZU growls]
He's fast. Too fast, and strong.
Quite the combination
for someone that size.
[JOZU grunts]
[CROCODILE]
Huh...
[DOFLAMINGO laughs] Congrats
on your escape from prison,
Gator Boy.
So, did you enjoy the
Pool of Blood during your stay?
Doflamingo.
Keep outta my business, or else.
It's not your concern.
Just making small talk.
So, listen. I think
we might make a good team.
[PRISONERS, LUFFY panting]
[MARINES]
Stop right there!
[PIRATE B]
Yeah, you wish!
Path's clear, Straw Hat!
Nice one!
Ace!
[gasps]
[PRISONERS yelling]
[LUFFY panting]
[MIHAWK]
Apologies, Shanks.
[LUFFY panting]
[MIHAWK] But I will not
hold back against him.
Hey, I know him!
[LUFFY]
"Hawk-Eye"!
[MIHAWK]
I wonder what is written?
Will my hand wipe
his name from history?
Or perhaps his fortune
shall spare him the fury of
this Black Sword I wield.
[LUFFY panting]
[NARRATOR] Luffy's progress
is halted by Dracule Mihawk,
Warlord of the Sea.
Cleaving apart the
massive wall of ice
surrounding the battlefield,
one blow from Mihawk's sword
will rend Luffy in two.
The Whitebeard Pirates counter
with a swordsman of their own,
but will his strength be enough?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
Luffy Comes Under the
Attack of the Black Sword!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!