Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[LUFFY]
"The Promise from a Distant Day!
The Pirates' Song
and a Small Whale!"
[HOGBACK]
All right, shut the gates.
[ABSALOM] This doesn't feel
right leaving Perona behind.
[HOGBACK]
We searched the whole island,
what else are we supposed to do?
[ABSALOM]
It's just strange.
Where the hell
did she disappear to?
[HOGBACK] Okay,
I think we're in the clear.
Drop the invisibility cloak.
Fasfasfasfasfasfas!
[HOGBACK]
A perfect escape! Fas!
[ABSALOM]
We really cut it close.
I was sweating some
invisible sweat there.
I'd still just like to know
why Kuma the Tyrant appeared
out of the blue
on Thriller Bark.
I can fill you in on that one.
Well, apparently Kuma
was sent to inform Moria
of who'd been chosen
to succeed Crocodile.
So there's a new Warlord?
Yes. And he's quite
the controversial figure.
His name's Teach,
but he goes by Blackbeard.
From what I hear,
he's a nasty piece of work.
Take a look.
Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
Fire Fist Ace.
Now awaiting execution
at the prison, Impel Down?
[HOGBACK]
Ace is easily
the most famous
henchman Whitebeard's got
working under him.
A fine gift for Teach
to present to the Government.
[ABSALOM]
True.
[HOGBACK]
There's a feeling out there
that this could
spell very bad news
for our Great Pirate Era.
The tides are turning
toward a maelstrom.
There couldn't be a worse time
for Moria to be
flat on his back.
I can see where you're
going with this, Doctor.
But I only care about one thing.
I want a nice wife.
Sure. Find me a corpse
that seems like your type.
I don't want a zombie!
I want a living woman
filled with blood and passion!
[USOPP] I can't believe
everyone passed out
in the courtyard and slept
through the whole day.
[FRANKY]
Are ya surprised?
We did fight for a
solid twenty-four hours.
[LUFFY]
I'm starving to death, Sanji!
[SANJI]
Then eat some more cheese!
I need more than cheese!
I'm a man, I have to have meat!
[SANJI]
Then help me bring
my cooking supplies
over to the courtyard.
Our grateful group
of survivors don't wanna
budge an inch from that place,
so we'll just
make the meal there.
Hope you don't mind.
We haven't felt the sun
on our skin in years,
so we're trying to soak it up.
My men are so relieved,
they're weeping with joy.
[USOPP] How can you
have this much energy?
It's weird. Really weird.
Are you certain that
you've got enough food?
[SANJI] We got back all the
food that was stolen from us.
On top of that, someone stocked
our stores with Moria's food.
I wonder who'd do such a thing.
Well, whoever they are,
they've got a kind heart.
[LOLA] As if the
food wasn't enough,
they left you all this, too.
You guys don't even
have to hunt for treasure--
it just delivers itself.
[NAMI]
I'm in Heaven.
This glass band is cool.
Yep! It looks slick.
I'm claimin' this one.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Don't take that. Right, Nami?
Oh, he can have it.
That one is just
costume jewelry.
[USOPP] That is not
what I expected you to say.
[NAMI]
But you?
You better not even think
of taking a single doubloon.
[LOLA] It would never
even cross our minds
to steal from
our saviors, Namizo.
Nice knife!
What did you just say?
Nothing! I'm sorry!
I didn't notice all
the gemstones in it.
Huh? It just kinda
slipped outta my mouth.
Who is Namizo? Y'know,
this is a little strange.
I've got this feeling like you
and I have met somewhere before.
Don't tell me you're... Lola?
I am, but...
I don't recall
telling you my name.
[NAMI]
It really is you, Lola!
I'm so glad we could meet again!
Lola?
What are you talking--
Whoa, hold on! The Lola?
Like the fat pig zombie Lola?
I doubt this makes
any sense to you,
so I'll explain later.
But for now...
...take this.
I want you to have it.
What? Wait, for me?
Are you sure?
[LUFFY and USOPP] Nami gave
away some of her treasure!
I'm headin' back in.
Is this everything
ya need me ta take?
[LUFFY and USOPP]
A storm must be coming!
A storm? Looks fine to me.
[LUFFY and USOPP screaming]
[ROLLING PIRATE 378A]
Now this is bliss.
C'mon, sun. Go on and
gimme everything ya got.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 378A]
I've never felt so alive.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 378B]
I'm just happy we are.
[LUFFY]
Hey!
[LUFFY] Sure hope
you guys are hungry!
It's Straw Hat!
Why didn't ya
ask us to carry that?
You guys have already
done enough for us!
[LUFFY]
Is Zoro up yet?
No, he's fast asleep.
He's in the mansion.
Get your ass up.
[LUFFY]
Chopper!
[FRANKY] Got everything ya
asked for bundled up here.
Oh, that's great, thanks!
[LUFFY]
How's Zoro doin'?
[CHOPPER]
I've never seen him
in such terrible
condition before.
He was teetering
on the edge of death.
It's bizarre.
Something happened
while we were passed out.
He was injured before,
but not like this.
[ROBIN]
It is strange.
And it's even stranger
that Kuma the Tyrant
would just up and leave.
And speaking of strange stuff,
why's Luffy so energetic?
[LUFFY] Yeah,
I don't get it, either,
but it's fine with me!
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
Ya wanna know what happened?
Then look no further!
We saw the whole thing
from start to finish!
Every damn detail!
And we can lay it out
like you were there!
[SANJI]
C'mere.
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
Hey, what's the big idea?
Sanji?
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
What gives?
The guy saved
your life, too, y'know.
[RISKY BROTHER MASK] Yeah, you
were tryin' to take his place,
but he knocked you out!
[SANJI]
Shut up. What did you two see?
Just hurry the hell up
and tell me what happened.
Well, after I
blacked out, I mean.
I know the first part.
--Huh?
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
That Warlord's power
was even crazier
than what you saw.
[RISKY BROTHER MASK]
He laid his paws on Straw Hat
and made this bubble
come out of him.
He said he'd extracted all
the damage done to his body.
Wait, he did what?
[RISKY BROTHER MASK] So he took
that big ball of suffering.
And then...
[KUMA] If you truly
wish to take his place,
then you must accept and
inflict his agony upon yourself.
As close to death
as you are already,
not only will it
undoubtedly kill you,
it will do so painfully.
Why don't you have a taste?
[RISKY BROTHER MASK] Just
the tiniest bit of that stuff
had the swordsman screamin'
like he was being murdered.
But that didn't stop him
from takin' on every ounce
of that big ball of pain.
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
It moved me to tears, man!
[RISKY BROTHER MASK]
Yeah! Same here, I was bawling!
I see.
That explains
why Luffy's just fine
and Zoro's damn near comatose.
Reckless moron.
Where the hell'd all
this blood come from?
Hey! Are you still alive?
Where'd that paw guy go?
What in the hell happened here?
What happened here?
Nothing at all.
Well c'mon!
Now that ya know,
let's go spread the tale
of how brave your friend is!
Damn straight!
Everybody's gotta hear this!
[SANJI]
Hold it.
You're keepin'
your mouths shut.
Zoro didn't do this
for Luffy's gratitude.
And besides,
how do you think
it would make Luffy feel
if he found out Zoro is
suffering from his pain?
Don't say a word or
I'll kick the crap out of you!
All right, you convinced me.
Yeah, you're absolutely right!
Everyone's still alive, right?
That's all that matters.
Now. Let's go eat.
Holy crap!
These Straw Hat
guys are so cool.
[RISKY BROTHER MASK]
With a crew like that,
their captain is
one lucky dude.
And now I know.
[LUFFY] Hey, you two,
where'd ya go?
Didn't you guys say you had
somethin' you wanted to tell us?
So what happened?
Why's it mean so much to ya?
Everyone's still alive.
That's all that matters.
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
Man.
I wanna tell 'em so bad!
[RISKY BROTHER MASK]
Right?
How're we supposed to sit
on such an amazing story?
What the heck?
[ROLLING PIRATES]
Let's dig in!
[RISKY BROTHER BROWN HAIR]
Man!
This is the most delicious
thing I've ever tasted!
[RISKY BROTHER MASK]
It's been years, entire years,
since we've had a proper meal!
[LOLA] I am so damn
happy to be alive!
There's plenty for everyone.
So don't hold back!
[ALL cheering]
Yohohohoho!
To indulge in
such delicacies again!
Why, my taste buds are leaping--
they're dancing
in unrestrained joy!
Oh my! But I don't
have taste buds, do I?
Will ya just
shut up and eat already?
[ROLLING PIRATE 378D]
Now that's a funny bone!
Yohohoho!
[BROOK] Honestly, though,
I, uh, 'scuse me.
Getting to gorge myself
on such mouthwatering
meals two days in a row,
I'm starting to worry
I've gained some weight!
You're nothin' but bones!
Now shut your damn jaw!
[ROLLING PIRATE 378D]
This skeleton's the best!
[ROLLING PIRATE 378J] How's a
skeleton able to talk, anyway?
[ROLLING PIRATE 378F]
I don't know, but I like 'im!
He's the funniest skeleton
I've ever seen!
[ROLLING PIRATE 378H] How can
you move without any muscles?
[ROLLING PIRATE 378I]
Ah, who cares, he's great!
[BROOK]
Oh, dinner!
[FRANKY]
Yeah!
[BROOK]
Dinner!
[FRANKY]
Come on!
[BROOK]
Dinner!
[FRANKY]
Oh, baby!
[BROOK]
Dinner!
[FRANKY]
Shake it!
[BROOK]
Dinner!
[FRANKY]
Super!
They haven't even
opened up the booze yet
and everyone's
already lost their minds.
[CHOPPER] It's as loud
as a battlefield in here
and he's sleeping
right through it.
[NAMI]
That's about normal.
I've seen him sleep
through typhoons.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Chopper, here!
Luffy!
[LUFFY] It's Zoro's portion!
Now drink up!
Back off!
It's gonna help him!
Zoro loves booze, it's
gonna make him feel better!
He needs medicine,
not booze!
[LUFFY] How 'bout meat?
That's like a medicine.
No, not quite.
Your concern'll just
have to be enough, okay?
[NAMI]
Your concern and that's it!
[piano playing]
I didn't even notice there
was a piano in this room.
[ALL celebrating]
Hey. What's this?
I thought you said you were
a violinist or something?
Yoho!
I am, but I can play
just about any instrument.
That so?
You're pretty talented.
Um... You mind talking
about what happened out there?
You had another witness.
I saw the whole thing.
I was quite touched
by the two of you.
By your bravery.
And your compassion.
Friendship is a beautiful thing.
You shouldn't put me
in the same boat with Zoro.
I just end up looking
stupid in comparison.
No.
You had just as much
resolve as he did.
There a song you'd like to hear?
Anything at all.
I gladly take requests.
Huh?
Anything I can think of?
Well. In that case--
[piano continues]
And you charged out--
♪ [BROOK (SONG)]
Yohohoho, yohohoho... ♪
I thought you said you were
taking requests, you jerk!
♪ [BROOK]
Yohohoho, yohohoho... ♪
♪ Yohohoho, yohohoho...
♪ [BROOK (SONG)]
Gather up all of the crew, ♪
♪ it's time to ship
out Binks' Brew ♪
♪ Sea wind blows,
to where, who knows? ♪
♪ The waves will be our guide
♪ O'er across
the ocean's tide. ♪
♪ Rays of sunshine
far and wide ♪
♪ Birds they sing, of cheerful
things, in circles passing by ♪
♪ [BROOK (SONG)] Bid
farewell to weaver's town, ♪
♪ say so long to port renown
♪ Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off ♪
♪ Cross the gold
and silver seas, ♪
♪ a salty spray
puts us at ease ♪
♪ Day and night, to our delight,
the voyage never ends ♪
I thought that was
Binks's Brew.
Wow, it's been ages since
I last heard this song.
Such a nostalgic feeling.
[piano continues]
Good pick, Brook!
I always loved this song.
Shanks's crew used to sing it.
[cheering]
[BROOK]
Of course, it's a classic.
All the pirates used to sing
it back in the good old days.
It was sung in
times of sorrow and joy.
Yohohoho!
[LUFFY]
So whaddya think?
You gonna join my crew?
We could use a musician, eh?
C'mon.
Ya got your shadow back.
You can sail anywhere
with us now, day or night.
[BROOK]
It's not that easy for me.
Although I'd like to,
there's something important
I haven't told you yet.
[LUFFY]
What's that?
[BROOK]
I have to keep my word.
I made a promise to a friend.
It's still my life's goal
to fulfill that promise.
And if I don't,
I wouldn't have the right
to call myself a man.
Oh. You're talking
about Laboon, right?
I know about that.
Franky and the guys
told me the whole story.
Is that so? Laboon.
I don't know how much
they told you exactly,
but he's a whale.
You see, there's a cape.
That's what I'm trying to say.
We've been to the Twin Capes
and we've met Laboon!
It's the truth, I swear it!
[LUFFY] And I can tell
you this for a fact, too.
Laboon has been right
there for fifty years,
waiting for his
friends to return.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 378C]
Hey.
Somethin' wrong, skeleton?
Why's the tempo slowin' down?
[piano continues slowly]
Consider this a
symbol of my promise
to come battle you!
[LUFFY] Of course,
it's a rush paint job,
so you'll have to be careful
and avoid hitting your head
or you'll rub it off.
Understand?
[WHALE vocalizes]
Good whale!
--[NAMI and USOPP] Bye!
--[LUFFY] Be good, whale!
See ya!
[LUFFY] So you can imagine
how surprised I was.
It's pretty crazy you turned out
to be one of the friends
he's been waiting for.
Kinda feels like fate, huh?
[LUFFY]
And that promise you made?
He still remembers it
just as clear as you do.
[LUFFY]
Laboon's gonna be so happy
when he finds out you're okay!
[BROOK] Please, just
give me a moment here.
Yohohoho!
I can't believe this.
So, what you're saying is...
...You guys met Laboon?
You truly did?
[LUFFY]
Yup!
[BROOK]
And even after fifty years,
all this time,
Laboon's still waiting
at the cape for
me to come back?
Just as we left him?
You're not joking?
Nope!
[SANJI] We can
back him up on that.
Your big buddy's
there, all right.
[USOPP]
Yep!
[BROOK]
And he's doing well?
Yeah, he's doing great!
He's as big as
a damn mountain.
[BROOK]
That's incredible!
The last time I saw him,
he was the size of a small boat.
He was so adorable.
He could be
difficult at times,
but ah, he loved music!
He was such a good boy.
Even now I remember
exactly what he looked like.
I can picture him.
When we said goodbye...
[loud, off-key chord]
[BROOK]
This is wonderful.
Even after all this time
he's still doing okay.
[BROOK sobbing loudly]
[BROOK] I've never been
this happy in my entire life!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 378A] What's up
with this little whale?
He won't stop
following our ship.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 378B] Probably
got separated from his family.
Poor guy,
lost in this big ocean.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 378C]
You look so sad, little guy.
You're just a baby, aren't you?
[WHALE vocalizes]
Hey, Captain Yorki!
How about we cheer up
the little guy with a song?
That's a brilliant idea, Brook!
All right, everybody
grab your instruments!
[BROOK]
Yohohoho!
The Rumbar Pirates
can bring a smile
to the face of any creature!
Let's show him
how we do it, boys!
[RUMBAR PIRATES]
Damn right, Brook!
[WHALE vocalizing]
[BROOK]
1, 2, 3, 4!
[lively music]
[BROOK] Laboon. You're
such a dear friend!
That's why we can't
take you with us!
The Grand Line
is far too dangerous.
We want you to wait for us here.
Once we make our way through
these treacherous waters,
We'll return to this cape
to see you again.
I swear it!
On the next One Piece:
"Brook's Past: A Sad Farewell
with his Cheerful Comrade."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!