[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] The final phase
of Eneru's diabolical plan
is just about to begin.
[ENERU] Run as fast as you can,
people of the sky!
This is Skypiea's last dance!
A party of angels
dancing in the sky! Haha!
You. Have you ever seen the
look on a mortal's face
when he suddenly
loses his footing?
[ENERU laughs]
[WHITE BERET I grunts]
Everyone! You have
to go to Cloud End
at the edge of the clouds
right away before it's too late!
We have to escape
to the Blue Sea!
Eneru's planning to destroy
this land and everyone on it!
If we don't evacuate now,
we're going to die!
If we want to live,
we must leave!
[CROWD shouting]
[NARRATOR] While the citizens
began to evacuate Angel Island,
Luffy rushed off to his
inevitable showdown with Eneru.
[inhlaes] Hey! Are you
the one they call Eneru?
[cheers]
What makes you God anyway?
You'll find out.
[yells]
[ENERU]
El... Thor!
One hundred million volt.
Vari!
[NAMI] If I'd thought about it,
I would've realized it sooner!
Lightning can't hurt Luffy.
He's made of rubber!
[yells]
[groans]
[NAMI] Eneru must have never
imagined there was someone
in the world who was
immune to lightning!
Luffy may be the only person in
the world who can battle Eneru.
They're natural enemies!
[LUFFY] "Maxim Surfaces!
Deathpiea Is Activated!"
[BOTH gasp]
Rubber. It doesn't
conduct electricity!
And so that means, Eneru can't
hurt a rubber person!
Go Luffy! Stop him.
[ENERU grunts]
You! You're no mere mortal!
What are you?
Me? I'm Luffy.
A pirate, and a rubber man.
What? Rubber?
I see. Rubber doesn't
exist in Skypiea.
He doesn't know what it is.
That lightning of yours...
won't work on me!
Mantra.
Gum-Gum... Whip!
[LUFFY]
Spear!
[NAMI yelps]
[gasps]
I don't believe it!
He can predict Luffy's moves!
[ENERU]
Heh.
[LUFFY grunts]
Luffy!
Don't push your luck.
[coughs]
Lightning can cause far more
than just electric shocks.
But I don't have to tell
you that, "rubber man."
You found out the hard way!
[LUFFY grunts] You're gonna
have to do better than that!
[grunts]
I see!
He's got that weird ability
to predict my moves. Dammit!
Lightning won't work.
Blows won't work.
Just what is this "rubber"?
Now, hold on.
This "rubber man".
He's a paramecia.
Even they have weaknesses.
Gloam... Paddling!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[ENERU]
I'm on a bit of a schedule,
so I don't have time to play.
He! He's changing
his staff into a blade!
[ENERU] Think of it as
lightning in solid form!
[LUFFY grunts]
[ENERU laughs]
[ENERU] As I thought, slashing
attacks are your weakness!
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
[yells]
Don't tell him that!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Gatling!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Where'd he go?
[gasps]
Luffy! Behind you!
[LUFFY gasps]
He can move right
through... the gold?
[LUFFY groans]
[AISA, PIERRE scream]
[gasps]
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY shouts]
[laughs] You may be
immune to lightning,
but not to electric
heat it seems!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...!
...Battle Axe!
[NAMI gasps]
[AISA, PIERRE gasp]
[ENERU]
You blasphemous brat!
All right! Gum-Gum... Gatling!
[ENERU grunts]
[LUFFY shouts]
[yells]
[ENERU] It's not as though
you grew more arms, Idiot!
Luffy!
[ENERU]
Sightseeing on sky island. Hmph.
You Blue Sea people certainly
picked a bad time to visit.
I am this land's god. I can
do anything my will desires.
I've long dreamed of
creating an ideal world!
This dream will
become a reality,
and I won't let anyone
stand in my way!
Least of all some whelp
from the Blue Sea world!
Now, where were we?
Ah, yes. How could I forget?
We were going to
watch this land die.
[laughs]
[gasps]
No! You can't!
[ENERU] Max. Two hundred
million volt Vari!
[LUFFY grunts]
[NAMI gasps]
[AISA gasps] Horsey-Bird!
What are we gonna do?
It's moving!
[PIERRE yells]
Luffy! Nami!
Behold! Maxim!
The ark that will take
me to Endless Vearth!
To the sacred land without end
that I desire! Rise Maxim! Rise!
[NAMI gasps]
It's... flying!
[NAMI] Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
This is bad!
[NAMI]
Luffy! Hurry up and stop Eneru!
But, wait a minute!
This ark's powered by Eneru,
so if he's defeated,
it'll crash with us on it!
But if he's not, the sky islands
going to be destroyed!
And if we stay here
and do nothing,
we'll be taken to some
land far away with Eneru!
Oh, I don't like our options!
No matter what happens,
we still lose!
[NAMI]
What are we gonna do, Luffy?
I'm really scared!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Don't be. Just calm down.
Calm down? But how?
[LUFFY] You sail with
the crew of the future
King of the Pirates.
So wipe that frown off,
all right?
King of the Pirates? And what
domain does he lord over?
He's the king of the seas!
The greatest king of all!
[ENERU]
Hpmh! So you say.
But we'll soon learn if
that's true. Won't we?
[WOLF growls]
[AISA] Here, look!
The ship! It's stopped!
It's stuck in the Vearth!
It can't go any higher!
But look! It's scraping away!
It's only a matter of time
before it breaks through!
[PIERRE giggbers]
[AISA] No, we can't.
We'll get in his way!
He may be from the
Blue Sea world,
but Luffy's
still a warrior!
A warrior's duel is sacred!
You should never
interfere in it!
[SKYPIEAN A]
We're going to be cast down!
[SKYPIEAN B]
This is the end!
[SKYPIEAN C]
Run!
Quickly, folks! The White
Berets will ensure your safe
evacuation from the island!
There's no need to panic!
Proceed in an order--
[SKYPIEAN D]
'Scuse me!
[MCKINLEY] Please,
everyone hurry get moving!
We don't have much time left!
[MCKINLEY]
We have to.
We have to save as many
people as possible!
Uh! Sir!
Sir, what are you doing?
You have to escape now!
I've always believed in our god.
If it's his desire to grant us
death, shouldn't we accept it?
Isn't it wrong if
we don't, Captain?
[MCKINLEY]
Eneru.
He doesn't have the
right to take your life
or anyone else's
for that matter!
Listen! We all have to survive!
And keep on living! All of us!
[MCKINLEY]
Now, please, sir, escape!
Live while you have the chance!
Grandfather.
Come on! Hurry!
Heso!
[SKYPIEAN E]
Captain!
[SKYPIEAN F]
A few of us are heading
to the Shandorian village.
[MCKINLEY]
The Shandorian Village?
[SKYPIEAN G]
If someone doesn't warn them
about what's happening,
they'll perish!
[SKYPIEAN E]
We have to do it!
[SKYPIEAN F] The Shandorians
are people, too! Just like us!
[MCKINLEY grunts]
You're right! Go! Quickly!
[ENERU laughs]
[ENERU] The circuit to this
ark's ultimate function
has been initiated and is now
running at full capacity!
Ultimate function?
It has a name.
It's called Deathpiea.
The despair that will
destroy this world.
[gasps]
Oh, no! Luffy!
[ENERU]
Deathpiea, activate!
[gasps]
[NAMI]
What is that?
[ENERU laughs]
[NAMI]
A cloud?
[ROBIN gasps]
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
Clouds?
[SHANDORAN A]
Chief! Come quick!
[SHANDORAN B]
Something's happening
in the sky over Upperyard!
[SHANDORAN CHIEFTAIN]
What is it?
[SHANDORAN B]
It. It just suddenly got dark!
[SHANDORAN A] I've never
seen the skies over this island
look like that.
[SHANDORAN C]
Strange. What could it be?
Do you think something
bad happened to Wyper
and the warriors?
[SHANDORAN CHIEFTAIN sighs]
[SHANDORAN CHIEFTAIN]
I hope not, but I, too,
have never seen such dark
clouds in the sky of the
White-White Sea.
[SKYPIEAN A]
Wh-What is that?
[SKYPIEAN B]
The sky! It's growing dark!
[SKYPIEAN C] It's the judgment!
This is the end!
[gasps]
[NAMI]
Are those...?
That's right. Thunderclouds.
Using my energy, Deathpiea
forces extremely turbulent air
currents together, which produce
those lovely thunderclouds
you see billowing out right now.
[NAMI]
Thunderclouds?
[ENERU] Soon they will envelop
all of Skypiea in darkness.
Inside them, energy will
continue to build
until it's reached
its absolute peak.
And then, on my signal,
they will unleash thunderbolts
of such magnitude that
every trace of this land
will be obliterated!
Allow me to demonstrate.
[CROWD scream]
That came from Upperyard!
Get to the ships!
Everyone, keep calm!
Don't panic!
Get on a ship and
head for Cloud End!
Damn you!
[horn honking]
[grunts]
Eneru!
[ENERU laughs]
You... just...
[ENERU] I just teased
the angels a little.
But after all, that is my right.
So being a god makes it
okay to destroy everything?
Of course. Everything here
is mine for the taking.
Their land. Their lives.
Speaking of which...
I'll continue celebrating
by taking yours!
[LUFFY shouts]
[LUFFY yelps] Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Hot! Hot!
[laughs] This spear has
been highly charged!
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Dammit!
How. How can I defeat a guy,
who can predict my moves?
[gasps]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
..Daze...
What are you doing? Hey!
[grunts]
[NAMI] He's dodging the
attacks unconsciously
and just relying
on his reflexes!
It's almost like he's a
blade of grass that sways
back and forth in the wind
instead of opposing it!
He's not thinking! That's why
Eneru can't predict his moves!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[pants]
But if I switch my brain off...
Then I can't attack him!
Don't stop now!
I gotta get my hands on
him somehow. Come on! Think!
There's gotta be a way.
That's it!
Gum-Gum... Octopus!
[NAMI screams]
Enough with the stupid ideas!
[ENERU] I take it you're no
fan of my Mantra, are you?
That's to be expected, since it
is the basis of my power!
That place should work!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[ENERU]
It doesn't matter what you try.
Except for your
immunity to lightning,
you're nothing but an annoying,
powerless mortal!
[LUFFY]
...Octopus...!
What? Why attack the ark?
...Fireworks!
[LUFFY yells]
[ENERU] You're ignoring me and
attacking the ship instead?
It's no use! You're even more
foolish that you appear!
[laughs]
[LUFFY shouts]
[ENERU grunts]
[gasps] Of course!
The punches are ricocheting.
He's not consciously
controlling them!
[LUFFY] I'm not letting
you get away again!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[ENERU]
No!
[LUFFY]
...Bazooka!
[groans]
[ENERU] No! He's charging!
I... I have to escape!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[ENERU]
He can't!
I... I'm a god!
[LUFFY]
...Rifle!
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[ENERU] Once you're gone,
the world will be mine!
[LUFFY] Shut up and
fight me, Eneru!
[ENERU]
Look around you, rubber man!
This island is being destroyed
right before your eyes!
[AISA] What should we do!
The ship's flying away!
[NAMI] Where's the fun
in gaining everything
you want all by yourself?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy Falls! Eneru's
Judgment and Nami's Wish!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!