Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] As the
Straw Hat Pirates continued
toward Fishman Island,
they drew near the halfway
point of the Grand Line.
Chopper!
[CHOPPER screaming]
[FRANKY]
Coup De Burst!
I can't even see
the top! It's huge!
[NARRATOR] Then they reached the
Red Line for the second time.
[NARRATOR] Once there, they
encountered Camie the mermaid
and Pappagu the starfish fishman
after rescuing them
from the belly of a sea king.
Anyway, thanks for
saving my life back there.
[HACHI] Nyuu!
Camie, you're all right.
[NARRATOR] Camie
pleaded with the Straw Hats
to save her
captured friend, Hachi.
And so the crew set
course for the base
of the Flying Fish Riders.
Wait, what?
Someone's here?
Ahh! Look!
It's the Flying Fish Riders!
Hey! It's them!
[FISH RIDER 386B]
Yeah, you're right!
Those are the Straw Hat Pirates
down there, no doubt about it!
[DUVAL]
The very pirate ship
I've been searching for
all this time.
All my waiting will
finally come to an end.
[DUVAL]
I'll have my revenge!
I'll kill that bastard
that ruined my life!
[LUFFY]
The Fated Reunion!
Save the Captive Fishman!
[SEAGULLS cawing]
[CHOPPER]
The Flying Fish just left?
[FRANKY] And they were the ones
who started the attack.
Weird.
[ROBIN] It seemed like
they received a message.
Maybe it was an order
for them to retreat?
I can't imagine why, though.
[LUFFY]
Those Flying Fish are cool!
I wanna ride one!
They can stay in the air
for five minutes, right?
That's five minutes
of awesome for me!
We're headed to their base now,
so we'll see them
again soon enough.
We better be careful, though.
It might not be
so easy next time.
[LUFFY] We could put it in the
aquarium with the other fish!
Then we could ride it
whenever we want!
Least we know they can attack
from the sea or the air.
Hey, how about lining
the deck with cannons?
Sniper Usopp will
blow 'em outta the sky!
Good thinkin', bro!
I'm worried.
I wonder if Hatchin is okay.
Worry about yourself
while you're at it, Camie.
Macro wants to catch you bad!
Don't drop your guard!
Yeah, you're right.
[RANDOM FISH RIDER 387A]
Master Duval!
The three riders have returned!
[FISH RIDER 387A]
I don't get it.
Why'd you ask us
to call off the attack?
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Yeah, what gives?
[FISH RIDER 386B] We could
have captured the mermaid
and those pirates
in one fell swoop!
[DUVAL]
Idiots!
[screaming]
[DUVAL]
Listen up.
I told you a million times,
I want those pirates alive.
'Cause I'm gonna
rip 'em limb from limb.
With my own two hands.
[DUVAL] Whenever I start
thinkin' about that guy,
it's like I got an itch
on my back I can't scratch,
and I swear it gets
worse every time!
No. Ah, no.
Here comes the accent!
[DUVAL] Every day I've
cursed that man's name.
Every day,
my hate for him grows.
It burns.
Head, just calm down!
Get a hold of yourself!
[DUVAL] And now that
bastard's comin' straight
to my front door.
And I'm gonna kill 'im!
This day is gonna be perfect,
even if it kills me!
You got that? You understand?
Yes!
I understand completely.
We won't ruin it for you!
[DUVAL] That's why you gotta
follow my orders to the "T."
'Cause I'm gonna
murder this punk,
and ain't nobody
gonna get in my way!
Okay, Head, whatever you want.
[DUVAL]
Hey, Macro Gang.
Yeah? What do you want?
What is it... Duva?
Wait, did you say "Duva"?
And you too, Tansui.
Can't you show a little
more respect than that?
You need to learn some manners!
Ahaha! He said "Duva".
That's funny.
That's enough!
I'm so very sorry.
You were saying,
Master Duval, sir?
Hey, Boss.
That mask guy talks funny.
Heh heh heh!
Will you shut up already?
My most sincere
apologies, Master.
These two are as dumb as bricks.
Just ignore everything they say
and I promise
they'll get the job done.
[DUVAL] You can run your
stupid fish mouths all day.
I don't care!
Far as I'm concerned, you're
my angels of good fortune.
I can't even begin to
tell you how grateful I am
for our little arrangement here.
You could try.
I told you to
shut up, Tansui!
[DUVAL] You can call it luck,
but thanks to you three,
I can finally meet
the Straw Hat Pirates.
I'll get my revenge.
Then I can finally
get my life back.
"Straw Hat Pirates"?
Uh... Now who might
they be, exactly?
[HACHI]
The Straw Hats?
It wasn't just my
imagination! Nyuuu!
[DUVAL]
Now listen good.
That guy...
The one I gotta kill
if it's the last thing ah do.
He's on that boat,
I can feel it!
I can feel my hands around
his neck as we speak!
[FISH RIDER 386B]
Head! Your accent!
You gotta calm down!
Man, he must really hate
the crap outta that guy.
[HACHI] I never thought I'd hear
the name "Straw Hat Pirates"
way out here.
[HACHI]
Nyuu! Hey! Big guy!
Agh!
That's "Master Duval".
Show him some damn respect!
[HACHI] You're saying
Camie has been captured
by the Straw Hat Pirates?
[HACHI] Nyuu.
This is bad. Really bad.
Of all the people
she could run into.
And they're all on
their way here together?
So it would seem.
They'll arrive any time now.
But she didn't seem
all that "captured" to me.
Looked more like she turned
to those pirates for help.
[FISH RIDER 387A]
Far as I could tell,
it looked like they were
working together just fine.
Well, it doesn't matter
who she brings.
In the end, they'll all
be rounded up, caught,
and sold to the Human Shop.
Once they're here,
they're history.
[laughing]
[HACHI]
That's what you think!
Those Straw Hats
are crazy strong!
Nyuu, I'm in trouble.
I wonder if Nami's
still with them, too.
I wonder if she's
still mad at me.
Well, duh.
Of course she would be.
I did all those
horrible things to her
when I was working for Arlong.
If I don't hurry up and
figure out some way to escape
before they get here,
I'll get my butt kicked
just as much as
these other guys.
I'm so screwed!
Whoa...
Hey, Master Duval!
The Straw Hats are here!
[DUVAL]
Finally.
The time has come.
Uh... Hey, Macro?
Yeah? Whadda ya want?
How 'bout you let me go
and I give you some
octopus fritters?
I can buy my own
damn seafood!
What kind of glutton
do you think I am?
[DUVAL] Did you see him?
Is he on the ship?
[FISH RIDER 387B]
Yes, Head!
He's there for sure!
All right, then.
Now that everything
appears to be in order,
I think it's time for you
to get what's coming to you.
Hey, Gyaro,
if you let me go,
I'll give you
lots of fritters.
Oh, come on.
No one's gonna...
Hey!
You're not actually
considering his bribe?!
[DUVAL]
Get to work, you maggots!
[ALL]
Sir!
[HACHI]
Hey, Tansui.
Listen. You like fritt--augh!
Oh, just knock it off already!
Hey, I see something!
[FRANKY]
From the looks of it,
I bet that's the
Flying Fish Rider's base.
So Camie's friend
Hatchin is being held
somewhere around here, right?
Hatchin...
[LUFFY]
Let's get moving!
We gotta save those
octopus fritters!
[FRANKY] What, did you miss your
snacktime today or something?
I'll go in there and
save him before you know it,
beautiful Camie!
Thanks!
You're the best, Sanjichin!
Hold on, guys!
Before you go, listen up!
[CAMIE]
Be careful out there, okay?
The Macro Gang have
managed to capture me
over 30 times already!
You get captured
way too often!
[USOPP] You get eaten
too often, too.
Looks like we're
about to cross over
into enemy territory.
I think my "can't go
on this island" disease
is coming back.
Well, this isn't
really an island.
They just built a village
on top of the water.
You should be good.
I mean I'm getting that
"I shouldn't go to a village
that someone built
on the water" disease!
That's weird.
Why would anyone wanna set up
their base way out here?
Ah, who knows?
For an enemy base,
it's sure quiet.
I've got a bad feeling.
Luffy! You sure about this?
Go! Straight ahead!
Shouldn't we at least
go over the plan again
or something?
Hey! Hatchin!
Are you okay?
Hey, Macro!
Show yourself!
Give us Hachi back!
That's their flag!
It really is the Straw Hats!
I gotta get outta here!
Damn. It's no use. I'm stuck!
That leaves me no choice!
Hachi Ink Jet!
Am I seeing things,
or is something in that cage?
What the hell?
Some kinda black thing.
Wait a second.
Is that...
It kinda looks like Hatchin.
Oh, wow!
We're in luck, Camie!
There isn't a
single enemy in sight!
Maybe they all decided that
this is snacktime or something!
Probably.
You two cannot
seriously be this stupid!
The blindest man in the world
could see that this is a trap!
They're totally hiding out,
waiting for us to investigate
so they can ambush us.
What a brilliant deduction!
That's genius!
I never would've
thought of that!
That's why you dumbasses
keep getting caught!
[HACHI]
Nyuu! I'm here, Camie!
I'm fine! There's no
need to worry, okay?
Hatchin!
It really is you!
What happened?
You're all black!
Uh, well,
they didn't do that.
It's my own fault, actually.
Anyway, this is a trap!
Get outta here
before they catch you!
Don't worry!
I can take care of myself!
I'll be okay, so just go!
There's something
about that guy's voice
that seems really familiar.
You noticed it, too, right?
Uh huh. His shape, too.
Yeah. I know who he is.
You do?
Let's just ask him and
get this over with already.
Hey, you! So how's
Arlong doing these days?
Oh! Not so good, actually.
Him, Choo, Kuroobi, and all the
others got caught by the Navy!
I was the only one who escaped!
Now I've given up
my life of crime
and I'm running
an octopus fritter shop!
Funny how time flies, right?
Arlong?
What an idiot.
[LUFFY]
It's you!
The dumb squid with the swords!
They tricked me!
Damn it all!
[LUFFY]
I'm right, aren't I?
You were one of Arlong's crew!
You're the octopus fritter guy?
What kinda crap is that?
Arlong?
Yeah. It was a
really long time ago.
Nami's hometown
of Cocoyashi Village
used to be under the control
of a nasty bunch of fishmen
called the Arlong Pirates.
Nami herself was in an
even worse situation
having to work for those jerks.
And this octopus guy, Hachi, was
one of Arlong's top henchmen.
[ARLONG laughing]
Hey, now.
You're not gonna run
out on me, are you?
Listen, little girl.
If you do that, I'll kill
everyone in that village.
Do you understand me?
Good.
Now which one
of you is Arlong?
Oh. So he's
an old enemy, huh?
Well, he was.
But Luffy and I,
mainly me, came along
and beat the crap outta every
last one of those guys!
Oh, wow!
Usopp, you're amazing!
Yeah. I know, right?
After we left the village,
I thought their whole crew was
gonna get arrested by the Navy.
But it looks like this guy
left them behind and escaped.
I see. Sounds like
quite the ordeal.
Listen up,
you dumb jerk fish!
Now that we know it's you,
there's no way
we're gonna save you,
so you better get
used to that cage.
Nyuu...
But... Well...
Uhm, y'know, um...
Just asking, but are
your octopus fritters
as yummy as everyone
says they are?
Why don't you
think with your head
instead of your stomach?
What a moron.
Hey, wait a second!
Does this mean that
you guys know Hatchin?
He must be like an old
friend of yours or something!
He's not our friend at all! No!
[USOPP]
Turn the ship around!
Namichin...
Sorry, we can't help you.
I know we said "yes" at first,
but we didn't know this was the
"friend" you were talking about.
Oh, come on!
You can't just leave him like
this after coming all this way!
Please!
[HACHI]
Don't worry about it, Camie!
Just leave, okay?
This is a trap!
This sucks.
Fine, then!
I'll have to do it!
Hatchin!
You're always saving me,
so now's my chance
to return the favor!
Pappagu?
[PAPPAGU]
I'm in!
I never would've thought
you guys would turn out to be
such a bunch of
heartless morons!
Morons! Morons!
Oh, shut up!
Just hang on, Hachi!
[CAMIE] I promise you, we won't
leave this place without you!
--Here we come!
No! Wait!
Just let 'em go!
Do you think
they're gonna be okay?
Yeah. I'm sure
they have a plan.
They wouldn't have just
charged in there without one.
[MACRO] We've got you now,
Camie! Muhahaha!
You've gotta
be kidding me!
That's just pathetic!
Muhaha!
Now we're all
gonna be filthy rich!
Especially since the only guy
who ever saves you can't!
You're not gonna escape
from us this time, Camie.
It's over.
[CAMIE yelling]
Why didn't you just run away?
Camie! Pappagu!
[SANJI] Bastards!
Camie hasn't done anything!
Sanji. Hold on a second, okay?
Camie! I'm still
gonna save you! 'Kay?
All right.
We might as well
save him after all.
Hachi isn't all that bad.
I'd go so far as
to say he's harmless.
I'm not gonna hold a grudge,
and besides,
we promised Camie
we'd help her, didn't we?
Oh, Nami!
I love when you're firm, but I
love when you're forgiving, too!
[USOPP]
Are you sure, Nami?
[ZORO]
It's really okay?
[NAMI]
Yep! Right, Luffy?
[LUFFY] If you say
it's okay, it's okay.
We'll save the octopus.
Look! His eyes
are octopus fritters!
[DUVAL] Are the
preparations in order...
...Flying Fish Riders?
[FISH RIDERS] Of course!
We're always ready!
Time for Gum Gum Pistol!
You leave them alone!
He's got Devil Fruit Powers!
[HACHI]
Straw Hat?
Damn! That little punk!
Thank you, Luffy!
You saved us!
Yeah! I got 'em, Octopus!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
You have my most
sincere gratitude
for saving little Camie.
I owe you one!
Hey!
Cut up the octopus' cage
and untie him, Zoro!
Right!
Be careful, Straw Hat!
The trap is still set!
The Flying Fish Riders
have got you surrounded!
They'll take you down
any way they can.
Don't let your guard down!
[DUVAL]
Now, attack!
[FISH RIDERS]
Sir!
You're the greatest!
I don't care if they
come from the sea or sky.
We'll be ready.
We're gonna beat
the crap out of 'em.
[LUFFY]
Listen up, you guys!
Time to fight!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Dammit!
Quick, while we
still have the chance!
Come on, let's
go get Camie back!
[GYARO and TANSUI]
Yeah!
Camie! Pappagu!
It's dangerous here!
You need to stand back!
Nyuu?
--Go, Luffy!
--Get him!
--Get him back!
Go!
Bring it, you
dumb Flying Fish!
Go! Go!
Get him back!
Guys, they're here!
[CHOPPER, ZORO, SANJI]
Right!
[DUVAL] I've finally found you,
Black Leg Sanji!
[LUFFY] Hey,
how does he know Sanji?
[DUVAL]
You're the one!
It's your fault
my life was ruined!
[USOPP] Whoa! He really
hates him, doesn't he?
[DUVAL]
I'm sending you to hell!
[LUFFY and USOPP]
What did you do, Sanji?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Tragedy!
The Truth Hidden
Under Duval's Mask!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!