[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR]
The Going Merry fell right into
the middle of the invincible
Marine fortress, Navarone.
[NARRATOR] But luckily,
Luffy and the others
managed to escape
under cover of night.
[NARRATOR] Nami successfully
disguised herself as a janitor,
while Luffy and Sanji
infiltrated the kitchen.
Murray?
So you're here.
[NARRATOR]
However, one of the crew, Zoro,
was captured by
their Marine foes.
[JONATHAN]
Welcome to Navarone.
[LUFFY] "Captured Zoro!
Chopper's Emergency Operations!"
[JONATHAN]
One down, six to go.
The infamous Roronoa Zoro,
one of Luffy's
Straw Hat Pirates.
Drake, go to the brig and
interrogate the prisoner.
But, Commander, my team and I
are already under
orders from you
to surveil and secure
the dining hall.
[JONATHAN]
Huh? You are?
You told me that pirates
are always hungry.
So sooner or later they'll
show up at the mess hall.
[JONATHAN]
I'll handle the mess hall.
Things are bound to be a
little screwy around there.
Jessica told me they got
some new cooks
from headquarters.
And how shall I conduct
Zoro's interrogation?
[JONATHAN]
I'll leave that up to you.
[yawns]
Oh, come on,
are you guys just gonna
sit there and stare at me?
Well, nothing to do but
get some more shuteye.
[ZORO snores]
[DRAKE]
Open the cell.
But, Lieutenant Commander!
The prisoner is
extremely dangerous.
[DRAKE] I am under direct orders
from Vice Admiral Jonathan
to interrogate the prisoner.
[MARINE AB] Yes, sir!
Please be careful, sir!
[cell door opens]
[ZORO]
Hm?
Roronoa Zoro.
Known far and wide
as a pirate hunter,
until you turned traitor
and joined the scum
you used to hunt.
[ZORO] You didn't come
all the way down here
just to tell me that, did you?
If that's how you
want to play it.
How many of you are there?
And what exactly is your purpose
in invading this fortress?
It was a clever strategy
to invade a base like
this from the sky.
How did you do it?
Did you build a launch pad?
Nope, we just came
down from the sky.
[DRAKE]
Don't mock me!
Calm down, big guy,
I'm not mocking you.
I'm just answering
your question.
I won't hear any more
of your lies, pirate!
Like I said, we came
down from the sky.
If you want to get specific,
we rode down on a
floating octopus.
Are you happy now?
Well, I guess we'll have
to do this the hard way.
You're gonna be sorry!
[groaning]
I'll find out the truth,
no matter what!
[CHIEF CLEANER]
Your next assignment
is to clean the old gym.
[NAMI]
Aye aye, boss!
Clean all this?
[NAMI]
And I gotta do it... by myself?
[CHIEF CLEANER]
I wanna see it sparkle!
Boy, I'd hate to be in your
shoes right now! [laughs]
This disguise was
clearly a mistake.
[MARINE A]
I heard that they captured
one of the Straw Hat Pirates.
[MARINE B] What, then that
wasn't a ghost ship?
[MARINE A] No, but this
guy is scarier than a ghost.
You're not gonna believe this,
but they caught Roronoa Zoro!
[MARINE B, MARINE AC]
Whoa!
[CHOPPER]
What?
[MARINE A]
And apparently there are other
crewmembers hidin', too.
Imagine, if we found even
one of them, we'd be heroes!
[MARINE B, MARINE C]
Yeah!
[CHOPPER]
Zoro got captured!
What do I do now?
[CHOPPER gasps]
Those Marines back there
didn't mention anyone else
being taken prisoner.
So the rest of the
crew has got to be
around here somewhere.
But where could they be?
This place is huge!
I'm so ready to get outta here!
--[MARINE AC] Hey, what's that?
--[CHOPPER gasps]
[NAMI]
If I keep that up,
I'll be dead before
they catch me!
[MARINE AC]
Hold it!
Help me! Help!
[MARINE AC]
I said hold it!
I guess those guys weren't
looking for me. [sighs]
Cleaning sucks.
Gotta find a new disguise.
Well look at that.
[CHOPPER panting]
[CHOPPER]
Oh, no! A dead end!
[MARINE AC]
He went that way!
[MARINE AD]
All right, fellas!
The corner is raccoon dogged.
I mean, the raccoon dog
is cornered!
What do I do? What do I do?
[MARINE AC]
He disappeared!
[MARINE AD] A magical
disappearing raccoon dog.
[MARINE AC]
Hmm...
He didn't disappear.
[MARINE AE] It'll take forever
to find him in here!
--[MARINE AD] Hey!
--[MARINE AC] Shh.
--What do we got here?
--Yeah. Ready or not!
[ALL gasp]
[MARINE AD]
What's going on?
[MARINE AE] Did the raccoon dog
leave his antlers behind?
[MARINE AC] I don't know,
but you can't make tasty treats
with antlers.
Let's go.
[MARINE AC] We must've
lost him in those hallways.
[sighs] Safe at last.
[gasps]
So where's the crate?
Should be over here.
[CLERK A]
Ahh. There it is.
Hey, what are they
doing with deer antlers?
I think they're
used in medicines.
[MARINE E]
What happened to them?
[MARINE F]
They said they ran into a storm.
Took a lot of casualties.
Hurry it up!
[MARINE G]
Get them to the infirmary, stat!
Let's see. Make a vertical
incision with the scalpel
and if it begins to bleed...
Blood, blood, blood!
Ugh, it's just my luck
that all the other doctors
got called away at once!
Oh, please don't let there be
any surgery patients today!
[CLERK A]
Doctor!
[KOBATO gasps]
Yes?
We brought the crate
of deer antlers
for the medicine
you're going to make.
Of course.
Right over there will be fine.
[CLERK A]
Yes, ma'am.
[CHOPPER]
Where am I?
[gasps]
[NAMI humming]
I look pretty good in this,
if I do say so myself,
and I bet the work
won't be near-- [gasps]
[gasps] I'm so sorry!
What are you apologizing for?
Just get to the
infirmary already!
What? Where? Huh?
[NURSE B]
There's been an emergency.
All nurses are to
report immediately!
I knew it! I'm screwed
no matter what disguise I pick!
Doctor, we have an emergency!
So, what kind of
emergency is this?
[NURSE A] Critically injured
sailors from the Stan Marey
need immediate attention!
Um, well, I'll leave
these patients to you
since that isn't my
area of expertise.
This isn't really
your expertise?
Well last time I checked,
you're the only doctor on
this entire base right now!
[KOBATO]
But--I'm just a pediatrician!
I don't know anything
about trauma!
That's outside of my specialty!
I see. It's a medical room.
But I wonder if that doctor
can handle those patients.
[MARINE G, NURSE A, NURSE B]
One, two, three!
Wow, these guys are all
in really rough shape.
Did they get hit by a cyclone?
Don't just stand there,
treat the wounded!
Right!
[NAMI] I don't have time to be
playing nurse with this bunch!
I need to be searching
for the Going Merry
so I can get us
outta this place!
[MARINE H groans]
Oh, I'm sorry!
[NURSE A]
Don't just stand there!
[NURSE B]
Doctor, what do we do?
Okay, let's see.
Painkiller--he needs 50
milligrams of painkiller.
[NURSE C]
Shall we prep the O.R.?
That's right, operate.
I have to operate...
[NURSES]
Doctor!
[NURSE C]
Doctor! Pull yourself together!
[NURSE B]
We don't have time for this!
[NURSE A]
Tell us what to do!
[NURSE B]
Doctor! Doctor, please!
You've got to wake up.
[NURSE C]
Ma'am, are you okay?
I gotta help!
[CHOPPER] I'll be
directing treatment today!
[NURSES]
Huh?
[CHOPPER] First, administer
this patient a dose of
both phenicol and cardiotonic,
then prepare some tialcillin.
Respond if you understand!
[NURSE B, NURSE A]
Yes, Doctor.
Yes, Doctor!
Now cross-match every
patient's blood type!
Begin pre-op treatment
for everyone who
requires an operation!
Get this patient on antibiotics
to treat tetanus
and any other infections
he may have!
[NURSE A]
Right!
What's the status of the O.R.?
The operating room
is ready, sir!
[CHOPPER]
Then move patients there!
Start with those in
critical condition!
[NURSE C]
Yes, sir!
C'mon. Snap out of it.
Chopper?
Nami?
What in the world
are you doing here?
[NAMI]
I should be asking you that!
Excuse me, but could you
tell me what's going on?
Where is everyone?
I seem to have fainted.
Wait. You're a doctor!
I don't know who you are
or where you came from,
but I'm glad you came along.
You sure saved us with
your expert instructions.
No one's saved yet, Doctor.
What?
The situation doesn't look good.
Without emergency surgery,
many will die.
Yeah.
There's no time to lose.
You must operate on the
critically injured now!
Yes. Operate. [chuckles]
[NAMI]
Hey, what's with you?
[KOBATO]
I-I can't do it.
Do what?
[KOBATO] I can't stand
to see people in pain
or bleeding or worse.
Honestly I can barely
even administer a shot.
So the thought of
putting stitches in,
or cutting someone is just...
Oh, just perfect!
This is a Marine base, you know.
How can you call yourself
a military doctor
if you can't stand the
sight of a little blood?
My field of practice is
children's medicine.
All the other doctors were
called away on business.
You see, I was only left in
charge as temporary substitute.
Temporary?
[CHOPPER]
Substitute or not,
you're in charge of the
infirmary right now, aren't you?
Uh, yeah, seems so.
It seems so?
Hey, Chopper, don't you think
it's time we get out of here?
Yeah, but...
I found out that
this isn't a lake.
It's connected to
the open ocean.
We just have to find
the Going Merry
and we can escape from
this stupid fortress!
[CHOPPER]
I can't go yet!
Huh?
You're a doctor. It's your duty
to preserve life, isn't it?
That is what I have sworn to do.
But still. I have limits.
Even the best doctors have
things they just can't do.
[CHOPPER]
The man who taught me medicine
used to tell me a story.
[CHOPPER] There once was a man
who was told by his doctors
that he would soon be dead.
In despair, he wandered
the wilderness
in search of a place to die.
Then as he walked
through a mountain pass,
he saw something extraordinary.
The entire mountain was covered
in brilliant cherry blossoms.
[CHOPPER]
After seeing this,
he went to visit
his physicians again,
where they were
astounded to report
that the man was now
completely healthy.
You are the only doctor for
those patients in there!
You alone can save them
from a terrible death!
A healer must never give up!
There is no illness
that can't be cured!
Don't ever let your
fear limit you!
There is no patient that we
doctors shouldn't try to cure!
[KOBATO gasps]
As doctors, we have the power
to make miracles happen!
We have to always believe that!
[KOBATO]
Then...
Will I...
...be able to see the
cherry blossoms, too?
No. I will show them
the cherry blossoms.
All of those suffering people
in the operating room.
That's the spirit!
I'll even stick around to help!
[NAMI] Hey! We don't
have time for this!
Yes, that may be true.
But my first priority always has
to be helping those in need!
I'm a doctor, Nami!
If that's your decision, then
I'll have to leave you behind.
Is that really what you want?
Doctor, the operating room
is prepped and ready to go!
[CHOPPER]
Good! I'm on my way!
Chop--I mean, yes, Doctor!
Right, let's go!
Hey, Chopper!
[CHOPPER] You can leave me
behind if you need to,
but I have to stay.
If I didn't, I'd be abandoning
everything Doctrine
taught me to uphold.
Jeez! Well I'm not just gonna
leave you here all by yourself!
Just who in the
heck is that guy?
[KOBATO] We'll start with
the critical cases.
There's a large iron shard
lodged in his upper torso
that must be extracted.
The patient has
been anesthetized,
so we are ready to
begin the procedure.
--Scalpel.
--Yes, Doctor.
Dr. Kobato, you'll be fine.
Remember, you are the only one
who can show these patients
the cherry blossoms.
[KOBATO]
Yes.
This incision runs close to
an artery, so be careful.
[KOBATO]
Right.
Nami, suction.
[NAMI]
Yes, Doctor.
[CHOPPER]
The shard has been removed.
--Done!
--Dr. Kobato,
we're not even close to done.
There are so many more patients.
[KOBATO]
Of course.
We can do it.
[KOBATO]
Yeah.
[DRAKE]
What?
An unidentified doctor
is performing surgery?
[MARINE I]
Yes, sir!
That could be our second
Straw Hat of the day.
[ZORO]
Chopper.
[DRAKE]
Pardon the intrusion!
[KOBATO]
We're operating. Please leave!
This is urgent! I assure you.
I need to ask you
a few questions.
[NAMI] Doctor, his blood
pressure is dropping fast!
[CHOPPER] Give him six
units of saline solution
and one unit of platelets!
[NAMI, NURSE B]
Yes, sir!
[CHOPPER]
He's out of danger now.
Continue the blood transfusion
and ready the dopamine!
[DRAKE clears throat]
Dr. Kobato!
[KOBATO] We're in the
middle of an operation!
If you're going to stay,
please be quiet!
Excuse me, did I hear you right?
You're performing surgery?
The doctor that nearly faints
every time she sees a paper cut?
There are reports of an
unidentified doctor here.
[KOBATO]
Get out!
Huh?
[KOBATO] The only thing you and
your thugs will find in here
are people giving their all
to save precious lives!
Is that clear?
Let's go!
[DRAKE]
Monitor them.
[MARINE I]
Sir!
[KOBATO]
Suture completed.
[NURSE B] That was the
last of our patients.
[NAMI]
Good job, Dr. Kobato.
[KOBATO sighs]
No, Chopper, don't!
[CHOPPER]
You really are a great doctor!
Thank you. But you're
a much better doctor
than I'll ever be,
Mr. Raccoon Dog.
You stupid face!
I'm not a raccoon dog,
I'm a reindeer!
[NAMI] It's like she
doesn't even notice
that Chopper just changed shape!
[JONATHAN humming]
[SANJI] Really, what are we
still doing hanging around here?
We don't even know if Robin and
Nami are out of harms way.
[SANJI] Ahh. But I can't
just abandon a task
that the lovely Jessica gave me!
Got that right.
What are you doing, you idiot?
Uh, I don't know.
Have you seen how awesome
this glow thing is?
Yes, I've seen how
awesome your thing is.
Now help me or figure out
how to get us out of here.
Oh, yeah.
How come we're still sitting
around this stupid kitchen?
We're still here because
you haven't figured out
a way for us to escape!
Hey, Sanji?
What now?
Do you think someone
could eat a raw octopus?
What does that have
to do with anything?
[JESSICA]
How's it coming?
Are you done yet?
If you don't hurry,
we won't be ready for
the next hundred soldiers.
Oh, my sweet Jessica!
I just finished the onions!
Well, looks like it's just
about break time. I'm beat!
[SANJI] But you haven't
done anything yet!
Since you're so eager to help,
I've got another 300
onions here for you!
More? You gotta be kidding me!
I am ever your humble
servant, sweet Jessica!
Hey, I think I know why
we're stuck in the kitchen.
And it's all your fault!
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[ZORO] That little game
of 20 questions sure hurt,
but I'm more worried
about the others!
Usopp, is our ship okay?
Robin, what's with that outfit?
Nevermind the captain
and that idiot cook!
Looks like the tide
is about to turn.
On the next One Piece!
[LUFFY]
Don't steal my line!
On the next One Piece!
"The Marine's Dragnet Closes In!
The Second Member Captured!"
[ZORO]
I'm gonna be a great swordsman!
[LUFFY]
Hey!