[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] Last time,
Nami found herself trapped
on the Ark Maxim until her
crewmates Sanji and Usopp
snuck on board to save her.
In fact, I'd bet my
favorite carving knife
they already know we're here!
They know we're here?
So what are we supposed to do?
[SANJI]
Stop freakin' out, for starters.
Once we're safely
inside, we'll split up
and head for the main deck.
Nami's gotta be up there!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Luffy
had a gold ball attached
to his arm by Eneru and
was thrown into the ruins
of Shandora.
But Luffy got back up
to settle the score.
[LUFFY grunts]
All right!
Dammit! I can't get
this golden ball off!
[AISA]
Hey, watch your mouth!
Of course, it's futile.
Why don't you be gone!
[NARRATOR] Ussop saved Nami
in the nick of time,
but he was unable to
withstand Eneru's great power.
It seemed Usopp was
about to meet his end.
El...!
Sanji, run!
Get going.
...Thor!
I was looking...
...for a light. Appreciate it.
[LUFFY]
"Capriccio for Despair!
The Impending Doom
of Sky Island!"
I'm going to cry?
Really.
[crash]
[ENERU]
What?
My ark!
Get ready... to cry, bastard.
Damn you!
[ENERU]
You did something below deck!
What have you done to my ark?!
[explosion]
You fool!
You wretched fool!
The gears have gone awry.
I must fix them.
[USOPP]
Good. He's gone.
Don't you worry.
Nami fell safely into
some island clouds.
[USOPP]
So high...
Not the jungle. Not the ruins.
Focus on falling into
the island clouds.
[grunts]
Usopp...
...Hopping!
[USOPP yelling]
Oh, no! I jumped too far!
I jumped too far!
[yelling]
No!
Oh, no! We're gonna crash!
We're gonna crash
and then we're gonna die!
[USOPP yelling]
How could I have
forgotten to unhook it?
[USOPP whimpers]
Huh?
[screams]
[NAMI]
Usopp! Sanji!
[USOPP]
Nami, is that you?
Sounds like you
made it down, all right.
What a relief!
Sanji!
Sanji, are you okay?
Oh, you got burnt
to a crisp for us.
I'm so sorry! I promise I'll
make it up to you somehow!
[USOPP] I can't breathe!
I can't breathe!
Nami, hurry! Hurry up and
pull me out! I can't breathe!
[NAMI]
Oh, sorry. All right.
Let's get the heck outta here!
[grunting]
Why won't you come out?
Curse you, blue sea dweller.
This vessel is not
so easily brought down.
I am fully acquainted
with the ark's drive circuits.
We may lack electricity,
but a backup system
harnesses the wind power
of 200 Jet Dials
I gathered in my
homeland of Birka.
They will keep this ship
aloft for quite some time.
No matter what
you feeble beings try...
This land and all its pathetic
inhabitants will perish.
[NAMI] 'Kay guys,
check out that huge vine.
If it's the same one I saw
when I was down in the ruins,
then it stands to reason
we're on the Island Clouds
right above them.
[USOPP] Ruins?
Oh, The City of Gold!
It's real?
It's real.
But Eneru took all the gold
that was there for himself.
If the ruins are beneath us,
Zoro and the others
should be down there.
I may not know
the lay of the land...
But I do know one thing:
staying here is dangerous.
You got that right.
Hop on! Let's find everyone
and get off this island.
That's a plan!
There are no safe
places left in Skypiea.
[LUFFY panting]
[AISA grunting]
[LUFFY grunting]
[AISA yells]
Luffy! Look out!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
So fast!
No, wait! Luffy!
That's the wrong way!
Go left! Left!
[LUFFY] There's no way
I can turn that sharp!
Gum-Gum...
...Hook!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY yelling]
Stop destroying my homeland!
Giant Jack is over that-a-way!
[LUFFY]
I know, but-- [crash]
[AISA]
Stop breaking things!
--[crash]
--Stop it!
[ENERU] Hmph. The thunderclouds
are gushing out nicely now.
[ENERU]
So the rats have scurried off.
They're shrewd, but so restless.
Ah, no matter.
The festivities
are close at hand.
[LUFFY]
Oh, man.
Robin and the others are gone.
Zoro and Chopper.
[AISA]
And Wyper and Gan Fall.
Well where the heck
did everybody go?
I'm guessing they
must have climbed up already.
Yeah, Robin must
have helped them.
Let's go.
Hey, Aisa.
[AISA whimpering]
[ROBIN]
I don't know.
Listen carefully.
If we don't do something,
Skypiea... will disappear.
What? It'll disappear?
My homeland will
be completely gone?!
Everything will fall.
He said this nation in
the sky was unnatural.
He said he'd send it
crashing to the ground.
Hey, Luffy?
What's up?
[AISA] Will the sky islands
really be destroyed?
[crying]
[LUFFY grunting]
[yelling]
[AISA]
Wyper and the others.
They're right through here!
[LUFFY yelling]
[ROBIN] I suspect the ship is
moving towards the Grand Belfry.
Wonder what happened to
Miss Navigator and the boys.
If they're on that ship,
it could mean they're...
[LUFFY]
We're through!
[AISA yelling]
[AISA]
Luffy, down there!
Stop! Stop!
[LUFFY]
Robin!
[AISA]
What're you doing?
[LUFFY]
Look after these two for me!
[AISA screams]
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
Stop!
Luffy!
[AISA screams]
You grew extra hands!
[ROBIN]
What have you got on your arm?
[LUFFY]
Robin!
The golden bell is at the
top of this vine, right?
And Eneru is trying to get
his hands on it, isn't he?
That's right.
If the Grand Belfry exists,
then the bell would be there.
But he's already--
[LUFFY]
Good.
[AISA yelling]
[ROBIN]
Luffy!
Gone, just like that.
So, young lady.
Have you seen our navigator?
A woman with orange hair?
You mean Nami?
She's on the ship.
[AISA]
Huh...
I only hear one voice
coming from the sky.
[NAMI]
There they are!
[USOPP]
Whoa! Robin!
Miss Navigator. With Long Nose.
And the Cook too.
[AISA laughing]
[NAMI]
Aisa!
Thank goodness! You all right?
Nami!
[USOPP]
Huh?
Zoro! Chopper!
Weird Old Guy!
And a guerilla!
Oh, oh, oh!
Everyone's been taken down!
Oh! If only I had been here!
[NAMI]
Wait, Aisa, where's Luffy?
Wasn't he with you?
Luffy climbed up
the vine to rescue you.
But since everyone's here,
Luffy has to face Eneru
by himself!
We missed him, didn't we?
Just now.
I tried to stop him,
but he wouldn't listen.
Dammit, Luffy.
He knows we're
running short on time.
We gotta go now!
Go on without me. I'll take
the waver and find him.
Just try to get to
the Merry somehow!
[LUFFY]
Ah, man!
That ship is movin' fast!
Eneru!
[SHANDORIAN B]
Quickly! Get on the ships!
The whole sky is turning black!
[CROWD yelling]
[CHIEFTAIN]
What's wrong?
We need to flee at once.
My daughter Aisa.
She still hasn't...
Ah. She still hasn't returned.
Aisa is a bright child.
We must have faith that
she is with some warriors
and will be protected.
Right.
[CROWD yelling]
[WHITE BERET A]
Hurry! Hurry up!
[WHITE BERET B] Captain! If we
don't use the boats at the dock,
we'll never fit everyone in!
They'd have to sail
all the way around!
You men!
Use dials to create rivers
inside the island at once!
[WHITE BERETS]
Heso!
Everyone!
You have to go to Cloud End
at the edge of the clouds
right away before it's too late!
Eneru is planning to destroy
this land and everyone on it!
If we don't evacuate now,
we're going to die!
[CONIS]
If we know anything about Eneru,
we know this.
He's always had the power
to bring us to despair,
to make us suffer and break us!
I tell you!
What happens now makes our
past suffering insignificant!
It's not going to do any
good sitting and waiting
for a miracle!
It's time to face the fact
that as far as this land
is concerned,
God has abandoned us!
Before we pray,
before we close our eyes
to what's really happening here,
we have to do what we can
to save ourselves!
We can't survive by hiding
behind his victims any longer!
If we do nothing...
No matter who we try to blame,
we're all going to lose our
lives, and it'll be our fault!
If we want to live,
we must leave!
[MCKINLEY] How many of
the islanders are left?
[WHITE BERET B]
Almost half of them!
People only, no more baggage!
And get everybody
out to sea right away!
[WHITE BERET B]
Yes, sir!
Hold it!
Nobody's leaving until
everyone pays the 2 billion
Extol departure fee!
Amazon, hurry!
You can still escape with us!
[AMAZON]
Huh?
[MAN A]
Hurry to Cloud End!
[AMAZON]
Huh?
[MAN A]
The sky islands...
...are about to be destroyed!
Oh, my.
The wind has stopped.
[thunder rumbling]
[CROWD yelling]
[MAN B]
Run! Run!
[USOPP]
Wha--?
[ENERU]
Now, then.
Let us begin the festivities.
The time for endings has come.
Mamaragan.
[MAN B]
Get away from the island!
[MAN C]
Run! Don't look back!
[yelling]
[MAN D] The lightning
keeps getting bigger!
[MAN E] The boats at the
docks have been destroyed!
[WHITE BERET B]
To the western end of the beach!
Quickly!
There are still boats there!
Run to the west!
[MCKINLEY]
Move, people!
Leave your belongings!
[SHANDORIAN A]
Chief!
We need to get you on a boat!
[CHIEFTAIN]
Great warrior Kalgara.
I beg you.
Protect us all.
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
Man, those lightning
bolts are huge!
We're gonna end up
sky dust if we stay here!
[engine revving]
[NAMI]
Guys! Go now!
Once I find Luffy,
we'll be right behind you!
Uh, yeah, right! I gotcha!
[USOPP]
Hurry, Robin!
We gotta find a way to
carry these guys to the ship!
Wyper!
[ZORO coughs]
Swordsman!
[GAN FALL groans]
Weird Old Guy!
Oh, good, you're awake now!
There's not a moment to lose!
D'you think you can walk yet?
[GAN FALL]
So... Eneru has begun.
We must all hurry now.
There is truly nothing
more we can do here.
Wyper.
[NAMI]
We have to get out of here!
Not even Luffy can handle
an enemy who can fly!
I have to get to him before
this island is obliterated!
[ENERU laughing]
Magnificent!
[LUFFY yelling]
You better not think for
a second that I'm gonna
let you get away
with this, Eneru!
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[NARRATOR] Some 400 years
ago, there lived a man
known far and wide as a liar.
No one believed
his outrageous tales
and he was executed for his
apparent lies and trickery.
But the truth lives on
in the clouds high above!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Led by a Bell's Sound!
Tale of the Great Warrior
and the Explorer!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!