[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me
my head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really, really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til
I get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[CROCUS] He's a unique
and magnificent creature...
Inside Laboon's body
beats the heart of a human.
[LUFFY]
"A Promise Between Men!
Luffy And The Whale
Vow To Meet Again!"
[CROCUS] All who have seen
Laboon ask the same questions:
Why does he continually strike
his body against the Red Line?
Why does he keep howling
at Reverse Mountain?
[CROCUS]
Listen closely,
and I will reveal to you
Laboon's tragic story.
[CROCUS]
One fine sunny day,
while I was fulfilling my duties
as the lighthouse keeper,
some good‐natured pirates
came down Reverse Mountain.
They were followed by a
baby whale, spry and chipper,
whom I would soon come to know
as the one and only, Laboon.
[CROCUS] He is an Island Whale,
one of the largest in the world.
They are a rare species
found only in the West Blue.
Laboon had developed
a bond with the pirates,
traveling with them
for much of their journey.
But knowing the dangers
of the Grand Line,
the pirates chose to leave
Laboon behind in the West Blue.
[CROCUS] But the stubborn little
whale followed them anyway.
As a general rule, Island
Whales are social animals,
and travel together
in family groups.
I suspect that Laboon
had somehow come to feel
that those pirates
were his family.
The wear and tear on the
pirates' ship was quite severe,
so they stayed here
for several months.
In that time, I, too, was able
to forge a close
relationship with them.
Thus, when the day of their
departure finally arrived.
[CAPTAIN] I have a favor
to ask of you, my dear friend.
Could you look after
Laboon for a few years?
When my men and I have completed
our voyage around the world,
we'll be back.
[CAPTAIN]
Listen to me, Laboon...
We're taking our ship to
the end of the Grand Line.
Until we return, I need you
to wait for us here with Crocus.
You can't come with us...
It's too dangerous, even
for a mighty whale like you.
Don't worry three years
will pass by like a flash.
And don't forget...
No matter the distance,
our friendship lasts forever.
Well, I guess it's time!
[CAPTAIN]
All right, men!
We're setting sail!
Hoist the anchor!
[CREW cheers]
[CROCUS]
Laboon!
You have to wait for us here
and mind Crocus, Laboon.
Don't worry we'll be back...
I promise.
[CROCUS]
That was fifty long years ago.
[SANJI]
Fifty years?!
So, Laboon has been
waiting all this time
for his friends to return...
No wonder he's upset...
That kind of wait
would drive anyone crazy!
[ZORO]
This is some canal...
Amazing this
whale's still alive,
with a hole like
this in his body.
[SANJI] I suppose you're
responsible for this?
[CROCUS]
Just a doctor's playful mind...
[USOPP]
Doctor?!
That's right.
Legally certified...
I also ran a clinic on
the cape once upon a time.
Before that,
I served as a ship's doctor.
[LUFFY]
Really?
That's great...
Then join us,
we need a doctor.
[CROCUS]
Don't be ridiculous.
I no longer have
that kind of energy.
Exploring the seas is
a young man's burden.
[SANJI] What kind
of a doctor hollows out
the inside of a whale...
[NAMI] Maybe it's
part of the treatment.
The girl is right...
With a creature of this size,
it's virtually impossible to
treat it from the outside.
Therefore, I devised a more
drastic solution.
Here's the exit...
[LUFFY]
The sky.
What is it?
[USOPP] Don't you think
fifty years is a bit extreme?
Those pirates sure know how
to test someone's patience!
[SANJI]
Idiot! Don't ya get it?
This is the Grand Line.
His friends are dead.
That whale can wait forever,
they won't be back.
Sad to say,
but that's probably true...
Back in the day when those
guys traveled the Grand Line
it was an uncharted sea,
a thousand times more
treacherous than it is now.
Ugh! Why are you all
being so pessimistic?
You don't know
that they're dead!
They could still
come back for him!
Come on. Have some
sympathy, will ya?!
I thought it was very touching!
I mean a whale still
believing a promise
his friends made
despite all these years?!
That's a true bond!
Right, pops?!
[CROCUS]
Indeed...
But the lesson here
is that reality is cruel.
Laboon's cohorts aren't dead.
The truth is,
they abandoned their quest.
I learned that they turned tail
and left the Grand Line.
[USOPP]
I don't believe it.
I mean, why abandon
him like that?
[NAMI] You say they ran
away from the Grand Line.
Do you know if they made it
through the Calm Belt alive?
[CROCUS] I can't claim to know
exactly what became of them,
but I doubt they'll ever
come back here again.
Seasons, weather, currents, wind
direction‐‐on the Grand Line,
these elements seem to
defy the very laws of nature.
Common sense is useless,
and the terror of that fact
can be quite overwhelming.
So, if I've got this straight,
what you're saying is,
these pirates were
a bunch of cowards,
who cared more about
saving their own asses,
than keeping a
promise to a friend?
Why would anyone abandon
such a loyal creature?!
Just look at him!
It's cruelty on a grand scale!
But if you've known all this,
why haven't you told him?
Laboon can obviously
communicate with you.
He seems to understand
humans quite well for a whale.
[CROCUS]
I did tell him...
...down to the last,
miserable detail.
I know this isn't what you want
to hear, but it's the truth.
Your friends left
the Grand Line.
The bond you shared
with each other was real.
Just as real as the promise they
made to return for you one day.
[CROCUS]
But, still... face the facts...
Those men are
never coming back.
[LABOON roars mornfully]
Laboon! Please!
I say this for your own good!
They're not coming back!
I understand that
you don't wanna accept it!
But you need to realize
that this is how things are!
Listen...
Laboon!!
[CROCUS] That was
the day that Laboon began
to howl at Reverse Mountain...
Soon after, he started slamming
his body against the Red Line.
It's as if he believes that wall
is what keeps his friends away,
and by breaking it, he can
clear the path for their return.
[SANJI]
I admire his dedication...
[USOPP]
Never gave up on 'em.
He refuses to believe me,
because then he'd have
to admit that it's over.
And that terrifies him
more than anything.
There's no way for him to
go back to the West Blue...
So, what we have is a
paradox of tragic proportions.
Laboon is a lost soul dying
to live with his friends,
but won't stop killing
himself to reach them...
Tragedy. Still for all the grief
those pirates put him through
they did the same to you by
saddling you with their burden.
I mean you've done
enough for Laboon.
What about you...?
[CROCUS]
The scars on his hide are deep.
Those in his heart
are even deeper...
He needs someone
to tend his wounds,
and I'm all he's got...
For years, he's battered himself
while I've patched him up...
A strange friendship,
but it works.
What the hell
is that idiot up to?
Ya gotta watch
him every second...
[SANJI] We've been watching him,
look what happens...
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Flower Arrangement!
Think he's aware
that's our mast...?
And now it's on top of a whale.
Why'd he do that?
Hey Luffy, stop
tearing up the ship.
[howls]
You... ass...! Luffy... stop...!
The boy...! He's dead!
Oh don't worry...!
It'll take way more
than that to kill Luffy!
Ha...! Gotcha!
What does he
think he's doing?!
[ZORO]
You wanna let us in on your plan
before ya kill yourself?!
[LUFFY]
It's a draw!
I'm stronger than I look!
But, I have a
feeling you knew that...
I can always tell when
someone's itching to fight...
Well, if you want a battle,
I'll gladly give you one...
Your shipmates used to
spar with you didn't they?
You miss it.
Well, I can rival
anything they threw at ya!
Tell ya what‐‐
after me and my friends
travel the Grand Line,
we'll come back
here and find you.
And then you better be
ready for a rematch!
[LUFFY]
Hey, not bad!
Consider this a
symbol of my promise
to come do battle with you...
Of course,
it's a rush paint job,
so you'll have to be careful
and avoid hitting your head
or you'll rub it right off.
Understand?
Good whale!
[USOPP]
Where are they?
Where are who...?
Oh, you mean those two wierdos?
I guess they escaped.
Must have happened when
we were distracted by Laboon.
I wonder who they were...
Miss Wednesday...
What are we going to do now?
First, put some
distance between us
and these morons.
Then we report to the Boss.
Our time for completing this
mission has long since run out.
[MR. 9]
I can hear the others now.
They're probably
already calling us traitors.
I know...
But without our weapons,
we've no choice but to go back
to the office and start over.
[MR. 9] And this time no
one will stop us...
Aaaah!
No, no! I couldn't have!
What is it?
It's... gone.
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
What?!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Hmm... What's this thing?
[MISS WEDNESDAY] How could
you have lost the Log Pose?!
[MR. 9]
I don't know!
I must've dropped it somewhere!
But we're not going
anywhere without it...
‐‐[MISS WEDNESDAY] How awful!
‐‐[MR. 9 gasps]
Ah! No! This can't
be happening...
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Wha‐‐?!
[MR. 9]
It's...! Ahhhh...
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Oh no!
[MR. 9]
The Unluckies!!
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
We're out of time!
[MR. 9]
Mr. 13!
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Miss Friday!
Don't be hasty!
Please, we can explain!
We'll check in with
Boss immediately!
Aaaah!
[screams]
Okay, then!
I finally have some
peace and quiet
so I can work on a plan
for the Grand Line journey.
Ah... Don't think I forgot about
you, Elephant Blue Fin Tuna!
Damn... That's my life...!
Luffy breaks it then
I put it back together!
Hey, get off your lazy butt
and give me a hand!
This ship isn't gonna
fix itself you know!
[NAMI screams]
You mind? Keep it down.
[SANJI] Is there some problem,
my dearest Nami?!
If it's food you're worried
about, say no more!
[USOPP]
Someone say "food"?
You idiots!
The compass is broken!
The needle just spins!
It won't stop!
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I don't know about you,
but I'm getting dizzy!
Whoa... This is cool!
It is sadly apparent
that none of you
possess the slightest knowledge
about how things work here...
Did you all come here to die?
Ah, great spread!
It's for everyone!
[CROCUS] There is nothing
wrong with your compass.
The Grand Line has little
regard for the rules of the sea.
Common sense is
useless in this place.
The needle... Why does it spin?
[CROCUS]
Because we are surrounded
by a powerful magnetic field.
The islands here are riddled
with magnetic minerals,
which cause all
sorts of abnormalities.
Also, the winds and
currents lack constancy
in their patterns.
As a navigator, I'm sure you
can appreciate this dilemma.
So then...
If we don't have
a way to tell direction,
this whole trip is hopeless...
Yummy!
I don't know what to say...
We're screwed...
Hey! You're the navigator,
so navigate us outta here!
This is delicious!
You oughta try some!
Would all of you just
shut up for five seconds
so I can figure this out!
This nose of the Elephant
Tuna is my favorite part!
Tasty!
If you have any hope of
navigating the Grand Line,
you're going to need
a Log Pose to guide you.
[NAMI]
Log Pose?
I've never heard of it.
It's a specially
designed compass
that can record levels
of magnetism.
[LUFFY]
Is it strange looking?
Why, yes, it does
have an odd shape.
[LUFFY]
Something like this?
Yes, exactly...
Only a fool courting
disaster would attempt
to travel the
Grand Line without one.
Understood...
Excuse me for one second.
So...
Why didn't you tell me you
had one of those Log things?!
[LUFFY] I found it on deck,
just laying there.
Those two weirdoes must've
dropped it when they escaped.
Did they?
[LUFFY]
Why'd you hit me?
Felt like it...
[LUFFY]
Oh, okay.
Huh, but there isn't a
dial face on this thing.
[CROCUS] You don't need one.
It's a special brand
of magnetism that runs
through the Grand Line islands.
Complete with its own set of
rules that makes it possible
to get around.
By recording the level of
magnetism between two islands,
you can chart a route
from one island to the next.
The log pose method
is really the only choice.
Since the magnetism here
presents huge problems
for conventional navigation...
As it turns out Reverse Mountain
is a great starting point.
It produces seven
levels of magnetism.
But it doesn't matter which one
you choose to start with.
Eventually all of them
will pull against each other
and form one route.
And the island at the
end of that route...
..is Raftel.
The last and most mysterious
in the Grand Line...
It's very existence
was confirmed
by the King of the Pirates,
the only known person
to have traveled the
Grand Line in its entirety.
Raftel...
That's it!
That must be where
the One Piece is hidden...
[CROCUS] That's the
most prominent theory,
but no one's been able to
set foot on Raftel Island since.
Don't worry.
We'll know soon enough!
Well, I'm satisfied!
You guys ready to go?
I told you that
was for all of us!
He... He even ate the bones!
A Log Pose...
We have to take
special care of this...
It's the key to finding the
greatest treasure of all time!
You greedy, bottomless pit!
You ate the meal
I made for Nami!
Well I hope you left room...
for your dessert!
[LUFFY] Ow!
Why's everyone hitting me?!
[SANJI] You never think of
anyone but yourself and‐‐!
[NAMI]
Sanji...
[SANJI]
Yes...?
[NAMI]
Both of you get out of my sight
before I wring your necks!
[USOPP]
Okay, so...
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but doesn't the Log Pose work
better when it's not broken?!
Oh no... Our log pose is ruined!
[CROCUS]
Calm yourselves...
I will give you my own...
...as a "thank you"
for helping Laboon.
Oh good, I'm not dead...
[SANJI]
Hello, dear lady.
Allow me to
help you to your feet.
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Oh, thank you.
[SANJI]
Nice day, don't you think?
[MR. 9]
Hey!
We need a favor.
[LUFFY]
Whisky Peak?
Huh. That's a funny name.
[USOPP]
So what is it?
[MR. 9]
That's where we live... Um, sir.
[NAMI]
How were you stranded?
Where's your ship?
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Well... It was destroyed.
Asking us for a
ride is pushing it, Mr. 9;
especially after you
tried to kill the whale?
What's with the wardrobe?
What are you supposed to be?
I am a king!
You're lying.
No, please!
We can't say!
She's right.
You have to believe us, our only
motive here is getting home.
We'd tell you everything
if we could, it's just that...
..."mystery" is
our company's motto.
You see, we have
to be mysterious!
It's sort of a rule...
[MISS WEDNESDAY] We have
confidence in your character.
Can't you give us
the same courtesy?!
[MR. 9]
Please! We're begging you!
Show some mercy!
Don't do it...
These two fools are
dishonest to the core.
They can't be trusted.
Listen...
I should mention that
our Log Pose was broken,
and we don't have another one,
so still wana ride with us?
What...?! You broke it?!
That was mine!
Those aren't cheap, you know?!
You're stuck here too?!
How long were you
gonna make us beg
before you
bothered to tell us?!
Oh... Sorry... I forgot.
Crocus gave us
his Log Pose, so...
[MR. 9]
Oh! Please have pity on us!
[MR. 9] That lousy bitch!
She tricked us!
It's fine...
You can ride with us.
[LUFFY] You said your home
is called Whisky Peak?
Let's go there.
Why?! These two are obviously
some pretty shady characters.
Why would we
take them anywhere?!
It's fine...
Don't sweat the small stuff.
We'll be all right.
Choose your route carefully.
Once you head out from here,
you'll be committed
to that course.
That's okay.
If we don't like it,
we'll try a different
route next time.
I see...
Okay...!It's time we get going!
[LUFFY] Now that me and
Laboon have an understanding,
I can leave with
a clear conscience!
Just who on earth do
you think you are anyway?
What's that...? Me?
Oh, I'm the man who'll
be King of the Pirates!
[MISS WEDNESDAY]
Not too bright, this one...
[CROCUS]
Should be good to go.
The Log Pose has had plenty
of time to store the route.
The needle should be pointing in
the same direction as the map.
It's pointing
directly to Whisky Peak.
[LUFFY]
See ya, pops!
Thanks again for the Log Pose!
Take care!
[CROCUS]
Have a safe trip, my boy!
[LUFFY]
I'm off, Laboon!
Be ready to fight
when I get back!
[LUFFY]
Next stop, Whisky Peak!
Ready gang...?!
Let's set sail...
I wonder...
Luffy and his
exuberant crew could be
the very pirates
we've been waiting for...
That young captain
sure has a way about him.
It's uncanny really...
[CROCUS]
Wouldn't you agree... Roger?
♪All that's in
my heart confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[LUFFY]
Hahahaha! What a feast!
[USOPP] Getting this
kinda classy treatment
as soon as we arrive?!
Oh, I love being a pirate!
[ZORO] Don't you
find it a little weird?
[SANJI]
So many cute girls!
Look at'em all!
[ZORO]
I still say something's wrong.
What do you think, Nami?
[NAMI] When it comes to
drinking games, I don't lose!
Bring it on!
[ZORO]
You too?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Town that Welcomes Pirates?
Setting Foot on Whisky Peak!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!