[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] A long time ago
in the waters of the East Blue,
there were three boys who
dreamed of becoming pirates.
Seven years after
Sabo's short-lived voyage,
Ace followed him to sea.
See you soon.
Keep training hard!
[ACE chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Three years after that,
Luffy departed from
his hometown, Windmill Village,
with his heart full of dreams.
[LUFFY] Sabo was first,
and Ace was second.
I may be the last to go,
but I'm gonna be the best!
I'm comin' for you, Ace!
And all my special
moves work now, too!
[NARRATOR]
But after the death of Ace,
Luffy's optimism from
that day is nowhere in sight.
Me? King of the Pirates?
What a joke!
I'm useless.
I'm so...
I'm so weak!
[LUFFY] "I Want to See Them!
Luffy's Mournful Cry!"
[PIRATE A laughs]
Anyone who stands between us
and the Grand Line
is getting wrecked!
And we're starting with
the chumps on that island!
[GARP]
Ready the cannonballs.
Meteor Fist Shower!
Heads up, scumbags!
[PIRATES screaming]
[DADAN grunts]
I... think you've
had enough today.
[DADAN grunts]
[BANDIT A]
It's Garp!
[BANDIT B] Garp is back and
he brought his battleship!
[BANDIT C]
Should we run?
[gasps]
[MAN H] I read about the battle
at Marineford in the paper!
Congratulations on your victory!
[GARP] Word travels
fast these days, huh?
[MAN I]
Is Luffy okay?
Now that Whitebeard's dead,
the pirates are
going out of control.
Is that why you're here?
Things have gotten bad.
We're afraid to go out. They're
like vultures staring us down.
I don't mean to complain,
but I'm afraid they could
invade any second now.
Not likely!
I just sunk three of 'em with
cannonballs on the way out here.
Really? Whew!
[GARP] Eh, they we're nothing
but a bunch of blowhards.
All bark and no bite.
But seas are gonna be
tense the world over
without Whitebeard
to scare off all the thugs.
Even if that's not
the Navy's "official" stance.
Anyway, since you're
so far from our base,
I prepared a little something.
See?
[MARINES]
Sir!
[MAN J] "Security by
Navy Vice Admiral Garp"?
That'll scare 'em off for sure!
[WOMAN A] One look at that
and they'll straighten right up!
While you're here,
there's one more problem.
A bunch of mountain bandits
came down to the village.
They took over Makino's bar
and they aren't leaving.
[GARP]
That so?
[MAKINO]
Please! Calm down!
[DADAN]
Hello, Garp!
Hey, that's one right there!
[DADAN]
How dare you show your face here
after what you've done!
[MARINES, CROWD gasp]
[MAN K]
Garp!
That's not good!
[MARINES]
Vice Admiral!
[panting]
Back off, men. She's a friend.
[MARINES]
Huh?
[DADAN panting]
[DADAN]
The hell I am!
You were right with
them on that battlefield!
Those poor boys and you didn't
do a damn thing to help them!
Why did you have
me raise Ace? Huh?
me take care of them
if it was going to end this way?
[gasps]
[grunts]
You stood there and
watched that boy die!
You care more about your
damn job than your family!
"The great hero of the Navy"!
I hope you're proud of yourself,
you heartless piece of crap!
[MAGRA]
Now, now, Boss. Take it easy!
[DADAN]
Say something, you bastard!
Why didn't you help him?
Why didn't you do something?
Look me right in the face!
You spineless wretch!
You answer me, dammit!
Dadan! Enough!
[MAKINO]
Mm-mm.
Makino...
[panting]
[DADAN panting]
How do you think he feels?
He's their grandfather.
He's suffering, too!
He was right there and
he couldn't do a thing!
You're wrong.
[DADAN]
"Garp is suffering"?
No.
[DADAN] The only one
who's really suffering here
is Luffy, damn it.
[MAKINO]
Okay, since you asked so nicely,
let's learn some manners today!
Thank you for the lesson.
Hah! Nice one. Wow!
[ACE]
Heh.
[MAKINO]
Well, close.
Since we haven't
actually started,
you should say,
"thank you in advance."
Really? That was wrong?
I dunno. Sounded
pretty polite to me.
That may be true, but it's
a special situation.
So, every detail
has to be perfect.
After all, Ace wants
to pay respects
to a very impressive captain.
A friend of yours.
Y'mean Shanks?
Yep!
But by the time
I get to meet him,
I'll be a captain myself.
As a pirate and
as your big brother,
I gotta thank him
for saving your life
or we're both gonna
end up looking bad.
'Kay, so let's pretend Shanks
is here with you right now.
What do you say?
[ACE] Hi. I'm Ace.
Who the hell are you?
Boo!
I know you're pirates, but I
don't think he'd be impressed.
Yeah! Be way more cool!
Fancy meeting you here.
Boo.
[gasps]
Trash talk! Trash talk!
Hey, punk! What's your deal?
Boo!
Mister? What's your deal?
[MAKINO]
Boo!
'Cause he didn't say "punk"?
[MAKINO]
Nope! Nope!
[laughs] Luffy, stop!
You're distracting poor Ace!
Go be stupid somewhere else.
We're learning here!
You little pest!
I'm not distracting!
Oh, yeah!
I found an anaconda nest
filled with a bunch of eggs
and they're super huge!
Let's grab 'em and cook 'em up!
What? Man, that sounds awesome!
No, not right now.
Aww...
[ACE] I'm gonna learn some
manners even if it kills me!
[LUFFY]
I can't go on my own!
What if the anaconda
mom finds me?
But if you're there with me,
we can beat it for sure!
C'mon, let's go!
[ACE]
I said no!
Luffy loved Ace more than
anything in the world.
[MAKINO crying]
Makino!
[MAYOR]
Hey, Garp.
What happened to Luffy?
The newspaper said he
went missing after the war.
That he did.
A submarine carried him away.
The Admirals attacked and tried
to stop him from escaping,
and afterwards,
they held a search,
but they couldn't find
a single trace of him.
There was no shipwreck,
so he's probably alive.
[CROWD sighs]
That's a relief!
Wait, so what's up
with this bandit?
She obviously seems
to know Garp,
but why did he let her
punch him like that?
Yeah.
[DADAN] Luffy's been a little
moron since the day I met him,
but no matter what he does,
I'm always on his side.
[DADAN] As much as I'm hurting,
I know he's got it worse,
and it breaks my heart.
[DADAN]
Luffy!
I know things
are hard right now,
but don't you dare give up!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, far away
and far along the Grand Line
in a place known
as the New World.
Shanks...
I don't know how I can
ever thank you enough.
No need to make
a big deal out of it.
Whitebeard was a rival,
but I still held a lot
of respect for the man.
[SHANKS]
Even Sengoku felt that way.
As for Whitebeard and Ace,
I'm sure you won't
object to their friends
taking care of the burial.
That's enough! Let me
take responsibility.
Well, I suppose it's
time for us to go.
Yeah, thank you again.
[SHANKS] I can only imagine
how tough this is on Luffy.
Even so, his brother
died like a true man.
Take it back or else.
You don't know anything about
the man who saved my life!
This is his era.
Don't you forget it!
[SHANKS] Maybe Ace
wouldn't want to hear this,
but that's exactly what
Captain Roger would've done.
[SHANKS]
There were times when I wished
he wasn't too bold
to run away...
[SHANKS]
Too bold to shed tears.
Listen, Luffy.
It's not only victory that
makes a man, but defeat.
Joy and sorrow alike.
There's no shame
in backing down.
[SHANKS]
There's no shame in crying...
...so long as you overcome it.
[LUFFY]
Damn it!
I couldn't save
my crew or my brother!
Why? Why? Why?
Why am I so weak?
Damn it! Damn it!
I'm useless!
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Go away!
Leave me alone!
[JIMBEI]
I cannot.
Although I understand your pain,
I will not allow you
to hurt yourself any more.
It's not your business!
This is my body!
[JIMBEI]
What of Ace, then?
Who sacrificed his
body to protect you?
Was that none of your business?
You bastard. Shut up!
Say one more word and
I'm gonna crush you!
If that would make you happy,
then why don't you try?
But let me warn you,
injured though I am,
you will not defeat me.
Not in that condition!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
[JIMBEI growls]
[panting]
[ACE]
Let me tell you something.
A while back, when I
was hunting down Teach,
I went to Alabasta Kingdom
and I saw my brother for the
first time in three years.
As soon as I saw his face,
a weight lifted from my heart.
And do you know why?
[yells]
Ow! Are you insane?
Stop! Luffy!
I've had enough
of your nonsense!
[LUFFY yells]
[JIMBEI grunts]
Boy, you can't see
a thing. You're blind.
You never doubted your strength,
but now the confidence
that once allowed you
to soar above the clouds
has been shattered.
Your brother, who was
your guiding light,
has faded away,
and your enemies stand so tall
and cast so great a shadow,
that you can do naught
but cower in the darkness.
And now, you strike
out like an animal
at the cage your doubt
has placed around you.
Hate to tell you though,
you're still not
strong enough to beat me.
So, you're smarter
than you look.
Now fire, Pacifistas!
[KIZARU]
Huh.
[LUFFY yelling]
Struggle all you like,
but you're trapped in
the palm of my hand!
[JIMBEI] So long as you are
consumed by regret and guilt,
you will never find
your way forward!
Luffy, your pain may be great,
but it mustn't devour you!
There is yet joy
beyond your sorrows!
What's gone may be gone,
but you still have something
left in this world to treasure.
Don't you?!
[ZORO grunting]
Hey, you wanna screw around?
Go do it somewhere else.
I'm tryin' to build muscle here!
Luffy! We've got a big
storm on the horizon!
Make preparations, quick!
[USOPP] I had a big one!
You just missed it!
But the next one is
gonna be even bigger!
Scram!
I'm almost done!
Just keep your pants on!
It's okay. No matter
how bad you're hurt,
you're in good hands!
By the way, this one
might sting a little bit.
Oh, Luffy!
If you like treasure,
this research is fascinating!
Come see!
What's up, buddy?
If you're checkin'
on the cola engine,
it's in super shape.
Wow!
And if you're checkin' on
me, well, I'm super, too!
[BROOK]
Good morning, Captain!
Rise and shine!
How about I play
you a little song?
Really get those bones moving!
[BROOK laughs]
Luffy.
Luffy!
Captain Luffy!
[ALL]
Luffy!
[LUFFY crying]
[JIMBEI]
Hmm?
My crew...
I still have my crew!
Zoro, Nami, Usopp,
Sanji, Chopper, Robin,
Franky, and Brook!
They're still out there,
waiting for me!
[sighs] Now do you see?
[LUFFY] I have to
get back to the ship
no matter how long it takes me.
Guys! Meet back on
the Sunny in three days!
[ALL]
Roger!
[LUFFY] Everything's a
mess and I'm already late,
but I have to make
it back to Sabaody.
I know they'll be there.
[ACE] It wasn't just
knowing he was safe,
or seeing him smile again...
When you've got a bungling
kid brother like me...
...ya can't help
but worry a bit.
He might be a bit much
for all of you to handle,
but take good care
of him for me.
[ACE] I mean, sure,
he wasn't the snot-nosed kid
following me around anymore,
but more than that...
He had friends...
A crew that he could depend on.
No matter what,
he'll be just fine,
so I don't have
to worry anymore.
[LUFFY]
I wish they were here right now.
I miss them.
I miss my crew!
[NARRATOR]
Luffy thinks of his friends
scattered across the seas.
Involved in their own struggles,
they all search for ways
to return to Sabaody.
When news from the War
of the Best reaches them,
they realize the situation
is even more complicated
than they feared.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Straw Hats in Shock!
The Bad News Has Reached Them!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!