[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] The Straw
Hat Pirates have fallen
right into the middle of
the impenetrable Marine
fortress Navarone.
Oh, come on.
[NARRATOR]
Zoro was captured.
You stupid face!
[NARRATOR] Luffy and Sanji
have infiltrated the kitchen
under the guise of
famous Marine cooks,
but danger draws ever closer.
[LUFFY]
"The Marine's Dragnet Closes In!
The Second Member Captured!"
[USOPP]
Marine Command Branch 8.
[ROBIN]
That's the official name,
but it's more commonly
known as Navarone.
The Marines' most
powerful stronghold.
The command center is most
likely in that central tower,
but that's about all we know.
Enough with all the
technical talk already!
Aren't ancient ruins
enough for you?
Now you gotta analyze some
stupid Marine fortress?
Knowledge is power.
Or have you forgotten that
we're in enemy territory?
[USOPP]
I haven't forgotten anything,
but we can't just stand
around looking at stuff!
I gotta get to the Going Merry
to see if my baby's okay.
Merry? Merry, where are you?
[ROBIN] It's reasonable
to assume that the ship
was seized by the Marines.
[USOPP]
Why are you so calm?
Don't you care about our ship?
Even if we can find
the Going Merry,
how will we escape with it?
Do you honestly think
that the Marines
will simply show us the way out?
Uh, well, I...
Which is why we must find out
all we can about
this place, right?
Yeah?
I wouldn't be a pirate if I
was scared of a few Marines!
I'm done with this.
I'll leave the standing around
and looking at stuff to you.
My leg!
Huh? Hey! That really hurt!
[MARINE A]
Found 'em?
[MARINES]
No, nothing!
We'll capture those
filthy Straw Hat Pirates.
Leave no stone unturned!
They couldn't have gotten far.
[MARINES]
Sir!
There's no escaping.
We've already captured the
legendary Roronoa Zoro.
[gasps]
Z-Zoro.
[ROBIN]
Are you all right, Long-nose?
[USOPP]
Did you hear what he said?
[ROBIN] The Marines
seem to have realized
that the Going Merry was in fact
full of pirates, not ghosts.
Now they're angry.
We need to worry about our
survival instead of our ship.
I don't care what you
have to say anymore!
That ship is more precious
than life itself
and I'm gonna go in
there and get it back!
Do you hear me?
I've made up my mind so
just stay out of my way!
See you on board!
So stubborn.
[gasps]
[groans] I weathered
that wretched storm
to come to a backwater base
in the middle of nowhere.
And they don't have the
decency to welcome me? Hah?
--Hey, you! Over there!
--[MARINE E] Sir!
I am here to meet
this base's commander.
So inform the officer in
charge that I have arrived
and wish to commence
the meeting post haste!
Yes, sir, but... Sorry, sir.
It's just I have to ask
what business you have
with our commander?
I have no obligation to explain
anything to you, Private!
I'm really very sorry, sir,
but I also have to
confirm your rank
and which division
you're attached to.
I will explain nothing
to you, understand?
Now contact your
commander immediately!
[MARINE E]
Of course, sir.
But I don't think
it'll do any good.
And just why is that, Private?
Well, sir, this is the hour
that Commander Jonathan
normally takes for lunch,
so he's probably eating in
the dining hall right now.
[SHEPHERD]
So call the dining hall, dimwit!
But, sir, you don't
know the credo
of Marine Command
Branch 8, do you?
You have a credo?
Rule one! You must wash your
hands before every meal!
Rule two! Never leave any
food behind on your plate.
Rule three! Never mention
work in the dining hall!
Rule four! Always brush
your teeth aft--
Enough!
You're saying that your
commander thinks
lunch is more important than a
VIP sent by Marine headquarters?
Is that correct?
Yes! That's correct, sir!
[SHEPHERD growls]
I can see that you'll
be of no use to me.
I'll find the commander
on my own.
But before I go, I have
one piece of advice for you.
If I were you, I would start
thinking of ways to explain
this situation to
the court marshal.
[SHEPHERD cackles]
[SHEPHERD]
This sector no longer requires
the presence of this
bloated stronghold,
or the peculiar,
isolated commander
who refuses to step
foot outside of it.
The Marines don't need either
of those outdated dinosaurs,
and I will make
sure to note that
in my report to headquarters.
That old badger won't
be eating and fishing
on the Marine's dime for long.
Enjoy your last few meals
at Navarone, Commander!
For soon, you will be
relieved of your duties here!
[SHEPHERD]
Hm?
Guess it was nothing.
[SHEPHERD]
Hm?
[gasping, groaning]
[ROBIN] Marine headquarters
inspection division.
You'll do just fine, Inspector.
[ROBIN chuckles]
Oh! So good!
This new cook is
totally awesome!
Amazing! It tastes even better
than the guys from the
morning crew said it would!
All right! The next
100 are waiting!
Hurry up and finish!
[MARINES]
Aye aye, sir!
[JESSICA]
Here you go.
Uh, Jessica?
This is the same dish you always
prepare for me, isn't it?
It sure is. Is there a problem?
Well, my men keep carrying on
about the incredible
food prepared by
the new cooks from Marie Jois.
Don't get me wrong,
I love your cooking.
But I'd really like to try
something from these new guys.
Oh, you're saying
you don't like it.
The head chef herself personally
took the time to
prepare a meal for you,
and you don't like it?
Would you rather eat the
same food as the grunts?
I'll have you know that
this meal was made
with love and care just for you.
I really appreciate the
love and care in my meal,
but I don't so much like
the broccoli and carrots.
Have you forgotten
our base's credo?
No. I'm eating, see?
It's good! Mmm!
[JESSICA chuckles]
[LUFFY] Whoa! It's like a
buffet of deliciousness!
Keep up the good work, guys!
You're doing great!
[SHINPACHI]
What's up with that other guy?
He's just been inhaling
the food nonstop.
Don't mind him.
His job is taste testing.
[SHINPACHI] It doesn't look to
me like he's tasting anything,
and he sure isn't
a very good cook.
You on the other hand
are clearly a master,
a true talent,
and you're getting very
popular among the troops.
Hey, thank you.
I'll be sure to write
down some of my recipes.
I have an order for table eight.
And make it snappy!
Aye aye, sir!
For a woman that
strong and beautiful,
I'd go through any culinary
torture to make her happy.
Done!
[COOKS]
So fast!
Hey! Looks good!
I'll be happy to
take that for you!
Hold it! If you
touch any of that,
you'll be eating the rest
of your meals in the brig!
Yeah, yeah, no problem!
Did he hear anything
I just said?
Who is this guy at table eight?
Jessica sure seems concerned
about what he's eating.
She's always pretty wound up,
but it gets even worse when it
comes to her husband's food.
My sweet Jessica's
a married woman?
No time for chitchatting,
get back to work!
Her husband is definitely
the luckiest guy in Navarone,
maybe even the world.
[SHINPACHI] She's married to
the commander of this place.
He's the commander?
Wait, Luffy.
Eat up!
Thank you. You're dismissed.
Right. Aye aye, sir!
[JONATHAN] Outstanding. It's
everything they said it was!
[JONATHAN] It's surpassed
all my expectations!
[LUFFY]
Mine, too!
[JONATHAN]
Hm?
[LUFFY grunting]
I just want a meatball,
you selfish jerk!
I see you've finally
decided to show your face!
[LUFFY]
Mmm.
Dammit, I'm already too late!
[JONATHAN]
Welcome, Straw Hat Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
I am Commander Jonathan,
Chief Officer of G8,
your sworn enemy.
Straw Hat Luffy.
I would rather not
resort to violence
in the dining hall,
so please be civil.
Just answer me one question
if you would be so kind.
If I answer it, can I
split that food with you?
If you answer the question,
you can have all of it.
[LUFFY]
Really? You got a deal!
Sorry I called you a jerk!
You idiot! Hurry up
and get outta there!
[JONATHAN]
No matter how hard I try,
I can't figure out
your purpose here.
I am certain that
Captain Smoker is the one
who defeated Crocodile
and in Alabasta,
your shenanigans resulted
in no discernable gain.
They acquired you neither
fame nor fortune.
Your motives remain a mystery,
and I want to know why it is you
came to Navarone of all places.
[LUFFY] That's easy!
We fell from the sky!
This is just where we landed.
Here in the Grand Line
it's just one crazy
thing after another.
I gotta say I'm really starting
to like this fortress.
The food here is great.
[JONATHAN chuckles]
[JONATHAN]
You should know that
even with the power
of the Devil Fruit,
one will find that
escape from our
charming little fortress
is impossible.
It would take nothing
short of a miracle.
Checkmate!
I'll leave when I'm good
and ready, Mister Commander!
[chuckles]
I doubt you'll talk so tough
when you hear that
we've captured Zoro.
Huh? Zoro?
That idiot!
All right, fortress guy.
Where's Zoro?
[JONATHAN]
Why do you ask?
Well, why do think?
So I can find him
and rescue my friend!
Don't be so hasty.
You'll be joining the
swordsman soon enough.
I'll make sure of that.
[BOTH gasp]
[LUFFY gasps]
[JONATHAN]
Hm?
You'll blow our cover!
We gotta get outta here!
[SANJI gasps]
Jessica.
Such a shame for someone
with skills like yours
to waste their life as a
filthy Straw Hat Pirate!
Give up while you
still can, pirates!
The cooks of Navarone are even
tougher than the soldiers!
Heh. Bring it on.
I come from cooks that
make you look like
schoolgirls playing house!
[SANJI] But still.
I can't attack Jessica.
What are we gonna do?
[JONATHAN grunts]
[MARINE I]
Man, I am starving!
[MARINE J]
Time to eat!
[MARINE K] I wanna try some
of that fancy new food!
[MARINE L]
Bring on the grub!
[JESSICA]
No! We almost had them!
[SANJI]
Now's our chance!
Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
See ya 'round, fortress guy!
[OFFICER B] Our enemy
is the Straw Hat Pirates.
You must be prepared to engage
them at a moment's notice!
For the honor of Navarone,
we must capture and deal with
them swiftly and without mercy!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[USOPP] These Marines
are really fired up!
I won't last long if I try to
play hide and seek
with these animals!
[USOPP] Subterfuge
is key. Yeah that's it.
I gotta blend in.
Well, what have we here? Ha, ha!
Transformation complete!
Now I'll be able to--
--[MARINE M] Hold it!
--[USOPP squeals]
As a Navarone Marine,
you will follow the
dress code to the "t."
Even your collar
is important, Private.
Don't ever forget that again.
[USOPP gasps]
My apologies, sir!
I assure you it
won't happen again!
By the way, could you
tell me how to get the dock
where the Straw Hat's ship is?
I'm new here so I'm kinda lost.
The docks are on the lower level
about six blocks down.
[USOPP] Thank you, sir! And I
really appreciate the guidance!
Wait! That dock is--
[USOPP]
Don't worry! I'll find it!
Oh, Merry!
You're really okay!
[MECHAO]
A fine boat.
Carvel model with a lateen sail
and an axial stern rudder
right down the center.
It's an older model,
but it can hold it's own
with the best of 'em.
Hey! Who are you?
[MECHAO] You don't know me?
You must be a rookie.
Uh, yeah.
[MECHAO] From the looks of it,
she's seen her share of action.
She's covered in patches,
but you can tell they
were expertly done.
Yep. This ship is truly loved.
So you can tell that
by looking at her?
Makes no difference to me
if it's a Marine ship
or a pirate ship.
I can tell at a glance
whether or not a boat has
gotten the proper TLC.
That means so much!
Thanks, old man!
[MECHAO] Well, I wasn't
complimenting you!
No, but I like the sound of it.
Is that so wrong?
You're a strange one,
aren't you?
[DRAKE]
You haven't changed a bit.
Still trying to compare pirate
junk to real Marine ships.
[MECHAO]
Lt. Commander, if you're here
about the ship repairs,
it'll be at least another week.
It seems that Marines
these days are
under the mistaken
impression that
ruining perfectly good
ships is their job.
Thanks to that,
the repair schedule
is completely packed.
[DRAKE]
Stand down, old-timer.
I didn't come here
to bother you.
I'm here to talk to your
new friend over there.
Hey, you!
[USOPP gasps]
Yes, sir!
What unit are you with?
[USOPP sputtering]
Did you forget which
unit you're in?
Uh, I think I'm pretty
sure it's unit 18, sir.
Of course, unit 18. That's
the sniper unit, isn't it?
Don't you idiots know
that this dock is
off limits to everyone except
for maintenance personnel?
Well, we snipers
are a forgetful type.
So sorry,
it'll never happen again.
I'll just be on my...
That's not necessary!
[USOPP]
It's not?
[DRAKE]
Arrest him.
[USOPP shrieks]
But I just want to get
back to my unit, sir!
It was reported to me that a
suspicious new recruit was seen.
And by the way,
unit 18 isn't a sniper unit,
it's a supply unit.
That's right! My bad!
I'm in a supply unit!
[MECHAO] Stop this immediately,
you brainless jackals!
Don't you know where you are?
For the dockworkers,
this place is holy!
If you shed even a single
drop of his blood here,
I'll make sure you regret it.
Put your swords down.
We'll take him to
the command center.
[MARINES]
Sir!
[JONATHAN]
Hmm. Is this him?
[DRAKE]
Commander.
The suspect insists
that he is a Marine.
But all of our evidence
indicates otherwise.
I think he's another one
of the Straw Hats.
[JONATHAN]
Hmm.
--You there.
--[USOPP gasps]
What's your name?
It's--
It's classified?
And your unit?
It's classified.
Why did you go to the dock
where the pirate ship
was impounded?
It's classified.
"It's classified."
[USOPP]
Uh-huh.
[DRAKE]
I say we throw him in the brig
and put the thumbscrews on him.
Hold on, Lieutenant.
But--!
[JONATHAN]
Come to think of it,
I heard that a special inspector
from Marine Headquarters
was supposed to arrive on
the Stan Marey this morning.
What?
A special inspector?
[DRAKE]
Commander!
[JONATHAN]
If he is an inspector,
then it's only natural
that he wouldn't be able to
reveal his name or what
unit he's attached to.
[DRAKE]
That's ridiculous.
An idiot like him--
[USOPP laughs]
So, you've figured it out.
Huh?
[USOPP] You should be proud
of yourself, Commander.
I am the special inspector
from Marine HQ,
but you can call me...
...Inspector Usopp!
Is there any illegal
activity in G8?
Are all military rules and
regulations being followed?
How is the morale for
the troops on base?
In order to answer
these questions,
I infiltrated the
base as a grunt.
And there you have it!
[MARINES]
We're sorry, Inspector Usopp!
This is insanity!
If he really is a
special inspector,
then that means he has higher
rank and more authority
than we do!
This man cannot be
higher ranking than me!
This man? This man?
What exactly are you
trying to say, Drake?
Have you forgotten that
you are only lieutenant?
You know, I've got
friends in high places.
I could have you court-martialed
for insulting a
superior officer.
How about it? Do you want
to have your next meal
in some wretched Marine
prison cell? Heh, heh.
--[DRAKE gasps]
--[USOPP chuckling]
[JONATHAN] Sorry for the
misunderstanding, Inspector.
I was just about to send
someone down to greet you.
Please, accept my apologies.
[USOPP] Of course, Commander,
everyone makes mistakes!
Commander! Special
Inspector Major Shepherd
from Marine Headquarters
has just arrived
and is requesting a meeting!
[USOPP screams]
The real one showed up?!
I knew it!
How dare you!
--[USOPP] I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
--You ass!
[USOPP]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm really very sorry.
[DRAKE] Are you apologizing?
I can't hear you!
Commander, pleased to
make your acquaintance.
Yeah, I bet you're sorry!
[USOPP]
Robin?
...apologizing in prison!
[USOPP] Looks like Robin
got a disguise, too!
Yeah, you're not so cocky now,
are you? You little twerp!
[USOPP]
Oh, hey there, fellow inspector!
Fancy meeting you here!
You know me, right?
I'm from your division!
It's me, Inspector Usopp,
remember?
Did you forget me because
you've been traveling so much?
Major Shepherd,
do you know this man?
No, sir, I do not.
[USOPP screams]
I knew it!
Don't act like you
don't know me! [screams]
[DRAKE]
Lock him up, men!
I will begin by investigating
the structural qualities
of this base.
Of course. Be my guest, Major.
If you need anything, just ask.
Thank you very much.
[USOPP]
Stupid Robin!
Does she suddenly hate
me now or something?
She just flat out
stabbed me in the back!
That's messed up, right, Zoro?
She ratted me out!
If she had only gone
along with what I said,
we probably would have had
the Merry back by now!
You should be more
grateful to Robin.
[USOPP]
Grateful? Why?
Why should I be grateful to her?
'Cause it means
you're with me now.
[gasps] I see.
Robin knew that I would really
be safer here with you.
She was thinking of my
well being all along.
But still.
This place doesn't
seem that safe.
[ROBIN] Perhaps I shouldn't have
started researching this base.
We may have had a chance
for a clean escape earlier.
Looks like there's only
one way out of this place.
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
Where are you, Zoro?
Come out, come out...
Shut up, will ya?
You're gonna get us caught!
This way!
[MARINE R]
So far we've captured Zoro,
and another man with
a really long nose!
[MARINE R] Straw hat Luffy
and the rest of his crew
have got to be close.
Find them!
[MARINES]
Sir!
Well, what do we
do now, Captain?
[JONATHAN] Straw Hat Luffy
and a very skilled cook.
A warrior and a man
with a long nose.
A doctor and a nurse
we've yet to see.
[JONATHAN] And one more, who
calls herself Major Shepherd.
[JONATHAN]
That makes seven crewmembers.
It's all starting to make sense.
[JONATHAN]
We've already captured the ship
as well as two
members of the crew.
The remaining Straw Hats
are within our reach.
So what is your next move,
Monkey D. Luffy?
I suppose I'll have to sit
back and see for myself.
[JONATHAN chuckling]
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[USOPP] Luffy! We're
right here, come and get us!
I mean wait! I changed my mind!
Zoro, what should I say?
[ZORO]
How should I know?
Tell them to come,
or not, or whatever.
[USOPP]
Well that's just not--
[LUFFY]
Don't worry, guys.
I'll be there in a j--
in a j-jiffy.
[USOPP]
What the? I see what those
Sea Prism Stones are doing!
[SANJI]
Oh, no! It's a trap!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy and Sanji's
Daring Rescue Mission!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!