[ITOMIMIZU] The Straw Hat
Dangers have managed
to pull off a
come-from-behind victory!
The final round of
the Davy Back Fight
comes to a dramatic end!
It's over, my
Slow-Slow Beam failed me...
We won! We won!
We won! We won! We won!
I'm begging you please
pick me this time!
Looks like it all worked out.
Seems so.
[ITOMIMIZU] Now it's time to
choose your new crewmember!
Who do you want,
Straw Hat Luffy?!
C'mon Chopper, get over here!
[sobbing hysterically]
[LUFFY chuckles]
I'll miss you, Choppy!
I was so scared!
I'm so happy you won!
Are you kidding?
Buncha suckers like that
could never beat my crew!
[ITOMIMIZU] We've seen blood,
sweat, and plenty of tears today
but the Davy Back Fight
has finally drawn to a close!
With the Straw Hats
reclaiming their doctor,
Tony Tony Chopper, I'd say
this match ends in a draaaaaw!
[FOXY]
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Huh?
Hmm?
Any captain worth his
weight in seaweed knows
that there are no "draws"
in the pirate world!
It's plunder or be plundered!
You won't let it end
like this, will you?
Wait is he saying
what I think he is?!
C'mon how 'bout
another three-coin game
to decide which one
of us is really the best.
Yeah, like we'd agree to that.
After all the cheating,
you'd have to be an idiot
to go for another round.
[gunshot bang]
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no, no, no.
Oh no, no, no, no, no!
You're on, Split Head! Hahaha!
What if we lose Chopper
again--or worse yet--
what if you lose me and
I get stuck with those weirdos
while you and all of our friends
get lost at sea and die?!
Okay, this is the last time.
I won't do it again, I promise.
You're kidding.
I don't know if I have
any tears left to cry.
He already agreed, so it's
not like we can back out now.
I doubt he would
go to the trouble
if he didn't have
something in mind.
Eh, I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Well, unless he's
thinking he can nab us
a shipwright from Foxy's Crew.
[ITOMIMIZU] It's time for
the second three-coin game!
The events this time are a
team-wide dodgeball showdown;
a brutal new twist on
a childhood favorite;
and a one-on-one
boxing beat down!
Like the previous game,
each crewmember
can only participate twice!
In other words,
last minute lineup changes
will not be allowed!
No two ways about it,
this time they're
gonna pick me for sure.
Yeah right, I know they've
got their eyes on me.
I'm doomed to spend the rest
of my life as their poster girl.
[FOXY PIRATE A and B]
Keep telling yourself that,
but we don't want
either of you on our crew.
You're too scary
and he's too weak.
With our second Davy Back Fight
of the day about to start,
I'm back in the announcer's
seat to explain the rules
of our first match!
The name of the game
is "Hit and Dead Ball!"
The balls in question
are the two you
see on the field right now.
If the opposing team hits
you with one of those babies,
you're out of the game!
The teams are divided into
on-court and off-court members.
They're free to choose
which ones go where
in whatever number
but once you run out
of on-court members,
you lose the match.
Keep in mind that although
the off-court members
can throw the ball around
just like anyone else,
they are not allowed
to enter the court
under any circumstance!
They make it
sound all fancy,
but it just seems like
regular old dodgeball to me.
[ITOMIMIZU] There are some
other miscellaneous details,
so be sure to read
the rulebook carefully!
That's the rulebook?
You wouldn't expect
it to be so thick.
[ITOMIMIZU] Hit and Dead
Ball is one of the greatest
and most time-honored
Davy Back Fight games!
Because it has been played
so many times over the years,
more and more
rules have been added
to balance and
perfect its form!
Only by strict
adherence to those rules
can the game truly be enjoyed!
What's the point in preaching
to us about the rules
if you're gonna end up
breaking them all, anyway?
Did you just give
us the rulebook
so we'll know how
bad you're cheating?
No, no, no!
Take a look at the
first page, mademoiselle!
"Referee Regulations. He who
makes a judgment contrary
to the rules written here
shall be beheaded on the spot."
Beheaded?! Scary!
And there you have it.
On that topic, this
game will be officiated
by a team of five
referees, headed by a vet
with fifty years of
experience, Rokuroshi!
With any luck,
we might actually get a
fair fight this time around.
[ITOMIMIZU] Team Foxy has a
veritable armada of players!
Truly a stupendous
spectacle to see!
Sadly, the Straw Hats
pale in comparison
with their diminutive showing.
Sporting a measly
seven members,
I must wonder if
they're even trying!
Okay, we get it!
[ITOMIMIZU] Let's get
this show on the road!
We'll start the match off
with the double opening tip!
Each team bring two players
to the center of the field.
Hey, do you mind if I do this?
Hm? Yeah, be my guest.
Go jump your
heart out, little guy.
All right!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Chopper has transformed!
It looks like he's not
just fluff after all!
He could turn out to
be a powerful player
for the Straw Hats!
Oh no! What's that?!
Now he's not cute at all!
Ready, set and go!
Nice catch! Now give 'em
a good spike to the face!
Aim straight for
Split-Head! C'mon Chopper!
Let's go!
Right!
[ITOMIMIZU] Oh no!
Our boss is in trouble!
What, he's already
out of the game?!
Yeah! You really showed
their boss who's boss!
Safe! Safe!
What do you mean "safe"?!
That was a clean hit,
you old fart!
It's a violation of Article 23!
Blows to the
face do not count!
You're kidding!
Now what?
Wow, Boss, that
looked like it hurt!
Puh-puh-puh!
Don't laugh, Hamburg,
you're gonna make Boss cry.
Get them while
they're distracted!
Give 'em a good
one for me, Sanji!
Yeah! I'll show them the
power of our sweet love!
Here they come!
You might wanna
clear out of here!
Hey take it easy,
we're still warming up here!
Eighteen members
of Team Foxy
are hereby eliminated for
getting knocked out of bounds!
Way to go!
[ITOMIMIZU] What a show
from the Straw Hats!
The chef and the swordsman
both blew nine players
right off the field!
Damn, I thought
I'd get more than you.
Yeah! Knock 'em dead, Sanji!
Knock em' dead, Zoro!
Pardon me.
Wow, do you think we can
take out nine people, too?
Nine? I'll do ten!
Gum-Gum Slingshot!
Out of bounds!
Ten members from
Team Foxy are eliminated!
Oh, yeah! That's a new record!
[ITOMIMIZU] Yet another strong
showing from the Straw Hats!
They're thinning
out the competition,
but Team Foxy
finally has a ball!
Let's see how many
I can knock out!
Go on Chopper! Even the
score! 9, 10, 11, or more!
Sure you got it!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Oh!
A last minute catch from
Hamburg saves the day!
Now Team Foxy has both
balls in their possession!
Could it finally be
time for a comeback?
Puh-puh-puh!
Nice work as always Hamburg.
Now why don't you pass
those balls to Big Pan?
Roger, Boss!
Right! This is it!
Take 'em all out in one shot!
Not me! Please not me!
Usopp! No!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What happened?! I can't see!
Out of bounds!
Mister Long Nose and 22 members
of Team Foxy are
hereby eliminated!
That looked bad.
Are you okay?!
Yeah It takes more
than that to kill me.
Hey, and look, I got the ball!
[ITOMIMIZU] Big Pan's
devastating dodge ball smash
eliminated the Straw Hat's
long-nosed sniper,
but caused a crushing
amount of collateral damage
to his own team!
Now Foxy and Hamburg are
the only ones left on the field!
At this rate,
the Foxy Pirates may be
undone by their own strength!
The match is now two to four!
What's next?
Who will reign supreme?
Hey, Boss. What now?
What do you mean "what now?"
I can't use my Slow-Slow Beam
as long as that
archeologist chick is here.
So, there's only
one choice left.
You mean "you-know-what"?
Puh-puh-puh!
"You-know-what" indeed!
Feh-feh-feh!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What a turn of events!
Now Hamburg is out
of the game, too!
Hahaha! Good one, Robin.
Hamburg is safe!
You sure?
Article 54 states that
while the face doesn't count,
the top of the head
is still fair game.
If I were you, I'd start
using my head fast,
before somebody chops it off!
The girl is right.
Hamburg is out!
I'm sorry, Sir.
The Straw Hat's
archaeologist has memorized
the massive rulebook
in only moments
by flexing the mighty
muscles of her mind!
You read all that?! Awesome!
Thanks for the compliment,
but I'm only about
halfway through.
Well either way,
they've only got one left,
so let's finish 'em off quick!
You got it!
Hey, Sanji? Tee-hee!
Yes, ladies?
Please don't hit our boss...
Tee-hee!
Just give that
ball to us, okay?
Of course!
You're so sweet!
Now would you mind getting
knocked out of the game?
As a favor? For me?
Aaah!!
Why, it would be
my pleasure, Ma'am.
You can hit me
wherever you like!
If you don't get up,
I'll knock you out!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Oh!
Love hunter Sanji has
been blissfully bludgeoned
and endearingly
eliminated from the game!
Now he'll be joining his
long-nosed companion
on the sidelines!
Bye-bye!
You make me sick.
We should've seen that coming.
On the upside, their
boss is the only one left.
We can't celebrate yet.
You never know what might
happen until the very end.
Yes, good point.
Huh? No way.
What the?!
[ITOMIMIZU]
There it is!
Hit and Dead Ball's
top secret weapon
finally makes an appearance!
Say hello to the
Mr. Accu-Cannon!
Feh-feh-feh!
Hey ref, are you
really gonna allow this?
That thing's obviously
against the rules!
So that's Mr. Accu-Cannon?
Wait, why are you
acting like you know
all about this doohickey?
Did I miss something?
I ran across an article
about it in the rulebook,
but I hadn't actually
seen the device until now.
Rule number three
hundred twenty-two.
The only weapon allowed
is Mr. Accu-Cannon.
Why would you make a rule
just for that dumb thing?
I dunno. Seems
pretty awesome to me!
What's the point?
Listen, I don't care
how big your Mr. Cannon
whatever is, you're
still gonna lose!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Feh-feh-feh...
Hey Porche, you ready
to finish them off?
I thought you'd never ask,
Boss! Better not blink!
Flower Hypnosis go!
Not again!
Hurry up and close your eyes!
[LUFFY]
Oh.
Can you play without
dirty tricks for once?
Now's your chance! Fire!
Oh, I will! Like
shooting fish in a barrel!
[thinking] I don't
have to see I can feel.
Even without my swords,
I'm still a swordsman.
[ITOMIMIZU]
What power!
The swordless swordsman
not only sliced the ball
in half with his bare hands,
he did it with his eyes closed!
Oh no.
Zoro of Team Straw Hat is out!
Why?! What'd I do?!
Huh?
[RUKOROSHI]
Rule number 645!
Even with hands,
no slicing the ball!
Rules also state that
Foxy gets a new ball!
What?!
Oh well, better luck next time!
Feh-feh-feh!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What a shame!
It was an impressive
move from Zoro,
but the rules are the rules!
You okay?
I don't think he's
taking this too well.
Hey--
Whatever you're about to say,
I don't want to hear it,
especially after that
stunt you just pulled.
Wow! The match
is now two to one!
And Mr. Accu-Cannon
is ready to go!
Feh-feh-feh!
Time to pick up
where I left off!
Yeah? Then let's
see what you got!
Bring it on!
Ultra-fast Level 5, go!
Let's see you dodge
this, you brats! Ha!
No! Choppy!
[ITOMIMIZU] The doctor makes a
noble sacrifice for his captain!
But is this the end for him?
Hey! They said hits to the
face don't count, right?
Was that his face?
Huh... Now that
you mention it,
I'm not sure where
that is, exactly.
With all that fluff,
it's sort of hard to tell.
He's so brave!
Hey ref, can't you see a
pirate's honor is at stake here?
I'm telling you,
that was his face!
That's right!
Any real man knows
to show some respect when a
pirate takes one for the team!
Hit in the face! Hit in
the face! Hit in the face!
What the?
Hit in the face! Hit in
the face! Hit in the face!
A pirate's honor is at stake?
Then the choice
is obvious, isn't it?
The ball hit him in the face
and blows to the
face do not count!
Yeah! You're the best!
However...
However?
Even if blows to
the face don't count,
you're out of bounds,
so you're still eliminated!
[ITOMIMIZU] Say it ain't so!
This is a real tragedy!
Even after the
ref acknowledged
his captain-saving-face-block,
he's still out!
The brave little doctor
will surely be missed by all!
Even so, he will be remembered
as a true man of the sea!
Choppy!
[LUFFY]
Hey, you still hanging in there?
Yeah, but it doesn't matter.
I'm out of the
game, either way.
Don't worry.
Leave the rest to me.
Oh and thanks,
Chopper. Nice save.
Eh-heh. What makes you
think I want to hear that?
That doesn't make me
happy at all, you big jerk!
Feh-feh-feh!
Not too bad, Choppy!
I can't wait till I win
and you're back on my crew!
Gotta go through
me first, Split Head!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Heh heh heh...
Both teams are backed
against the wall as
our courageous captains face off
in a climactic confrontation!
Feh-feh-feh!
I'll warn you,
this is gonna hurt.
I think I'd give up
now if I were you!
Ha! Why would I give up
when you're the one
who's gonna lose?!
I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Why don't you take
a good look around
before you start
spouting nonsense?
[ITOMIMIZU] Here it comes!
The Omni-Directional Shift!
[PORCHE]
Say your prayers, rubber boy!
[USOPP]
What're they doing now?!
Hey! What's up
with all those balls,
old man that's gotta
be against the rules!
The rulebook clearly
states that players can use
as many fake
balls as they like.
You talk big, but you're
just as bad as the last ref!
Damn unless we can
get a ref of our own,
we're never gonna
see the end of this.
Don't pay any attention
to those guys, Luffy,
you and Foxy are the only
ones with a real ball!
Just keep your eye on him!
Oh! How did she know?!
What's wrong with this guy?
I'm starting to think
his brain is split, too.
[FOXY thinking]
If they call me "Split-Brain,"
I swear I'm gonna cry.
Sorry, pal. It looks
like I'm gonna have to
break your
Mr. Whatchamacallit thing!
Ahh!
Here goes!
Hello!
Take this!
[PORCHE]
Oh my! Where'd this come from?
Better watch where
you stretch that arm!
C'mon boys, let's shuffle!
Shuffle time, Shuffle time,
Shuffle time, Shuffle time.
This is bad. If he can't
tell which ones are real
and which ones are fake,
he won't be able to dodge!
Feh-feh-feh!
All right Mr. Smart guy,
do you know which
balls are real now?
Better figure it out
fast before they hit you!
Shut up! I'll just
catch all the balls,
and then it won't matter!
Don't you get
snarky with me, boy!
Just sit back and accept
your defeat with grace!
Now, time to
let those balls fly!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
Hmph! Nice try
but you're finished.
Hey, look out behind you!
Luffy! Don't dodge.
Let it hit your face!
Right, easy for you to say!
He did it!
All right!
Straw Hat Luffy, you're out!
Why?! I thought it didn't count
if you got hit in the face!
Rule 999! Ingesting
any part of the ball
results in instant
disqualification!
Check the rulebook yourself
if you don't believe me.
Unfortunately, he's correct.
It's on the very last page.
What, why does
that rule even exist?!
[ITOMIMIZU]
It's over!
Straw Hat Luffy
has eaten his way
to defeat as Team Foxy claims
victory in the first round!
[NAMI]
Not again!
♪ ending song ♪
[USOPP] I remember playing
this game when I was a kid!
[FOXY] A kid wouldn't
last 5 minutes here
and neither would
a weakling like you!
[USOPP]
Go get 'em, Zoro!
[ZORO] You're a part
of this crew, too!
[USOPP] Yeah, but
all those scary guys
are playing this time.
Besides, I'm a
weakling, remember?
Hey, I'm just kidding!
Put that sword away! Help! Help!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece :
"Showdown on the Cliff!
Red Light, Green Light!"
[USOPP] Huh?
Did Zoro get lost again?