[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[seagulls squawking]
What a day!
It's gorgeous!
As long as we can
stay on this heading,
we should reach the Marine
Base in no time at all.
[LUFFY] Wow, Coby!
You're great out here.
You mean we're actually gonna
reach the place we
originally set out for?
[COBY]
Of course. It's nothing.
I'm just using the skills that
every sailor should have.
[LUFFY laughs]
You know, there's really
nothing to be so giggly about.
Because...
...at the Marine Base...
...they're holding the
great pirate hunter...
Roronoa Zoro.
[COBY] This is the man
who's diced up his bounties
like a an animal bent on
carnage, a blood thirsty beast.
He's been called nothing less
than a living, breathing
demon in human form.
[LUFFY]
"Enter the Great Swordsman!
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro!"
We're here!
The Marine Base city!
Luffy, seriously,
you're out of your mind
if you think the right thing to
do is get this guy to join you.
Well, I haven't
made up my mind yet.
I gotta see if he's a good guy.
He's imprisoned because
he's obviously not!
[LUFFY] Hey, is that guy
Zoro around here somewhere?
[WOMAN A gasps]
[CROWD screams]
[CROWD whimpering]
Maybe we shouldn't mention
the name Zoro here, okay?
Let's head to the base
and check it out.
You wanna be a Marine, right?
Well, of course I do, Luffy,
but I really don't think
I'm ready just yet.
From what I've heard, the
man in charge of this base
is named Captain Morgan.
[CROWD screams]
[CROWD whimpering]
[LUFFY laughing]
This town is such a weird place.
[COBY]
That was odd.
I mean, I understand if
they're scared of Zoro,
but why did they flip
when I mentioned the
Marine Captain's name?
I don't know... I've got
a bad feeling about this.
Maybe they were all just jumpin'
around for the fun of it.
And how would that
make any sense?
[LUFFY]
This looks like the place.
I made it...
[cries]
This is where you
and I part ways, Luffy.
We didn't have long
together but‐‐
[grunts]
[LUFFY]
Where's the foothold?
[COBY]
Get down from there!
What're you doing?!
They'll see you!
Now where's this demon?
[COBY] They wouldn't
keep him out in the open.
He's probably tucked in a
prison cell below ground.
[LUFFY]
There he is!
Uh. I'm gonna get closer!
Coby, look!
[COBY sighs]
I'm telling you he's not‐‐ Uh!
[COBY]
That hood on his head...
...and a haramaki...
It's Roronoa Zoro!
If we untie those ropes,
he can just walk away.
Oh, don't be such
an idiot, Luffy!
There's no telling what
a bandit like him will do
if you let him go!
He might just kill us both!
Don't worry, I'm strong.
I can protect us.
[COBY]
He's lost his mind!
[ZORO]
Hey, you two!
[COBY screams]
You're an eyesore.
Get lost.
[COBY screams]
[COBY] Luffy, trust me,
there's no chance you'll survive
with someone like
him on your crew.
[RIKA]
Shh.
[RIKA grunts]
[COBY gasps]
[COBY yelps]
Luffy, we gotta stop her!
She'll be killed! Either by the
Marines or the demon himself!
[ZORO]
Whaddya want?
I thought you might
be getting hungry now,
so I made you a
couple of rice balls.
You got a death wish, kid?
Just scram.
[RIKA]
But you haven't eaten anything
the whole time
you've been tied up.
Here!
I've never really
made them before...
...but I did my best,
so I think they're fine.
[ZORO gasps]
Listen, kid, I'm not hungry!
Now stop irritating me,
and get outta here!
[RIKA]
But‐‐
Do not make me kick
your ass, little girl!
[HELMEPPO]
Now, now.
No one likes a bully.
[ZORO growls]
[HELMEPPO chuckles]
Roronoa Zoro,
you seem to be
handling this well.
Don't you agree?
Hey, look. Now there's
another weird guy.
That's great!
He must be with the Marines.
Now we know the
girl will be safe.
Looky, some tasty rice balls.
[RIKA]
That's not for you!
[HELMEPPO gasps, screams]
Too sweet!
They're packed with sugar!
You're supposed to use
salt, you idiot, salt!
But I...
I thought they'd
taste better sweet.
‐‐[HELMEPPO] Gimme that!
‐‐[RIKA yelps]
[HELMEPPO grunts]
[RIKA]
No! Stop!
‐‐[RIKA] I worked so hard!
‐‐That's just awful.
[HELMEPPO grunts, sighs]
[RIKA cries]
But I...
...worked so hard
to make those...
Too bad...
You must've not read
the notice that was posted.
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed.
Signed, Marine Captain Morgan.
[RIKA gasps]
[laughs]
It seems even little
brats fear my daddy.
His daddy?
So that guy's father
is Captain Morgan?
You!
Toss this kid out right now.
[MARINE A gasps]
I said, throw her
over the wall, soldier!
Now if you won't
follow my orders,
I'll tell my father.
Yes, sir! I‐I'll do it!
[RIKA whimpers, gasps]
[RIKA]
No!
Sorry about this.
Try curling up into a ball.
[RIKA gasps]
‐‐[RIKA screams]
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
[RIKA screaming]
[LUFFY grunts]
Thanks, mister!
[COBY]
Luffy! Are you two okay?!
What about you, little girl?
Are you all right?
I can't believe how
wretched a person he is.
Now where are you
hurt? Anywhere?
Damn you.
[HELMEPPO laughing]
[HELMEPPO snorts, laughs]
You're just dead set on
staying alive, aren't you?
That's right.
And I'm gonna make it through
the month without any problems.
Right... Good luck with that.
[HELMEPPO laughing]
Only ten days left.
[HELMEPPO] Oh, you still
assume you'll make it
to the end of those ten days.
[HELMEPPO laughing]
[COBY]
How can that man be so cruel?
Luffy?
Uh! What the‐‐?
Where did he go?!
[ZORO gasps]
[LUFFY]
So, I hear you're a bad guy.
[ZORO]
Are you still here?
[LUFFY]
You're stuck out here
for all the world
to see and nothing.
Are you really all that strong?
[ZORO]
Mind your own business!
[LUFFY sighs]
If I were you, I'd probably
starve to death in three days.
[ZORO] I've got more spirit
than you could ever have,
which is how I'm gonna
survive this ordeal.
This I swear.
Hah, what a weirdo!
Wait, hold on.
Could you... pick
that up for me?
You're gonna eat this?
'Cause it's mostly
a ball of mud.
Shut up and give it to me, now!
[LUFFY]
Uh...
[ZORO coughing]
Should've listened to me.
[ZORO]
It was good.
Thanks for the food.
[RIKA]
Really?
That's right!
He ate every last
grain of rice there was.
That's great!
I wonder if Zoro
was really as evil
as everyone
thinks that he is.
He's not!
He's good... because...
He got himself punished...
...for us.
You're, uh... You're
making no sense.
Sorry...
It's that dumb Helmeppo.
He's the son of Captain Morgan.
[HELMEPPO]
Step aside! Step aside!
Make way for my
beautiful pet doggy!
Anyone who doesn't move,
I'll have executed!
[HELMEPPO laughing]
‐‐[WOLF roars]
‐‐[CROWD screams]
[RIKA screams]
[MAN screams]
Stop it, you mean ol' thing!
You, little girl!
Is there some kind of problem
with how my beloved
dog is behaving?
Rika, put it down!
You don't want to
get us in trouble.
[HELMEPPO snickering]
‐‐[WOLF roars]
‐‐[RIKA screams]
[HELMEPPO screams, gasps]
[CROWD chattering]
Who the hell are you?!
Wait! You're him... It's you!
You're the Pirate Hunter Zoro!
[ZORO]
And if I am?
What is a pirate hunter doing
defying the Marines, huh?!
[ZORO] Can it, and let me
finish my meal in peace.
[screams]
[HELMEPPO grunts]
[HELMEPPO groans]
[screams]
[ZORO] You're getting
on my nerves, pal.
You and that precious
mutt of yours.
[whimpering]
[chuckles]
You do realize...
...if my dad finds
out about this...
...he'll surely execute
the girl and her mother.
Ha, ha. So what do you say
to a little deal between men?
In place of the kid and her mom,
we string you up instead...
...for, uh, say one month!
You survive that one month,
and I'll be so nice
as to let you live, too.
Whaddya say?
Sound fair?
Then one month it is.
[RIKA] It's been three
weeks since that day.
Helmeppo keeps punching and
kicking him while he's tied up.
He's being so unfair!
I don't...
I don't know how to help him!
‐‐[RIKA cries]
‐‐I see why you're upset.
[glass shattering]
I'm hungry.
Bring us whatever you got and
keep the check for yourself.
[laughs]
And bring me a bottle
of your finest moonshine
or whatever crap you serve.
And put some speed to it,
lady; I don't have all day.
Oh... That's more like it.
I'm trying to think of
something interesting to do
seeing as how I'm bored
out of my skull here.
I suppose I can execute Zoro.
[HELMEPPO cackling
[HELMEPPO groans]
You... You just hit me!
[COBY]
Luffy, no!
You can't hit him!
This guy is scum!
You actually hit me!
I am Captain Morgan's
son, you know!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, like I care!
You'll care after he
executes you for this!
Why don't you just
be a man and fight?
Luffy, just ease off some.
Why are you trying to get
on the Marines' bad side?
[LUFFY]
I've made up my mind.
[COBY gasps]
Today...
Zoro joins my crew.
[MORGAN]
I am...
...great!
[MARINE B]
Yes, sir!
You are right,
Captain Morgan, sir!
[MORGAN] And yet, the taxes
we collect don't even compare
to my sheer degree of greatness.
Yes, right, sir.
I guess that the
citizens' wallets
just aren't very deep
these days, sir.
[MORGAN]
The issue at hand here
is their level of
respect for me.
Wouldn't you agree?
[HELMEPPO sobbing]
‐‐Daddy!
‐‐[MORGAN] Hm?
There's someone outside that
I want you to slaughter,
and I want it done now!
‐‐[wood clattering]
‐‐[ZORO groans]
[ZORO grunting]
[KUINA]
Hah!
[ZORO]
Ah!
You're weak, Zoro...
Nothing ever changes.
[ZORO]
I made a promise to her...
And I can't afford to
die in a place like this.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[ZORO]
Huh?
You again...
Don't you have things to do?
I'll untie you, but only if
you promise to join my crew.
Your what?
I run a pirate crew, and I'm
looking for people to join up.
No way!
I'd never stoop to
joining up with a criminal.
Screw that business.
And what's wrong
with being a pirate?
They're despicable!
Like I'd ever wanna
join up with one.
Oh, come on! Gimme a break.
Everyone already knows you
as some viscious bounty hunter
always out for blood.
People can say whatever
they want about me,
but I've never done a single
thing in my life that I regret.
I will make it through
this challenge.
And after that, I'll
accomplish what I want.
Yeah... That's great.
But I've already decided that
you're going to be on my crew.
What?! You can't do that!
I hear you're one of
the best swordsmen around.
[ZORO]
Well, I am!
But that idiot Captain's
son took mine away.
Guess I'll just have to
go get it back for you.
[ZORO]
What?
So if you want your sword,
you're just gonna
have to join my crew.
Now you're really
pissing me off!
[LUFFY laughing]
Wait... he's actually
gonna bust in there alone?
Hey, genius!
The base is in the
other direction!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Gum Gum Rocket!
What...?
What the hell is this guy?
[MARINES]
Heave ho!
[MORGAN]
That's it! Stop right there.
Now stand it up
in one final pull!
Well, dad?
Are you gonna get revenge
on this guy or what?!
I mean he just outright
struck me in public!
You never hit me before!
Why should he be able to?
[MORGAN]
Do you have any remote idea
as to why I've never hit you?
Well?
Uh... Is it because
you think I'm great?
[MORGAN]
No...
It's because‐‐
[HELMEPPO screams]
[HELMEPPO groans]
[MORGAN]
You're a stupid fool...
...who isn't even worth hitting.
I don't want you to
get the wrong idea.
The only great one around here
is the man you call your father!
[HELMEPPO groans]
[MORGAN]
Which reminds me.
I heard a rat snuck into
the crucifixion yard.
[HELMEPPO gasps]
Yes. That's right, the little
girl, but I had her dealt with.
I hope that means killed.
No, I...I didn't kill her.
She's just a kid...
[MORGAN]
You there!
Go into town, find this
girl, and kill her!
But... sir!
You can't be serious...
She's just a little girl, sir.
[MORGAN] I don't care
if she's a child or not.
Anyone who disobeys
my orders is a traitor!
[LIEUTENANT]
No, sir...
I can't do it.
[MORGAN growls]
[MORGAN grunts]
[HELMEPPO screams]
[MARINES]
Lieutenant!
You... You killed him!
My strength was what I used
to rise to the rank of captain.
Listen!
In this world,
titles are what matter!
That means by being the
captain of this base
and the highest ranking officer,
I am the most superior person
as far as the eye can see!
This means...
that I do everything right!
Am I correct, men?!
[MARINES]
Sir! You are correct, sir!
Let's put killing the
girl on hold for now.
Observe,
the greatest symbol of
my unending authority.
It took years to
complete, but here it is.
‐‐Now stand it up!
‐‐[MARINES] Heave ho!
[MORGAN]
Display my greatness at
the top of this
base for all to see!
That's weird...
There's nobody here.
I gotta find that
crazy idiot son
and get Zoro's sword
back for him. Huh?
‐‐[MARINES] Heave ho!
‐‐[MORGAN] Pull men!
‐‐Heave ho!
‐‐Harder!
[MARINES]
Heave ho!
[MORGAN]
You there!
[MARINE E whimpers]
You bumped it.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Sounds like something's
goin' on up there.
I'm sorry, sir!
I was reckless!
I didn't mean it!
[MORGAN] I consider the
slightest scratch on this...
...nothing less...
...than a traitorous activity
that's punishable by death!
Guess I should check it out.
Gum Gum...
...Rocket!
‐‐[MARINE E screams]
‐‐[MORGAN yells]
[LUFFY]
Huh‐hoo!
Wah... I jumped too far!
[MORGAN]
Huh?
What is that thing?!
It flew up from the ground!
‐‐[LUFFY] Got it!
‐‐[MARINES gasping]
[MARINES screaming]
[MARINES grunting]
[MORGAN gasps]
[HELMEPPO, MARINES scream]
[LUFFY]
Uh...
Sorry 'bout that.
Seize him and hold him,
so I can kill him myself!
[MARINES]
Sir! Right away!
That's him! That's the guy!
He's the one
‐‐who punched me, daddy!
‐‐[LUFFY] Hey, it's you!
[screaming]
I've been looking for
you all over the place.
You have something that
I really need to get back.
‐‐[HELMEPPO] Let me go!
‐‐[MARINES] Helmeppo!
[HELMEPPO]
Someone help me!
[MORGAN]
Do not let that man escape!
[MARINE J]
Captain!
There's someone in
the crucifixion yard!
What?
I'm surrounded... by traitors.
[GIRL grunts]
[MARINE K]
After him!
Hurry!
[MARINE L]
Sir, yes, sir!
Someone's rocking the boat.
[HELMEPPO screaming]
Okay, so tell me where
Zoro's sword is.
[HELMEPPO]
I'll tell you! I promise!
Just please stop dragging
me across the carpet.
Fine, which way?
In my room. We just passed it,
behind you on the left.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Now we gotta go
all the way back.
Don't move!
Except for letting Helmeppo go!
No way.
But you can try
shooting me if you want.
[HELMEPPO]
No! Please don't shoot!
Don't‐‐ Get the
hell outta the way!
[COBY] You have to
get out of here, Zoro.
That maniac's going to kill you
for what you're doin' right now!
[COBY]
I can't stand to watch
the Marines behave
like this anymore.
A true Marine
should be honorable.
Look, kid, I can't leave!
I got ten days left.
And, then they're‐‐
Well, not quite. They're
gonna execute you tomorrow.
They're what?
[COBY] Helmeppo never intended
to honor your agreement.
He planned on killing
you from the start.
Which made Luffy really angry,
so he just knocked him out.
He did?
Now that the Marines are mad,
they're dead set
on catching Luffy.
Don't worry, I'm not gonna ask
you to become a pirate, though.
But I hope you'll help him.
You have a lotta
strength you can offer.
[COBY]
Luffy's the only person here
who can actually save
you from execution.
And of course...
You're the only one
here who can save him
from a very similar fate.
[MORGAN]
End of the line!
[MORGAN] For the crime
of treason against me,
I sentence you both
to die where you stand.
[COBY yelps]
This looks like yours.
[LUFFY]
Bingo!
Hold on. There are three here.
Hey, weirdo, which one
of these is Zoro's?
‐‐[HELMEPPO whimpering]
‐‐[LUFFY] Guess he passed out.
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Coby!
[COBY whimpering]
You've been pulling some
interesting moves around here.
What is this? Some kind
of poorly executed coup
you two planned
with the straw hat?
[ZORO] I've always fought
alone like a real man does.
Not like a coward...
...who hides behind his
wall of expendable cronies.
[MORGAN]
Roronoa Zoro.
Don't you dare underestimate me.
You may be a strong fighter,
but under my authority,
you're just the rat we
throw out with the trash.
Take aim!
[ZORO]
No...
I can't afford to die here!
You're weak, Zoro...
Nothing ever changes.
[ZORO grunting]
[LUFFY]
Gum Gum...
...Rocket!
Fire!
[LUFFY grunts]
‐‐[ZORO] What?!
‐‐Luffy, no!
Straw Hat!
[MARINE gasp]
[LUFFY laughs]
See ya!
[LUFFY laughing]
That won't work on me!
Told ya I was strong!
What the‐‐?!
Who the hell are you?
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
And I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[ZORO] I'm gonna be the
world's greatest swordsman.
[LUFFY] Why not be the world's
greatest swordsman pirate?
[ZORO]
What would you know about it?
[GIRL] The soldiers have
started to go crazy!
[LUFFY] Maybe because we're
enemies of the Marines now?
Let me untie your ropes.
[GIRL]
We have to hurry!
There's gotta be a
map of the Grand Line
somewhere in this base.
[LUFFY] Oh, uh.
The ropes are tighter now.
[ZORO]
What?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Morgan versus Luffy! Who's
the Mysterious Pretty Girl?"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!