[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy escaped the
War of the Best with his life,
but failed to save his
brother from execution.
In the days after,
only thoughts of his crew
could save him from despair.
It was then that
Dark King Rayleigh
made an unexpected suggestion.
Let me offer you
some friendly advice.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[gasps]
[RAYLEIGH]
Hmm.
It's all right.
Luffy.
[JIMBEI]
This is all so unexpected.
Please, Rayleigh,
it's far too soon for this.
Luffy?
[RAYLEIGH]
Just my opinion, of course,
but I do think it's
what you and your crew need.
Luffy's body and mind alike
have suffered from
this terrible ordeal.
Although there is
truth in your words,
if he cannot heal,
then all is meaningless.
But my crew won't know.
That's true,
they'll likely return to
Sabaody as you agreed before.
The events at Marineford were
publicized all over the world.
Though you're still reported
as "missing," I'm sure.
[LUFFY]
Then I have to go see them.
[HANCOCK gasps]
[LUFFY]
They're waiting for me.
A promise is a promise, right?
So, I need to go to Sabaody.
Well, then I may have
another suggestion for you.
Huh?
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, on the
floating island of Weatheria,
the world's foremost
meteorologists
are busy coping with
a most unruly guest.
[HAREDAS, OLD MAN B panting]
Is it truly, truly,
truly true? [pants]
That young lady... [pants]
...tried to escape?
We're a bit high up for that!
I shall explain. Hmm...
[NAMI panting]
[gasps]
Why, where are you
off to, young lady?
[yells]
Carry on.
[OLD MAN B]
She dashed through
the Weather Field,
lickity-split.
Quite irresponsible, I must say!
Then, she descended into the
Balloon Terminal, unsupervised!
[NAMI]
Sorry, coming through!
Don't try to stop me!
[BOTH yell]
[NAMI grunts]
[OLD MAN B] Then, with
a heavy backpack at her side,
she hijacked a balloon
and took off!
However...
[gasping]
[NAMI] What the heck's going on?
This thing's out of control!
[NAMI screams]
[NAMI grunts]
[NAMI]
It didn't do this last time!
Did I grab a broken one?
Oww!
[gasps] Huh?
[OLD MEN]
Hm?
My balloon's gonna crash! Help!
[OLD MAN F]
No! It's coming straight for us!
[OLD MAN G]
Goodness! We're doomed!
Hurry! Run away!
[OLD MEN scream, groan]
[OLD MEN groan, gasp]
[OLD MAN B]
And there you have it.
Too much excitement for me!
[HAREDAS] Hmm. She may
be a fiery young lass,
but I didn't think
she would do that.
Now that I know the "what,"
it's time for us to
figure out the "why."
I'll give back what I borrowed,
just let me out of
this stupid bubble jail!
I've got somewhere to be,
okay? It's really important.
C'mon! It's just
a misunderstanding!
Oh, wait a sec! Haredas!
Get Haredas and
he'll sort this out!
Pretty please?
[OLD MEN growling]
We're old and you're scary!
Who knows what kind
of trap you're plotting!
This is a place of law!
You'll be punished
for your crimes!
Yes, what if we shocked her?
Or drowned her a bit?
Which better befits a thief?
Ugh. You guys got it all wrong.
Please, let me out!
At least give me a trial!
[OLD MEN]
No way, missy!
[HAREDAS]
Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, hello, Haredas!
[HAREDAS]
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Well, well, what a pickle!
Hey, young lady.
[NAMI]
Hey, yourself.
Another outburst!
You just weren't made
to take it easy, were you?
But never fear!
You remember this fellow, right?
Here, I'll show you a trick.
Take your tightly tied
wind knots, like so...
--[thud]
--[groans]
[OLD MEN]
Haredas! No!
[HAREDAS groaning]
I was counting
on you to help me!
Get me outta here!
I'm in a rush, all right?
[OLD MEN]
Are you okay?
Haredas, speak to us!
Tell us you're not dead!
[groans] Yes. Or no?
I mean, maybe?
[OLD MAN I] She hit that
kind and gentle man!
What a beast!
[OLD MAN J]
Doctor! Someone call the doctor!
[NAMI growling]
[HAREDAS]
That's most curious!
So, she stole an armful
of weather balls
and our research notes,
then tried to
make a break for it?
See for yourself.
It's all right here.
Young lady!
I'm a pirate.
What did you expect?
What's wrong with
a little theft?
Gotta make a living
somehow, don't I?
[OLD MEN] Simply reprehensible!
Such an awful human being!
We have a villain in our midst!
Whatever shall we do?
Ugh. Just let me go.
You guys don't want me here
and I don't want to be here!
You got back everything I stole.
What does it even matter?
Would you stop flipping
out for five seconds
and listen to me?
I'm in a hurry here!
This is important!
[OLD MAN I] Don't get too close!
She's terribly violent!
All right,
I'm listening. Let's talk.
Though I should tell you,
stealing a balloon was
both foolish and dangerous.
You need proper
training to pilot one.
You could've easily died.
Prior to this little outburst,
you were perfectly eager
to study here with us.
What's gotten into you?
Huh?
--[OLD MEN whimpering]
--[NAMI] Read the front page.
[HAREDAS]
The paper, eh?
You see that article about
the pirate named "Luffy"?
He's the captain of our ship.
Is he?
Oh, I've seen
that fellow before!
The boy's a real upstart.
Caused quite the ruckus
in Marineford, they say.
He's famous for that
straw hat that he wears.
[HAREDAS]
Look at that grin.
He's a charming little
rogue, isn't he?
[NAMI] Our crew has been
separated for a while now,
so he doesn't even know
if we're alive or dead.
I had no idea what he was going
through until I read that paper.
I've been taking it
easy all this time
while he was down there
fighting for his life.
[HAREDAS]
Hmm?
He saw his brother killed
right before his eyes.
I didn't even know.
I couldn't do anything.
And now he's waiting for me.
And for the rest of
the crew, I'm sure.
[OLD MEN gasping]
Luffy is strong, but this
is too much to bear.
I want to be there for him.
I want to help him.
[NAMI crying]
[OLD MEN screaming]
Hey, hey! Don't cry.
You'll be okay!
[OLD MAN H]
Hurry up and let her out!
[OLD MAN E] We're the
real villains! Look at us!
Abducting an innocent young
girl and making her cry!
[OLD MAN J]
Give Haredas the key!
[OLD MAN K]
Quickly now!
[HAREDAS]
We're sorry, young lady.
Let's sort this out and--
--[OLD MEN gasp]
--[HAREDAS screams]
[OLD MAN I]
That's odd. Where did she go?
[OLD MAN E]
I don't see Haredas, either.
[OLD MEN gasp]
[OLD MEN]
Huh? How did she move so fast?
Thanks for everything!
Bye, bye!
[OLD MEN]
Huh? "Bye, bye"?
She pretended to cry
to take Haredas hostage?
And she's stealing
our stuff again, too!
We can't let that
little harpy escape!
Away we go!
[OLD MAN H]
The world below isn't ready
for the genius of our research!
[OLD MAN E]
I know! I know!
Take me to the sea! Anywhere!
I can't do it by myself!
Impossible!
[NAMI]
Make it possible!
[NAMI] Luffy, hang on,
just a little bit longer.
I'm sorry. Every time
we've been in trouble,
you've been there to help us.
Just this once, I hope
we can return the favor.
[OLD MEN]
Help! Thief! Get back here!
You've already captured
me, young lady.
You don't need to pretend
to cry like that anymore.
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI]
Shut up!
[HAREDAS screams]
[NARRATOR] We now return
to Future Land Baldimore,
a mechanical island where the
genius, Dr. Vegapunk, was born.
[KITTON]
Grandpa! It's an emergency!
The freak! The freak! The freak!
I mean, the Frank! I mean
the Franky, Mr. Frank.
I mean, I mean, Franky!
Just calm down
and tell me, Kitton.
Franky!
He's acting all different again,
but this time it's scary!
He's like some kinda monster!
Someone get me a ship!
[KITTON yelps]
He's coming for me!
Tell the truth, Kitton.
You put something strange
in that poor man's stomach
to see what would
happen, didn't you?
Like habanero juice or
kimchi soda or some nonsense?
Nuh-uh, not this time!
--[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER] Hm?
--[KITTON screams]
[KITTON whimpering]
[FRANKY panting]
It's an emergency, Gramps.
I gotta go see my friends.
I know this's sudden, but I
won't take no for an answer.
I need a ship, dammit,
and I need it right now!
A ship?
Sorry to say, but that
won't be possible.
Huh?
We don't have a ship.
There's not a single one
on the entire island.
There's a liner that
comes to our country
each month to bring us supplies,
but we don't have any
sea-faring vessels of our own.
All right, fine, when's
the liner due back, then?
Not for a while yet, I'm afraid.
It stopped by last week.
That's no good.
I can't wait. There's gotta
be some way around this.
[FRANKY grunts]
You may have noticed this island
is surrounded by walls of ice.
For better or worse,
it works like a fortress.
The only ships that
can reach us are
specially-equipped icebreakers
and certain Navy vessels.
[groans] Well, this is bullcrap!
[FRANKY] I could get
supplies to build a ship,
but that still
wouldn't be fast enough.
[FRANKY growls]
Please calm down.
Do you want some
tea or something?
[FRANKY gasps]
[FRANKY]
Mm. This aroma is just lovely!
[ALL yelling]
[FRANKY]
I ain't got time for this!
I'm tellin' ya,
I gotta blow this joint
and I gotta do it fast!
[BOTH whimpering]
[FRANKY panting]
My captain needs me right now!
I'm lower than dirt
if I let him down.
Damn it all.
I didn't know.
I understand how
important this is to you.
But there's nothing
you can do but wait.
[FRANKY grunting]
Oh! Here's an idea!
Yeah?
If I recall, Dr. Vegapunk
developed an icebreaker.
It should still be tucked away
in his laboratory, I'd think.
Of course, it's been years since
anyone's touched the thing.
[FRANKY chuckles]
Who can say if it
still works. Oh!
I know it's dangerous,
so I'll stay home this time.
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER gasps]
Then I know just where to go.
Hold on. You've gone there?
Both of you
without a word to me?
[FRANKY, KITTON]
Yeah.
--[FRANKY] And it was awesome.
--[KITTON] Sure did.
What?!
If it's broken,
then I can fix it.
I am a shipwright after all!
That's not exactly
the concern here.
I'm takin' this
party to the lab!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Wait! Listen to me!
[FRANKY]
It's cold!
[siren blaring]
[MARINE C]
We have an intruder!
[MARINE D] Someone's broken
into Dr. Vegapunk's lab!
What should we do?
Dammit! Apprehend them,
but don't use any firearms!
His inventions are too valuable.
We can't afford to have
even one damaged. Understand?
[MARINE D]
Yes, sir!
[FRANKY panting]
Get back here!
Crap! They musta
tightened security
after the last time I broke in!
I can't get anything done
with these guys chasing me!
[grunts]
Hold on. I get it now.
We can't shoot in here.
[MARINE D]
Don't let him get away! Go!
[FRANKY] Wait, what d'you mean
the lab is full of treasure?
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Vegapunk is the head
of the Navy's science division,
so all of his works are
valuable. Priceless, really.
Our country's very proud of him.
Although, I suppose it's his
mind that's the real treasure.
At any rate, he spent his
youth working in that lab,
tirelessly.
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Have you noticed that mountain?
A rather unnatural
shape, isn't it?
I never gave it much
thought, but yeah.
There's a story behind it?
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
It's a project Vegapunk
began as a child. It was meant
to protect the island's people
from frigid weather.
He built it by
transforming the animals
in the forest into
a robotic work force.
Unfortunately,
it remains unfinished.
It's a sort of geothermal system
to heat up the whole island.
[grunts]
The world just can't keep
up with his imagination.
That's why so many of his works
remain buried here in
a state of half-completion.
Sometimes, the technology or
funds he needed didn't exist.
Even though he couldn't
get rid of the cold,
knowing that he cared,
knowing that he worked so hard,
warmed our hearts at least.
[whimpers]
That story is super depressing!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Ya think so?
But the people here are happy
to wait for his return.
Whenever that may be.
Please respect our feelings
and stay out of that lab.
After all, it's equipped
with a self-destruct button,
in case you wanted to know.
But why? Not the button.
I mean, why did you think
I would want to know that?
Like I was gonna press
the dumb thing?
Either way, that
sounds pretty scary.
Why don't we forget about
this whole mess and go home?
I'll make you some
nice, hot tea, okay?
Sorry, kiddo, no way.
I didn't come all
the way out here
with no pants on
just to turn around.
I'm gettin' that icebreaker
if it's the last thing I do.
Don't get me wrong,
I appreciate your hospitality,
but I read the paper today
and it turns out that my captain
has gone through hell and back.
So, bye!
You guys have a nice life!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
I know it's tempting,
but no matter what, don't press
that self-destruct button!
Would you give it
a rest already?
Why the hell would I want
to do something like that?
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER grunts]
[panting]
[MARINE E] Hey! I saw someone
down this hallway! Over there!
Hurry!
I can't find the ship
with them chasing me!
[MARINE E]
Halt!
Did you hear?
The Marines came by and said
someone broke into the lab.
That's not good. Let's just
hope they catch him.
They're probably looking to
sell stuff on the black market.
Even a blueprint from that
place would be worth a fortune.
[MARINE F]
This way?
Well, that was a pain
in the butt. Huh?
[MARINE A] I shouldn't
need to you remind you,
but so much as sneeze on one of
Dr. Vegapunk's masterpieces,
and you'll spend the rest
of your life in prison!
I don't care if you're a Marine!
[MARINES]
Sir!
I can't believe the
doctor cooked up
all this stuff when
he was so young.
'Cause this is super brilliant
work if I've ever seen it.
Half of this is so advanced,
it'll take another hundred years
before the world is ready.
Maybe I don't wanna
mess with this.
As a fellow engineer,
I gotta respect the man's work.
Huh?
Sweet! He's got
a pirate mark, too?
[BOTH screaming]
[CROWD screaming]
[ALL gasping]
[FRANKY]
So, hypothetically...
...if by some crazy chance
I press that button,
like you said...
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Hm?
Yeah, go on.
[FRANKY] You wouldn't, like,
hold it against me, would you?
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER, KITTON]
Of course, we would!
[NARRATOR] News of this incident
quickly spread across the world
and history would remember it
as "Baldimore's Nightmare."
[NARRATOR] Zoro makes
a wild dash to the sea
as Mihawk watches on.
Will the master swordsman
impart wisdom to Zoro,
or will their reunion end
in another deadly duel?
Meanwhile, Luffy begins
a daring plan of his own.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Encounter! The Great
Swordsman Mihawk!
Zoro's Self-Willed
Deadly Struggle!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!