[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are
turning on each other.
After arriving in Alabasta,
Luffy and the others
ran afoul of an old enemy:
Marine Captain Smoker.
But there to save Luffy
in the nick of time
was the man who
controls flame,
Fire Fist Ace,
who as it turned out, was
also Luffy's older brother.
[LUFFY] "Ace And Luffy! Hot
Emotions and Brotherly Bonds!"
Move it.
Afraid I can't. You understand.
[MARINES gasp, murmur]
[gasps] It's Fire Fist Ace.
So you're the Straw Hat's
brother, are you?
[SMOKER]
White... Spark!
[CITY FOLK gasp, murmur]
[CITIZEN 2]
A fire?!
[CITIZEN 4]
That's no ordinary fire!
What's going on back there?
[USOPP] Looks like a fight
between smoke and fire!
So that's the kind
of power you get
after eating a
Flame Flame Fruit.
[KAROO squawks]
[NAMI] Speaking of Devil
Fruit, Luffy, is it true?
Is that guy really your brother?
[LUFFY]
Yep! His name's Ace!
Look, I'm not surprised to hear
you have a brother, Luffy.
But what's he doing here
on the Grand Line?
Ace is a pirate too,
just like I am!
He left home three
years before I did
to go search for the One Piece!
Anyway, he bought us some
time, so we can't waste it!
Let's get back to the ship!
Sure, Nami dear!
Wow, I never woulda thought
I'd run into my big brother
in a place like this!
[USOPP]
Agh! Which way do we go?!
[NAMI]
Left, Usopp! Everyone get that?!
[SANJI] Yes Nami, I'll
follow you wherever you go!
[ZORO]
You lovesick freak!
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
[LUFFY laughs]
[SMOKER] A fight
between flame and smoke
is ultimately pointless.
As we've just made obvious.
Where's the Straw Hat
and his crew?
[MARINE A]
They're gone, sir!
[MARINE B] So is Ace!
We've lost sight of him!
I run into the Straw Hat
in the Grand Line
and have him as
good as captured.
But then,
you just had to get in
my way, didn't you, Ace?
[NAMI] Get everything stowed!
We're shoving off right away!
[USOPP]
Aye‐aye!
Set the sails!
[CHOPPER] But it took us
so long to finally get here,
and now we're leaving
already, Vivi?
Yes, but remember,
we only stopped here to get
the supplies we're going to need
for the rest of the journey.
And now that we
have all of them,
we're going to head upriver
into the interior of Alabasta.
Our next destination is...
the City of Green, Erumalu.
Erumalu?
[ZORO]
Hurry!
[USOPP]
I am!
[SANJI]
Pick up the pace!
[USOPP]
Ready!
[NAMI]
Right! Set sail!
Huh?
Uh...
Ah damn it.
Uh, guys...
[groans]
[USOPP] You know, I have
the strangest feeling
we're forgetting something...
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, so do I.
[NAMI] It's not something,
it's someone.
[ZORO]
Gah, that stupid moron!
[LUFFY]
What the...?
Huh, well that's weird...
I coulda sworn they
were right here.
But now they're all gone.
Where'd they go?
[ACE] Well, I guess giving you a
chance to escape was pointless.
Hey!
[ACE chuckles]
Hiya, Ace!
It's been awhile, hasn't it?
You could say that!
‐‐[ACE laughs]
‐‐[LUFFY chuckles]
[laughs] How many
years has it been?
Eh, I don't know.
But you haven't changed
much over that time.
You're a little taller, but
you pretty much look the same.
So do you, aside from
those powers you got
from eating that Devil Fruit,
you haven't changed a bit!
[ACE groans]
[LUFFY] 'Member when you used
to sneak into the fields,
eat a hundred watermelons,
spit the seeds out
like a Gatling gun
and run away?!
No that wasn't me,
that was you!
[LUFFY] The farmers would
chase you and you'd
scream like a girl!
[ACE] That was you, too!
I watched and laughed!
[LUFFY groans]
[ACE groans]
[BOTH groan]
I guess we're still the same!
Sure are!
Just like old times!
[ACE]
Wait...
Wasn't your crew looking
for you a few minutes ago?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
Hey. What are you doing
in this country, anyway?
[ACE] Huh! I take it you
never received the message
I left for you back
on Drum island.
Message?
Well... I guess that's a no.
But don't worry,
it's no big deal.
It was just to let you know
that I'd be in Alabasta
for a few days.
I'm in these waters
on some business.
Business, huh?
Yeah, I'm with the
Whitebeard Pirates.
Catch.
The Whitebeard Pirates?
[ACE] See this tattoo?
That's our mark.
And it's my pride.
[LUFFY]
Huh.
So, Luffy!
Why don't you and your
friends come join us?
Come on, it'll be fun!
Whaddaya say?
No thanks.
[ACE laughs]
Ah, I had a feeling
you'd say that.
That's too bad, 'cause you see,
Whitebeard's the greatest
pirate I've ever met.
That's why I'm going
to help him become
King of the Pirates.
And not you, Luffy. Sorry.
Heh, that's fine.
I guess we'll just
have to fight then.
Because I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
[LUFFY gulping water]
[ACE] Stop it! Don't drink
it all, you mooch! Hey!
[MR. 11] Something big
must be going on in town.
All the Marines onboard wouldn't
have left me and the ship
unattended like this
if there wasn't!
[MR. 11 sighs, laughs]
Oh well, whatever it is,
it's given me a perfect
opportunity to escape!
[BILLIONS A]
Mr. 11.
[MR. 11 groans]
Well now, since you
know my codename,
that can only mean that
the three of you are
members of Baroque Works!
I'd guess Millions.
Hurry up and untie me!
You're right about one thing.
We're with Baroque Works.
But we're in line to become
number agents, you see.
We're not millions,
we're billions.
You are a numbered agent,
but looks like you're
barely one at that.
A stronger agent would
have never been captured
by the Marines like this.
[MR. 11]
Can we discuss this later?
Like when I'm not tied up maybe?
Now help another member out
before all those
Marines come back!
Heh, heh. Oh, we'll
help you all right!
[gasps]
[BILLIONS A] Right off
this mortal coil that is!
A Billions can get promoted
to a Number Agent
whenever there's a seat to fill!
[GERONIMO grunts]
And your position...
is about to be empty.
Wait! No, hold on!
‐‐[bang]
‐‐[MR. 11 yells]
[BILLIONS D]
Hey!
[BILLIONS D pants]
You won't believe it!
Fire Fist Ace is here!
[BILLIONS A]
What?! Fire Fist Ace?!
You mean the Second
Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates?!
Heh, if we can take someone
with his reputation down,
then we're guaranteed
to become Number Agents!
[ACE]
All right, enough chitchat.
We need to find your friends
before the Marines do.
Do you have any idea where
they could have gone?
[LUFFY]
I don't know.
They might've gone
back to the ship.
Well, that's a start.
Where's it docked at?
Actually, I'm not
sure. That's funny.
Huh, jeez.
[ACE] You know, Luffy,
pirate ship captains
usually remember where
they leave their ships.
Yeah, but I was hungry,
and I forgot.
You haven't changed at all.
So, tell me about your crew.
What are they like?
Who are they?
Well first there's a tough guy
who carries around three swords,
wants to be the greatest
swordsman in the world.
Then there's a navigator
who likes maps and
tangerines and money.
There's also a cook who
makes really yummy food.
There's a liar, too.
Oh! And we just got a doctor
who happens to be a reindeer!
Really, you don't say.
Sounds like you've got
a motley crew there.
[LUFFY] We also have a
princess and her giant duck.
[ACE]
Oh?
[LUFFY] Everyone in my
crew is so interesting!
[ACE]
Sure sounds like it,
but I'd wager you're the
most interesting one of all.
But still, only a handful
of people for a pirate crew.
That's just like you.
I'm still lookin' for
a musician though.
[BILLIONS A]
Stop right there, Fire Fist!
[footsteps approaching]
[GERONIMO]
You've got no place to run, Ace.
Your head is mine!
It's my ticket to a promotion.
Prepare to die!
Um... is it okay...
...for a ship to set sail
without it's captain onboard?
The first place the Marines are
gonna look for us is the harbor.
So our top priority
is to hide the ship.
I know of a secluded cove
that's up ahead.
We can anchor the ship there.
All right, so we lay low,
let things cool down a bit,
and then go back for Luffy.
Good grief! That guy
attracts trouble
just like a dead guy
attracts vultures.
Yeah. That's the only reliable
thing our captain ever does.
It's our lucky day, boys.
This'll be easier than
shootin' fish in a barrel.
[BILLIONS D]
Heh.
[BILLIONS C]
Hey, look at that other guy.
Is it just me, or does he kinda
look like Straw Hat Luffy?
Hey... now that you
mention it, it is him!
He's worth 30 million Berries!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Well well, it looks like our
lucky day just got even luckier.
That big promotion's
only a hop, skip, jump,
and two severed
pirate heads away!
[ACE]
Anyway, let's go find your ship.
We'll start at the shore.
[LUFFY]
'Kay.
Hey! Stop, you two!
[BILLIONS A]
Hold it right there!
[GERONIMO growls]
You can't walk away from us!
Get 'em!
[BILLIONS yell]
‐‐[BILLIONS E groans]
‐‐[BILLIONS G grunts]
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY]
What's going on?!
[BILLIONS H yells]
[BILLIONS Q]
Give 'em a taste of your steel!
[BILLIONS I]
Hold 'em down!
[BILLIONS yell]
[BILLIONS gasp, yell]
Whoa! What the hell?
His arms stretched out!
Aw man, he must have
Devil Fruit powers!
Have these back
'cause I don't need 'em!
[bullets fire]
[GERONIMO yells]
[LUFFY]
Whoa...!
[GERONIMO yells, groans]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
[GERONIMO]
Ow! Hot!
[LUFFY]
...Bazooka!
Don't be scared, men!
Yeah, he's right!
The rank of Number Agent
is riding on those two!
[BILLIONS C]
After them!
[LUFFY]
Here we are!
[ACE]
You see your ship?
[LUFFY]
Hm...
[BILLIONS A]
You can't escape from us!
You clowns just never learn.
[LUFFY]
Oh! There it is!
Hey, over here
you guys! We're here!
[ACE] Luffy, you go on ahead
and‐‐oh, you already went.
[NAMI]
Oh, I don't believe it.
I found Luffy!
Are you sure?
[SANJI] Yeah, that stupid
mug is definitely his.
Uh‐oh.
[LUFFY]
Hey, guys!
‐‐[VIVI gasps]
‐‐[SANJI, CHOPPER yell]
[VIVI]
Sanji! Tony! Are you all right?!
Oh, Luffy came back.
[ZORO]
Yeah, the hard way.
[LUFFY laughs]
Sorry 'bout that guys, my bad.
[SANJI]
Yeah, you're sorry all right!
The sorriest excuse
for a captain
who's ever sailed
the sea, you moron!
Do you have any idea how much
trouble you've put us in?
Can't you at least try and
act like a captain sometime?
I'm sorry... Oh!
That's right! Where's Ace?
[SANJI]
Ace?
[ZORO]
You were with your brother, huh?
[USOPP]
Wait a minute.
You didn't just
leave him, did you?
[LUFFY]
Um, sorta, but don't worry.
Ace is really strong.
So how strong is he?
Well, let me put it like this.
When we were younger,
I was never able to
beat him in a fight, and this
was way back in the days
before he ate a
Flame Flame Fruit!
That's how strong
my big brother is!
You mean there's a
flesh‐and‐blood person
that you couldn't beat?!
The big brother of a monster
is an even bigger monster.
I guess so, 'cause Ace used to
beat me up all the time. Ha, ha!
But I bet now I could
kick his big butt!
[LUFFY laughs]
[ZORO] I'd like to see you
try and back that claim up.
[ACE]
So... exactly whose butt's...
...getting kicked?
Oh, hey, Ace!
This is my crew I was
telling you about!
[ACE] Nice to meet you
and thanks for taking care of
my kid brother!
I know he's a handful!
[ALL]
Oh, no, not at all.
Come on, be honest. This is
Luffy we're talking about!
Isn't he a bit much for you
to handle at times?
[ALL]
Not at all.
[ACE]
You're good people.
Well, sit down and relax.
I'm sure you two have
lots of catching up to do.
I'll make some tea.
No, that's thoughtful,
but I don't want to impose.
[SANJI] He's not exactly
what I expected.
[ZORO]
I'll say.
He's polite, helpful,
and gracious,
the polar opposite of Luffy.
One of 'em only cares
about stuffing his face.
There's no way
these two can be brothers!
While the other only
cares about his brother!
I wish I had a wonderful
brother like that!
Brother? I wish I had a
wonderful captain like that.
Sanji! He's kidding!
See! I told you they
were interesting. Ha, ha, ha!
[VIVI]
Baroque Works!
Those are the Billions' ships!
Are we going to let them
escape from the Billions?
[BILLIONS]
No way!
We'll show 'em what Baroque
Works' Billions are made of!
Full speed ahead!
Those guys again?
‐‐[ACE] Luffy.
‐‐[LUFFY] Hm?
Leave it to me,
I'll handle them.
[NAMI,VIVI]
Eh?
He's going all by himself?
And in that dinky boat, too.
I wouldn't worry
about him if I were you.
They don't let
just anyone become
the Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
[BILLIONS E]
Is he insane?!
Fire Fist is heading
right towards us!
[BILLIONS H]
Let him come!
Our ships are gonna make
matchsticks out of his!
He jumped!
[BILLIONS A]
Open fire!
[BILLIONS B]
Blow him to pieces, men!
‐‐[BILLIONS gasp]
‐‐[STRAW HATS gasp]
[ACE]
Heh. Fire Fist!
[BILLIONS yell]
[ACE]
Heh.
[ALL gasp]
‐‐[LUFFY laughs]
‐‐[USOPP] He roasted them!
[TASHIGI] Captain Smoker! We've
combed the entire city, sir,
but Straw Hat Luffy and his
crew are nowhere to be found.
Do you wanna know
who I saw with them?
Vivi, and I'm certain
it was her, too.
Vivi? As in
Princess Vivi Nefertari?
But what would she be doing
with the Straw Hat pirates?
She must be their hostage.
They probably abducted her
in the hopes that her father
would pay a hefty ransom.
Doubt it.
She wasn't acting
like a kidnap victim,
more like part of the crew.
The Princess...
acting like a pirate?
Something strange is happening.
I just wish I knew what it was.
[SERGEANT]
Captain Smoker! I'm sorry, sir!
But it appears that Mr. 11
was killed onboard the ship
while we were off
searching for the Straw Hats!
Who, by the way, we still
haven't located yet!
Call off the search
for Straw Hat Luffy,
I have a pretty good idea
where he's headed.
He's after Crocodile.
I'm sure of it.
Why Crocodile? He's one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
A pirate given
government approval!
[SMOKER] I find all of the
Seven Warlords despicable,
but Crocodile's
the absolute worst.
[TASHIGI]
Politically‐speaking,
isn't he an ally of the World
Government and the Marines?
Crocodile might have
the powers‐that‐be fooled,
but not me.
They're delusional if they
think giving him a sanction
will make him obey.
He's a pirate!
There's one thing you always
need to remember, Tashigi.
A pirate's a pirate,
no matter where they go.
They never change.
Crocodile will
lead us right to him.
Straw Hat'll show up
wherever he is,
and I'm sure we'll
find out what's going on
when we get there.
There'll be no escape
for him, not this time.
‐‐[LUFFY] Woo‐hoo!
‐‐[USOPP] All right!
[USOPP] Since he's one of us
now, here's to Fire Fist Ace!
[CHOPPER, USOPP, LUFFY]
Cheers!
Wait! Who said I was
joining your crew?
And to delicious drinks, eh?
[CHOPPER, USOPP, LUFFY]
Cheers!
Oh, don't worry.
You can't take anything
they say seriously
when they're like this.
They get all goofy
when they drink.
[LUFFY, USOPP] Medicine isn't
delicious, it's terrible!
[CHOPPER, USOPP, LUFFY laugh]
Ace! Are you sure
you don't wanna join us?
It'll be fun! I promise.
I can't right now.
I'm chasing someone.
He's a pirate named Blackbeard.
Uh... Blackbeard?!
We've heard of him. He was the
one who attacked Drum Kingdom!
You see, Blackbeard
used to be a member of
the Second Division of
the Whitebeard Pirates.
He was one of my own men,
but he committed
the most unforgiveable sin
a pirate could.
He killed one of his
fellow crewmembers
and then he jumped ship.
As Commander of his division,
it's my responsibility
to take care of him.
[USOPP]
So that's why you're after him.
I came here because
I'd heard that Blackbeard
was seen in Alabasta,
in a place called Yuba,
so that's where I'm headed.
[NAMI]
Hey...
That's our
destination too, right?
[VIVI] Exactly. We've just
entered the Sandora River.
We'll take it to Erumalu,
where we'll dock,
and then we'll proceed on foot
until we reach Yuba, here.
The leader of the
rebel army is there.
That's where we're going.
You don't say. Do you
mind if I tag along?
Nami, Vivi, I'll
follow you anywhere!
Just tell me where to go!
Hopefully it's off of a cliff.
[SANJI]
What'd you say, Zoro?!
[NAMI]
Cool it, you two!
Well, looks you'll be with us
for a little while, Ace!
[USOPP] Ha, ha! We're all really
happy to have you aboard.
[laughs]
This is gonna be fun!
To Ace!
‐‐[KAROO squawks]
‐‐[ALL] Cheers!
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[NAMI]
This is Erumalu?
[LUFFY]
Huh? There's nothing here!
[VIVI]
Erumalu, the City of Green.
[LUFFY] City of Green?
There's no green anywhere!
[VIVI] It was a thriving
city until recently.
[USOPP]
This place?
[VIVI] Karoo, I have a very
important favor to ask of you.
I want you to
go to Alubarna.
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Erumalu, the City of Green
and the Kung Fu Dugongs!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!