[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[gasps]
[yells]
[screams]
Thanks, I owe you one.
I thought I was
a goner for sure.
It's really no big deal.
Buggy...
the Pirate Clown, right?
What's it to you?
Just who are you, lady?
I've been looking
for a certain young pirate.
What'd ya say?
Should we find him together?
[LUFFY] "The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!"
[ALVIDA]
Where are we going, Buggy?
[BUGGY] Well we're‐‐
None of your business!
[ALVIDA]
I said where're we going?!
Ouch. All right.
Since you put it so nicely...
To find my crew.
My dear crew.
I wonder where they've
ended up without their captain.
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum Bazooka!
[BUGGY yells]
[CABAJI]
We have to retreat!
[MOHJI] We're doomed!
Run for your lives!
[CROWD yells]
Is everyone here?
Okay, buddy check.
Sound off if you think
you're missing yours.
I'm here!
Got mine.
[PIRATE C]
Right here.
Okay.
[PIRATE E] Captain Buggy
didn't make it back.
He's not all here!
[ALL sobbing]
[PIRATES wailing]
Captain Buggy!
[CABAJI] It's been so long
since we lost our captain.
[MOHJI]
Who knows where he is now.
We have to decide
what we should do next.
The crew is lost without
someone to lead them.
Aaah!
Nami! This is all her fault,
that stupid little thief.
Just you wait, Zoro.
You will die by this blade.
[ZORO]
Ahchoo!
Zoro... 'Course you're
gonna get sick
if you sleep in the open air.
I mean doesn't it
get cold at night?
I've never been sick,
not a day in my life.
Ya know... I don't remember
ever being sick either.
Not once.
Then someone must be
talking about me,
or so the saying goes...
Oh, that's so fake. Pfff!
[sneezes]
Uh. Somebody must be
talking about me.
It sucks being this beautiful.
They all talk about me.
[LUFFY, USOPP yell]
[BUGGY PIRATES sobbing]
[PIRATE D]
Captain Buggy!
[sobbing]
[PIRATE B] Before he died,
I hated Captain Buggy.
I always thought he was
cruel and heartless.
But now I see
how hard he worked.
He really just wanted
what was best for his crew.
With Captain Buggy
we were able to
pillage and plunder
to our hearts content.
I don't know if it'll be
the same with another captain.
Let's honor our missing leader.
He deserves a flashy
goodbye from us.
[MOHJI, RICHIE sobbing]
[CABAJI]
Rest in peace... captain.
Leave it to me.
Your faithful number two.
Cabaji the Acrobat
is ready to take your place.
[MOHJI]
Hmm?
[CABAJI]
I will take the helm and lead
the Buggy Pirates
back on the path to glory.
[MOHJI]
Stop right there!
Cabaji!
It is I, Beast Tamer Mohji,
the captain's
right hand man who should
take his proper place
as our leader.
I've always been
the next in line
and nobody is going
to take that away from me.
I'll be glad to take you
as my second in command,
but you're looking at the new
captain of the Buggy Pirates.
[MOHJI snarls]
[CABAJI snarls]
Heh. All right then,
looks like we'll have a fight
to see who'll be
the next captain!
[PIRATES]
Yeah!
That's just fine by me.
[PIRATES chuckle]
[PIRATES chanting]
Mohji! Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji! Cabaji!
[PIRATES chanting]
Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
[grumbles]
On your mark... Get set...
Go!
[MOHJI yells]
[CABAJI] Acrobat Technique
Monkey Showman!
Secret Technique:
Candid Camera Police Trio!
Extreme Wrath at the Steam Bath!
[MOHJI coughs]
[CABAJI]
Die... Mohji!
[ALL gasp]
[RICHIE gasps]
[CABAJI, MOHJI]
[CABAJI] I guess we'll settle
this the old‐fashioned way.
Hand to hand combat.
And I wouldn't have
it any other way.
Now I get to tear you
apart limb from limb.
[ALL gasp]
[PIRATES chanting]
Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
[chanting continues]
[thudding, whacking]
[PIRATES cheering]
[ALL snoring]
[muffled]
It's no use. Just give up.
You know... you can't
take it... anymore.
[muffled] I didn't understand
anything you just said.
I'm going to be
the captain, you hear me!
No, you're not!
[CABAJI, MOHJI yell]
[ALL snoring]
[snores]
[chuckles]
[roars]
[BOTH] Richie!
The greatest captain ever!
[FIRE DRAGON roars]
[ALL scream]
[RICHIE]
Hmm!
[RICHIE roars
[roars]
[PIRATES]
Captain Richie!
[roars]
[OWL]
Hmmm?
[RICHIE roars]
[OWL hoots]
[PIRATES]
Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
He's the Greatest!
[PIRATE D]
After the loss of Captain Buggy,
Richie is the one
who will lead us now!
All hail Captain Richie!
[PIRATES continue chanting]
[PIRATES chant]
He's the greatest! He's a lion!
Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
[PIRATES cheer]
[drumming begins]
[drumming continues]
Who are you? Why're you here?
You must leave now,
or you will face
the consequences.
You are trespassing.
This island belongs
to the Bear Claw Tribe
and you will be shown no mercy.
[PIRATES gasp]
Help, captain!
[RICHIE growls lowly]
Oh, so their captain wants to
pick a fight, is that it?
[RICHIE growls lowly]
[BEAR CLAW A] Then we shall
fight to the death.
[RICHIE growls lowly]
[BEAR CLAW A growls lowly]
[drumming speeds up]
[roars]
[BEAR CLAW A yells]
We surrender.
[BUGGY screams]
Hey! Hey!
[ALVIDA] What is it?
You don't need to yell.
I'm standing right here.
Did you find something?
Look. Right there.
That's my ship!
The Grand Flashy Flagship
of the Buggy Pirates!
[ALVIDA] So, why'd they
give you such a big grave?
[BUGGY] What, big...
Are you talking about my nose?
Did you say big? Huh? Huh?
You're dead! You hear me? Dead!
I said "big grave." That's all.
Not tall? So I'm short.
Is that it or do you
wanna call me stupid, too?
[grunts]
Wait... You said "grave."
[ALVIDA]
Took you long enough.
[BUGGY]
But who would do this?
Who would use
such an old picture?
[sighs]
And what did they bury?
Hey. There's somebody passed out
on the ground over there.
[BUGGY]
No!
Mohji! Cabaji?
What the hell
happened to you two?
Cap‐Captain Buggy...!
[gasps]
You're alive!
Never leave us again!
[CABAJI] We thought
you were gone forever!
I missed you guys so much!
So... uh...
Who kicked your asses?
I'd like to say hello!
Uh...
I don't remember anything
except getting knocked out.
We were attacked.
But I have no idea who did it.
[ALVIDA] Looks like your boys
have been introduced
to the Bear Claw Tribe.
Is that so?
Yeah. We better hurry up
if you want to save your crew.
[ALL shriek]
The Bear Claws are cannibals.
[PIRATES, RICHIE yell]
Took a crap in the pot.
You can't eat us now.
And I peed myself.
We'd all be dry
and stringy anyway.
Just eat this guy.
He looks tasty.
He's got much more meat on
his bones than I do. Eat him!
This isn't happening.
This isn't happening!
Don't worry.
It'll all be over soon.
We're the Bear Claw Tribe.
We know how to prepare anyone
to taste quite delicious!
[PIRATES holler]
What are we gonna do
with these things?
Appetizers?
I'm not so sure those chunks
would be very good to eat.
[BEAR CLAW D]
Give them to the dog.
[sniffs]
No way.
I think it might
make him throw up.
[BUGGY]
Chop, chop...
[BEAR CLAWS gasp]
[BUGGY]
Chop, chop, chop, chop...
[BEAR CLAW A yells]
[groans]
[PIRATES yell]
[thud]
[PIRATES groan]
[gasps]
It can't be!
[sobs]
[BUGGY]
Chop‐chop‐chop‐chop‐chop‐chop...
Chop‐chop,
chop‐chop‐chop‐chop‐chop,
chop‐chop, chop‐chop,
Flashy Reassemble!
[BUGGY laughs]
I'm back!
[PIRATE holler, cheer]
And now...
my favorite! Showtime!
Super Flashy Buggy Ball!
[laughs]
[BEAR CLAWS yell]
[whistles]
[MOHJI]
Richie!
[roars]
[CABAJI]
Acrobat Technique:
Extreme Wrath at the Steam Bath!
It's time for
the Beast Tamer Mohji!
[RICHIE roars]
[BUGGY laughs]
I'm Captain Buggy
the Clown Pirate!
You didn't really think you'd
be able to hurt me, did you?
[BEAR CLAWS gasp]
Your tribe has done
such a good job
looking after my men.
Let me give you your reward.
Here I come, boys!
[laughs]
Chop‐Chop Kick!
[BEAR CLAW D, E groan]
Aah! Chop‐Chop... Punch!
Die flashily!
Chop‐Chop Buzz Saw!
[laughs]
Cop‐Chop Festival!
Chop‐Chop... Punch!
And Chop‐Chop Carnival!
Yay! Captain Buggy is back!
Try to eat us now!
[chuckles]
[PIRATES cheer]
Thank you. You saved us.
My adorable little children.
I've missed you all
so very much.
Where have you been
captain, sir?
Please tell us what
happened to you at sea!
[BUGGY grunts]
[BUGGY screams]
How dare you shoot at me?!
[screams]
That damn Straw Hat
is the reason for all of this.
I promise that
I will make him pay!
[growls]
[PIRATE B] Uh... Captain Buggy,
sir... Who's the pretty lady?
[PIRATES murmur]
Finally. I've been waiting
for someone to mention her.
This is the woman
who saved my life
and her name is...
Hold on...
I don't know her name.
Sorry, what was your name again?
[chuckles]
[CABAJI ] All right! The Buggy
Pirates are back together!
So captain, what orders
do you have for us?
To find and kill
Monkey D. Luffy!
[PIRATES cheer]
Hey... I think I see
an island, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Really? That's great!
[chuckles]
What island is it?
[NAMI] I can't believe
you forgot. I just told you.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
So that's the island
where Logue Town is located.
I wonder if they have a market.
The locals have to buy food too.
That's true.
Looks like I might have to
redo the menu then.
Fresh vegetables.
[ZORO]
I hope they have a sword shop.
Using three sword style with
just one sword kinda blows.
Think it's time to remedy that.
[USOPP] Oooh. I can't wait to
check out their equipment shops
for some cool stuff.
[LUFFY]
That's it, huh?
That's the island
where Gold Roger
was born and then
executed, right?
Okay. So you did remember.
Where the King of the
Pirates met his fate.
This place is known as the "City
of the Beginning and the End."
♪All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[LUFFY] So this is the city
where Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates, died!
[SANJI] This place
is filled with great food
and beautiful girls!
[USOPP] Think they got
anything on sale?!
[SANJI]
What are you, a housewife?
[LUFFY] I'm gonna find out
where they kill people.
[ZORO]
I want some swords, but...
[NAMI]
Do you have money?
[NAMI] I can lend you some
at 300% interest!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Town of
the Beginning and End!
Landfall at Logue Town!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!