Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfas!
That's Dr. Hogback's
laugh, for sure!
Mm-hmm.
So is this
the secret lab?
I sure hope it is!
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfas!
My work is almost finished!
At last!
My beautiful marionette!
Fasfasfasfas!
Behold, Cindry!
This is a true work of art!
The work of a genius!
What we're
about to see here is
the creation of a new zombie.
And that means
that Dr. Hogback made
all of the other undead
creatures on the island as well.
There's no other explanation.
[RYUMA]
Nyohohohoho!
Good evening!
What's the matter?
If you're going to
stand there and stare,
you might as well go inside.
"Yo ho ho ho?"
That isn't Brook, is it?
[groaning]
It's an old man
with serious injuries.
Are you nuts?
It's a zombie!
Don't make fun of me!
[SANJI] Are zombies
usually this energetic?
I'll show you how
dangerous zombies can really be!
Oh, you guys
want a fight, huh?
Then I'll show you how
dangerous pirates can be!
[CREW] 600 Million
Berry Jackpot!
[LUFFY] "His Name is Moria!
The Great Shadow-Seizing
Pirate's Trap."
[LUFFY] So, what are all
you guys doing out here, huh?
[ZOMBIE 343A]
Well, zombie stuff, mostly.
You know, being buried.
[ZOMBIE 340G] Hanging out.
Rotting and stuff.
[ZOMBIE 340D] Yeah. Pretty
much rotting and hanging out.
[ZOMBIE 343B] Yep. Same here.
[LUFFY] You're not
lying to me, are you?
No! Really!
That's the truth!
We swear! Zombie stuff!
That's all!
[LUFFY] I see.
Then let me ask you something:
Did a man with a long nose,
a woman with orange hair,
and a reindeer that looks like
a raccoon-dog come through here?
Oh. Yeah. Right, right, right.
We may have seen them,
but we're not supposed to...
Sorry. We can't say.
Yeah. We're all under
specific orders not to
share any information about
stuff like that with anyone.
Sorry 'bout that.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 343A] Yeah!
We have our orders!
Huh?
Orders! Orders! Orders!
Orders! Orders!
[LUFFY] Oh, I see. So you're
not gonna tell me, huh?
I mean, yeah! We saw 'em!
These zombies are wimps.
Wow.
Those guys are part of my crew.
Listen up. You didn't do
anything to them, did you?
Wait. They're on your crew?
No! We didn't! Right?
Right! We did nothing at all!
Nothing at all!
[ZOMBIES] Nothing at all!
Nothing at all! Nothing at all!
I want the truth. Right now.
This guy did something.
Hey! Shut up! Tattle tale!
And anyway, you're
the one that bit 'em!
Actually, we all did.
Idiot! Shut up!
Ah!!
[sounds of fighting]
[LUFFY] Looks like
they ran outta here
and headed for that mansion.
I'm glad they're alright.
Not sure about Brook, though.
[SANJI] That's fine.
Don't worry about him.
[ZORO] Let's find the others.
Oh, man. How lame!
Those zombies were
a bunch of weaklings.
Yup.
Pounding their sorry faces in
doesn't even count as a warm up!
Still, this is no
time to let your guard down.
You never know when
someone a lot stronger
than those guys is gonna pop up.
Whoa. Wait.
You're not getting scared,
are you, buddy?
Gonna cry?
Up yours! I'm not scared!
A swordsman is never
afraid of the dark!
We'll see, when
I knock your lights out!
Come on! You wanna
piece of me?
[MALE VOICE] Wait!
Stop! Hold on a minute!
[heavy breathing]
I saw you fight those zombies.
All of you have such
unbelievable strength!
There's something I'd
like to talk to you about.
Would you please listen?
Old man with serious injuries!
Idiot! We told you!
They're zombies!
Uh. Actually, he's
right on the money.
That's too confusing!
Can't you just
be a zombie? Jeez!
Alright. So what did
you want to tell us?
[SPOIL] There's an evil man
who must be brought down!
And I think you youngsters
are strong enough to do it!
He's left a trail
of victims in his wake.
If you defeat him,
they'll all be rescued!
If you'd help me get my shadow
back, I'd be ever so grateful!
Your shadow?
Hold on, did we
just find another guy
who had his shadow taken away?
Lemme take a look.
It's true! See?
He really doesn't have a shadow!
He's just like Brook!
Well damn. That sucks.
So who did that to you?
Is he here?
Somewhere on this island?
Mor... Moria.
His name is Moria.
And he's terrifying.
Moria?
You don't mean--
[ROBIN] Gecko Moria,
by any chance?
[SPOIL] That's right.
Yes. That's him.
[LUFFY] Robin,
do you know this guy?
[ROBIN] Yes, but only by name.
And if I remember correctly,
his former bounty was even
higher than yours, Luffy.
[SANJI] Wait. "Former"?
So that means--
[ROBIN] Yes.
Gecko Moria is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
[CREW] He is?
Are you sure? Really?
Yes. Gecko Moria is a
man of many mysteries.
But, what's a big shot like
that doing in a
dump hole like this?
[SPOIL] I'm not sure, exactly.
What I can tell you is that
he's left behind many victims,
most of which are wandering
around lost in this very forest.
[ZORO] Just how many is "many"?
[SPOIL] Who knows?
The fact that you were
all invited here as well
means that Moria is
out to get you, too!
No doubt about it!
Invited? We weren't--
I see. Huh.
[sobs]
We hide in this dark forest,
scared of zombies and
all the other creatures here.
We can't head out to sea
because we'll be
exposed to the sun!
With this body
weakened the way it is,
it's hard to find the
will to keep on living.
Once.
Just once before I die,
I want to walk under the sun!
To feel its warmth on my skin!
Just one more time!
Bwaahahahahah!
That's awful! How touching!
You've been through so much!
Such a gut wrenching story!
But I'm not crying, got it?
Jerk! You won't make me cry!
Oh, come on, you big crybaby.
You're way too compassionate
about this kind of stuff.
Enough of this!
Hey, creepy grandpa!
Only ladies get to persuade
people with their tears!
Show a little backbone, will ya?
[thinknig] Oh, boy.
Well, you're in luck.
We're actually looking for
a guy that steals shadows,
and I'm pretty
sure he's the one.
If he's coming after us, then
that just makes things easier.
I'm gonna kick his ass,
and if that saves you while
we're at it, it's fine by me.
Okay?
Oh! That's very kind of you!
Thank you! Thank you!
You've given me new hope!
[VICTIM 343A]
We can't thank you enough!
[VICTIM 343B]
We're counting on you!
[VICTIM 343C] Yeah!
Tear Moria a new one!
What the hell?
The other victims, huh?
It's not polite to eavesdrop!
[RANDOM VICTIM 343A] Oh!
Sorry about that, Mister
Freaky Curly Eyebrows Guy!
[SANJI] That's a
crappy way to apologize!
[LUFFY chuckles]
Oh. What the hell?
Gaaaaah!
You three?
Why are you here?
Hey. That guy was--
Well, I could have sworn
it was Brook back there!
Yeah, I know!
But he wasn't a skeleton.
He had skin. Like a mummy!
[USOPP] He had wooden clogs...
Hey! Listen to me
when I talk to you!
Then maybe.
You fools!
He found us!
Indeed! Now.
What did you see?
Didn't I tell you never to
peek into my research room?
We didn't see anything!
Right! Nothing! We swear!
Uh-huh. I didn't
see anything at all!
Really?
Really! It's the honest truth!
We certainly didn't see--
that zombie you were making!
Dumbass!
Alright, fine then.
[HOGBACK] I'm sure
you've figured out some
of my secrets by now,
but you're too late.
In but a few minutes,
the Night Hunt will begin!
The Night Hunt?
[HOGBACK] Woe unto
those foolish enough
to wander this
island after dark.
No intruder shall
survive the Night Hunt!
[ABSALOM] You can't properly
start the Night Hunt
if you're still buried,
now can you?
[ABSALOM] What are you doing?
You can't hurt! There's no pain!
It's all in your imagination!
You guys are all dead! Get it?
Oh, yeah.
[ABSALOM] Now, rise!
Zombie Soldiers!
[ABSALOM] No matter
how many times you fall,
you get back up
and attack again!
That's what makes a
zombie so terrifying!
[ZOMBIES] Yeah, we know.
[ABSALOM] Don't be like that!
Stop slacking off!
Get a grip on
yourselves, zombies!
Now which one of you
wants to tell me who I am?
I know! The Leader!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 343B ]
Our glorious Leader! Absalom!
[ZOMBIES] Leader! Leader!
Leader! Leader! Leader! Leader!
Who likes to peek at girls!
Leader! Pervert!
Pervert! Pervert!
Shut up!
Horo horo horo horo horo!
[KUMACY]
Oooo!
[KUMACY] Oo! Oo! Welcome back,
Mistress Perona!
How are you?
[PERONA] Shut up, Kumacy!
Ugh! Your voice is so deep!
It's gross! Just can it okay?
[KUMACY] My apologies.
[PERONA] Either be
cute or get lost!
I won't have ugly
things working for me!
Horo horo horo horo.
[NIN] Hurry! Hurry up!
[GYORO] It's starting!
It's starting!
[BAO] Time for the Night Hunt!
[NIN] Twelve O'Clock Midnight!
Moria! Master!
Master Moria!
It's time to get up, Master!
[snoring]
Nin! Do it!
[NIN] Right! Here goes!
[ALL THREE] Master Moria!
[MORIA] I was
having a bad dream!
[NIN] Really? Great!
Aren't those the best, Master?
[GYORO]
Master Moria has been sleeping
since the Night Hunt
four days ago.
Even so, that hasn't stopped us!
Knowing that you'd be
hungry when you awoke,
we have prepared
a very special meal
that's sure to
appease your appetite.
And they're a tough bunch!
Amazing fighters, too!
They're the pirates that brought
down the island of Enies Lobby.
Known as
"The Straw Hat Pirates!"
Aren't you pleased? Master!
Imagine what you
could do with them!
Kushishishi!
Is that rain?
Man, that sure came
from out of nowhere.
[FRANKY]
It's really coming down, too.
Should we run for the mansion?
[LUFFY] Hang on a sec.
Huh?
I see something really
big by the mansion.
Over there. It looks
like some kind of mark.
[FRANKY] A mark?
The rain's clearing the fog.
I see it. Is that a flag?
No. I'm pretty
sure that's a sail.
[LUFFY] What?
Yes, you're right.
Hey! Why're you
still following us?
Right about what?
Like he said.
What you see is a sail
of gigantic proportion.
It's so large that seeing
the entire thing at
once is quite difficult.
You see, Thriller Bark is not
the island it appears to be.
Believe it or not, it's actually
the world's largest pirate ship!
This whole island
is a pirate ship?
The largest one in the world?
Awesome!
I get it.
So "Thriller Bark," huh?
A bark is a type of sailing ship
with three or more masts.
But it's hard to believe
this entire island
is some sort of boat.
[SPOIL] The back of
the mansion is where
you'll find the main mast.
It's also the home
of Gecko Moria.
Now! Zombie Soldiers!
The Zombie Generals
will lead the attack.
Let's finish off those pirates!
The rest of you
will find ways to corner
and overtake those among
them that fear the undead.
Show them no mercy.
Together, we will crush them.
Now go! Make me proud!
[PERONA] There's the bell!
The moment has arrived.
It's time to get serious.
Horo horo horo horo.
If those pirates think they
can escape this place alive,
they're gravely mistaken.
Are the preparations
complete, my zombies?
[cheering]
[MORIA] In this dark realm,
one of ghosts, and ghouls.
This place we
call Thriller Bark.
They are going to
see nothing short
of the nightmare to
end all nightmares!
Well, here we go.
To the Ghost Mansion!
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfasfas!
It finally begins!
Are you ready, Absalom!
[ABSALOM] Of course I am,
who do you think's in charge?
[HOGBACK] Me!
[ABSALOM] Go wild,
Zombie Generals!
[HOGBACK] Uh, yes.
Zombie Generals. Go wild.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Feast of the Zombie Song!
The Night Hunt's Bell
is the Sound of Darkness!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!