Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
[MORIA] You say you're
gonna kick my ass?
[LUFFY] Yep.
That's right.
[MORIA] Well. I say that,
but with your power.
I doubt you can even
lay a finger on me.
[MORIA]
Come, Brick Bat.
[LUFFY]
...Gatling!
[LUFFY] Damn! These things
keep blocking me!
How am I
supposed to punch him?
Haaaa...
[LUFFY yelling]
[PERONA] Stop running!
[USOPP] You stop running!
[KUMACY growling]
Get rid of that
guy already, Kumacy!
[KUMACY] I won't let you lay
a finger on Mistress Perona!
For such a fluffy
stuffed animal
that thing really packs
a punch, doesn't it?
He can't unzip
his own zipper,
but he sure is good
at running and wrecking stuff.
[KUMACY] Now I'm angry.
[KUMACY growls]
[SANJI] And skip, and skip,
and skip, and skip.
Why, is that a Nami I see?
Get your hands off her!
[SANJI] Sorry to
keep you waiting.
Your knight has arrived.
I'm running very
low on patience.
I can't waste my time fighting
with some weakling like--
[ABSALOM grunts]
[SANJI] And you say I talk
too much, you creeper!
Master Absalom!
Veau Shot!
[SANJI] You say you're
running low on patience?
Well, I'm way
beyond that, buddy.
I'm so pissed off,
I'm about to explode!
[SANJI] And this is isn't
just about Nami, either.
Oh no. There's an issue.
A little something,
between the two of us.
That goes back a long way.
[LUFFY]
"A Clear-Clear History?
Sanji's Stolen Dream."
[ABSALOM panting]
[ZOMBIES gasp]
[ZOMBIE 358B ]
He knocked him flat.
[SANJI growls]
[ABSALOM grunting]
Alright, let's talk about this.
You said there's an issue?
Damn straight.
For starters. You're a thief.
You stole Nami,
and you stole my dream.
[ABSALOM wheezing]
His dream?
[ABSALOM] I don't know
what you're talking about.
You've got me confused
with someone else.
We've never even met before.
But... if you want
to pick a fight with me.
We'll start with
my hands of the dead!
C'mon! I'll blow you away!
The guns. Take 'em off.
Huh?
[SANJI] Don't play dumb.
Take off those bazookas you've
got strapped to your arms.
[ABSALOM gasps]
[SANJI] I'll only
say this once.
If Nami gets
injured in your crossfire,
by the time
I'm done with you,
you'll be twice as dead
as those zombies of yours.
Impossible. How
could he have known?
I tried asking you nicely.
Now take those
damn things off!
What the...? Bazookas?
Where did those
even come from?
[ABSALOM growls]
I figured it was
something like that.
A guy with your power's only got
so many tricks up his sleeve.
I know you can turn invisible,
and I know you can turn anything
you touch invisible, too.
But that's the
extent of your powers.
Against me, your tactics
are as transparent as you are.
Because I know everything
about the Clear-Clear Fruit!
Who the hell are you?
Who told you all that?
This guy.
Do you think he and Absalom
have got some kind of history?
That's the only thing
that makes any sense.
He knows so much
about his powers.
And yet he has no
recollection of this grudge.
[SANJI] I scoured the
Devil Fruit Encyclopedia
when I was a kid. I didn't
even believe half of it.
And most of the fruits'
abilities didn't sound like
they were worth
the curse anyway.
Except for one.
There was one fruit
that spoke to my very soul.
And I made the decision.
If I ever had the luck
of finding that fruit.
Then I would embrace the
curse and swallow it whole,
no matter what the cost!
But of course.
There's only one of each
Devil Fruit in the entire world.
[ABSALOM growls]
[SANJI] So I knew
that if I ever met
the power holder
with that ability.
My dream would be vanquished.
See what you've done?
The only thing I wanted
was to experience
invisibility for myself!
But you just had to go
and find the
Clear-Clear Fruit first!
You took its powers and you
stole my dream along with it!
That's why he's mad?
My dream, I saw it so clearly.
I could do so
much good with it.
Use it to protect...
...nude girls!
No, I mean, I could
help all mankind and...
...nude girls!
No, I had this beautiful
vision of the future and...
...nude girls!
He just wants to
peek at naked girls!
He's a complete pervert!
Shut up!
After a lifetime of
fantasizing about that fruit,
I know how much you
can peep--no, wait, I mean,
could help humanity with it!
Understand?
[SANJI growls]
Not only did you kidnap
Nami and endanger her life,
but you've squandered
all of the good
I could've done for this world!
Nude girls!--no, I meant wrath,
prepare to suffer my wrath!
So that's the issue here?
You're mad I ate the Clear-Clear
Fruit before you got to find it?
Y'know, That's the most petty
damn thing I've ever heard!
That's the word. Petty.
[ABSALOM] You are
a jealous pervert!
[SANJI] You have no right
to call me that!
It takes one to know one!
You're right!
They're the same!
The exact same!
[ABSALOM] I'm done
listening to this nonsense!
You're taking out your
anger on the wrong guy,
and now I'm gonna give it back.
[ABSALOM growls]
I don't just have
the jaw of a lion.
I've got elephant's skin.
And 600 pounds of muscle
from bears and gorillas!
Dr. Hogback built this body
from the most savage
beasts you could imagine.
It's a savage patchwork
masterpiece of ferocity.
A masterpiece!
The Clear-Clear Fruit
you crave so much?
It's just a bonus.
Yet another weapon.
It's just a tool to
enhance my strength.
Understand?
[SANJI] So what?
You still peeped!
He's got a pretty
good point there!
[thinking] No mere human
could keep kicking me like this.
My body would shatter
the bones in his legs.
But he keeps on attacking me
like I'm a bag of feathers.
Hmph! But still,
the last laugh will be mine.
[ABSALOM] You wanted this
Devil Fruit power of mine,
and you want to steal
my future bride from me.
But face the facts,
they're both mine!
The next thing I'm taking
from you is your life!
[USOPP] Back there.
once he grabbed Nami,
she disappeared too and we
weren't able to chase after him.
[SANJI] So you're
comin' after Nami, huh?
Well you're not getting her!
[ABSALOM growls]
[ABSALOM] What are
you even looking for?
I'm invisible, moron,
but you can still feel my power.
The power of the jungle!
[ABSALOM] Oh, really?
You think you can save her
by sacrificing yourself?
[ABSALOM chuckles]
Well that's fine with me.
Let's see how it works out
for you! Mystery Man Handler!
Mystery Man Kicker!
[ABSALOM] Put her down gently
now, before you drop dead!
[SANJI] You evil bastard!
[SANJI grimacing]
[SANJI] I'm so sorry, Nami.
[ABSALOM laughing]
[ABSALOM] You dropped her!
Guess you don't care so
much about her after all!
[SANJI grimaces and coughs]
[SANJI] Forgive me, Nami.
You look so beautiful.
I don't wanna ruin your
white dress with blood.
[SANJI]
That damn coward,
using his cheap powers
to hide from me.
[SANJI] At least now I know
the reality behind my dream.
[SANJI panting and gasping]
[SANJI] I'm glad.
Glad I didn't find that
damned Devil Fruit after all.
Oh...!
[SANJI] I can peep
fine the way I am!
He's gonna peep after all!
[SANJI pants and coughs]
[ABSALOM growls while walking]
[ABSALOM] Let go of
me, dammit! Let go!
[SANJI] I've got
you now, you bastard.
With all the different animals
you've got stitched into you,
you're gonna make one
damn tasty casserole.
[ABSALOM]
I said let go of my leg!
Don't get cocky with me!
[SANJI] Extra Hache!
Absalom!
Nude Girls. No.
You wanted to get married?
I now pronounce
you man and wall.
[LUFFY] Get away from me!
[LUFFY] Stop it!
Kushishi!
Don't worry, kid.
They don't actually drink blood.
To think. You
defeating me. Ridiculous.
[LUFFY] That's enough!
Rookie pirates. So cocky.
You fools are just
setting yourselves up
for your own humiliation.
Damn. Now Gum-Gum...
Brick Bat. Go!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Kushishishishi!
Bastard! You've really
pissed me off! Gum-Gum...
He jumped!
Is he trying to escape?
What a coward!
...Stamp!
Ahhh! You brat!
What a cheap shot!
Ha! Your ass just got kicked!
How 'bout that?
[LUFFY laughs]
[PERONA running and panting]
[USOPP running and panting]
[KUMACY running and panting]
He won't stop chasing me!
If I could just figure out
how to finish him off,
I could get rid of
all the other pirates!
Damn that long-nosed jerk!
He won't stop chasing me!
If I could just figure out
how to finish him off,
I could get rid of
that snotty ghost girl!
Damn that zombie bear!
[KUMACY] Stop running!
Quit chasing me!
And quit running, ghost girl!
Auugh! Quit chasing me!
Hurry up and take care
of him already, Kumacy!
[KUMACY] Come back here!
I'm right behind
you, ghost girl!
Aaaa! No!
[KUMACY]
Quit harassing my mistress!
[KUMACY] You're scaring her!
Stop it! Go away!
[KUMACY] I'm coming, Mistress!
[USOPP] Fingers crossed!
[USOPP] Poke, poke,
poke, poke, poke
What kind of sick monster would
make such a violent teddy bear?
[KUMACY] Quit running from me!
[USOPP] Oh, yeah, I forgot.
C'mon. Special Attack.
Flame Ball!
[USOPP] It worked, it worked!
You're just like
the other zombies after all!
[USOPP] Now let's
add a dash of oil.
For a little entrée
that I like to call
Don't-Cross-This-Line technique!
[KUMACY] What the...?
[USOPP] Come and get me now,
you stupid bear!
I'm brilliant! A total genius!
And now that you're
out of the equation.
Your precious mistress
kooky laughter
ghost girl is going down!
Nobody messes with the king.
Alright then, it's time to
teach that ghost girl a lesson.
Yep, a lesson in complete and
total defeat. Eh, what the..?
She was right here.
[PERONA] Looking for me?
Right this way. Horo horo horo!
[USOPP] Is this
some kinda trick?
Where is she?
Did she go outside?
No, that can't be right.
This tower's so high,
she'd have to be... Aaaaah!
[PERONA]
Horo horo horo horo!
What? How the hell are
you floating like that?
I thought your power
was to control ghosts?
Okay. Before we
go any further.
I should ask.
What is your power?
That's my little secret.
No one messes
with the princess.
Oh, and by the way.
I know how to beat you now.
And when I'm through with you.
Your friends are next.
They won't have a
chance in the world!
[NEGAtIVE GHOSTS]
Horo horo horo horo!
Oh, come on!
What the hell?
And everything
was going so good!
[PERONA] Is something wrong?
Not a single one
of your attacks hit me.
[USOPP] Hold on, here!
Which attacks can I use?
I've got sniping,
negativity, bluffing,
my 8,000 followers,
aw man, I'm screwed!
Why aren't any of
my attacks working on her?
What do I do? What do I do?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Save Me, Hero! My Enemy
is the Immortal Princess."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!