[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
The Whitebeard Pirates have
successfully
pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines
still block the path to Ace.
The battle is heating up!
After Luffy narrowly avoids
a deadly encounter with Mihawk,
a battalion of human weapons
known as Pacifistas appear.
[PIRATE AA]
Look at the bay head!
There's something out there!
[PIRATE BB]
What... What the hell are they?
Of course.
I wondered when I'd get
a glimpse of the
Government's human weapons.
[IVANKOV]
Huh? Huh? Huh?
I'm confused.
[LUFFY] "The Extermination
Strategy in Action!
The Power of Pacifistas!"
They all look just
like the Warlord, Kuma!
No way. It's gotta be
some kind of an illusion.
Well, this just got weird.
I think I know those guys--
they went on a rampage
here a while back!
[MAN B] It's like having
an army of Warlords!
But there weren't that
many when they attacked us!
[DRAKE roaring]
Head office! Reporting in!
You gotta hear this!
Hello? Anyone?
So this one's gotta be
the real Kuma, right?
I thought this
was just some rumor,
but I've heard word that
Dr. Vegapunk has been working on
some kind of human weapon,
and he's been shipping
out the prototypes
to backup the Navy.
This could be them.
[PIRATE AA] Well, That looks
like a "human weapon"
if I've ever seen one.
[PIRATE BB]
Sure, but why are they all Kuma?
Hey, Uncle!
This isn't looking like
the plan we talked about!
I thought the pirates were
supposed to be rounded up
inside the bay, so we could pick
'em off like fish in a barrel.
Why're they scattered
all over the place?
That big guy with the axe--
Can you make out
what he's saying?
I believe I've
deciphered the Navy's plan.
They leaked the intel about
the decision to
expedite Ace's execution,
knowing that it would send us
into a frenzy to save him.
After that, all they had to do
was slowly back up their forces
to fully lure us
pirates into the bay.
And then they block
off the bay head with
their human weapons
to close the trap. Checkmate.
Now it all makes sense.
That's why Whitebeard ordered us
to sink those Navy ships
instead of advancing.
He saw through their plan.
If it weren't for him,
we would've been trapped.
Yeah.
We can still attack
from the front and the rear,
even if they're not
closed in the bay!
Stick to the plan and take
down the allied forces first.
Eliminate any
pirate that's trying
to stray from the
enclosure to advance.
And there you go.
Got it. And if our ships
get caught in the crossfire?
Let's try to keep it
to a minimum, okay?
Heh. So, that's the plan, huh?
[SENTOMARU]
Then, time to work!
Line up as many
Kumas as you want!
We'll knock 'em down!
[PIRATE J yelling]
[laughs]
[gasps]
[PIRATE J sputtering]
[PIRATE J]
No! No, please!
[PIRATE J yells]
[PIRATES gasping]
Now, fire, Pacifistas!
Th-They vaporized them!
[PIRATES gasping]
Sick bastards are even willing
to sacrifice their own men.
[WHITEBEARD]
Hmm...
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
Don't lose faith! March on!
Charge the plaza
with all of your might!
[PIRATE K grunts]
[PIRATES, MARINES yelling]
[MARINES screaming]
[MARCO] The only
retreat I know is death.
But I'll rescue Ace before they
can send me down that road.
Everyone! Get off the ship, now!
Destroy those
mechanical monsters!
[DOMA PIRATES]
Yeah!
[MCGUY]
Hmm.
Have at you.
[MCGUY]
I shall not falter!
[DOMA PIRATES shouting]
All units get off the ice
and defend the front line, now!
Do whatever it takes to ensure
the pirates don't
reach the plaza!
Go! Fall back!
[MARINES grunting]
Hurry!
[VISTA] It's quite
the unexpected pleasure
to cross blades with the
world's greatest swordsman.
Aren't I a lucky guy?
[MIHAWK] Your swordsmanship
is of no small renown, either.
We were certain to cross paths.
Now show me your skill.
I'm happy to give you a peek.
Rose Rondo!
[MIHAWK gasps]
What flowers would
you like on your grave?
Onward! Drive them in!
Hell, no! Now, suck on this!
Heh, hah. How's that feel?
[PIRATE L yelps]
[PIRATES screaming]
There's no way those things
are made of flesh and bone.
Well, they're
obviously not human.
Then what are they?
[MAN C gasps]
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN D] Hey,
what happened to the screen?
[SENGOKU] Struggle
all you want, Whitebeard.
We still have the upper hand.
Ready to crush you.
[SENGOKU] As soon as every
video feed has been cut,
activate the encircling walls.
And once that's set, we will
immediately execute Ace
and round up all of
our remaining enemies.
Yes, sir!
[panting]
[LUFFY]
Move it!
[MARINE CC gasps, yelps]
[MARINES grunting]
They're about to kill Ace.
I better hurry!
[gasps]
Sorry, back to square one.
[LUFFY grunting]
Luffy, no!
[LUFFY grunts]
[panting]
Jimbei.
[LUFFY] The admiral's
gettin' in on the fight.
Dammit.
Yet we must press on,
regardless!
We knew we would face
insurmountable odds
and undefeatable foes.
Them sending out their best
only means we're too close
for their comfort!
[LUFFY grunts]
Time to die, son of Dragon.
[MARINE C yelps]
Hey, Ace's brother,
you're not runnin'
outta steam, are ya?
[LUFFY, JIMBEI gasp]
[JIMBEI]
Whitebeard's commanders!
We won't find any
better backup than that!
You can't let one man halt
your advance. Now, follow us!
Yeah! Let's take 'im!
[IZO] The Navy's pullin' back,
so now's our chance!
We're breakin' through
these bastards!
Ooh. Lookee here.
It's a real fight.
[MORIA laughing]
[MORIA] Well, if it isn't
10th Division Commander Curiel!
Look at that angry glower.
Do you really wanna die
with such a sour face?
You do realize you'll be buried
in this bay if you stay here?
First, Ace will die,
and then your cronies will
be trapped and wiped out.
I honestly couldn't care less
about who's gonna win this war.
But watching Whitebeard die?
That's fun!
Pops and Ace won't die--
not while I'm around!
Shall we put this
match on hold, Vista?
Much as I hate to, we do have
other matters to worry about.
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATES yelling]
We've gotta back down.
So, let's go, Smoker!
Didn't you hear the orders?
Yeah... I heard 'em.
[SMOKER]
Next time, Straw Hat!
Luffy, you can do it.
Stay strong.
[SENGOKU growls]
Why the hell hasn't
the video feed been cut?
[MARINE D] Sorry, sir!
It'll just be another minute!
Hey! Have you found it?
[MARINE FF]
Uh, no!
We're still searching,
but it's just gone missing!
[PRISONER AA]
We're all set!
[PRISONER BB] Hey, Gaffer,
you're blockin' the shot.
It seems like they've cut all
the camera feeds except for one.
But what's with this stupid
message--just show us already!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL humming]
[PRISONER CC]
The camera's good to go.
[PRISONER C]
Okay then. We're going live...
...in five, four,
three, two, one. Action!
Hey! It came back on!
[PRISONER A]
So... Um. Ahem.
Uh, sorry. We apologize
for keeping you waiting.
Wait, who is that talking?
[PRISONER A] Uhh.
We're live here at Marineford,
surrounded by the dead bodies
of pirates and marines.
They're doing a commentary?
[gasps]
Hey! What's going on down there?
What is this feed?
[PRISONER A] Wait...
Is that who I think it is?
Oh! It is!
I can't believe it's him!
He's been laying low
for all these years, but
he was a member
of the legendary crew
that served under Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates!
[CROWD]
Huh?
Who is it?
[PRISONER A] Can it really
be the renowned pirate,
Captain Buggy?
[BUGGY]
Huh?
I'm sorry,
did someone say my name?
Huh?
[CROWD]
Huh...?
It is classified information,
but I admit it--
I am the legendary pirate...
[PRISONER A whispering] Hey!
Hold it, Captain Buggy! Stop!
You've got a nosebleed!
[BUGGY grunts]
[BUGGY yelling]
Cut now! Stand by!
Get a hankie, dammit!
[SENGOKU]
What the hell is happening here?
How many times have
I ordered you fools
to cut the stupid video?
We can't move with
the world watching!
I understand, sir!
But I'm afraid that the escaped
prisoners have somehow managed
to steal one of the video
transponder snails from us!
What?! How did you
let this happen?
[PRISONER DD]
Make-up!
[PRISONER B]
Ready to roll!
All right, guys,
mark it! Take two!
In three, two, one, and...
[PRISONER A]
Oh! Is that who I think it is?
The legendary crewmember
of Gold Roger and
the sworn brother of Shanks,
of the Four Emperors?
Could it really be the
mythical pirate, Captain Buggy?
Did someone say my name?
Stop those idiots
right this second!
[PRISONERS screaming]
[PRISONER A]
Whoa! That was close!
[PRISONER EE]
They found us, run for it!
[PRISONER A] I just saw
you get sliced in half by
the infamous "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk,
but there's not even
a scratch on you!
[BUGGY]
Who, me?
That's right! I'm Buggy!
The living legend!
[MAN AA] Blow them away!
I want them dead!
[MAN BB]
Cut back to the war, dammit!
[MAN CC] Why are we
getting video of this moron?
[MAN DD] Go back to Ace,
we're gonna miss the execution!
[MAN EE] I wanna see that
army of Bartholomew Kumas!
[PIRATES screaming]
They're driving
us into a corner!
[DOMA]
Stand tall, men!
We can't stop now! Not until
we know that Ace is safe!
Let's go!
[DOMA PIRATES yelling]
[WHITEBEARD]
Hmm...
Hey, Pops.
[WHITEBEARD]
Hm?
Oh, Squard.
Good to see you're alive.
[SQUARD]
Yeah, barely.
[WHITEBEARD] Is that so? I was
trying to reach you earlier.
How're things lookin'
at the bay head now?
I'm sorry to say, but your
allies were beaten pretty badly.
As for me, I only managed to get
out of there through sheer luck.
[WHITEBEARD] Sengoku is
one merciless bastard.
He's pulling out every
dirty trick he can think of.
Judging by your shift in tactic,
I'm guessing you
picked up on the Navy's plan.
[WHITEBEARD]
I've known Sengoku
and what he's capable
of for a long time.
I see.
[WHITEBEARD]
Little does he know,
it works in our favor for them
to attack us from the rear.
I'm joining the fight.
Our only chance is
to keep pushing forward.
[SQUARD]
I couldn't agree more.
Huh?
What's Squard doing up there?
You have 43 allied captains
willing to die for you.
We're all in your debt,
for now and for always.
We consider it a privilege
to risk our lives
for you and your crew.
[yells]
And I'm grateful,
but this fight is--
Yes, I know. This fight is
to save a member of your family.
The great pirate
Whitebeard is a man
who would do anything
for his family.
And your loyalty
inspires loyalty.
That's why everyone
followed you to this hell.
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
I do wish things were different.
[SQUARD]
But at the end of the day...
[SQUARD] ...I'm not
a part of your family.
[explosion]
[WHITEBEARD gasps]
[NARRATOR] After witnessing
Squard's betrayal
against Whitebeard, ripples of
distrust and uncertainty
spread within his alliance.
And yet Whitebeard's faith
will not be shattered.
And it soon becomes clear
that his allies are falling
into a clever setup,
launched by the Navy.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Akainu's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!