[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of
pirates go to battle
across the seas in search
of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
set sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer
numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind
of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Encouraged
by Dark King Rayleigh,
Luffy overcame his sorrow
and returned to the site
of his brother's death.
While there, he both
paid respects
and delivered a secret
message to his crew.
One by one, they received it
through the newspaper.
Normally, Luffy wouldn't
do something like this.
There's gotta be a catch here.
[CHOPPER]
I got it, Luffy! Don't worry!
A change of plans, then!
Yeah, okay, okay!
So that's it. Very well, then.
Roger that, Captain!
Yes, Luffy! Yes!
[crying]
[NAMI]
But honestly, Luffy.
How 'bout how I feel, huh?
You're so selfish!
I gotcha, boss.
Ah-hah. How very clever of you!
No need to worry, Luffy.
[STRAW HATS] See you at
Sabaody in two years!
[LUFFY]
"Luffy's Training Begins!
To the Place We Promised
in Two Years!"
[JIMBEI]
There he is.
Hey, Jimbei! Thank
you for everything!
No, Luffy.
Please, it is I who
should be thanking you!
When we met at Impel
Down, I begged you.
I said I would put my life
on the line for Ace.
And yet, your brother died,
while I still live.
Please forgive me!
You did all you could've done.
Don't beat yourself up.
If it weren't for your help,
I probably wouldn't have made it
into Marineford
in the first place.
You can be proud.
You're right as always.
And who can say,
one day there may still
be something I can do
to help you on your journey.
Until then, see you on
Fishman Island in two years!
Be sure to bring your
entire crew along.
I look forward to
meeting everyone!
[LUFFY]
You got it!
Take care, Jimbei!
[HANCOCK] Luffy, I'm so
glad that you're back
to your old self.
A twinkle in your eye,
that smile--
charming, confident,
and carefree!
Just seeing your face has
put my heart aflutter!
I'm weak in the knees!
My goodness, I could almost die!
I'm dizzy.
Hey, Hancock, you okay?
[gasps]
[clears throat]
Yes. Yes, of course I am.
Pardon my manners, but could
you take us to the island now?
I'd like to begin Luffy's
training as soon as possible.
[HANCOCK]
Y-Yes, certainly!
Kuja! Set sail for Ruskaina!
[AMAZONS]
Aye-aye, Snake Princess!
[RAYLEIGH]
This island will be perfect.
It has 48 seasons a year,
so you'll constantly have to
adapt to the harsh conditions.
[LUFFY]
Whoa. Sounds neat!
[LUFFY chuckles]
Oh, Luffy?
While you're here,
I'll be sure to bring you
the most delicious food from
Amazon Lily every day.
Doesn't that sound nice?
Yeah! Thanks, Hancock! You rock!
Let's see, could
you start off with
that specialty
gorgon-somethin' or other?
That stuff's really good!
Wh-Why, yes, of course!
[AMAZONS]
Yay! That's our princess!
I'll bring anything you desire.
And as much of it as you want!
Oh, my.
I do believe he's uttered my
name at least ten times now.
[sighs]
That must mean we're engaged!
[NYON]
No, it doesn't!
And didn't you say
a little while ago
that you were married?
Foolish girl doesn't even know
the proper order of things.
No, Hancock. Sorry, but I just
can't have you spoiling him.
His sole purpose
here is to train.
He can't let distractions
get in the way.
[HANCOCK]
What?
Huh?
You have got some
nerve, old man!
Luffy has the right to
decide that! You got it?
And be careful how you respond.
I can turn you to stone!
There are plenty of
things to eat here.
Luffy needs to hunt for himself.
That's part of the training.
[NYON] You'll ruin his
nyose, Snake Princess!
If he can't get by with
roughing it for a while,
then maybe he
shouldn't be a pirate.
This is all for Luffy's benefit!
Luffy. Then, this will
help him become stronger?
Yes, it will.
If this is all for Luffy...
...I'll be patient!
[grumbles]
[HANCOCK] But, Rayleigh, this
island is truly dangerous!
If anything should
happen to him--
[RAYLEIGH] That's why it's
an ideal place to train him.
If you're that worried,
make a wish on a star.
Are you ready, Luffy?
Sure am!
[chuckling]
Goodbye, Luffy! It's been fun!
Don't get killed, okay?!
Bye!
[HANCOCK]
Luffy, take care of yourself.
[LUFFY laughing]
[RAYLEIGH]
You'd better remember this tree.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[RAYLEIGH] Even the most savage
beasts stay away from it.
It's the only safe
area on this island.
[LUFFY]
I don't think I'll forget it.
It's pretty funny lookin'.
[LUFFY laughs]
And another thing to note.
You may have guessed,
but we're the only humans
on the entire island.
Behold the vast wilderness.
Supposedly there was a country
here a long time ago.
But as you can see, the humans
lost the struggle for survival.
The land is rough and
nature relentless.
[gasps]
[laughs]
This place smells
like adventure!
[LUFFY laughing]
[creatures roaring]
The island is crawling
with vicious creatures.
Far too many to be counted.
Now, by my estimation,
there's about 500 animals
you don't stand a
chance of defeating yet.
Unless you become stronger,
you might even get
killed in your sleep.
How do you know so much
about this place?
Did you used to live here?
Yes, as you will.
And you'll obtain the
same power I did then.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[RAYLEIGH]
The power known as Haki.
Haki?
[MAMMOTH A roars]
Hey, watch out! There's a...
a huge thing behind you!
What are you doing?
Don't just stand there!
[RAYLEIGH]
Listen to me, Luffy.
Believe it or not,
Haki is a latent power
that everyone has
within themselves.
Wow. I think it's
a giant elephant!
Like, five times
the normal size!
[RAYLEIGH] Observation,
fighting spirit, intimidation.
Haki is really no different
from any combative instincts
normal humans have.
[RAYLEIGH] However,
most of them live their lives
without tapping into
their true potential,
because they don't have a
teacher like you do now.
You mustn't have any self-doubt.
Only then will you
become stronger.
[roars]
Run away!
Time for... Second Gear!
Jet Pistol!
[gasps]
Damn it. This guy's no joke!
He's super fast for
as big as he is!
[yells]
[roars]
Now watch very carefully.
There are two prominent types
of Haki used in battle.
[LUFFY]
Get outta there!
[RAYLEIGH]
Don't worry.
The elephant will try to
hit me with its trunk
coming in from the right side.
[gasps]
First is the power to
feel the presence
of others more strongly.
This is known as
Observation Haki.
No way.
[RAYLEIGH]
If you enhance this power,
you can even tell where
unseen enemies are located.
You can determine
how many there are,
and predict what their
next moves will be.
Really?
That left kick won't work.
[LUFFY gasps]
Mantra.
On Skypiea, it has
a different name.
There it's called Mantra.
Huh?
Uh! Damn it!
[RAYLEIGH]
Next, the Armament Haki.
Think of it as covering
yourself in invisible armor.
[MAMMOTH A roaring]
Rayleigh, no!
[chuckles]
That move, I've seen it before.
Ashigara Dokkoi... Shove!
[MAMMOTH A groaning]
[RAYLEIGH]
Armor that's hard enough
can even be used as a weapon.
Huh?
Hey!
I shouldn't be able to feel
that! I'm made outta rubber!
Consider it another benefit of
knowing how to use this Haki.
Unless they have a
specific weak point,
those with Devil Fruit
powers are hard to hit.
Armament Haki provides the only
other effective countermeasure
against such enemies.
[gasps]
Take those with
Logia-type Devil Fruits.
Their body composition makes
them seem impossible to touch.
But Armament Haki has
the power to strike them.
Ah. So that's how you
were able to hit Kizaru.
Interesting!
With that kinda Haki,
I'd be able punch Smokey
or Aokiji or anybody!
[RAYLEIGH] You can also transfer
Armament Haki to a weapon.
Have you ever seen the
Kuja Pirates' arrows?
I have.
It was like they were
made out of steel.
Observation and Armament.
They're the main
two types of Haki.
However, there are some
people in this world
who can use another
type of Haki.
[roars]
[RAYLEIGH]
Watch closely.
[LUFFY gasps]
[gasps]
The power to intimidate your
enemies into submission.
This is Conqueror's Haki.
[RAYLEIGH] The most well-known
legends of the Grand Line,
they often have the
rare Conqueror's Haki
at their disposal.
However, although you can
control the Conqueror's Haki,
unlike the other types,
there's no way
to train yourself to use it.
The Conqueror's Haki embodies
the spirit of the owner himself.
Strengthen your spirit,
and you strengthen its power.
Hey! That's what you did
at the auction house.
Everybody just passed out!
Ah. So you already
know what it is.
Then again, that's
not very surprising.
You have the power as well.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Don't you dare!
Here's a tip, don't
use Conqueror's Haki
until you can handle it,
as in fully control it.
Or otherwise, you'll end up
overwhelming innocent people
who get caught in the action.
Huh? What's the matter?
Amazing!
No wonder you were
his first mate.
You can knock out
half your enemies
without even laying
a finger on 'em!
[laughs]
I guess I was tougher
than you thought!
Actually, wait.
I just realized, I've seen all
sorts of people use Haki.
There's Shanks, Grandpa,
Eneru, Aisa, and Hancock,
plus her sisters and
all the Kuja warriors!
This is true.
But still, learning how to
use Haki is no easy task.
Usually, we'd need a lot
more time to train right.
But thankfully,
you're qualified.
Here's how it'll work.
Start with the basics.
In two years' time, I'll teach
you how to use all three types,
even Conqueror's Haki.
Most users, tend to
focus on one type.
Or rather, they play
to their strengths,
if they don't have the talent
to master every single art.
That's fine for them, but
I think you'll want to aim
much higher than that.
And if you can
develop all three,
you'll have so much
more at your disposal.
[LUFFY]
Uh-huh. Sounds like fun!
[RAYLEIGH]
Well, then.
I'm now officially your trainer.
Don't think for a second
I'll go easy on you!
Yeah? Give me
everything you've got!
Huh.
[RAYLEIGH]
All right, let's begin.
[LUFFY]
Oh! Just one last thing.
[RAYLEIGH]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
If I remember right,
the old man said this tree
is the only safe place.
For two years, I'll
disappear from the world
and hang up my hat here.
[SABO]
Ace, Luffy, listen.
The three of us, we're
gonna leave this country.
We're gonna sail the seas,
and see the world.
And we're gonna have
lots of adventures.
We'll be pirates!
[chuckles]
[ACE] I'll be so tough that
all the other pirates
and all the Marines
will bow at my feet!
Everyone in the whole
world will know my name!
That's gonna be the legacy
I leave behind when I die!
[chuckles]
[LUFFY] Then I know
what I'm gonna be, too!
The King of the Pirates!
[BOTH]
Uh.
[laughing]
[LUFFY]
Oh, almost forgot.
The Vivre card.
[LUFFY]
Everybody.
Luffy.
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy.
Luffy!
Oh, hey, Luffy!
[STRAW HATS]
Luffy!
[laughs]
[RAYLEIGH]
C'mon, Luffy, hurry it up!
Let's get started!
[LUFFY]
Be right there!
'Kay, Old Man. Let's do it!
[RAYLEIGH]
Hm.
First off, don't
call me old man.
Call me "Sir Rayleigh."
Or how about
"Professor Rayleigh"?
Maybe "Master Rayleigh."
[LUFFY] Gotcha!
Thanks, Old Man Rayleigh!
[RAYLEIGH]
Ugh. Fine.
Hey, Zoro! And Usopp!
Sanji and Nami!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
And Ace and Sabo!
[LUFFY laughs]
I'm making you guys
another promise.
I'll get stronger no
matter what it takes!
[NARRATOR] Two years after
the War of the Best,
the Straw Crew finally
returns to Sabaody.
However, the archipelago
has changed
and with dangerous pirates
lurking around in droves,
their departure to the
New World may not go
as smoothly as they hoped.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Beginning of
the New Chapter!
The Straw Hats Reunited!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!