[LUFFY coughing]
[LUFFY]
Damn, you guys are strong.
C'mon! Could you at least
tell me why we're fighting?
[PAULIE] I think we're
the ones who deserve
an explanation here, not you.
Someone broke into
Iceberg's house last night
and shot him five times!
They were from your crew!
Iceberg was shot?
Thats news to me.
That can't be, we--
No way!
We didn't shoot Ice Pops...
That's just crazy!
Listen kid, you
might as well fess up.
I'm telling you,
we didn't do it!
[PAULIE]
Iceberg said it himself.
There were two people who broke
into his room and attacked him.
He may have been hurt
but that doesn't mean
he didn't get a
good look at them first.
One of them was a
big guy with a mask on.
The other was a tall
woman with black hair.
Iceberg told us
he recognized her
and the government confirmed
that she's a
member of your crew.
The Archaeologist, Nico Robin.
You're lying.
I won't ask you
why--maybe your crew
came to Water 7 on a
mission to kill Iceberg.
Or maybe you really did
want your ship repaired
and attacked him on a whim
after we turned you down.
I don't know how you
pirates think and I don't care.
Point is, you tried
to kill my boss
and now I'm gonna
have to take you down.
[CITIZEN A] So he's
one of the culprits?
Tie him up Paulie,
don't let that pirate go!
This is bad.
So he got shot five times,
but Iceberg's still alive?
Don't look so surprised.
That guy's as tough as nails!
But if they tried it once
then these scumbags
might try to go after
Iceberg a second time, too.
So we're gonna
settle this now.
[KAKU]
"Dead or Alive."
The World Government
doesn't care either way.
This is what it means to
have a bounty on your head.
Therefore, you can't complain.
No matter how terrible
your fate may be.
You've broken the law
and now the law has
turned its back on you.
[LUFFY]
That's right.
We chose to live this way.
We're all outlaws.
But I don't care.
You're wrong!
If you knew Robin
you wouldn't say that!
So you take that back!
♪ opening song ♪
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Let me talk to Ice Pops!
This has to be a mistake!
There's no way it was Robin!
We'd be fools to let
you anywhere near him!
Criminals have no
right to make demands!
He's right!
Tie up the culprits!
Those bastards can't get
away with shooting our hero!
Send 'em to the gallows!
Hey, wait! Just calm down!
[CITIZEN F] Hold on!
You can't fool me, missy.
I saw you with
that Straw Hat guy!
I bet you're one of the
criminals, aren't ya?
Really?!
Yeah! She was
riding along with him
on a Yagara when he got here!
We've got you now!
You're gonna get
what you deserve!
Stop it! Let me go!
Nami!
I'm telling you people,
we didn't do anything wrong,
you're making a mistake!
And why should we
trust anything you say?
You scumbags are pirates
and probably assassins, too!
[LUFFY] This doesn't
even make any sense!
There's no reason why
Robin would attack him!
Yeah! Not only that,
we'd never even heard of Iceberg
until we met him yesterday!
You brats just keep
saying that all you want.
It's over. Fact is you
picked on the wrong guy.
The moral of the story is,
if you make an
enemy out of Iceberg.
Then you make an enemy out
of the entire Galley-La Company.
And that's not the half of it.
You also made an
enemy out of everyone
in this whole city,
you understand?
Listen, I don't want
to fight any of you!
We can still talk
about all this, okay?!
[PAULIE] I don't give
a damn what you want!
Word of this is gonna
spread like wildfire.
There's no place to
run and no place to hide.
It's the end of the road.
You pirates are going down.
[CROWD cheers]
[CITIZEN I] That's what you
get for messing with Galley-La!
What's the
matter, Straw Hat?
You not even gonna
go out with a fight?
I just told you.
We're not enemies and I don't
want to fight any of you!
[LULU] Since pistols
don't work on you.
We'll have to
go with Plan B.
Damn it all. I guess these
guys are going all-out, huh?
[CROWD cheers]
[CITIZEN J]
Bulls-eye!
[thinking]
No. He got away.
Wow, they almost had me.
Ah, uh-oh.
Can't dodge anymore.
[CROWD cheers]
[CITIZEN F]
All right, nice shot!
Hahahaha!
Yeah! And that's why
Galley-La is our pride and joy!
Whoo!
Feels good to
see them lose!
You bet! I hope they blow
that sorry sucker sky high!
Wheeew...
Naw I shouldn't say that.
After all, Straw Hat's
our enemy too.
I haven't beaten him
nearly enough, not yet.
[FRANKY]
And to be fair.
I was here first, wasn't I?
I enjoyed your little
show but this's my stage
and the only
star here is Franky.
So get out of my way!
Galley-la!
[KAKU]
Hold your horses.
We'll be done
with him in a second.
Then you can fight us
to your heart's content.
Listen, you. I called
dibs on Straw Hat
before all of you
even got here!
No. Screw it.
You don't even care
what I say, do you?
[CITIZEN K]
Paulie! Watch out!
[CITIZEN L]
Get outta there!
[CITIZEN M] Franky's going
nuts again! Run away!
Huh?
Connector Set.
[chuckles]
[CITIZEN O] He brought down
a crane with that attack!
It's lethal!
[PAULIE]
That was him?
[LULU]
Looks like a cannon hit it.
[CITIZEN P]
He's about to fire!
Get 'em bro, your
cannon's ready to go! Hey!
Don't expect me to shoot
a cannonball or anything.
The shells I fire are
made of nothing but air.
Still these babies
break the speed of sound.
Air, huh?
[CITIZEN Q]
Run for your lives!
What the hell?
Auuuuuuuuuhhhhh!!
Augh!
Coup de Vent!
[CROWD screams]
[chuckles]
Man, he wasn't kidding,
that thing hits like a
hurricane to the face.
[CITIZEN R] Another
crane is coming down!
[CITIZEN S] Get outta here!
It's gonna fall on us!
[CITIZEN T] Hurry up!
[CITIZEN U]
Here it comes!
Hahahaha!
Yeah! Let it fall!
[FRANKY]
Hell, I don't care!
Let's bring the whole
damn shipyard down!
He really is a cyborg!
I thought he was kidding but
that air shot was no joke.
I've never even seen
technology like that!
B-But hey...
No more angry mob at least.
[LUFFY]
Nami! Run!
Luffy!
You didn't get hit
back there, did you?
It's gonna take a
lot more than that
if those guys
wanna get rid of me!
Okay, come on.
We need to get going.
I'm not sure how, but
we've gotta talk to Ice Pops.
What? Now?
When the whole town
is out searching for us?
[CITIZEN V]
Hey! Look!
Straw Hat is getting away!
Uh-oh.
They're trying to surround us.
Nami.
Huh?
Better hold on tight, okay?
No, not okay!
[CITIZEN W]
Stop them!
[CITIZEN X]
They're too fast!
[CITIZEN]
Follow them!
Well, he's not on
the deck at least.
Maybe he's still
too hurt to move.
But if we don't want
him to recognize us,
we can't risk
getting any closer.
Here we go.
You ready to do this?
What's that?!
There's a gigantic Storm
called Aqua Laguna
that's on its way
here right now?
That's right!
By midnight tonight
this entire beach
will be completely
underwater as well as
half of the town! Crazy, huh?
That's terrible, we should
get out of here right away!
Yes, sir, if we were smart,
that's exactly what we would do!
Let's evacuate to higher ground!
Good idea, let's do that!
Evacuate!
[crashing noise]
[SANJI]
Run away!
That's weird, I could've sworn
I heard someone out here.
Be sure to evacuate!
Evacuate, Usopp!
They were saying
something about a storm?
Well, actually the wind
is awfully strong, isn't it?
[KIWI]
Bro?
[FRANKY]
Hm?
[KIWI]
They're getting away.
Don't you want
to go after them?
Nah that last Coupe de Vent
I did ate up all my fuel.
You see this?
My pompadour's limp.
No kidding. It looks like
a willow swaying in the wind.
What a mess. Stupid Galley-La.
I'll take care of that Straw Hat
as soon as I'm done refueling.
Hahaha.
But that kid ain't
half bad, y'know.
He certainly earned
his big bounty. Hahahaha!
[KAKU]
Geeze Louise.
Even for Franky
this is too much.
Today just isn't our day.
[PAULIE]
Franky or no Franky,
we can't let Straw Hat escape.
Aqua Laguna is
gonna hit tonight.
There are only two Sea Train
departures left today.
Since the Straw Hats
can't leave on their ship
the Sea Train's the only ticket
they've got to
get off the island.
This is our chance.
Have every member
of Galley-La spread out
and hunt them down.
We'll settle
this before sunset!
Granny, look! It's Water Seven!
Don't get too excited
and fall in the ocean now!
[train whistle blowing]
If that isn't Galley-La HQ,
I don't know what is.
No surprise since it's right
next to Dock One. And look.
The place is totally
swarming with reporters.
Those tough-looking guys
are probably shipwrights.
I'm willing to bet
that's where Iceberg's at.
You sure about this?
Of course I am.
The only way for me to
find out what's going on
between Ice Pops and
Robin is to ask him myself.
I can't stop you but
you should keep in mind
that everyone
on the island
is trying to hunt
us down right now.
So listen, before
you do anything rash,
sneak around and figure
out where Iceberg's room
is so you know
where you need to go.
[LUFFY]
All right, I'm off.
What?! No!
They can't find them.
Huh?
Who's that?!
[SHIPWRIGHT B]
Wait! It can't be!
[REPORTER A]
Someone broke the window!
[SHIPWRIGHT A]
We're under attack!
Straw Hat Luffy broke in!
He must be after Iceberg!
He's doing this in
the middle of the day?!
He's got some guts
coming after us now!
[SHIPWRIGHT E]
Where is he?
He's taking the stairs
up to the third floor!
[SHIPWRIGHT G]
Where are the foremen?!
[SHIPWRIGHT H] They all spread
out looking for Straw Hat!
No one is here!
[SHIPWRIGHT J] He's wearing
a red vest! You can't miss him!
[SHIPWRIGHT K] Don't
let him get to Iceberg!
[SHIPWRIGHT L]
I found him!
[sighs]
[SHIPWRIGHT M]
Hey! Over here!
Where is he? Where is he?
[SHIPWRIGHT N]
Don't shoot a pistol, you idiot!
We're inside! You're
gonna disturb Mr. Iceberg!
[KALIFA]
I know you need to rest.
I apologize for the commotion.
[ICEBERG]
Mmwell, what's going on?
Apparently, Straw Hat Luffy has
broken in and is running amuck.
In that case. I have a plan.
[SHIPWRIGHT O]
Found him!
[LUFFY]
Uh-oh!
[LUFFY] Whoa, that's
a lotta shipwrights.
[SHIPWRIGHT P] He's going
to building 2! Follow him!
Luffy, wait!
It's you.
[SHIPWRIGHT Q] Kalifa, did you
see a pirate come this way?
If I had, then you'd know.
And by the way,
you're far too noisy.
Mr. Iceberg still needs
his peace and quiet.
[SHIPWRIGHT Q]
You're right. Sorry.
Looks like the Straw Hat
hasn't made it this far yet.
Let's stand watch
around this hallway.
This is where
he's headed for sure.
Mwell hello there, Pirate Boy.
Were you looking for me?
Sure was. Thanks for
saving me from those guys.
[ICEBERG]
Considering the angry mob.
I assume that you didn't
burst in here just to murder me.
[LUFFY] All I want is to
hear your side of the story!
Last night. I saw Nico
Robin here, without a doubt.
And mind you. I have
nothing against any of you.
I have no reason to lie.
Are you sure it wasn't
someone who looked like her?
[ICEBERG]
Shut up and listen, boy.
I didn't call you in here
to bicker about who did what.
I have a favor to ask
and it would be
in your best
interest to grant it.
[ICEBERG]
No matter what it takes.
I have to see Nico Robin again!
[NEWSPAPER GUY A]
Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
The Straw Hat Pirates
were the culprits
in the attack
against Mr. Iceberg!
The Water-Water
Newspaper will purchase
any information related to their
current location or actions!
We know that the
culprits are still here
on the island, so be
sure to stay on the lookout.
We must band
together to hunt down
the Straw Hats and
send them to the Gallows!
[TOWNSPEOPLE]
Yeah!
♪ ending song ♪
[NAMI] There's no way
Robin's the culprit, right?
[CHOPPER] I just
want to see her!
[NAMI] There's shipwrights
looking for us everywhere!
[CHOPPER]
We'd better find her quick!
[NAMI] They say a huge
storm's coming, too!
[CHOPPER]
What're we gonna do?
[NAMI] Maybe Robin
betrayed us after all.
[LUFFY] No!
I refuse to believe it!
On the next One Piece :
"Eternal Farewell?
Nico Robin, The Woman
Who Draws Darkness!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!