[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Fireworks!
[WHITE BERETS yell]
They defeated the White Berets!
Unbelievable!
[laughs]
[MCKINLEY] Sorry, criminals!
You have no chance of escape.
You should've behaved and
done what I told you to do.
Of all the upholders of
law here in Skypiea,
we White Berets are
the most lenient.
However, they are not
nearly as forgiving!
[MCKINLEY laughs]
[MCKINLEY]
Congratulations.
You are now considered
second degree criminals.
You can try to cry for mercy...
[MCKINLEY laughs]
[MCKINLEY]
...but you all will be judged...
...by the Priests of Upper Yard!
Heso!
[LUFFY]
"Is Escape Possible?
God's Challenge
is Set in Motion."
What's wrong with those guys?
Forget them.
That old lady ratted us out.
She lied to us.
She said it was okay
for us to pass through.
But when we did, they
accused us of illegal entry?
That's flat out fraud!
Exactly.
But then, even if we were
told we couldn't pass,
we would've just forced
our way through.
I mean, how was that little
old lady gonna stop us?
Shut up!
In any case, you're in
a great deal of trouble.
You're now second-degree
criminals, and as such,
I'm afraid Conis and I are
unable to assist you any longer.
Why are you talking to us
from way over there?
I don't really see
what the big deal is.
I'm surprised you're not
used to this by now.
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
I've been meaning to ask.
Why'd you come back, Nami?
What?
We were finally gonna
get to set sail
and head out on an amazing
adventure until you--
I mean, we were about
to come looking for you.
We were getting worried.
[LUFFY chuckles]
I think you and I need
to have a little talk.
[yelps]
[NAMI]
Forget about your big adventure.
It's never gonna happen.
You haven't seen what I've seen.
That island is full
of the type of people
you don't wanna mess with.
I don't care who
you think you are.
Granted, we don't know
what this guy is,
but his powers are real.
And there's no way I'm ever
goin' back there again.
So forget it. Got me?
How 'bout you just relax
here while the rest of us go?
We're wanted criminals!
I'm not staying here a
minute longer, either.
Are you nuts? Get your
priorities straight.
The adventure is always
the most important part!
My priorities are life
first, then money.
Please tell me I'm
third on that list.
Don't push me.
[USOPP]
You raise a good point.
We put all of our energy into
just trying to get up here.
But we never really
thought about
how we were gonna get back.
[SUU]
Suu.
Is there a safe way back
to the Blue Sea World?
Can we ever even go home again?
There is a way,
but at this juncture,
I'm afraid it's no longer safe.
Your only hope for escape
is to make your
way to Cloud End.
From there you can travel home.
What's Cloud End? And how are
we supposed to get there?
[CONIS] It's a region
that lies far to the east.
The only way for
you to get there
is to travel across
the White White Sea.
Okay!
So we sail east, and we
eventually get home!
But I don't wanna go home.
Your other option is stay
and get sentenced to death.
Listen to me.
I don't want you causing
any more trouble
for Conis and her dad.
No. Don't worry about us.
Even if we leave right now,
there's no guarantee we'll
make a clean escape.
We don't have any time to
lose, so just get on the ship.
You'll have your
adventure, I promise,
but right now, we
need to get going.
So come on everybody.
Let's set sail.
[OTHERS grumbling]
Thanks for all your help!
We really appreciate it!
Ooh! Hold on.
Come on! Now what?
Hey, old man!
Huh? What is it, Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Can I ask I favor?
Ya mind if we take the
leftovers from earlier?
Of course not.
They're all yours.
Woohoo! Come on, Sanji!
Make us lunch!
Glad you got priorities.
In that case, could I ask for
a teensy little favor, too?
You're an engineer, right?
I don't suppose you could
spare any parts or tools
to fix our ship?
What's mine is yours, Usopp.
Feel free to take
anything you need.
Uh, guys. Where are you going?
[LUFFY]
Hello! They got food!
Tell ya what, you go ahead
and ready the ship for departure
and we'll be back
before you know it.
He's dead-set on goin'
to that island.
Doesn't he get it?
Don't take it out on us.
You know how he is.
Seriously, try to relax.
Chopper. You're still on
my side, aren't you?
Aren't you?
Don't answer that.
[CHOPPER]
Heavy point!
I was about to drop the
ladder for you, you know?
[ZORO] You know there's no
persuading Luffy of anything.
He won't listen even if
we all gang up on him.
Fine, then I guess
I'll just stay put.
Well, you're free to do
whatever you want.
I know that.
But if I stay here,
I'll be killed!
Yep. Quite a predicament.
Jerk.
Robin.
Let's go beat some
sense into Luffy.
Won't work.
[sighs]
I guess we'd have
a better chance
against the White Berets.
And you know they've
already gotta be gathering
reinforcements to follow us.
[MCKINLEY chuckles]
[MCKINLEY]
Follow you? Idiots.
Eneru and his Priests
aren't going anywhere.
Why should I bother when
your true judgment awaits?
Once you weigh anchor,
your challenge will begin.
Your ship will set
its own course
to the forbidden
Sacred Grounds.
[MCKINLEY]
The Upper Yard!
I-I feel I need to
tell you something.
[NAMI] There's a cloud
current that'll take us
down to the White Sea?
Yes.
By entering the current,
you can cross the vast expanse
of the White White Sea.
Then it will take you all
the way to Cloud End
and you won't have to
worry about getting lost.
Really?
[CONIS]
As long as you ride the current,
nobody will be
able to catch you.
[NAMI]
Hm.
I've got it:
We won't tell Luffy,
we'll just sail the Going
Merry into the current.
And what? We just
hope he doesn't notice
until it's too late?
Even so, I seriously doubt
he'll give up his quest.
[NAMI growls]
If you like, I'd be
happy to guide you
to the entrance of the current
to make sure you set
off for home safely.
Great.
Now we have to make sure
Luffy doesn't catch wind
of what's going on.
But don't worry.
We'll take care of that.
Then ready your ship
and I'll be back with the
others as soon as I can.
You got it. We really
appreciate it, Conis.
[giggles] You're welcome.
[LUFFY]
This is really good.
[SANJI] Save some for the trip.
And for the rest of us.
[LUFFY] There's plenty here.
Why hold back?
This does have
to feed all of us.
Conis! Refill!
Why don't you get it yourself?
Speaking of, where is Conis?
[PAGAYA] I think she went to
bid farewell to the others.
Oh, I brought you some more tea.
[PAGAYA] So you're the
shipwright for your vessel,
aren't you?
Well, not really.
Actually, I'm a sniper.
[PAGAYA]
Wow. That sounds exciting.
Yeah, I guess so.
But it means we don't have a
regular shipwright in our crew.
Let's see, how can I
put this delicately?
I am cursed with supreme
skill on every subject
and the whole crew relies on me!
[laughing]
[USOPP]
Yeah, it's a lotta work,
but without me the ship
just wouldn't function.
My official title
is Sharpshooter,
but I'm also the co-captain.
And that's why everyone
calls me Captain... Usopp
[PAGAYA]
Ooh, your color arrangement
clearly denotes the work
of a professional.
Of course.
I consider the plating
of food an art form.
[NAMI]
Bye, Conis! See ya in a bit!
[CONIS]
Be right back.
Ha! Finally, a light at
the end of the tunnel.
For a while there I was
really getting worried.
I'm still a bit skeptical
that the current
will actually take us home.
Why's that?
If what she says is true,
and this current really exists,
wouldn't it stand to reason
that we would hear
more stories of people
returning safely
from sky island?
But you have to remember
that very few people
ever manage to find their way
up here in the first place.
So, of course, you're not
gonna hear many stories
about people coming back.
And even if they did
find the current,
there's no guarantee their
ship could withstand
the high speeds it requires.
Good point.
A lot of captains don't know
when to call it quits.
Let's hurry and weigh anchor.
Get ready to set sail.
Chopper, use your Weight Bonus
and help us out with
the heavy lifting.
[CHOPPER] I keep telling you,
it's called Heavy Point.
[NAMI]
What?
[CHOPPER]
Nothing. Never mind.
[NAMI]
Now wake Zoro up.
[ROBIN]
But how?
[CHOPPER] Don't worry.
I don't need his help.
[NAMI]
We better hurry.
Conis gave us this chance,
and we can't waste it!
[CHOPPER]
Heavy Point!
[SANJI]
Maybe I'll put this here.
Naw, that doesn't work.
Throws off the
whole arrangement.
If I put the red one here
and then the emerald green
broad beans across the back...
Yeah. Ah, now this
looks delicious.
I sure hope Nami and Robin
appreciate the hard work.
Wow! It doesn't even
look like food.
I've never seen such
a beautifully prepared
lunch before.
Here.
I made one for you as well.
Really? Custom made just for me?
I've prepared all the food today
according to a
theme I've chosen.
I call it: "Love is a
Cruel Mistress Feast
for a Fallen Angel."
I see.
I don't get what
all the fuss is.
It's just a box lunch.
How dare you trash my work!
You better watch your mouth!
A great meal starts with
great presentation!
[LUFFY] Why bother?
It all comes out the same.
[SANJI] You're stuffing your
face without even looking!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, and...?
Why're you so mad?
It still tastes good.
'Cause food should please your
eyes as well as your palate!
[LUFFY]
Well, that's just stupid.
Not even I can eat with my eyes.
[SANJI] That's not what
I meant, you infant!
[LUFFY] 'Course I did kinda eat
with my nose once. But...
[SANJI]
Oh, just stop talking!
Now we just wait till Luffy
and the others get back.
All set?
All set.
[yelping]
Chopper! What's going on?
[chuckles]
What's goin' on?
I think we might already
be caught in the current.
[gasps] Hey!
Something's wrong with the ship.
[SANJI]
Huh?
What is it?
Take a look! She just started
rockin' all of a sudden!
Really?
Hope they're not havin'
a party without us.
Hey, look. It's Nami.
Wait. Why in the world
is she wearing a t-shirt?
I'm pretty sure we have more
pressing concerns right now!
Guys, look! The ship
started moving.
But why?
They wouldn't just leave
us here, would they?
Whoa!
I don't think I've ever seen a
ship sailing backwards before.
But they haven't even
set the sails yet.
Huh?
There's something underneath!
I think we're being
dragged away.
But by what?
[screaming]
You sure we're not stuck in that
current Conis told us about?
[ROBIN] No. I think we
have a bigger issue here.
[LUFFY, SANJI, USOPP]
'Kay, what is that?
It must be--
[PAGAYA] It's the legendary
White White Sea
Super-Express Lobster!
[LUFFY, SANJI, USOPP]
What?
Guys, we're being hijacked!
We'll have to abandon ship!
C'mon, we've gotta move right
now! While we still have time!
We can't leave the ship.
Without it we won't be
able to get back home.
Then I'll stay behind!
Just go now!
Forget it! You can't defend
the whole ship by yourself!
[ZORO]
I'll manage.
Oh, come on.
[cracking]
That's more like it.
[gasps]
All right. Makin' progress.
[ROBIN] I don't think
that'll get you anywhere.
[ROBIN]
Come back on board.
Why should I?
[ROBIN] You'll never be able
to significantly damage
that creature, and we've got
bigger problems now. Look.
What?
[ROBIN]
A school of vicious sky fish
are following us
ready to attack.
We can't jump ship
and escape now.
Even if we manage to
defeat the sky fish,
I'm sure that more will
arrive to take their place.
Our punishment has
already begun.
And there's no way to stop it.
Heaven's Judgment.
They must be taking us
to the forbidden island.
Guess they got tired of waiting.
Eneru's really got it in for us.
Oh, no. Please.
I can't go back there.
Luffy. Help us!
Sanji, Usopp!
[SKY FISH roaring]
[laughs]
Why, Nami? Why a t-shirt?
You're still thinking of that?
This is awful, Luffy!
What are we gonna do?
We have to rescue
Nami and the others!
[LUFFY]
Hmm.
I wonder...
Where're they're going?
Where're they're
going? Yes, right!
[LUFFY]
I got nothin'.
[PAGAYA]
Um, well.
[LUFFY, USOPP, SANJI]
Huh?
[PAGAYA]
Oh. Uh...
The Super-Express Lobster
is a messenger of Eneru.
He must be taking your friends
as a sacrificial offering.
If that's the case,
they are being taken to
the northeast Upper Yard.
To the sacrificial altar.
Say what?
You don't mean that Nami
and Robin and the rest...
The rest?
...are gonna be sacrificed?
To that wannabe God?
That bastard!
He better not harm a single hair
on my Nami's pretty head!
[PAGAYA]
But listen carefully,
because I have not yet told
you what else will happen.
What? There's more?
[PAGAYA]
You see, in Heaven's Judgment
there are actually two different
types of criminal punishment
and I've only told
you about the first.
The second punishment
is a challenge.
Your friends are currently
hostages in Eneru's hands.
And they are being taken
to him even as we speak.
Hostages?
I'm afraid I must tell you,
the criminals who are
to receive the judgement
are the three of you
standing before me.
Wait. What are you
trying to say?
If we only had a map.
[USOPP] Uh. I know I've got one
of Skypiea with me somewhere.
[PAGAYA]
Well, this one is very old,
but it looks like the general
shape of the island
is correctly rendered.
Conis, is everything all right?
I'm fine.
It's just--
[LUFFY]
Don't worry.
We'll figure something
out. We always do.
[chuckles]
How can you be sure?
[PAGAYA]
This is where we are now.
The sacrificial altar where
your friends are headed
is located a good distance
to the northeast,
here in the Upper Yard.
And I'm afraid there's only
one way to get there.
[PAGAYA]
You have to take the Milky Road
that leaves this island.
And your only means
of transportation
will be the waver.
The road will take you
to a great forest
where the Priests are
awaiting your arrival.
Well, let's see.
There's gotta be a better way
for us to get there unnoticed.
If we just ride up
to the front gate,
we won't stand a chance.
Couldn't we sneak
around the side?
Usopp's right.
If we take the main road,
they'll see us coming
and set a trap.
That may be
but even if you do
find your way ashore,
there's no way that you'll ever
make it to the altar on foot.
You see, your old map differs
from the current configuration
in that now the Milky Roads
criss-cross the entire island.
The cloud canals you mentioned.
Correct.
There are hundreds
of them, of all sizes,
running every which way.
I don't think anyone really
knows where they all lead.
[LUFFY]
Hmm. I see.
That's why your only course
of action is as I've said.
You must follow the main
Milky Road to the island,
and from there continue
until you reach the altar.
Is that so?
And even if we do find
another way ashore,
the canals will block us
from continuing inland.
[PAGAYA]
That's right.
Did I mention the man-eating
fish that prowl the canal?
Geh. Man-eating fish?
Sounds like they've
covered all their bases.
So you're saying, if we want
our friends and ship back,
we have to walk right up
to their front door
and march on it.
This is part of the
challenge you mentioned?
Part of Heaven's Judgment?
Yes.
In Upper Yard, there are
four powerful Priests
of unimaginable strength
who await you.
[ringing]
[LUFFY] Hmm. Sounds like
a piece of cake.
I mean, all we have to do
to get our friends back
is beat up these Priests, right?
You make it sound easy.
[laughing]
Finally, a little action!
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[LUFFY] Conis, why are you
shaking like that?
[CONIS]
I guess I didn't notice.
[LUFFY]
And you seem kinda pale, too.
[CONIS]
I...
[LUFFY] You shoulda just
told us you were scared.
[CONIS]
You shouldn't talk to me.
[LUFFY]
What?
[CONIS] According to our laws,
if I see a known criminal,
I must take them to
the authorities,
or I'll be sentenced to death.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Trap on Lovely Street!
The Almighty Eneru."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!