Ice Age.
[AOKIJI] I'm impressed that
you were able to survive,
especially as a child.
You managed to betray,
sidestep, and escape
from everyone in your past.
You survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
And now you've chosen
this crew as your next haven.
Every organization
that she's had something
to do with in the past
has been annihilated.
Pistol!
[AOKIJI] You have some
very loyal friends.
But you'll never change,
will you Nico Robin!
No! That's not true!
Robin!
I'm not who I--
Aaaah!!
[growls]
[LUFFY]
You bastard!
Stop yelling. If you thaw
her out carefully, she'll live.
However, her body is
extremely fragile in this state,
so you'll need to
handle her with care.
If any part of her
breaks, she'll die.
For example, if I were to
smash her apart, like this.
Robin!
No!
[LUFFY]
Stop!!
That was close!
[NAMI]
All right!
[CHOPPER]
That was amazing, Usopp!
What in the hell are you doing?
Usopp! Chopper! Quick!
Take Robin and
run back to the ship!
Thaw her out and keep her safe!
Right! You got it, Captain!
[USOPP]
Hurry! But be gentle, okay?!
[CHOPPER]
It's cold...
[USOPP] I know! But
Robin's even colder, genius!
[AOKIJI] Don't bother. The world
would be a much better place
without that woman in it.
[NAMI]
Not to split hairs.
But a pirate crew
pretty much consists of
people just like that.
You got that right, lady.
Now, if you don't mind.
Kindly step aside.
Nami!
[SANJI]
You're not gonna...
[ZORO]
...mess with this crew!
Wait! Nobody attack him!
[LUFFY]
Stay back, and don't interfere.
I'm gonna fight
him one-on-one.
[LUFFY]
What do you say?
The two of us can
settle this on our own.
Fine by me.
But since I don't have
a ship to take you back.
Then I'll just have to kill you.
[shower running]
[USOPP] She... She can't
breathe like this, can she?
[CHOPPER] I think she's in a
state of suspended animation.
[USOPP] Doesn't that mean she'll
die if we don't do something?!
[CHOPPER] If we warm her up
too quickly, she'll shatter.
We have to restore her body
temperature from the inside out.
Are you sure that this
is really gonna work?
I don't know.
But it's the only thing I--
Whoa, wait a minute,
you don't know?!
This is Robin's life
we're talking about here!
I know! But I've
never treated someone
whose entire body
was frozen before!
I know that Aokiji
said she was still alive.
But I just don't see how
that could be possible!
Don't give me that crap!
If you can't do
anything to save her,
then no one in
the whole world can!
You understand me?
You are the doctor of the
Straw Hat Pirates, got it?!
I know, okay! Just shut up
and stop yelling at me!
[ZORO]
Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
What's going on?
Why are just the three
of you here? Where's Luffy?
There's no time to explain!
We need to go back right away!
Help us do something about
this frozen arm and leg!
Oh! Right!
We... We need to douse
every part of your body
that's frozen in water!
But we're using the
shower room for Robin.
How is Robin? Is she okay?
Uh... It's too early to tell...
[loud splash]
What are you doing?
Will this do, Chopper?
Yes! Once the
ice begins to melt,
start rubbing
the affected areas
and then come up to
the ship right away!
Nami! Come aboard and
help us treat Robin!
[NAMI]
Right!
What the--?
Why are you guys here?
What happened? Where's Luffy?
Fighting Aokiji one-on-one.
One-on-one?!
You mean you left Luffy there
to face him all by himself?!
Those were the Captain's orders.
Are you crazy?!
Can't you tell when an
order is unreasonable?!
I can't believe you would be so
cold-hearted to just leave him--
Hey! It was a duel!
Can't you understand that?!
It's what he wanted!
Stop it, both of you!
This isn't the time!
Right now. We need
to stay focused, okay?
[ZORO] Whether this
decision was one of
his passing whims
or not, it doesn't matter.
Whatever happens,
we have to be ready to
deal with it, understand?
[AOKIJI] You really are
an odd one, aren't you?
[LUFFY]
Auuuughh!
Gum-Gum... Storm!!
Now, it's Ice Time.
[LUFFY]
What do you say?
The two of us can
settle this on our own.
Aw, man. You tricked me.
The moment I agreed
to fight you one-on-one,
I settled on defeating
you and you alone.
But that was your
plan, wasn't it?
If I were to attack your crew
now, I'd be the bad guy here.
Isn't that right, Captain?
Or maybe you actually
thought you could beat me.
Let me give you
a piece of advice.
Keep a close eye on Nico Robin.
Eventually, she'll grow to
be more than you can handle.
[AOKIJI] The nature of the
violent fate she was born into
will be a greater danger
than you can imagine.
More of a burden than you
could ever hope to bear.
That's what it means to have
that woman as part of your crew.
You have been warned...
...Mister Monkey D. Luffy!
[AOKIJI]
It would be easy to break you
and kill you right here and
now but I have a debt to honor.
[AOKIJI] Consider us even for
you taking care of Crocodile.
As well as... uh... uhh...
Oh, never mind...
Something to do
with Smoker, see ya!
[ZORO]
There he is!
[SANJI]
Luffy!
[ZORO]
He's still in one piece!
[SANJI]
That's good news!
[ZORO and SANJI] I'll carry him!
Let's get him to the ship!
Stop saying what I'm saying!
[AOKIJI] If they follow their
Log Pose from this island,
their next destination is--
It's Water Seven.
The City of Water, huh?
Oh my, my, my.
Would you look at that?
They're getting really close to
our headquarters, aren't they?
[CHOPPER]
Both of their hearts...
..are beating!
Yeah!
[USOPP]
Luffy!
[SANJI]
Robin!
No! You can't go in yet!
I don't want them
disturbed, understand?
Hey! Doctor Chopper!
How about I make
them some food?
Calling me Doctor
won't make me feel happy
or anything, you stupid jerk!
But I suppose some
warm drinks would be nice
for when they wake up.
I'll carry them in
to the lounge later.
Aye-aye, Sir!
Hey, Nami, should we set sail?
No, not yet. Not while the
Captain's out of commission.
The Log Pose has
our new heading,
but let's rest
here for the day.
Hmm?
[ZORO] What's wrong,
Usopp? You look beat.
Are there gonna be
more guys like him?
Coming after us
everywhere we go?
This is crazy.
I don't know how much
more of it I can take.
Get some sleep, idiot.
You're just exhausted, okay?
[NAMI] In order for
Luffy and Robin
to get some rest and recover,
the Going Merry
remained anchored off
the uninhabited
island for four days.
After that, we set sail.
Today marks the third morning
since we resumed our voyage.
The weather is clear and sunny.
Mostly spring, with
occasional bouts of summer.
It's beautiful!
[SANJI]
Nami! Looook!
I made this potato paille
especially for you,
mademoiselle.
I hope you enjoy it.
Delicious!
[SANJI]
That makes me so happy!
Hey! Keep it down, jerk!
Some people are trying
to sleep around here!
Sorry about that, cactus head.
My most sincere apologies.
What, you cigarette
snorkeling dartboard?!
[SANJI] Huh?
What did you call me?
[SANJI]
Dartboard. Dartboard eyebrows.
What?!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
[CHOPPER]
...ffy!
[USOPP]
Lu...
Hey!
[BOTH]
Whoo!
We've been waiting for this!
Luffy!
This is me, frozen!
[laughter]
Ugh, I can't believe
this is how he behaves
after almost freezing to death.
Whataya think?
[USOPP]
You nailed it!
That's exactly
what you looked like!
[NAMI] Make sure you
clean all that up, Luffy!
'Kay! Hey Nami, is that food?
What are you eating?
Some potato paille.
Potatoes, huh? I love potatoes!
Sanji! Make me some!
Just how many hours
a day to you have
to lie around and sleep, anyway?
That's none of your business!
I'll sleep as long as I like.
Wanna fight about it?
[NAMI]
Okay, you two. Enough.
Sanji, our Captain has requested
some of your potato paille.
[SANJI]
You got it, Nami!
[LUFFY]
Sanji! Potatoes!
[SANJI] You're still
recuperating,
but that hasn't slowed
your appetite down in
the slightest, has it?
So this is paille, huh?
Good stuff!
Why is it called that?
Because the meat is taken
from the tail of the
giant beast Paille.
I should know.
I was the one who killed it.
It was over 100 meters long!
Whoa! 100 meters?!
That's amazing, Usopp!
And I did it all
before breakfast.
[CHOPPER] Wait, you
woke up early to kill it?
Chopper, have you
forgotten who I am?
[CHOPPER] Oh! I get it!
You're Captain Us--
Yes! That's right! I am the
great and almighty Captain Uso--
[door opening]
Hm?
Hmm?
[NAMI]
Robin!
[SANJI]
Robin! Good to see you!
[CHOPPER]
Robin!
Are you feeling okay?
Do you still have a chill?
Your treatment helped
me out tremendously.
Thanks! You're a
wonderful doctor!
Calling me a wonderful doctor
won't make me happy
or anything, you stupid jerk.
[USOPP]
He sure looks happy.
[LUFFY]
Yep.
You should take it easy, Robin.
Luffy's already recovered enough
to where he's running around
and screaming like an imbecile.
But you can just relax
and take your time.
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
That wasn't a complement!
Hey, Robin!
Would you like me to make
you something to warm you up?
Do you have an appetite?
I do.
May I have some coffee, please?
[SANJI]
Of course! It's my pleasure!
Hmm?
What the heck is that?
Man, this paille
stuff is delicious!
I can't stop eating it!
Yeah, I know!
I bet we could make some
money selling this stuff.
Luffy, come quick!
There's a... There's a
frog doing the front crawl!
[LUFFY]
What?
See for yourself!
It's headed to your side!
Really?
I wonder if it's that
same frog we heard about.
Come on, Luffy.
Are you really
gonna take anything
that goofy Admiral
told you seriously?
There's no way a frog
would do the front crawl.
It's... HOLY CRAP!
THERE'S A FROG DOING
THE FRONT CRAWL!
[LUFFY]
Come on! After him!
[ZORO, USOPP, and CHOPPER]
Aye-aye!
[LUFFY] Take in the sail!
Stand by the oars!
Bring the ship
about to 2 o'clock!
[ZORO, USOPP, and CHOPPER]
Aye-aye!
[LUFFY]
Hurry!
[ZORO]
I don't know why,
but I get the feeling we
really have to follow it!
Sorry to keep you
waiting, mademoiselles.
Uhh... what's happening?
What the--? What's going on?
It seems like the ship
has changed its course.
Hey! What's the deal here?
Why'd you change our
course without asking me?
Nami! You're never
gonna believe it!
We found this huge frog
with scars all over its body
and we're following it!
A frog? What?
We have to catch up to it,
capture it, cook it,
and eat it for lunch!
You wanna eat it?!
[NAMI]
You're right!
Huh...
Is that a lighthouse?
Now what's a lighthouse
doing way out here?
I wonder if
anyone lives there.
[LUFFY] What's up?
Do you see an island?
Not really.
It's just a lighthouse.
There's not enough there
for the Log Pose to point to.
What about the frog?
Tell us which way the frog went!
Not a chance!
It looks like the frog is
headed to the lighthouse.
Frogs should be
marinated in white wine
to dissolve the mucus.
Then, you coat them with
flour and fry them up crisp.
Sanji! Snap out of it!
If the Captain says
we're going after the frog,
we really don't have
much choice in the matter.
Robin...
[LUFFY]
Let's go! Full speed ahead!
[ZORO, USOPP, and CHOPPER]
Aye-aye!
[NAMI] Why are you all
going along with this?!
[ZORO, USOPP, LUFFY and CHOPPER]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
[LUFFY]
It's flying!!
Quick! Don't let it get away!
Let's get up ahead of it
and block its course!
[ZORO, USOPP, LUFFY and CHOPPER]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
I guess we ran
ashore or something!
Nami, Robin! Say something!
Are you two okay?
Yeah, I think I'm okay.
Same.
[relieved] Oh...
Thank goodness.
[bell clanging]
Huh?
What is that sound?
What the heck? What's going on?
[distance distant whistle]
Wait, that sounds like a...
[bell clanging and
chugging noises]
No way! Out here?!
Huh...?
[NAMI]
Full reverse! Right now!
Turn 180 degrees!
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY]
What the heck is that?
[NAMI]
A ship? No, it's...!
[SANJI]
It's headed right for us!
[LUFFY]
Amazing!
[CHOPPER]
No, it's not!
[USOPP]
Let's get out of here!
[ZORO] Hey, that frog's
headed right for it!
[SANJI]
Is he trying to ram it?
[LUFFY]
No! Wait! My meat!!
[CREW]
That's not meat!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"The Dashing Sea Train and
the City of Water, Water Seven."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!