[BULL MASK] I'm afraid you're
no match for our martial arts.
[BULL MASK] Now stop resisting
and hand us the document
before you soil
it with your blood.
[thinking]
Damn it.
I really thought
I could beat them.
[PAULIE]
I shoulda known better.
This was all my idea.
Iceberg didn't tell me to fight.
He told me to get
the hell out of here.
[PAULIE] To run and
leave the blueprints behind.
You know why?
'Cause those are
nothing but fakes.
[SKULL MASK]
Wha...?
[BULL MASK]
What?
Damn it! I got stuck again!
Stupid walls always
getting in my way!
I hate 'em! I hate 'em!
What? Straw Hat.
[SKULL MASK]
Tempest Kick.
He cut right through the wall!
What are these?
[BULL MASK]
This is an emergency situation.
We don't have time
to deal with you.
I can't move!
[BULL MASK]
Restrain Paulie, too.
Go home! I have nothing
to give you people!
[BULL MAKS] Then we
have a problem, don't we?
[BULL MASK] What does one say
to a man who's marked for death?
First, let me be frank.
You disappoint me.
[ICEBERG]
Lucci!
[SKULL MASK]
This is your own fault.
You should've handed
over the blueprints
when the government
asked nicely.
[ICEBERG]
Kaku!
Pity. I was hoping
we could walk away
from this story without
resorting to violence.
[ICEBERG]
Kalifa.
It's a shame you're as
hard-headed as your master.
[ICEBERG]
Blueno, from the bar.
That means you've been with
the government all this time.
Indeed.
Needless to say,
going undercover
was like second-nature to us.
Now since everyone's being
so honest with each other,
let's try this again.
I don't have time to play games.
Tell me before
someone else gets hurt.
Where is it?
Where are the blueprints
for the ancient weapon Pluton?
♪ opening song ♪
[LUFFY]
Storm's coming, huh?
Better finish this up before
the wind gets even worse.
[CROWD jeers]
What's he doing?
Give it back.
We need the money...
...to fix the Merry!
Her scars are deep.
That's our money; it's to heal
her wounds, understand me?!
You can't have it!
Give it back to me right now!
Oh, I see now.
That must be the ship
he needed the money
to have repaired
he was talking about.
What a disaster.
Yeah, even if we didn't
come here to nab him,
Aqua Laguna would
still wash him away.
Hmph! Talk about bad luck.
Okay.
I had just enough lumber
to patch up the rough spots,
so it should hold,
even if it's not pretty.
[FRANKY]
You're wasting your time, pal.
Who, who's there?
[FRANKY]
C'mon, you're kidding me, right?
Or did we beat you so bad
you already
forgot who I am?
Pull it together, man!
Oh no, anybody but him!
W-W-What do you want?
L-L-Leave me alone, you bastard!
Now, now let's all calm down.
As long as you play it cool,
I won't have to hurt you.
[FRANKY] Even I'm not
crazy enough to fight a guy
in the middle of this storm.
But if we don't wanna sink,
it looks like I'll have to take
that ship of yours
hostage as well.
What're you talking about?
Well, I have a score to
settle with Straw Hat you see.
So I came here to kidnap you.
I used the back side.
They're fine.
[NAMI] I hope you're
proud of yourself,
beating those
poor shipwrights!
[CHOPPER]
You're so strong, Zoro!
Whatever. Might
as well go ahead!
[CHOPPER]
Zoro! This way!
[ZORO]
Got it.
No! Over here!
We're leading the
way for you, stupid!
How can you get lost already?!
Oh. Here.
Zoro's gone! I think
we lost him forever!
Is he doing this on purpose?!
Zoro, where did you go?!
See? I can do that stuff.
Cause I'm rubber.
Okay, that's good!
Now do that with
the rest of your body!
Sure. Just gimme a sec.
Easy! 'Cause I'm rubber!
All right.
Good. Now help me.
[LUFFY]
No prob!
You're gonna pay
you masked bastards.
[LUCCI]
It's true,
we've been undercover
for the last five years.
Ah, but don't worry,
we took our jobs as
shipwrights very seriously.
I understand how
shocked you must be.
However, we can't
devote any more
time to this matter.
We will achieve our goal
by any means necessary.
So if you're thinking
about resisting
for the sake of
being difficult,
I suggest you reconsider
for your own good
as well as ours.
I assume you're already
familiar with Cipher Pol.
It's the government's
supreme intelligence agency
with eight branches.
Their worldwide bases
are referred to as
CP1 through CP8.
Together, they serve
as the government's eyes
and ears in every
corner of the globe.
Of course I know.
But how do all of you
fit into that picture?
[LUCCI]
Good question.
As the 9th Cipher Pol unit,
we officially do not exist.
And by virtue of that,
we possess a certain privilege
that the other branches lack.
One that necessitates
a degree of secrecy.
A "privilege"?
[LUCCI]
That's right.
Consider it a blade we
wield in the name of justice.
If a citizen is "uncooperative"
towards the government,
we may execute them.
You fools.
You can't use justice
as an excuse for murder!
[LUCCI] Recently, the
government has been forced
to change its way of thinking.
For example, rather than
fearing Pluton's revival
they have decided
to awaken it,
to use the ancient weapon
as a force of justice
that can bring an end
to the Great Pirate Era.
And now, for some reason,
you want to stand in their way.
It's almost as if
you have no sympathy
for all of the people constantly
being victimized by pirates.
You should reconsider
where your loyalties lie.
Don't kid yourself.
If the weapon is restored,
the world is going to
fight over its power.
It will only breed
more destruction.
Are you saying you don't trust
the government, Mr. Iceberg?
That would be a shame.
Not at all. It's human nature
that I don't trust, Lucci.
Show some respect!
Remember, you're
not my boss anymore.
Kaku, check his pulse.
'Scuse me.
[LUCCI]
Here's the situation.
A while ago we
came up with a bit
of a hypothesis
about the blueprints.
You needn't worry.
Although we could torture you,
we have more effective
means of extracting the truth.
All you have to do is lie there
and listen to our hypothesis
without saying a word.
Even if your mouth
won't cooperate,
your pulse will
tell us the truth.
Hahaha!
The wind is out to get you!
Better be careful!
Hey, Granny!
Aren't we going back?
The storm's coming!
Oh yeah? Seems
like a perfect time
for a stroll around
town if you ask me.
Gives me a little
time to sober up.
Oh? Then why're you
still drinking, Granny?
You can't sober up
and booze it up
at the same time, can you?
[KOKORO] Hahaha.
Sure I can!
I haven't been drinking
all my life fer nothing!
Huh? All your life?
That's not true!
[CHIMNEY]
That's not true.
That's not true. That's
not true. That's not true!
It hasn't been all my life.
It's only been eight years.
[steady heartbeat]
[LUCCI] Now that
we're all comfortable,
let me explain
the thought process
leading to our hypothesis.
First of all, the way
that you allowed us
to retrieve the fake blueprints
is highly suspicious.
After you decided
that the culprits
were related to the government,
you intentionally revealed
the location of the fakes,
presumably in the
hopes of fooling us.
However, what if your
assumption was wrong
and the culprit's
intention was to kill you
rather than to
retrieve the blueprints?
In that case, the
fakes would be useless,
the real blueprints
would be lost
and the will of the
original shipwrights
would not be passed on.
Surely you considered
that possibility.
I know you're no fool.
And yet, despite
creating a decoy,
you've seemingly
made no attempt
to pass off the actual
blueprints tonight.
That must mean you've already
entrusted them to someone.
[steady heartbeat]
We still don't know
where they are,
but we can assume
that you don't have them
with you anymore.
That's our hypothesis.
Ah-ah! No squirming.
[LUCCI]
This is still just a theory.
I admit.
We haven't found any
decisive evidence.
And despite the
fact that we've kept
you under surveillance
for the past five years.
We've never seen you
do anything suspicious.
Assuming you did entrust
the blueprints to someone,
they would have to be an
accomplished shipwright
to make any
sense out of them.
[steady heartbeat]
Now if we add that to our theory
things start to get interesting.
For example,
let's take a closer look
at the fake blueprints
that you left us.
Here at the bottom,
you can see the signatures of
three different shipwrights.
"Tom," "Iceberg,"
and "Cutty Flam."
And the company
name "Tom's Workers."
You probably thought that this
detail wouldn't mean anything
to whoever took the bait
but you had no idea your
enemies were so close.
That was a grave
miscalculation on your part.
If the person who broke
in had been an outsider,
once they found out
that the blueprints
had nothing to do with Pluton,
they would probably
have throw them away.
However.
Since we've been
shipwrights ourselves
for the past five years,
the names of the designers
are very interesting.
There's a visitor,
sir to see you.
[steady heartbeat]
[LUCCI] Although
many people know
of the legendary
shipwright, Tom,
the details of his actual
company are shrouded in mystery.
It's believed to have
existed on this island,
but there's no roster
or register to be found.
It was no easy task finding out
that you were one
of Tom's apprentices.
What few reports
we have indicate
that he taught only
two shipwrights.
And a government
official verified
that one of them died in
an accident 8 years ago.
[KOKORO]
Real shame.
I know Cutty Flam was
a bit of a loose cannon,
but I sure hate to see him go.
[LUCCI] It struck a chord.
I thought to myself
"now where have
I heard that name before?"
[steady heartbeat]
He said he's a friend
from years back.
Do you know anyone
named "Cutty Flam"?
[ICEBERG]
It was about four years ago,
shortly after we started
our undercover operation.
He was a man who
has passed through
Galley-La's gates
many times since.
But only once did
he ever use that name.
I remember it clearly.
So do I.
[steady heartbeat]
[KALIFA]
Shall I show him in, sir?
No, turn him away.
[LUCCI]
In other words.
Tom's second apprentice,
Cutty Flam, is still alive...
And living in
this town no less.
But now, he goes by "Franky."
[rapid heartbeat]
[FRANKY]
What's with all the secrecy?
Something going on?
Huh?
Hey what're these?
The blueprints for
that old battleship?
[ICEBERG] Don't call
yourself Cutty Flam anymore.
Huh?
It's only a matter of time
before the
government targets me.
I want you to take these
and leave this island, Franky.
Seems pretty obvious now, huh?
[KAKU] I can't believe
it took us all these years
to figure out the connection.
Our searches on him
turned up nothing.
I must admit that
his true identity
was a well-hidden secret.
And because he's an oaf
and a ship dismantler,
we never really
gave him much thought.
It's ironic, really. Since we
never questioned our reports,
it didn't occur to
us that a dead person
might actually still be alive.
The setup was quite
convenient for you, I imagine.
Since the Franky family
often came to the shipyard
to sell lumber, there
were plenty of chances
to pass off the blueprints.
You managed it well, he was
close when you needed him,
yet always at a safe distance.
That would also explain why
you were so confident
in dealing with us.
You knew that we were
looking for the blueprints
in the wrong place.
And while it might seem strange
that your most trusted foremen
had not heard of the blueprints,
they couldn't possibly
be as close to you
as Tom's other apprentice.
From this line of thinking,
everything checks out.
Not only that.
Your racing pulse has confirmed
that our hypothesis is true!
C'mon, hurry!
[ZORO]
Hey!
You sure this's the right way?
Don't even go there!
Their injuries are pretty bad.
All right, that's gotta be it--
the closed door at
the end of the hallway!
Looks like a lotta people
got hurt guarding that door!
[ZORO]
Hmm? Uh... Hey...
What're you waiting for?
Cut down the door
and beat the bad guys!
We're right behind you!
Hurry it up!
All right, I'll do it,
but not cause you told me to!
Hey, Straw Hat! Wait!
[loud crash]
YAAAAAA!!
This is the wrong
room, you idiot!
It's the one next door!
You hear me? Ugh...
Yeah? Oh. Oops.
[LUCCI]
Don't blame yourself.
You're only human.
And under these circumstances,
no one would be able to hide
the truth from us for very long.
So just be grateful that
justice will prevail in the end.
Thanks so much for
the last five years.
But you've outlived
your usefulness.
Let's find Franky
before the storm hits.
You bastards!
Hm?
Give Robin back!!
Luffy!
Luffy?
You again?
Robin! I finally found you!
Hey, Luffy!
Where were you when we had to
beat up all those shipwrights?!
Robin! Why did you leave us?!
Hold on a sec.
Something's not right here.
Well, well, well...
Paulie, Straw Hat.
[PAULIE]
Iceberg.
What is this?
[PAULIE]
What the hell's going on?!
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY] Robin,
what're you doing
hanging around with
jerks like them?!
[NAMI]
Yeah!
You know they work for the
government, right? What gives?
[ROBIN]
This is goodbye.
[LUFFY]
Hey! Don't leave!
We're not done talking yet!
[ROBIN] I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid we are.
For now and evermore.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"Come Back, Robin!
Showdown with CP9!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!