[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
After losing his brother, Ace,
Luffy fell into despair,
but when he was reminded
of his crew, he decided
to send them a message that
reached across the seas.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[NARRATOR] On the small
Sky Island of Weatheria.
[OLD MEN]
There she is!
[OLD MAN A]
We finally found her!
You've fooled us
for the last time!
It was bad enough that you stole
our research notes
and tried to run away!
But you toyed with
our feelings as well!
Our hearts, forever tainted!
You'll pay dearly
for your treachery!
[OLD MEN]
You thieving harpy!
--Okay.
--[HAREDAS] Huh?
[OLD MAN A]
There's our research notes!
[OLD MAN E]
And the Weather Ball!
[OLD MAN C]
And the hostage, Mr. Haredas!
Even if you return everything,
it's too late for forgiveness!
I'm so sorry.
I regret what I've done.
Nobody listen.
We can't trust her!
I won't be happy
until I've punished her
with my own two hands!
Punish me? How naughty!
[OLD MEN]
Huh? Naughty?!
[NAMI]
How could you?
Hey, stop that!
You know I didn't mean it
in the naughty kinda way!
I mean we need to,
um, to discipline you?
[OLD MAN B]
Stop talking to her!
She'll keep making us sound bad!
--[OLD MEN gasp]
--[NAMI] Tch!
Did you just try to "tch" us?
You big bully!
How cruel of you to pick on me!
[OLD MAN B]
Lighten up on the poor girl!
Did you all forget already?
The stuff she stole
and misery she's caused?
[OLD MAN E]
Oh, well.
[OLD MAN C]
Quit falling for her trap!
[NAMI]
There must be a mistake!
I wouldn't do such things!
Uh, on second thought...
You seem like a nice young lady.
Those fools don't know what
to think anymore, do they?
[OLD MEN yell]
Let's run her off the island!
Once and for all!
[NAMI]
Not that!
I'm sorry! I'll
never do it again!
[OLD MAN B] How can you
expect us to trust you?
[NAMI]
It's all right, I get it.
You want me to show
you how sorry I am.
[NAMI] To win back your trust,
I'll jump off this island.
--[OLD MEN gasp]
--[NAMI] My sacrifice will
pay for my offenses!
[OLD MEN gasp]
[NAMI]
Goodbye, cruel world!
Idiots, what have we done?
Don't be hasty, my dear!
Why don't we sit down
over a cup of tea
before you do
something so drastic?
[NAMI]
Farewell!
[OLD MEN]
Forgive us!
Okay then, as long
as you're sorry!
[OLD MEN gasping, yelling]
Now that that's settled,
I'm gonna stay here a bit longer
to learn more about the weather!
Also, my name is Nami, so stop
calling me "young lady" please.
First off, I'd like a house
of my own to live in.
Everybody needs a little
privacy, am I right?
I'll need a bed, too,
and feather pillows
and nice big bathtub.
No, wait--a jacuzzi!
Thanks, you guys!
Sky grandpas are the best!
Time to rock and roll!
Whoo!
[OLD MAN C]
S.O.S, Haredas! S.O.S!
[HAREDAS]
Good grief.
[NAMI panting]
[HAREDAS]
I don't understand.
You were desperate to get
off this island before.
Well, I suppose
that's your business.
Could you refresh my memory?
How does this place work?
Oh, of course.
Weatheria travels on the wind,
traversing the entire world,
though a bit slowly.
Now and then we'll send
a few of our scientists
down beneath the clouds
to pick up supplies
and gather information.
[NAMI]
Information?
Yes, to check our
records against others'.
Despite all of our research,
there are many mysterious
weather conditions in the world
that we've only been able to
scratch the surface of and--
[NAMI]
What?
Pay attention!
Oh, wow. This is crazy!
Lightning rain?
Indeed, but only on one island.
Quite strange.
It's a terrifying,
but intriguing sight.
That island is located
in the New World.
But of course,
if you brave those seas,
then you've got
to expect the unexpected,
no matter how
outlandish it may be.
[chuckles]
It's a big world out there!
Haredas.
Please take me as your student.
Teach me all you know
about the weather.
Especially in the New World!
Such a desperate plea!
Of course it is!
The lives of my crewmembers
are at stake here, y'know!
I'm their only navigator!
And when I'm on that ship,
then I take full responsibility!
It's my job to find our way,
and I will not let my captain
down, no matter what it takes!
That's because Luffy
wants to become the
King of the Pirates.
To help him, I need
to be the best navigator
the world has ever seen!
Sounds like your
captain is very lucky.
He has such a thoughtful
and clever crewmate.
[NAMI sighs]
Yeah, I have to be.
What does that mean?
Well, he is determined,
and he's reliable as a captain,
but he doesn't know
anything about the sea.
[NAMI crying]
He's so ridiculous.
Without my help,
he would be lost.
[NAMI]
Luffy.
Please help me.
He's gonna pay!
I owe him, but he's such a pain.
Huh?
I mean, he's real
high maintenance!
[HAREDAS chuckles]
Good! Then you two
balance each other out!
And I wanna give him
all the help he needs.
[NAMI]
Just like he helped me.
[NAMI] Anyway, can you tell
me about the Weather Ball?
Well, it's complicated.
One of Weatheria's masterpieces,
but quite delicate!
You must be careful.
Misuse it and the whole world
could go topsy-turvy!
[NAMI] Can it be used
as a weapon, then?
[HAREDAS] Hey, why are
you even asking that?
[NAMI]
Hmm.
[HAREDAS]
Quit smiling!
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
Nami!
Nami, you'll
always be my friend!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
on the Mechanical Island...
...in the Future Land,
Baldimore.
[MARINE A] Nothing new
on the surprise bombing
at Dr. Vegapunk's lab.
[MARINE A] We still
haven't found the culprit.
[FRANKY]
Hey, hurry up!
[ALL screaming]
[MARINE A]
It was, without exaggeration,
the greatest loss of our time!
Have you heard anything at all?
Well, rumor has it that
one of the intruders
looks a lot like a gorilla
if you can believe that.
Sorry, that's pretty
hard to believe!
I don't think he made it
all the way to the harbor.
You can't reach that
end of the island unless
you've got something that can
break through all of this ice.
Only our ships have
that kind of equipment.
People are claiming
the intruder was
none other than Cyborg Franky
of the Straw Hat Pirates.
But the only place
he's been spotted
the past month
is the Sabaody
Archipelago.
And there's no way
he could've made it
to Baldimore
from all the way
over there.
[MARINE B]
Captain Gorilla!
The search team is about
to head to the mountains!
Tell them to wait!
I'll be there shortly!
[KITTON]
What's this?
[FRANKY] The explosion must've
uncovered a hidden entrance.
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Now, that's a surprise!
I've never heard
of such a thing!
[KITTON gasps]
I can hardly believe it.
Dr. Vegapunk had
another laboratory,
right under our noses!
[barking]
[FRANKY] This must be where
he made all the cyborg animals
that worked on his projects.
[KITTON gasps, yells]
[FRANKY]
Don't break anything!
You are the last person
I wanna hear that from!
I admit, I did blow away
some valuable stuff,
but it was mostly
knick-knacks and gadgets--
things to improve
your quality of life.
That's nice, but
it's not what I need.
I'm more interested in
the weapons he designed.
The ones he's got right here.
[FRANKY]
This is insane!
There's everything from
battleships to bio-creatures.
And this is the place where
he cooked it up, day after day!
[FRANKY]
All right! It's settled!
I'm gonna live here!
--[KITTON] Huh? Here?
--[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER] Huh?
Yeah!
[ALL scream]
Thing is, I'm still gonna
need cola and stuff,
so I hope you guys don't mind
if I come by to
visit you sometimes.
[GROUP scream]
It's not that bad!
As long as you
keep this a secret
I won't cause trouble
and trouble won't find me.
--So do we have a deal?
--[GROUP screaming]
What is wrong with you three?
It's just my face!
[KITTON]
Your face is a nightmare!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Don't look at us!
There!
Is this better?
[GROUP screaming, gasps]
[GROUP]
That's not so bad.
[FRANKY]
F-F-Franky!
[GROUP screaming]
'Scuse me. It's cold in here.
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Then put on some pants!
Perfect. Now it's nice and warm!
You're still not
wearin' any pants.
This doesn't make sense.
Didn't you say that you
wanted to get off this island?
[FRANKY]
Maybe before, but...
My dream...
It would be my honor,
if you'd take my ship
and sail across the world!
Luffy...
[FRANKY]
...because of you,
I was able to
hold onto my dream.
[LUFFY]
Franky!
Thanks, the ship is great!
Just like you said,
it's the best!
We'll take good care of it!
Oh, I hate to break it to you,
but if you want
your undies back,
then you're gonna
have to join our crew!
[FRANKY] To think
I almost turned ya down.
I might've spent the rest of my
life without seeing the world.
[FRANKY] Who knows how
many seas we'll cross,
and what kind of trouble
we'll get into along the way.
[FRANKY] But when we reach
the end of our voyage,
I can truly call our ship
"the ship of dreams."
[FRANKY]
So, listen up, Luffy.
The Thousand Sunny isn't
givin' up, not ever.
[FRANKY]
And as her captain,
I know you aren't
givin' up either.
So, let's sail.
[FRANKY] I'm gonna study
my cold, hairy butt off.
When you see me again,
I'll be more super than ever!
Hold on tight, Luffy!
Our adventure's just begun!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Uh, hey, your tiger's on fire.
[FRANKY]
Huh?
[FRANKY screams]
[FRANKY] Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Put it out, put it out!
[screaming]
Hey, what was that?
[FRANKY screaming]
A monster! Stand your ground!
[FRANKY yelling]
[MARINES scream]
[ALL screaming]
[FRANKY] That's right,
Luffy, leave it to me!
Together, we'll conquer
the seas of the New World!
[MARINES scream]
[NARRATOR]
This day, a legend was born.
And for many years to come,
people would speak
in hushed voices
of the Burning
Beast of Baldimore.
[NARRATOR] In the Kamabakka
Kingdom on the Grand Line.
Say, what was the article
that caught your
attention in the paper?
Roger that.
Odd, it seems to have
calmed you down.
A message from Luffy.
A hidden message
in the newspaper
that only his friends
would understand.
Wanna know what it is?
Oh, wait, you don't
believe I'm his friend
to begin with,
so I'm not gonna tell you!
[IVANKOV]
You think you're cute, huh?
Hey. This meal is pretty
good. Who cooked it?
What a pleasant surprise!
You have quite the
discriminating palate!
It's weird though.
Suddenly, I feel like there's
this energy flowing through me.
[IVANKOV giggles]
[IVANKOV] That's because you
just ate a dish of aggression!
Such creations are
this island's specialty!
--[QUEEN A] Yes!
--[QUEEN B] Yes!
--[QUEEN C] Yes!
--[QUEEN D] Yes!
[QUEENS]
Yes!
Behold! The chiseled muscles
on my lovely candies here
are works of art!
[CAROLINE]
Ooh!
[IVANKOV]
They belie their gentle hearts.
How did my candies
become so lovely?
By eating the
dishes of aggression!
You are... what you eat!
Body, mind, and soul!
Food holds the key
to keeping it all healthy!
For example, if all
people in the world
drank a glass
of milk every day...
[IVANKOV]
...there would be less crime!
It's perfectly logical!
In other words...
[ALL]
...aggression is good!
The food you eat
can build your body?
Can't say I've ever thought of
approaching it that way before.
Those "candies" of his...
If they could build muscle
I wonder what else
is possible with that food.
Whoa! Does that mean
I could cook sexy food
and make Robin and Nami
even hotter than they are now?
'Cause that sounds awesome!
What are we gonna
we do with this guy?
What do I do with myself?
That settles it!
You gotta teach me
this magic food thing now!
Yeah, you wish!
[SANJI groans]
[SANJI groaning]
[IVANKOV]
Hold your horses, buster.
You have to earn it!
Listen, there are
99 vital recipes in all!
There are many New Kama Kenpo
techniques, but this one
is passed down as
a form of bridal training!
The secrets of Kamabakka
Kingdom don't get shared
with just any randy scum
that makes their way to us.
If you wanna learn our recipes,
you need the heart
of a true maiden!
And these ladies would
love to teach you!
Not a chance!
Sorry to disappoint, but
I'm not here to be gal pals
with your freaky little friends!
I was born...
...to love the most beautiful
ladies in the world!
[IVANKOV]
Not!
Hee-haw!
[QUEENS cheering]
Well, quirks aside,
you've got guts, boy.
I like you,
so that means
I'll give you a chance!
[SANJI]
Oh, yeah?
[IVANKOV chuckles]
But a chance is just a chance,
because I'll be giving the
recipes to the 99 grand masters
of New Kama Kenpo
on this island.
If you're half the man
you think you are,
you can defeat them and claim
the recipes for yourself.
Also, do not let
your guard down,
because every
New Kama on the island
will be trying to put this
adorable dress on you!
Hope you have fun protecting
your fragile manhood.
--[SANJI grunts]
--[QUEENS chuckle]
[QUEEN E]
Oh, Sanji!
[QUEEN F]
Say goodbye to sleeping!
[CAROLINE]
This sweet dress...
If you've never worn one before,
you're in for a treat!
They're so breathable!
--[SANJI gasps]
--[ELIZABETH] Join us!
It's nice to be girly!
[screams]
[IVANKOV]
It's just you
versus the island
of New Kama Kenpo!
Let's begin!
If you can win this fight,
I'll also throw in a ship!
Not a bad deal, if you ask me!
So, what do ya say, boy?
[SANJI gasps]
[LUFFY]
So listen, Mr.Cook!
Why don't you leave
this boat and join my crew?
--Huh?
--[LUFFY] I could use a cook
like you on my pirate ship!
[gasps]
I'm not worried.
[SANJI]
Hmph.
Because I don't think it's time
for me to die just yet.
[ZEFF] I've seen one
or two like him before--
stubborn kids who'd rather die
than have to turn away from
a fight once it's started.
I don't believe
I've heard an answer.
Could it be that
you've given up already?
Well, if you quit, then we--
[SANJI]
When I win this...
[IVANKOV]
Huh?
When I finish
beating all of them,
I bet I'll be a whole lot
stronger than I am now.
[ZEFF]
Even with 100,000 more weapons,
our chore boy can still
bring him to his knees
because he does not know fear.
[SANJI]
Hey, Luffy,
hang in there just
a little while longer.
[SANJI] I promised myself
that one of these days
I'll go to the Grand Line.
[LUFFY laughs]
Well, let's go right now!
[SANJI] It just isn't
the right time--not yet.
[SANJI] Say, have you
ever heard of the All Blue?
[LUFFY]
No.
[SANJI]
You've got to be kidding me.
That sea is a miracle.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so's mine.
Now is as good a time as any.
Why not start
my quest right now?
[LUFFY]
Sanji.
[SANJI]
I'll be joining your little crew
on your journey to
be King of the Pirates.
[gasps]
Do you hear me, Luffy?
I wanna be your cook.
[SANJI]
Luffy, when we meet again...
...you'll see.
[SANJI] I'll be the best damn
chef in all of the New World.
I'll make food fit for
the King of the Pirates!
[SANJI]
Until then...
...I must survive...
...this hell.
[SANJI]
I accept your challenge.
Now give me your worst!
[QUEENS yelling]
That's better!
Remember, we're not
going easy on you!
Just shut up and fight me.
[IVANKOV] You heard
him, ladies! Go to town!
[SANJI grunting]
[GREEN HAIR QUEEN]
Hi, Sanji!
Aww, don't give me
the cold shoulder!
[SANJI]
Can it!
How feisty!
[GREEN HAIR QUEEN yells]
[SANJI groans]
[SANJI]
Pull it together!
I can't lose yet! Not to you!
[gasps]
[SANJI groans]
[ELIZABETH groans]
That wasn't nice!
[SANJI groans]
--[QUEEN G] Peekaboo!
--[SANJI yells]
--[PINK HAIR QUEEN grunts]
--[SANJI groans]
[SANJI]
Luffy,
both of us are getting through
this, no matter what it takes!
So, I heard you're
fighting me for my recipe?
Well, Caroline is ready!
Come and get it, if you dare!
This is convenient.
After that last battle we had,
I owe you a proper beatdown!
[CAROLINE yelling]
[SANJI yelling]
Here I come!
[SANJI]
Make no mistake--I will win!
[NARRATOR]
With their reunion on hold,
each member of
the Straw Hat Crew
finds a new goal to strive for.
Thankfully, their surroundings
are ripe with opportunity.
Determined to push
forward into the New World,
they vow to show their captain
their new strength
the next time they meet.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"I Will Get Much, Much Stronger!
Zoro's Pledge to His Captain!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!