Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
You've made a
mockery of human life!
Fasfasfasfas!
What a narrow-minded
thing to say!
I gave them a new life,
and yet you think they should
just be rotting in the ground?
Observe!
[HOGBACK]
Ha!
[HOGBACK] Now, while you're
down there, lick the floor.
[CINDRY]
Yes, Master Hogback.
[CHOPPER]
A human being
whose heart and
body have been separated
is no human at all!
You've took a corpse that
had no choice in the matter
and turned it into
nothing more than a monster!
Every time you make
one of these creatures,
somewhere there's
a human you've devastated!
And what would a
stupid reindeer pirate-doctor
with such limited medical skill
possibly know about life?
Cindry! Rise!
Rise and kill them all!
One! Two! Three!
Listen, Cindry,
you don't have to
take orders from that maniac.
You--
I'll kill you.
Just because it moves
doesn't make it alive.
To be alive,
you gotta be free!
You're treating
her like she's nothing.
Anything that exists like
that can't be a human being!
Dogguin! Jigoro!
Help her! Quickly!
Save Cindry!
Kill the others!
[JIGORO]
Three Sword Style.
One hundred and eight...
...Caliber Phoenix!
Careful with that
attack, you almost killed me!
[DOGGUIN] He said, "Kill the
others" -- I'll start with you!
And once I do, I'll say,
"Jump off this tower
and put an
end to yourselves!"
My body, it won't move.
What? Cindry!
Kushishishi!
He's back!
[LUFFY]
What's going on?
Now, the time
has arrived at last,
my beautiful Oars!
Kushishishi!
[LUFFY]
"Oars Roars!
Come out, Straw Hat Crew"!
Hey! Cindry, what's
the matter with you?
Cindry, answer me!
What's going on here?
This isn't funny, Cindry!
Please!
Say something already!
[CINDRY]
My body, it won't move.
And these tears won't stop.
Your body won't move?
Do you expect
me to believe that?
And stop the
crocodile tears!
If you didn't have a
shadow put in your body,
you would be dead!
And who do you have
to thank for that, huh?
A zombie's only purpose
is to serve its master!
I made you, and I can
unmake you just as easily!
It's strange.
It seems as if the
original owner of the body
is fighting back.
Yeah, but that person
died over ten years ago.
Does that mean
a body without a soul
can still have
a will of its own?
Who can really say?
Even if we read every book
in every library in the world,
we wouldn't know.
I will kill both of them.
There we go!
That's the
Cindry I know and love!
Good to have you back!
Try to buy
me some time, okay?
I'm getting
the hell out of here!
It's a shame.
For a moment, I actually
thought a miracle had happened.
It's time for Doce Fleur!
[CHOPPER]
You get back here!
Are you kidding,
do you think I'm crazy?
Uh-oh. It sounds like
Oars has finally returned!
You stupid pirate deer!
Why are you siding with
a corpse instead of a genius?
Let me go!
You're not even
human to begin with,
so what the hell do
you even care, you monster?
The captain of our crew
is just fine
with monsters like me
and moss-heads
and perverts and cyborgs, too!
And all of us
get along just fine!
And unlike you, our captain
doesn't need to turn
people into zombie slaves
to get them to listen to him!
I don't care! Let me go!
Now!
Certainly.
Leave it to me.
Pierna Fleurs!
Why do I suddenly
feel as if I'm walking on air?
[HOGBACK]
Help me!
T-T-Time out, Doctor Chopper,
let's be reasonable!
Try to consider the
consequences here for a moment!
If you splattered
my genius brains
all over the
floor right now,
you'd be doing a disservice
to the medical community!
I don't care!
That "genius brain" of yours
is even more
rotten than your zombies!
I thought you
were a man of reason,
Doctor Chopper!
Can't we
work something out?
Eat this!
Now, Robin--
Chopper Suplex!
This guy's even
bigger than a giant!
Is that really my zombie?
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
You've kept me waiting,
haven't you, Oars?
It seems your
body and shadow
have finally fused properly.
I take it you'll
be obedient from now on?
Let's find out.
Answer me,
who is your master?
Gecko Moria.
You are my master.
No way!
Kushishishi!
Hey, what the hell
do you think you're saying?
I thought you were
'sposed to be my shadow!
You don't have to
listen to this guy--
He sucks!
Huh?
Who are you, and what's
with that dumb hat?
Kushishishi!
Now that
everything is in order,
let me give you
your first mission!
Take a look at your arm.
I've placed some
wanted posters there.
[MORIA]
These dastardly fellows
are causing a ruckus
on your poor master's island.
They're called
the "Straw Hat Pirates."
[MORIA] Find them,
crush every last one of them,
and then put them
back on their ship!
If you kill
one or two of them,
it's no problem.
Besides, their bounties
are over a hundred million,
so they won't fall
apart after a few punches,
even from you.
So don't hold back!
I want to see
every ounce of your power!
[MORIA]
Understand?
'Kay.
You got it, Master.
Oh. Found one.
It's Straw Hat.
So long. Straw Hat!
What?
You're running away?
Get back here!
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
Hey! That's my move!
You jerk!
[OARS]
...Bell!
Huh?
Uh-oh!
[HOGBACK]
What now?
Tha-That's Luffy's Zombie!
Oars! Help!
The floor's
going to collapse.
Chopper!
Over here, quickly!
Got it!
[CHOPPER]
Wow, that was a close one.
That giant is Luffy?
Hogback and Cindry
fell to the floor below
and it doesn't look
like they're moving.
[HOGBACK]
Too heavy. Damn it.
Cindry, hurry up!
Get over here
and move this rock!
This isn't funny, Cindry!
I really need
your help right now!
Oars is going to crush me
like a giant cockroach!
I can't die!
I'm far too smart to die!
I have so much left to give!
I'm your master, damn it!
Why are you just
standing there? Hurry!
I can't move.
My body won't move.
Say what?
Enough already!
I don't want
to hear anymore!
The only will a zombie has
is the will to follow orders!
So hurry up and save me!
You're nothing but
a corpse with a pretty face!
Don't pretend you're human!
Hey!
I'm dying here, Cindry!
Oars is gonna stomp me!
[HOGBACK screaming]
Oars, look down here!
Watch where
you're stepping, damn it!
[HOGBACK]
It's me, you oaf!
You'd still be dead
in a block of ice right now
if it wasn't for my genius!
[HOGBACK screaming]
[USOPP] Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
That last tremor was
one thing,
but this feels like the
whole mansion's coming down!
It's the Luffy Zombie!
[USOPP screaming]
Uh-oh.
That doesn't sound good.
What's going on here?
Crap! What now?
Is that thing
Luffy's Zombie?
[SANJI]
Damn it.
Nami, hey,
now would be
a good time to wake up.
There's nothing I can do.
Guess I'm just
gonna have to run for it.
Hey, Nami?
Nami?
She just disappeared.
[ABSALOM growls]
It's you again.
[ABSALOM] Looks like
the tables have turned.
You bastard.
So you're still alive, huh?
If you wanna finish this,
stop hiding and bring it on!
[ABSALOM laughing]
[ABSALOM]
Well, well.
That troublemaking giant
is finally under our control.
[ABSALOM] In other
words, you're screwed!
I think I'll be taking
my bride for good this time!
[SANJI]
Like hell you will!
You give Nami back!
Where the hell
are you hiding her?
[ABSALOM]
Aw, are you lonely?
Then why don't you
play with Oars, here?
Hey, that felt
like an earthquake--
What just happened?
I haven't a clue.
But whatever it was,
it made my hairs stand on end.
[BROOK] Ah, but I'm a
skeleton, so I don't have--
Oh no, wait a minute.
That's right,
I do have hair.
You fight so hard
to protect your afro,
then you forget you have it?
[FRANKY] Maybe I'll give
you a pompadour like mine.
Would that help you remember?
[BROOK]
No, no thank you.
[FRANKY]
Get over here!
What is that?
No idea,
but whatever it is,
it's giving me goosebumps.
Or, it would, but...
Oh, man.
It's some
kinda giant monster!
Have mercy!
That's...
That's a zombie.
[FRANKY]
Ah crap.
[FRANKY] That must
be Luffy's zombie.
Hey, look down there!
Someone else came
out of the building,
and it looks
like Chef Curly Brows!
[coughing]
Damn it!
I failed her.
What the
hell is he doing?
He's gonna get stomped on!
[LUFFY]
Moria!
--Kushishishi!
--Get back here!
Are you running from
your shadow or chasing me?
Giant monster me
is gonna be a problem,
but if I wanna get
everyone's shadows back
then I guess I'm gonna have
to beat you anyway, aren't I?
So get back here!
Too bad!
But it looks
like the last laugh
belongs to me!
[ABSALOM]
She's still out cold.
I'll take her
someplace safe.
Don't you worry!
It may be in private,
but we'll have our wedding yet.
My sleeping beauty.
[ZOMBIE PANDA]
Is Mistress Perona all right?
[ZOMBIE KOALA]
I think so.
She passed out,
but it doesn't
look like she was injured.
[ZOMBIE PANDA]
Where's Captain Kumacy?
Did that
long-nose guy purify him?
[ZOMBIE KOALA]
How did this happen?
Let's get out of here.
This mansion's
as good as done-for.
We can let
the special zombie
take care of
the Straw Hats for us.
This is rotten, man!
We gotta get outta
here, like right now!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 364A] The special
zombie's going on a rampage!
[ZOMBIE 343A]
I'm going back to my grave!
Look!
He's taller
than the mansion!
[MOC DONALD] He's just
stomping over everything!
We could be next!
That is not good!
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
Hey, Robin! Chopper!
We're in trouble here!
Big trouble!
The-- The Luffy
Zombie has our faces.
No wait,
I mean, on his arm!
He has our wanted posters!
What do we do now?
Aw man, this is no joke!
He's gonna hunt us down!
Show yourselves!
Come out, Straw Hats.
You can't hide from me!
Damn it, Luffy.
Your zombie's gonna
be a real pain in the ass.
C'mon, Captain,
you're not gonna tear
apart your own crew, are you?
It seems he's
been given the order.
[CHOPPER] I just hope
the real Luffy is all right.
Don't eat me, I'm all bones!
Are we supposed to
fight that damn thing? No way.
[ZORO]
Looks like fun.
[CHOPPER]
Sanji!
[FRANKY] That thing
may look like a big lug,
but it's fast on its feet!
You fight it head-on
and you're done for!
[CHOPPER]
Are you crazy, Sanji?
What are you thinking?
[FRANKY]
This is it.
It ain't gonna be pretty,
but we're gonna have to show
that monster what we're made of!
[FRANKY]
You ready?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
Luffy is the Enemy!
The Ultimate
"Zombie vs the Straw Hat Crew!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!