Mozu!
Kiwi!
I apologize for
the interruption.
It's just those
two ladies weren't
being very accommodating
about letting us in.
What the hell are you
bastards doing down here?!
Iron Body!
Hey! What's the big idea?
What gives, Blueno?!
You got some kinda
problem with me?!
Oh trying to pull
a reverse move?!
You dumbass, you should
know better than that!
No one pushes me around!
You should be pourin'
me a drink, remember?!
What did you forget
you're just a bartender?
And what's with
that outfit anyway?
What the hell are you up to?!
Not yet!
Whoa! Are you okay?
Come on man, get up!
Killing him now would put
our mission in jeopardy.
We need him alive.
Right.
Hey! What's going on here?!
I mean what did you do to piss
off these shipyard guys so bad?
The freak with the bird?
How'd he get a hit
like that on me!?
And what's the deal?
Why're you guys
comin' in on my turf
with a chip on your shoulders,
actin' like you own the place?
And hittin' girls?!
That's so not cool!
Kiwi and Mozu are like my
little sisters, you know?!
How'd you freaks even
find us here anyway?
This is my ultra
top secret base!
How we found you's irrelevant
as we are here right now.
But know this.
We came to this town
assigned to a covert operation.
We're special agents--
spies working for the
world government.
I assume even you
would know why
we came here and
what we're after.
Franky, we know the
secret that you're keeping.
Cutty Flam.
The rumor was that
Tom's apprentice
perished about eight years ago.
But you're still alive.
That's some pretty
amazing detective work.
I'm real impressed.
But I'm startin' to get a
sour feeling down in my gut.
Where is he? Where
the hell is Iceberg?
He's dead.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
It's too late to
feign innocence.
We already know everything.
It's only a matter of time
before the
government targets me.
I want you to take these
and leave the island, Franky.
Tom entrusted them to Iceberg
and Iceberg
entrusted them to you.
Hey, boys, come here.
It's about time I let you
in on somethin' important!
It's been a long game but
now we're at checkmate.
See, I know you have the
plans for the ancient weapon.
Hand over Pluton's
blueprints, Cutty Flam.
Flam, huh? That's
kind of a funny name.
How about we just call
you Franky instead?
Whatever.
Are you listening?
Hand them over this instant.
Oh, did you say hand?
What the hell did he just do?
It was so fast I couldn't
see what happened.
Hey! Are you okay?!
Oh my.
You found a room.
What do you suppose is
this filthy place's purpose?
Those are drafting tables.
Yes. Where blueprints are made
and perhaps hidden. Find them!
Look here, nameplates.
Cutty Flam. Iceberg. Tom.
The shipwright.
This picture.
Keep your paws off of that!
You're pokin' your noses
into my personal space.
My memories! This is the
place where I grew up.
What used to house the
shipbuilding company,
Tom's Workers.
Where the best
damn shipwright that ever
lived plied his craft.
Sea King!!! Eat this!
Ahhhhhh! Watch out Iceberg!
Hey! What in the hell
is wrong with you!!
Ow!
Idiot! Don't you know
you're not supposed to
be goofin' around right now?
We got real ships to work on,
not your crappy toys!
Don't yell at me when
you don't have a clue
what you're talkin'
about, ice-for-brains!
It isn't some crappy toy,
it's my super battleship,
The Battle Franky!
Whatever it is, you
need to leave it alone
before someone gets hurt!
This is Scrap Heap Island!
I can do what I want!
Wait! You'll see.
I'm gonna build a
battleship awesome enough
to take down a sea king!
Bull! What you're gonna
do is get yourself killed!
Oh yeah?
Yeah! Quick!
Nu-uh!
Real quick!
If you wanna be a man.
Show some gusto!
Well there's the ol'
launching ceremony.
One more ship sailing
with gusto! Right, buddy?
Erp! Erp! Erp!
That's about enough
work for today.
Whaddaya say
we head on home?
Erp! Erp!
Man, I'm hungry!
Let's see what's for dinner!
Erp! Erp!
Hey, hold on! Wait for us!
So today's Battle Franky model
was number-what-are-you-up to?
Eight sir! It was
really beautiful!
No it wasn't!
Your dumb weapon that he
let you build for some reason
fell apart after you almost
killed both of us with it!
Nobody asked you, ya
stupid Ice-for-brains!
Ice-for-brains?
Well you're Flunky!
Alright. That's enough
fighting, boys. Cut it out.
He started it. Not me!
My word. Don't
encourage those two, Tom.
Was it that funny?
Keep laughing and
they'll keep misbehaving.
Speaking of misbehaving.
I heard that another
ship carrying lumber
was attacked by pirates.
I swear, ever since the King
of the Pirates was executed
this place has just gone rotten
with those no-good bums.
They're taking over the city.
The people's spirits
are really low.
And because of all the
flooding from Aqua Laguna,
we can only get lumber and iron
if we ship them in
from other islands.
But with all the storms
and pirates everywhere,
it's near impossible.
The shipyards are starting to
get so desperate for customers,
they are literally fighting
each other for them.
So many have
closed down already.
At this rate, Water Seven is on
a course to sink into the ocean,
and fade from
the world's memory.
And to think, this
city made its name
making unforgettable,
unsinkable ships. Such a shame.
Hey, you built a big,
super-awesome pirate ship once,
now didn't ya Tom?
Will ya teach me how to
draw up blueprints for one, too?
What's so funny, huh?
Franky, there's no such thing
as blueprints for a pirate ship.
It's the flag, boy. Skull
and bones means pirate ship.
And a seagull flag
means that it's Navy.
Whatever you build
just remember this.
Build it with pride and a
whole lot of manly gusto!
You sure are working late
tonight. What're ya drawin'?
This here. Is hope
for our island.
It is?
Yep. Well at least,
that's what I'm hoping
that it'll turn into someday.
Now, to bed with ya.
Yes, sir.
Huh? Whoa!
The Judicial Ship is here!
What the heck is that?
A mobile court. I wonder
who they're here for.
Whaddaya think you're doing?
Let him go ya big stupid jerk!
He didn't do anything wrong.
Don't you worry.
I'll be just fine!
No Tom!! Come back!!!!
Justice was brought
to Gold Roger,
The King of the Pirates,
by way of execution!
His ship, the Oro Jackson, was
built by none other than Tom,
who stands before
this court today!
As penalty for aiding and
abetting that vicious criminal,
Tom will be taken
to Enies Lobby,
where he will be executed!
No!
The verdict was read! Guilty!
They're gonna execute Tom!
They say it's
because he built a ship
for the King of the Pirates.
Damn shame.
That thing brought a whole
lot of grief into the world.
Now, building ships
is not a crime.
And one may sell them to almost
anyone who wishes to buy.
But we must make an exception
for the King of the Pirates.
On the charge of providing
meaningful assistance
to the man who
terrorized the entire world.
We hereby sentence Tom
to death. Take him away!
Come on, time to go.
Move it! You heard him!
Hurry up!
Go already!
Hey, what're you doing?!
I've got a new design.
For a completely new
kind of paddle steamer!
A train that will run on the
surface of the ocean with gusto!
Shut up and get movin'!
This once great island
has lost its gusto.
Our trade is not what is used
to be. People have lost hope.
Water Seven is
slowly sinking away.
Every day our hard working
citizens are filled with worry.
I can lift their spirits.
I will by building our
good people a sea train!
Quit flappin' your gums
and move your feet.
No, let him stay.
Huh?
Sea train. Tell me more.
It's like a ship.
But one that puffs out
steam and runs on a track.
It'll go between the islands,
carrying people and
all kinds of goods.
Even other ships.
Most importantly, it won't be
affected by conditions at sea.
That's ridiculous!
A railway on the water
will be ripped to pieces
once Aqua Laguna comes around.
And even if it doesn't,
what're ya gonna do about
all the Sea Kings out there?
It doesn't have to be a
completely fixed track.
It'll be submerged
under the water a bit,
so it won't be
bombarded by the waves.
It'll sway just like
a rope in the water.
The sea train will
just use the tracks
as a guide to get
from place to place.
I'm also considering
installing a mechanism that
emits a loud dissonant sound
underwater to discourage fish
from getting anywhere
near the tracks.
It should work on
Sea Kings as well,
so they won't pose a threat.
Whoa, is all that possible?
If we connect St. Poplar, Pucci,
San Faldo and this island.
We can create a booming economy
that will help out all of us.
Amazing!
I will be finished with
the blueprints very soon.
But it will take a master
shipwright to build it.
Now could this sea train
run to Enies Lobby as well?
Without a doubt, your honor.
Once the plans are in the can
and the railway is in the water.
People can go with gusto
from island to island
for work or play!
And once again Water Seven
will be a city filled with hope!
How long will it take?
10 years.
Then build it!
If you agree to
develop this sea train,
I will give you
the time to do it.
Consider these next
ten years as probation!
That's great news!!
Good luck, Tom!
Save Water Seven, please!
I'm glad you think
this is so funny.
I thought you were a goner.
I was worried sick over you.
But I guess if this
plan of yours works out,
they're willing to forgive
and forget the whole
Gold Roger affair.
Mwell! I just gotta tell ya
how amazed I am with ya Tom!
What a great idea!
It's unbelievable!
To think that you just came
up with that on your own!
It's Brilliant! When you told--
Thanks for the grub!
Come on, Yokozuna!
I'll teach you the front crawl!
Erp!
Hey, we're all celebrating
here and you wanna leave?
What's your deal!?
My deal?! What happened
to Tom was so unfair!
He built the only
ship that was able
to sail the whole Grand Line!
Something no one else
in the world could do.
And those jerks wanna
put him to death over it?!
They don't realize
how hard that is!
They couldn't even
string together a raft
if their lives depended on it!
I mean, I know that the
whole reason our office
is under this bridge is
'cause those stupid people
kicked you out of
town over that ship!
You're the greatest
ship builder the world
has ever known and they
treat you like garbage!
What're ya laughin'
at ya big yellow weirdo?
You're crazy! Stop attacking
him, ya stupid kid!
Why does he have ta
laugh at everything?
No, no, no!
You're doin it wrong!
Stroke harder and
push that water back!
Erp! Erp!
No! No! Do it harder!
Don't hold back!
That Franky's got a lotta nerve.
If I were you, I'd kick
him out for what he just did!
Mwell, I know the boy
can be a handful,
but he's a fellow shipbuilder.
At his young age,
he's almost on par with the
best craftsmen on the island.
He does build battleships, yeah.
His problem is he's too honest.
Two years ago, I met that
kid on Scrap Heap Island.
He'd gone there to collect
junk to make a cannon,
and was firing it with gusto!
Old guy hey! Help me out.
My good-for-nothing
parents ditched me!
Apparently, his folks
couldn't handle
his rambunctious behavior,
so they threw
him off their ship.
Sounds like a couple of
heartless pirates to me, eh?
What a joke.
Now, Tom.
He is one tough kid.
He's had a rough go at it,
but he's still got a good heart.
I'm positive that both of
you boys are gonna grow up
to be world-class
shipwrights some day.
There's no need
for you to be rivals.
I don't know about all that.
It's like he's allergic
to sanity or something.
Mwell. I just need to
finish those blueprints
and then we'll build
ourselves a sea train!
Yeah. I bet he
won't help at all.
He can do whatever he wants!
Suicide?
That's the word. Head of
the fourth largest shipyard.
What a tragic story.
They ran out of materials
so he took a ship out
to sea to get some more.
Lost fifty men on the water.
They had to close down his shop.
Aw man. Will this
be how it ends?
Is this how Water
Seven finally dies?
Hey! Did you guys hear?
Big news from Scrap Heap Island!
No way! Did they do it!?
Did Tom's Workers actually
finish the sea train?!
Whoa! Is this crazy
thing really gonna work?
I don't know if I trust
something built by a criminal.
I'll try it out!
What the heck, me too!
They gonna tell us
how it works?!
All aboard ladies and gentlemen!
There it goes!
The paddles are
grabbing the railway!
Man that is the
coolest thing ever!
Twelve years ago,
departing from an isolated city
in decline and full of
passengers who'd almost given
up hope for a brighter future.
The sea train
"Puffing Tom" embarked
on its maiden voyage
across the sea!
So this is the home of your
dearest memories with Tom.
I'm telling ya, I ain't
got the blueprints!
You're wasting your time!
Well seeing as you're a
criminal just like he was,
you shouldn't be surprised when
you meet the same grim fate!
You don't know anything
about the real Tom!
So shut your damn mouth!
On the next One Piece:
"Spandam's Scheme!
The Day the Sea Train Shook."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!