Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Look! The drawbridge
is lowering!
Our reinforcements
pulled it together after all.
And just in time, too.
I'm trembling with excitement!
Hey, Robin! We'll
save you! No matter what!
Come on, hurry up!
Lookin' scary there, Zoro.
So, I hear you're a bad guy.
Are you still here?
You're stuck out here for all
the world to see and nothing.
Are you really all that strong?
Mind your own business!
When I joined up with Luffy,
I never thought it
would bring me here.
Now die!
You're weak, Zoro.
Nothing ever changes.
I made a promise to her.
And I can't afford to
die in a place like this.
You again?
Don't you have things to do?
I'll untie you, but only if
you promise to join my crew.
Your what?
I run a pirate crew and I'm
looking for people to join up.
No way! I'd never stoop
to joining up with a criminal.
Screw that business.
And what's wrong
with being a pirate?
They're despicable.
Like I'd ever wanna
join up with one.
Oh, come on! Gimme a break!
Everyone already knows you
as some vicious bounty hunter,
always out for blood.
People can say whatever
they want about me.
But I've never done a single
thing in my life that I regret.
I will make it
through this challenge.
And after that,
I'll accomplish what I want.
Yeah. That's great.
But I've already decided that
you're going to be on my crew.
What? You can't do that!
I hear you're one of
the best swordsmen around.
Well, I am. But that idiot
Captain's son took mine away.
Guess I'll just have
to go get it back for you.
What?
So if you want your sword,
you're just gonna
have to join my crew.
Now you're really
pissing me off!
Wait. He's actually
gonna bust in there alone?
Do not let that man escape!
Captain! There's someone
in the crucifixion yard!
What?
I'm surrounded by traitors!
You have to get
out of here, Zoro.
That maniac's going to kill you
for what you're doing right now!
I can't stand to watch
the Marines behave
like this anymore.
A true Marine
should be honorable.
Look, kid. I can't leave.
I got ten days left.
And then they're--
Well, not quite.
They're gonna
execute you tomorrow.
They're what?
Helmeppo never intended
to honor your agreement.
He's planned on killing
you from the start.
Which made Luffy really angry,
so he just knocked him out.
He did?
Now that the Marines are mad,
they're dead-set
on catching Luffy.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna ask you to
become a pirate, though.
But I hope you'll help him.
You have a lot of
strength you can offer.
Luffy's the only person here
who can actually save
you from execution.
And, of course, you're the
only one who can save him,
from a very similar fate.
End of the line!
You've been pulling some
interesting moves around here.
What is this?
Some kind of poorly
executed coup
you two planned
with the Straw Hat?
I've always fought alone,
like a real man does.
Not like a coward,
who hides behind his wall
of expendable cronies.
Roronoa Zoro. Don't you
dare underestimate me.
You may be a strong fighter,
but under my authority,
you're just the rat we
throw out with the trash.
Take aim!
No.
I can't afford to die here!
You're weak, Zoro.
Nothing ever changes.
Gum Gum--
Rocket!
Fire!
What?
Luffy, no!
Straw Hat!
See ya!
That won't work on me!
Told you I was strong!
What the--?
Who the hell are you?
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
And I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates.
Right. You must be completely
out of you rubbery mind.
Do you have any
idea what that means?
King of the Pirates means
King of the Pirates.
How could it mean
anything other than that?
Yeah, when he first
told me, it was shocking,
but he's completely serious.
That's how he is, I suppose.
Cause he actually seems
to have every intention
of becoming King of the Pirates,
and obtaining the
world's ultimate treasure.
The One Piece.
Here's what I promised you.
There's three.
I couldn't tell which was yours
so I just took all of them.
All of them belong to me.
I use santoryu,
the three swords style.
Take 'em already!
Just know that if
you fight with me now,
you'll be a government
defying villian.
So it's either that,
or you're left out here
and killed by the
marines execution style.
What are you, the son of
the devil? It doesn't matter.
Cause if I don't
choose your side,
I'll just end up
dead on these sticks.
So let's do it.
So you're finally
gonna join my crew!
This is the best
thing ever! All right!
Would you quit
celebrating already
and get these ropes off me?
What the--? What is he?
The bullets just
bounced right off him!
Straw Hat's no ordinary
human like the rest of us.
He must have eaten
one of those devil fruits
that we've heard all
those rumors about.
Devil Fruit?
Come on! Hurry!
They got these
things on here tight!
Come on! Quit screwing around!
It doesn't matter
what abilities they have,
all who oppose me are executed!
If the guns won't work, we chop!
That's funny.
The knots got tighter
instead of looser.
Give me one of
my damn swords now!
Luffy, look!
Roronoa Zoro!
Wow! That's so cool!
Make one move and you die.
He's scary!
Today I officially
become a criminal,
having fought the Marines.
So, I'll become a pirate.
That, I can promise you.
But I want you to know one
thing, while I'm with you,
the only thing I dedicate myself
to is fulfilling my ambition!
Which is?
To be nothing less than the
world's greatest swordsman.
If somewhere along the
way I have to give that up,
then I want you to
accept responsibility.
After which you get
to apologize to me.
The world's greatest swordsman.
Sounds pretty good.
The King of the Pirates
wouldn't have any less
than the best on his crew.
Big talker.
From this point on, no matter
if I'm a criminal or not,
I will spread the name
Zoro throughout the world!
What are standing
there frozen for?
I want you to kill all
three of them right now!
You might wanna duck.
Gum-Gum Whip!
Yes! You knocked 'em all down!
Wanna tell me what you are?
I'm just a guy who
ate the Gum-Gum fruit.
What's the Gum-Gum fruit?
A rubber person?
It looks like he does
have the Devil Fruit powers.
Captain, we don't stand
a chance against them!
Yeah, just look at them!
They're insane!
We couldn't even take
on Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order.
Every marine that just
spouted weakness,
pull your gun out
and shoot yourself.
I can't do anything
with weak soldiers!
What babies. This'll be easy.
Luffy!
Bring those Marines
crumbling to their knees!
Rankless, low-life bums!
You have no right
to defy my superiority!
I am Marine Captain
"Axe-Hand" Morgan!
And I'm Luffy. Nice to meet ya.
Look! He's been hit!
You runt.
Now die!
I don't think so!
The Captain's getting
pummeled out there!
It's embarrassing.
You call yourself a Marine.
But you destroyed
my friend Coby's dream.
Straw Hat! Stop right there!
Look at what I got!
Are you stupid or
something? I said stop!
If you would pay
attention to me,
I have a hostage here
you might wanna look at!
Helmeppo's crazy!
Hey.
If you value your
squatty little friend's life
you won't move a muscle!
I'm serious one move
and I'll shoot him! I swear!
Luffy, listen!
Don't let anything that happens
to me stop you no matter what!
Even if I die!
Of course. You got it.
You hear that, you big idiot?
Coby is ready to
die by your hand.
Don't you move!
I said don't move or
I'll shoot! I swear it!
Luffy! Behind you!
Gum Gum.
Time's up.
For I am fearless Marine
Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
Daddy, hurry up
and kill him already!
Pistol!
Nice one!
Thank you.
I'm just doing my job, Captain.
What happened? Why'd it stop?
Damn those marines!
They really piss me off!
Stop getting in the way!
Don't worry about
those tremors, Robin.
Like I said, I'm just
trembling with excitement.
We will save you.
No matter what happens.
Well, you said there's a
whole bunch of bad guys, right?
And you look scared
out of your mind.
For your information
I have nerves of steel,
I'm perfectly okay
with tons of bad guys!
After all, you're looking at the
legendary Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the high seas!
Dammit!
Alright, fine I'm scared!
Why shouldn't I be,
they're Captain Kuro's men!
These guys mean business!
I don't need pity!
If you guys are sticking round
cause you pity me, just leave!
I don't need you laughing at me!
We're not laughing at you.
We're helping because
you are honorable.
You really think we'd
risk our lives out of pity?
Aw. You guys!
Usopp!
It hurts. It hurts
so bad, I can't move.
Even if you did somehow
catch up to Jango,
he'd end your life
in the blink of an eye.
Staying there is
what's best for you.
I don't care.
I don't care that
I'm weak. I'll protect them.
I'm Captain of
the Usopp Pirates!
A brave warrior of the sea who
fights for what he holds dear!
I will protect everyone in
the village if it kills me!
On my word you will never
set foot in that village!
What's his deal?
He's yellin' about something!
Check it out! He's crying!
What's so funny?
Luffy! Me and Usopp are gonna
chase down that hypno-freak.
Is that a problem?
No! Hurry!
Looks like you're one
step too late, swordsman!
Wouldn't say that!
Excellent! That branch was
getting in the way of my shot!
What?
Usopp, you're here!
Now! Time for
the Exploding Star!
You're really doing it.
You're going to
take to the ocean.
Yeah. I've decided to get going
before I have time
to change my mind.
Please, don't stop me.
I won't. I know it's
time for you to go.
Kaya don't be sad about it.
Just think the next
time I come back here,
I'll tell you about adventures
that'll sound more like
lies than my old lies.
Good. I'll look forward to it.
You guys take care!
I hope we meet again sometime!
How come?
Well, because I-- Are you
antisocial or something?
I'm taking off for
life on the high seas
and I hope that we'll eventually
meet again that's all.
What are you talking
about? Get on already!
Huh?
We're friends,
right? So, get on.
This is it.
I'm really a pirate Captain now!
Don't be stupid, Usopp!
I'm the Captain!
Hey! Straw Hats!
Why are you all
just standing around?
We're not "standing around"!
The bridge broke --
there's no way over!
It's halfway down, isn't it?
That's more than enough.
I'll be there in
about 4 seconds.
Jump into the waterfall!
Give it all
you've got! Trust me!
Monster Granny?
What did she say?
Well she said jump
into the waterfall.
Look, it's the sea train!
Hey. What's with
that devious chuckle?
Let's go!
This is On-Location
Tsubaki, a shady reporter
who'll be helping us
out with this report.
His favorite words
and catchphrase are:
"I'm so happy
that words fail me".
This is On-Location Tsubaki.
Luffy, you set out
to sea alone, right?
Please, tell us how
a complete simpleton
such as yourself was
able to survive on his own.
Uh, okay! Before I set sail,
I packed up lots of meat
and water that
I got in the village.
But I ate them
right after I left.
I'm so dumbfounded,
words fail me.
So after that,
I was starving and thirsty.
It was a really rough time.
I managed to stay alive
by eating mushrooms
and other stuff some
goof left on the boat.
No one left mushrooms!
They grew there
because of the humidity!
Every once in a while,
a giant fish would jump
out of the sea
and try to eat me!
And I was always
glad when they did!
I'd beat 'em up
and eat 'em whole!
Ate them? You could've died!
It sounds to me like you
were just absurdly lucky.
But I knew I'd be okay!
'Cause I believe in myself!
Whoa! That's so powerful,
words fail me.
And it wasn't long after that
that the intellectually
challenged Zoro
joined your crew.
I bet your answers
won't be much better.
You two idiots were
made for each other.
How've you been
able to stay alive?
I set out to sea way
before Luffy did,
so I was more
experienced than he was.
I'd already gotten
used to it, more or less.
Since he's a complete moron,
our survival was up to me.
Every once in a while, a giant
fish would jump out of the sea
and try to eat us, and I was
always glad when they did.
I'd beat 'em up
and eat 'em whole.
As much as I wanted to be wrong,
I knew you were
going to say that.
In other words,
you two could have starved
to death at any time,
putting an abrupt end
to all of your adventures.
Maybe so. But it takes
a real man to die
and then come back from
the dead without dying.
Whoa! That's so stupidly
manly, words fail me.
Right! That's when
Nami entered the picture!
Yep! One of the first things
I noticed about them
was their surprising lack of
planning or sense of danger.
Which is exactly why, once
I joined their crew,
I put myself in charge
of food management.
It was a challenge.
I had to think of ways
to preserve our cheese,
bread, meat, and water.
If it wasn't for me, I'm sure
those two would be dead by now.
So, in other words.
They owe me their lives.
Whoa! That smile is
so scheming, words fail me.
Which brings us to
the lying coward Usopp:
next to join the gang.
With him came the Going Merry,
a fine ship you buffoons
somehow managed
to leave the village with.
That's right. And they've always
been grateful to me for it.
You weren't the one
who gave it to us, jackass.
Yeah, it was Kaya.
Only because I was
good friends with Kaya!
Less fighting, more talking.
At this point, did something
change in your lives?
Uh-huh! Usopp's
a great fisherman,
so we caught fish
instead of beating them up!
But they were dinky fish,
like sardines and stuff.
Not much of a meal.
You jerk! I think
seasonal fish taste better
than those sea monsters
you were eating!
The Merry happened
to have a galley,
so that was the time I started
cooking for you guys.
And Usopp had a lot
of good seasonings
for some strange reason.
Truth be told,
Nami's cooking was great!
It just wasn't free,
which is kinda lame.
We told her to never cook again!
A girl's gotta make
a living, you know!
Devils come in all shapes
and sizes, don't they?
Finally, we have the chef who
keeps his kitchen oh-so clean
and his thoughts oh-so dirty!
To be honest, I only
wanna cook for Nami!
The others can suck it!
Since Sanji joined the crew,
meals aren't just something
we have to have to stay alive:
we really look forward to them!
If we catch any fish
or birds or stuff like that,
he'll turn them all
into really yummy food!
And, due to his
culinary expertise,
we always get balanced meals!
When he took over the cooking,
I was able to focus
on being the navigator.
That's the only
thing he's good at,
so the rest of us
make the best of it.
What? Bastard!
Now then, Sanji.
I think the time has
come in this interview
to let our viewers know exactly
what the food you eat during
your journeys tastes like.
Again, words fail me.
You're a terrible reporter!