[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people who
seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[IGARAM groaning]
Can't die here.
I have an important
mission to complete.
I must keep going...
[MR. 5] Three of you lost
against a single pirate?
Now that's just sad.
[ALL gasp]
[IGARAM] Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Why are you here?
You mean you haven't
figured it out?
There are people
here whose crimes
against the company
are grave enough
that the Boss has sent
us to deal with 'em.
[MR. 5] He said someone
had learned his secrets.
I don't know what
secrets, exactly.
I don't wanna know obviously
someone else did.
So, while we were
conducting our search
to find out who had uncovered
the Boss's secrets,
we learned something.
[laughs] It turns out
a rather high ranking individual
from a certain kingdom
has somehow managed to
infiltrate Baroque Works.
[IGARAM]
They know! It's all over now.
Die! Igarappappa!
You will not lay a hand
upon our princess;
not while the captain of
Alabasta security still stands!
[VIVI]
Igaram!
[MR. 5] Igaram, Captain
of Alabasta security,
and Princess Vivi Nefertari
of Alabasta Kingdom,
we have come here in the name
of the Boss of Baroque Works
to see that you are
both eliminated.
[LUFFY]
"All Out Battle!
Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!"
[ZORO]
Ah, damn it.
Luffy's trapped. I'd better
go do somethin' about it...
Go on! Princess Vivi,
you have to escape!
Igaram!
[VIVI gasping]
[MR. 9 gasps]
Igaram!
[MISS VALENTINE]
Don't bother.
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
[VIVI grunts]
Dirty monsters!
[MR. 9] You mean you're really
a princess, Miss Wednesday...?!
Oh, wow!
A very busy princess
right now, Mr. 9!
[ZORO] Well, I've had enough
fun for one night. See ya!
[IGARAM]
Princess Vivi...
Oh, Igaram!
You're hurt!
[IGARAM]
Vivi, please...
...forget about me.
You must get away from here.
For our... homeland.
[gasping]
If you were to be harmed,
Alabasta Kingdom would suffer.
Please Princess, you must hurry!
If you think you can escape
from us, you're mistaken.
Let's see if you can take me!
[VIVI gasps]
[MR. 9] This whole princess
thing is pretty confusing,
but we've been fighting
together for a long time.
So get going.
I'm going to buy you some
time for a head start.
Thank you, Mr. 9.
Pretty manly of me,
don't you think?
Bye‐bye, Baby!
I hope you're prepared for this!
All that is asked of us
agents is to do our jobs
and to do them well.
Forming such pathetic
friendships is for the weak,
it's time that you learned
that my Nose Fancy...
[MR. 9]
Bloody Bat!
[MR. 5]
...Cannon!
[MR. 9 yelps]
Oh, no, MR. 9!
Wait hold on a second did that
just come out of his nose?
Hey, what are you doin'?!
Swordsman I have a most
unreasonable request,
but I need someone with
strength such as yours!
Yeah, right!
You gotta be kidding!
Would you let go of me?!
Both of those villains
possess Devil Fruit Powers,
and there's nothing
I can do to stop them.
That is why I'm begging you now.
Please protect Princess Vivi
of Alabasta in my place!
Let go. Huh?
‐‐[MR. 5 grunts]
‐‐[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
[VIVI gasping]
[VIVI]
Karoo! Run!
And off she goes.
She won't get very far.
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Right behind you, Mr. 5.
Surely you will be rewarded if
you can deliver the princess
safely to our noble home
of Alabasta Kingdom.
I am just a humble servant, but
I am begging you to do this.
Please, protect the
princess! I beg you!
[IGARAM coughs]
Forget it! I'm not helping you!
Until a few minutes ago, you
were still trying to kill me!
What do ya think I am a fool?!
[NAMI]
So, about this reward...
[ZORO, IGARAM]
Huh?
I'll take it.
All right. How does a
billion berries sound?
Nami?
Huh...?! What did you say?!
Ma... Ma... Maaa.
[ZORO]
I thought you were asleep.
[NAMI]
Gimme some credit.
Who in their right mind
would go to sleep in a town
that welcomes pirates
like Whiskey Peak.
It was all an act,
a charade, a pretense.
Oh, I can't drink anymore
but I have to win the contest.
[grunts]
Whatever.
Maa... Maa... Maaa...
So, why don't you go ahead
and promise us that
one billion berry reward,
huh, Captain?
Because if we don't agree to
help your precious princess,
then she's probably gonna die.
I'm just a simple soldier.
I cannot promise such
an immense reward.
Surely you aren't suggesting
your princess's life
is worth less than that.
[IGARAM grunts]
Right?
[gasps]
Doesn't really fight fair,
does she?
[coughs] I can't
promise anything,
but if you're willing to deliver
the princess to Alabasta,
then you had best negotiate
the terms of the reward
directly with her.
[NAMI] Heh. Which means I
have to save her first, huh?
[IGARAM] Please understand.
Her life is in danger!
[NAMI]
Oh, all right.
I'll go ahead and save your
darling princess for now.
Ah!
[ZORO]
Hm?
Well, Zoro, go get her!
Screw that! No!
If you want to make
money, then fine,
but you don't have
to involve me in it!
[NAMI]
Don't be stupid and stubborn.
The money that I make
is certainly mine,
but the contracts that I
land benefit all of us.
Why can you not see that?
Do you seriously expect me
to buy into that crap?!
What? All you really have to
do here is cut up a few guys.
[ZORO]
Oh, really, is that all?
Don't boss me around like
you do that idiot cook!
Oh, I see.
You're just afraid that you're
gonna end up losing to them.
You wanna try saying that
again, you greedy brat?!
You're a big baby who's
afraid of losing...
[LUFFY]
Bathroom.
[ZORO] You'd better shut
your mouth right now.
Besides, did you forget?
You still owe me some
money from a while back.
What? I don't owe you anything.
[NAMI] Yeah, I lent you a
hundred thousand berries
for some swords in Loguetown.
And I gave you the hundred
thousand back almost right away.
Someone gave me the swords,
so I didn't even need
your stupid berries.
Maybe so, but you agreed
to pay me 300%,
bringing your total
to 300,000 berries.
[ZORO]
I need to borrow some money.
[NAMI]
Sure! For 300% interest.
And you agreed to it,
you still owe interest.
I gave you the 100,000
back the same day!
You can't really expect
me to pay you interest!
Sure can.
Come on. Can't you even
keep one little promise?
[ZORO grunting]
Now, just do what I say, and
I'll consider calling us even.
Someday you're gonna die
a horrible death.
Oh, yes. And I'm sure
I'll go straight to Hell.
[ZORO]
Damn woman!
[NAMI laughs]
Thanks Zoro!
[ZORO]
Shut up!
[IGARAM]
I'm so ashamed.
[NAMI]
Hm?
If I had been stronger,
I could have protected
Princess Vivi like she deserves.
Oh, she'll be fine.
He looks stupid,
but he's really strong.
[IGARAM] If anything were
to happen to Princess Vivi,
the kingdom of Alabasta would
be... it would be done for!
Huh?
She must escape! She has to...
[VIVI]
Run, quickly!
Run, Karoo!
There's a ship docked back
behind the cactus rocks.
We're going to take it and
escape from this place.
Then we'll be on our
way to Alabasta.
[LUFFY sighs] Much better!
Now back to the sleep...
Mm?
What the heck happened here?!
[VIVI]
Hurry, Karoo!
[KAROO squawks]
[gasps]
[VIVI]
Karoo, stop!
[KAROO squawks]
Oh, no, it's Mr. 5.
They found us!
Hurry, Karoo. Move!
[KAROO squawks]
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
[MR. 5] It's kinda cute
that she's trying.
[VIVI gasps]
Miss... Monday!
[squawks]
Go on.
You can reach the ships
by going through here.
I'll stay here and
hold off the others.
[VIVI]
You sure?
[MISS MONDAY] After losing to
that green‐haired swordsman,
we're all going to be punished
for failing our mission anyway.
At least if I do that,
I can go down
while helping to
protect a friend.
[MISS MONDAY] What are you
waiting around here for?!
If you get killed or captured,
Mr. 8 and Mr. 9
will have sacrificed themselves
for nothing. Now get going!
[VIVI]
Thank you.
[MR. 5] First Mr. 9 defected,
and now you...
Miss Monday?
I am not going
to let you pass.
Because I've made a
promise to a friend.
[laughs] That's adorable.
[MR. 5]
You are an utter disgrace.
[MISS MONDAY growling]
[MISS MONDAY yells]
[MISS MONDAY gasps]
[MR. 5]
To the name of Baroque Works!
No... Miss Monday...
How could they?!
[MR. 5 chuckles]
That's why they call me
the Bomb Man.
You see, I can make any
part of my body explode,
and thanks to my
Bomb‐Bomb Fruit power,
there hasn't been
a single mission
that I have failed to complete.
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
[gasps]
[MISS VALENTINE] And thanks
to the Kilo‐Kilo Fruit power
that I possess, I can
bury that traitor,
Miss Monday, in
the ground forever.
I can change how much
I weigh whenever I want.
Right now I'm light enough to
be lifted by a slight breeze.
But I think it's time
to start gaining weight.
Five kilograms...
Fifty kilograms...
[VIVI whimpers]
A hundred... Five hundred...
A thousand...
Ten Thousand Kilogram Press!
So... Do you really still
think you can escape from us?
You don't have a chance
of gettin' out of here
in one piece.
[VIVI gasping]
[whimpers]
[VIVI] I will survive...
I will escape.
I will make it back home
to Alabasta Kingdom.
Take this.
My Nose Fancy...
...Cannon!
Mister Bushido!
That could've been me!
So who is this clown?
[groaning] I just cut
someone's snot.
Damn it.
I don't have time for this.
Don't you ever give up?!
[VIVI gasps]
I'm here to help.
So just calm down.
What? You're helping me?
[MR. 5]
Heh.
[NAMI]
Tell me...
...Baroque Works. Exactly
what kind a company is it.
It's a... secret
crime syndicate.
It specializes
in assassinations,
espionage, and bounty‐hunting.
The "company" is so secretive
that none of its members know
the Boss's name or face,
but they will still do anything
that the Boss commands them to.
[NAMI]
Hm. I don't get it.
Why would any rational person
listen to some big boss
whose identity they
don't even know?
[IGARAM] The ultimate
objective of Baroque Works
is the creation of
an "ideal" nation.
And everyone who does well
within the company now
will be guaranteed high social
standing within this nation.
This is the promise that drives
them to blindly follow.
[NAMI]
Now that makes more sense.
[IGARAM] The agents all have
numbers as their codenames.
The Boss's codename is Mr. 0.
So, the closer an agent's
number is to zero,
the stronger and more
skilled they are,
and the higher their future
standing will be.
The agents from MR. 5 and above
are especially powerful.
Incredibly so.
I take it that you must be
the swordsman who beat up
all the lowly employees who
were stationed out here.
[MR. 5]
Why would you wanna protect
the princess of Alabasta?
[ZORO] Let's just say that
I have my own reasons.
[MR. 5]
Well, one way or another,
we're gonna have
to eliminate you.
You see. You're in our way.
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
Aw, what a shame.
[MR. 5 chuckles]
[LUFFY]
I found you!
[gasps]
[MR. 5]
Hm?
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
[MISS VALENTINE]
What is it now?
Luffy!
Thanks for coming,
but I got this one.
Unless that greedy brat
dragged you into this, too.
[ZORO]
Huh?
[LUFFY panting]
You are gonna pay for what
you did! I'll kill you!
[ZORO]
Huh? What?!
What kind of nonsense have you
gotten into your head this time?
[LUFFY]
Shut up and get ready!
Because I'm about to kick
your ungrateful little ass!
Un... grateful?!
That's right!
[LUFFY] What happened?
Who did this to you?
It was that friend of yours...
The mean swordsman
with the green hair.
Zoro?
Everyone here was nothing
but nice to us.
They welcomed us and threw us
a party and they gave us food,
and you repaid them
by cutting them all up
with those swords of yours!
Yeah, but... There's something
you don't know.
Just shut up, and fight me!
This guy's just
a complete idiot.
[KAROO]
Mm.
Heh. And now they're fighting
amongst themselves.
How pathetic.
[laughs] If we wait long enough
maybe they'll kill each other
and we won't have
to bother with them.
[exhales] Hold on Luffy.
Can you just listen
to me for a second?
They were actually‐‐
[LUFFY]
No excuses!
Wait! No!
[LUFFY growls]
You trying to kill me?!
Uh‐huh... Die!
[ZORO groans]
Damn it, listen!
[LUFFY yells]
He's gone crazy!
Luffy stop this!
[MISS VALENTINE]
Well, Mr. 5.
It looks like they're too
busy beating each other up
to cause us any trouble.
Apparently.
So why don't we just leave
those two idiots to the fight,
while we do the job that we
were sent here to complete.
Eliminating Princess Vivi
of Alabasta Kingdom.
[LUFFY] Hey, tough guy,
quit running away.
[ZORO]
Listen to me...
[MR. 5]
Shall we, Miss Valentine?
[MISS VALENTINE]
Yes, Mr. 5.
[gasps]
[ZORO]
Quit screwing around, damn it!
Ya dumbass!
[MR. 5]
Now you and your friend
have really managed to get
in the way of our plans.
[MISS VALENTINE]
What happened? What's going on?
[MR. 5] Since you two want
to kill each other so badly,
I tell you what.
We're gonna do you a favor.
We'll kill you both
ourselves. Okay?
[MISS VALENTINE]
Now I'm really annoyed!
I hope you're ready
to experience my
Kilo‐Kilo Fruit power!
Ha, ha, ha! Prepare to be
smashed into a thousand
tiny pieces and buried a
hundred meters in the ground.
[VIVI] Mister Bushido! You have
to get out of the way...
[ZORO]
Be quiet.
[gasps]
I have more important things
to worry about right now.
[LUFFY]
That was a good workout.
I've finally managed to
digest some of that food.
He... He fought...
Mr. 5... and won?!
He took out one of
Baroque Works' best agents!
All right, now let's
finish this.
‐‐[ZORO] Okay, Luffy...
‐‐[MISS VALENTINE] Here I come!
Everyone who lives
here in Whiskey Peak
is really a bounty hunter.
Which makes all of
them our enemies.
Hey, pay attention to me,
you jack ass!
[MR. 5 groans]
You're just lying!
Enemies wouldn't give us
tasty food, would they?!
[MISS VALENTINE]
Taste my 10,000 Kilogram Press!
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
Fine then.
It doesn't look like there's any
sense in trying to talk to you.
[LUFFY growls]
You know, you're really a moron.
This time I'm not
gonna hold back.
It'll be your own
fault if you die.
[LUFFY]
Sounds good to me!
Just a sec.
What's going on here?
I thought you guys were
on the same side!
Ready for my Gum‐Gum...
[ZORO]
Oni...
[LUFFY growls]
[ZORO growls]
[ZORO] ...Giri!
[LUFFY] ...Bazooka!
[ZORO]
Let's see which one's stronger.
Your rubber hands or
my steel, whaddya say?
Yeah, let's settle this
once and for all.
[ZORO]
Tatsu... Maki!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Pistol!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY groans]
[ZORO groans]
Well now what am I
supposed to do?
I don't know how safe we'll
be going through there.
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY yelling]
[ZORO growling]
[LUFFY grunts]
[ZORO groans]
[MR. 5]
Damn it.
Those two are makin' fools
of us all on our own turf.
The name of Baroque
Works will be shamed
if we fail in our mission here.
Mr 5, we can still defeat them.
We haven't failed yet.
[MR. 5]
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
[MISS VALENTINE]
Right, Mr. 5.
[MR. 5]
You can't beat us.
Prepare to die at the hands of
Baroque Works officer agents!
[BOTH]
Shut up and go away.
[BOTH gasp]
[LUFFY, ZORO]
You're interfering...
[BOTH whimper]
[BOTH]
...with our fight!
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[NAMI] Whose bright idea
was it to bring her?
Now we'll have more
people after us!
[LUFFY]
Well, I'm excited!
[ZORO]
Yeah, quit complaining.
[LUFFY]
A real, live princess!
[NAMI] You don't get it, do you?
We're in trouble here!
[ZORO] Give it up! We've already
decided that Vivi's coming.
[NAMI] You'd better be prepared
to pay up in full for this!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Deliver Princess Vivi!
The Luffy Pirates Set Sail!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!