[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[SANJI]
Hey, Sniper King!
[ZORO]
Things have gotten serious.
Hurry up and jump
down from there.
--No, Usopp!
[ZORO]
He--He can't be--
Where are you, Usopp?
[USOPP yelling]
[USOPP]
Someone say my name?
Why'd you make us
think you were dead?
[USOPP] You guys couldn't even
be bothered to catch a hero
who's plunged off an
exploding, falling building?
Some friends you are!
[FRANKY] You noticed the ship
on the other side of the bridge,
right?
I'm thinkin' it's our best
chance to get out of this mess.
Well, we're already
wanted criminals,
we might as well
steal a ship.
Franky...
...Transform!
Now gaze upon Franky Centaur!
[FRANKY]
Hey, get back here!
[LUCCI] But that
doesn't mean you should.
It's obvious that you're
pushing your body too far.
And I doubt that you
can take much more.
Not very clever, are you?
You're shortening
your own lifespan,
just for a few
minutes of strength.
It's better than
letting you take away
everything I care about!
I'll do anything
to keep that from happening.
But you've still lost,
even if you do defeat me!
Tempest Kick!
But don't let me
stop you from trying.
I'm interested to see
how far you'll go
in your misguided attempts
to save your little friends.
This isn't a game
we're playing, damn it!
[RANDOM MARINE 304E
screaming]
[RANDOM MARINE 304E]
Look behind the fog!
[RANDOM MARINE 304F]
The ships are here!
[SPANDAM]
Hey! Why're you running?
Get back here!
Oh, no!
[SPANDAM chuckling]
[SPANDAM] You asked for it, Nico
Robin! The Buster Call is here!
[SPANDAM] The invocation
of merciless death.
The Buster Call
has finally begun!
[LUFFY] "I Can't Protect
Anyone Unless I Win!
Third Gear Activated!"
[RANDOM MARINE 304A]
I repeat.
Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his crew of
approximately sixty pirates.
To ensure their demise, destroy
everything on Enies Lobby!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[SPANDAM]
Hey! Wait. Stop!
Hey! Stop running, dammit!
Open your eyes!
Oh, come on, the battleships
aren't gonna attack the bridge!
Not as long as
I'm on it, at least!
It's exactly like
my father said it was!
He told me he stood unscathed
amidst the destruction!
[RANDOM MARINE 304A]
For the time being,
avoid targeting the bridge
where the criminal
Nico Robin is.
[SPANDAM] Hey, come on! I'm
telling ya, you're safe with me!
They wouldn't even think
of harming the chief of CP9!
[laughing maniacally]
This is just complete
and total madness.
Hey. You okay?
[ROBIN]
I can't stop shaking.
[ELDER STAR B] Now commencing
the Buster Call.
All ships, fire at once.
Everything on the island
of Ohara is your target.
Let nothing remain.
Annihilate the devils of Ohara!
Burn it to the ground!
In the name of justice!
[ROBIN] The Buster Call--
A merciless act of destruction;
indifferent to the
horror it creates.
There won't be
a single life spared.
Its hellfire consumes all.
How can this happen?
Not even once. But twice?
[USOPP] Try to pick up the pace,
you guys! We're in a hurry here!
Quit bossing us
around, you moron!
[USOPP] Hey, my
injuries are bad enough,
let's not hurt
my feelings, too!
Speaking of which, could you
guys be a little more gentle?
You know, you were unconscious
before we picked you up,
and to be honest, I think
I liked it better that way!
How can you talk to your
fearless leader like that?
Especially when I've been
so seriously injured
in the line of duty!
All of my ribs
are broken! All six!
Well, you've got
more ribs than that!
Man, you're a royal
pain in the ass.
[USOPP] To change the subject,
I'm sure you're dying to know
the secret of my
new weapon, Kabuto.
Let me explain.
The great weapon of the
even greater Sniper King is--
If you don't can it, we're
gonna make you get up and run!
So much pain. Did I mention
my ribs are broken?
All ten are smashed.
[SANJI]
You've got more.
[USOPP] Really? Uh, twenty?
No, no, I mean thirty.
Actually, one hundred!
[ZORO and SANJI]
Even more!
[USOPP] Is my body made
of nothing but ribs?
Was that cannon fire?
You can always leave it to those
Navy boys to put on a big show!
Awesome! They're firing cannons!
It's not the same as shooting
off a bunch of fireworks,
you know.
Anyway, do you guys
know where Luffy's at?
Oh, yeah, pirate lady,
it was the coolest
thing I've ever seen!
Did you see those great
big doors back there?
The pirate guy
knocked 'em down!
Luffy did?
It was awesome! Even though
he got all small from it.
[GONBE vocalizing]
Wait, back up.
He got "all small"?
[CHIMNEY]
Uh-huh!
[LUFFY]
So this is it, huh?
Third Gear!
[screaming]
[CHIMNEY]
It's open.
[LUFFY] All right!
Time to head out!
No way! How'd you
make yourself all tiny?
[NAMI]
He said 'Third Gear'?
And then busted through
iron doors and turned small?
What is going on?
[KOKORO] I don't know, but that
Straw Hat sure is a lot of fun!
[CHIMNEY] Yeah, Granny!
The pirate guy's
almost as awesome as you are!
None of this is making
any sense to me at all.
Anyway, we'd better hurry.
Hey, Granny? I think I hear
something weird comin' this way.
[GONBE vocalizing]
[NAMI] Yeah,
I hear something, too.
We don't have time
to go worryin'
about any strange sounds.
If it's comin' this way, we'll
find out what it is soon enough.
We're gonna make those
government jerks pay!
Granny, you are the coolest!
[GONBE vocalizing]
Is that--
[ALL]
Water!
--What the hell is going on?
--Why is there water?
--Why is this happening?
--What do we do? Where do we go?
There's no way out!
Somebody help us!
Whether your friends die
in that tunnel or not,
there's no way anyone
can make it here now.
You bastard!
Even this room will
be submerged before long.
[HATORI coos]
You get back here now!
We're above sea level now,
so we can finish this fight
without the fear of drowning.
[HATORI coos]
You can hear that, right?
The rumble of the
ships' cannon fire?
I wonder how your pirate crew
is faring up there?
And Nico Robin, I wonder
what happened to her?
I'd be pretty concerned
if I were you.
[LUCCI] I won't stop you if you
want to run off to save them.
I'm not takin' my eyes off you
until you're down for good.
Whatever's goin' on,
my friends can survive
anything thrown their way,
but if I turn
my back on you now,
all you're gonna do
is try and kill them.
So I'm not going anywhere
'til you and I are through.
[SANJI] Sounds like
they've started the attack.
[USOPP]
Speaking of sounds,
I keep hearing something
weird from down the tunnel.
Ya hear me tellin'
you to shut up?
Come on!
[USOPP]
So much pain.
[USOPP] Hm, there's definitely
something wrong here.
Unlike the two of you,
I have a finely tuned
sense of perception,
and I'm telling you there's
something strange up ahead.
The sound I'm hearing must be--
Hey! Wait for me!
[USOPP]
I'm up!
I broke another thirty ribs!
Wait up, dammit!
How do you expect me to run
with all these broken ribs?
Come back!
[NAMI, KOKORO,
CHIMNEY, GONBE screaming]
Where's this water
coming from, Granny?
That doesn't matter, Chimney,
just keep running!
[ALL screaming]
You've got some determination.
It's almost a pity you're
on the wrong side of the law.
Although, let's see if you
can back up those big words.
It's gonna turn out the same
whether you live or die!
[laughing maniacally]
Hey. C'mon. Quit trembling
and go capture Nico Robin!
The sooner this is over
and done with,
the sooner I'll be seen
as the world's hero!
Why even the Buster Call
sounds like
a firework celebration
held in my honor!
[laughing maniacally]
Razor!
[LUCCI]
Finger Pistol!
[LUCCI] Tempest Kick!
Leopard Tail!
You really think
you can defeat me?
I can't protect anyone
unless I do!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Rifle!
Iron Body Empty Tree!
[LUFFY screaming]
[LUCCI]
Razor.
Even though you're going to die,
you've done well to get this far
against the World Government.
Still, you're no different than
any other pirate I've fought.
You've got guts,
but it takes more than that
to defeat someone like me.
Now Gum-Gum Pistol!
[LUFFY yelling]
Flying Finger Pistol.
Sting!
Rapid Fire, Triple Sting!
Flying Finger Pistol.
Fire Sting.
I'd be sorely disappointed
if I'd been expecting
any sort of real
challenge from you.
I bet you wasted
all of your strength
on those leg pumps
earlier, didn't you?
[LUFFY] So, you were lookin'
for a real challenge, huh?
Well, I got one more trick.
Just remember
this was your idea.
Third Gear!
[LUFFY]
Bone Balloon!
Balloon?
The power moves
from one bone to another.
[LUFFY] Take a look!
My left arm is now...
...the arm of a giant!
[LUCCI] You can't intimidate
me with your tricks.
Now Gum-Gum...
Iron Body.
...Giant Pistol!
Wha-- What the hell
is that thing?
[LUCCI] Justice will never lie
down and surrender to evil.
If there's a soldier
incapable of standing up
to protect what's right,
that makes him a criminal
in my eyes.
Everything I do is
in the name of justice.
Until now, and until I die!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Shivering Past!
Dark Justice
and Rob Lucci!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!