Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring outs
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Now Gum-Gum...
Usopp! This is your chance!
Let's see how ya
like my Special Oil Star!
Triple Shot Punishment!
Armee De L'air...
Power Shoot!
[ZORO]
Great Shock... Slash!
Now Cien Fleurs!
[ROBIN]
Big Tree!
What the... What's that?
And Clutch!
[OARS] I can't stand
like this! I'm gonna fall!
[FRANKY]
Skywalk!
We gotta make
this snappy, Chopper!
Right!
--Super...
--...Frapper...
--...Gong!
Bad Manners...
...Kick...
...Course!
Fall, damn you, fall!
Slow start,
but score one.
[LUFFY]
"The Silent Assault!
The Mysterious Visitor,
'Tyrant' Kuma!"
She's... She's so brutal!
It's like she's some kind of
crazy pirate demon woman!
Exactly what
the hell is going on?
Do you want to explain
where the treasure is?
You're the one who should be
explaining things, pirate woman!
Let me go! It's payback time!
Prepare to die!
You think you can take me?
There isn't anyone alive
that can stand
between me and my treasure.
Anybody who so
much as touches it
is in for an
unpleasant surprise.
--Ha-ya!
--You're dead!
Now Thunder Charge... Swing Arm!
She made my everything hurt.
And I know we said way too much.
Don't forget: Mistress Perona
loves treasure, too!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
That's right!
She'll never
take it away from her!
Still, I wish we hadn't
told her about the shortcut.
--We messed up.
[NAMI]
That cheeky little brat!
How dare she try
to take my treasure!
And she wants
to steal the Sunny,
load it up, and use
it as her getaway boat?
Sorry, sweetie.
You don't know
who you're messing with!
[NAMI] I've gotta hurry
and get back to the Sunny!
Hold on. What's up
with this weird bridge?
It doesn't look like
everything else around here.
It's narrow, but
it's really well made.
[OARS]
Stupid bastards!
That's it! Now I'm angry!
I'm gonna make you pay!
Holy crap!
[NAMI thinking] Fortunately,
dealing with that guy
isn't my top priority right now.
No thank you!
I didn't see anything!
[OARS]
Oh, now you done it!
When I get up, I'm gonna stomp
you pipsqueak pirates flat!
There won't even
be bones left to bury!
[screaming]
Oh, crap!
This guy is
seriously pissed off!
This is bad! Really bad!
Here he comes!
What the hell?
Dammit! I can't move!
My horns are
stuck in the ground!
This sucks!
Ahhh...
You're stuck, huh?
Heh... Heh...
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368A]
No way!
You don't think that...
All that screaming sounds a lot
like it's coming from Oars!
Maybe Oars just likes screaming
when he's kicking ass!
I mean, come on,
it's not like he could
actually be losing, right?
[OARS]
Hey! Cut it out!
[USOPP]
Retreat!
--Right!
These guys are
like little demons!
Guess that wasn't
enough to keep him down.
So it seems, unfortunately.
[ZORO]
Okay.
What are we gonna do now?
If we're gonna take down
a giant monster like this one,
we need to
re-initiate Tactic 15!
You're right, Franky!
I think we should
give it another shot!
Yeah!
[USOPP]
But this time,
you have to dock
into your position, Robin!
We're counting on you!
I told you! Never!
What is wrong with you morons?
There's no way
Robin's going to take part
in something
so humiliating! Got it?
Whoa.
Hold on. Maybe...
[SANJI]
Now that I've actually stopped
to think about
my sweet Robin docking.
I'm kidding! It's a joke!
Don't get angry
about it, my love!
Either way, don't even think
about pulling that stupi--
[FRANKY]
Let's do it!
Standby, men!
Take your positions!
[FRANKY]
Pirates Docking Three!
The Not-So-Giant Robot Warrior!
[USOPP]
The docking is Complete!
[FRANKY]
Hey! Eyebrows!
Can I get a hand here?
Oh, wait.
I mean... Can I get a leg?
C'mon, Sanji!
Do it! Now!
I like this plan.
Sure. Here.
Let's go!
Now fly!
Arme'e de L'air...
Robo-Shoot!
Come on!
You three can't do nothin'!
[USOPP]
That's where you're wrong!
[FRANKY] We're coming for you,
you big ugly bastard!
Take this!
--Pirate Robot Warrior
--Special Attack!
So after all that,
this is their attack.
I believe that's a "yes".
Dammit!
Docking Three totally sucks!
I'm embarrassed I had
anything to do with this crap!
That's not neat like last time.
You're stupid!
That's what we
want you to believe!
Now! Witness the true terror
of Pirates Docking Three!
Moron!
You think you've got what it
takes to be King of the Pirates?
You're all size and
brute strength, nothing more.
You're the world's tallest joke!
[FRANKY AND CHOPPER]
Moron! Moron!
What'd you call me?
Just a few pirates
knocked you flat,
and you think
you're gonna somehow
be the King of all of them?
Give up! You're nothing
but an embarrassment!
Yeah?
I'm gonna "embarrassment" you!
Pipsqueak pirates!
I'll smash you flat!
[USOPP, CHOPPER AND FRANKY]
That's it! Jump!
Yeah, we did it!
[OARS]
Owie, owie, owie!
[FRANKY] How does it feel
to knock yourself down
with your own punch?
Alright!
Robin, did ya see? Did ya see?
Everything went
just as I planned!
Way to go,
Pirates Docking Three!
Wow, you guys are the best!
[ZORO] Nobody's buying
that crap, stupid cook.
That's your second
time down, monster!
--Yeah! Two times!
Whoa! I'm falling again!
[USOPP]
Run for it!
--Crap! He didn't fall!
Damn! We were so close, too!
He's as stubborn as he is tall.
I don't have time for this.
I gotta save Nami!
Hang on a second.
I just got an idea
on how to stop him.
I've had enough of
these half-assed plans.
Listen to me, dammit!
[USOPP]
From what I've seen,
even though he's
big and red and all,
this guy still has traces of
Luffy's personality left in him.
[CHOPPER]
What are you talking about?
He already told us he
didn't recognize any of us
and that Moria was his master!
Yeah, but even so.
[FRANKY] What the hell
are you doing to us, Robin?
Hurry up and dock
onto my left arm!
[CHOPPER]
Robin! We need you!
[USOPP] Come on, it's fine!
Just do what I'm doing!
No.
I'm not embarrassing
myself like that.
Whassa matter?
She won't do it?
[SANJI] What, why are you
acting all disappointed?
Why ya think?
I want to see the robot!
Right at that moment,
his other half leaked out.
The part of him that's still
Luffy is in there somewhere.
See what I mean?
I think you're right.
Yeah. So how does that help us?
Well, it means that
this guy's weaknesses
are the same
as Luffy's weaknesses.
[USOPP]
Check it out!
Look! There's a
huge hunk 'a meat!
A hunk 'a meat?
Show me! Where is it?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
I see it! It looks yummy!
Gimme! I love meat!
[FRANKY]
Knee Crush!
[ZORO] Does halfway
down count as three?
Even if there were rules,
I don't think this
guy would follow them.
Alright!
He's down again after
a blow to the kneecaps!
[USOPP and CHOPPER cheering]
That was embarrassing.
Keep it up, you guys!
Just stall him 'til the captain
beats the crap outta Moria!
Hurry up and get those
shadows back, Straw Hat!
There's no reason to
keep screwing around like this.
Let's put him down for good.
[FRANKY]
Hold on!
I thought the idea was for us
to keep this big monster busy
to make sure he doesn't
get in Straw Hat's way!
There's no way we
can beat this thing, man!
There wasn't any meat.
You tricked me
and broke my kneecaps.
A fight isn't truly
over until you've won.
He's not just
a giant, he's a zombie!
To beat him,
you're gonna have to purify him!
That's right, Zoro!
We're just buying time!
Take it easy!
If you don't wanna help,
stand back.
I don't feel like waiting
around for Luffy to win, either.
You're crazy!
They've made up their minds,
there's no stopping them.
[OARS]
Now Gum-Gum...
[ZORO] A dinosaur
could step on this blade
and it wouldn't
bend a millimeter.
They say that hardness is
the greatest characteristic
of a Black Blade.
[RYUMA] The legendary
owner of this blade
may have long since fallen,
but its story does not end here.
With you as its master, this
sword will surely be satisfied.
[ZORO]
With Shusui here,
I've finally gotten my
hands on a first rate sword.
And I think this is the
perfect time to try it out.
Stop it!
Why you gotta be so stubborn?
Just let Luffy beat Moria!
Dammit!
Where'd that jerk go?
I'm sick of all
this running around!
I don't see him anywhere.
Hey, wait!
[LUFFY]
Gum Gum...
Rocket!
A-ha!
[NAMI]
Stop right there!
Who is that?
What does she want?
It's that pirate woman!
[NAMI]
What do you think you're doing
with all that treasure
I was gonna steal?
And what are you
doing onboard the Sunny?
Horo horo horo!
I was worried there for
a second, but it's only you.
How'd the wedding
ceremony with Absalom go?
Over already?
Oh, gimme a break!
Who would ever want to marry
that invisible
pervert beast-man?
Then I take it you
managed to escape the wedding.
Absalom can't do anything right.
So. What are you gonna do?
As you surmised,
I do plan on stealing your ship
to escape from Thriller Bark
and I'm bringing
all the treasure with me.
If you try to stop me,
I'll fight you.
And you won't like that.
You're not very strong,
so the Mini Hollow Ghost Army
will be more than
sufficient against you.
The only one among you
that put up a fight against me
was that depressing
long-nosed guy.
Who is that?
--Mistress Perona!
--Run! Don't look back!
Just who in the hell are you?
We don't know him,
but he's definitely an enemy!
Just now he made some of our
brothers vanish without a trace
right before our very eyes!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368A]
He's no ordinary man!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368B]
He's dangerous!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368C]
Whoever he is, he's bad news!
[NAMI thinking]
"Vanished"?
No, it can't be. I think...
I think I know who this man is!
[PERONA]
It's him.
One of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
"The Tyrant," Bartholomew Kuma.
The atrocities he committed
when he was a pirate
are beyond the pale.
[screaming]
[ZOMBIE PANDA] One of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea?
Do you know what that means?
He's got the same
rank as Master Moria!
What's a guy like him
doing here on Thriller Bark?
[NAMI thinking]
You've gotta be kidding!
[KUMA]
Do you work for Moria?
[PERONA]
What? Master Moria?
I was, but I'm not anymore!
I've had enough of this!
I'm just trying to...
to escape from this island.
I want no part of it!
She's telling you the truth!
[ZOMBIE 368F]
That bastard!
What does he think he's
trying to do to Mistress Perona?
If you could take a vacation,
where is it you'd like to go?
He's making small talk?
This is not the time
or place for such nonsense!
But if I were
to go on a vacation,
somewhere dark and damp,
somewhere with an
old, creepy castle,
I'd spend every day there
singing a song of curses.
She answered!
That's the
Ghost Princess for you!
I agree!
We loved your answer,
Mistress Perona!
I got caught up in my daydream!
[PERONA]
Stop screwing around!
I admit, I was taken aback
when I realized who you were.
But I've got nothing to fear.
With my Devil Fruit powers,
there's no one
I can't take down,
and that includes you!
[PERONA]
Are you listening to me?
I'd imagine your shadow is
pretty strong, isn't it Kuma?
Good! Then I'll take it
from you as a parting gift
to my former master, Moria,
so prepare yourself!
[PERONA]
Negative Ghost!
And Special Hollow!
Alright! There it is!
Mistress Perona's
Ultimate Combo!
[KUMA] Before you interrupted
with all that yelling,
I was simply going to
ask you where Moria is.
Where did she go?
What happened
to Mistress Perona?
[ZOMBIES]
Mistress Perona!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368F]
What was that? I'm scared!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368G]
She disappeared! But how?
What did you do with
Mistress Perona, you bastard?
Unforgivable!
Where's our princess?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368F]
You're gonna pay!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368I]
He's scary!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 368J]
Run for it!
You're the
Cat Burglar, aren't you?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates?
[KUMA] I've heard
that Monkey D. Luffy
has an older brother.
Is that true?
[NAMI]
Huh?
[NAMI thinking]
No way!
He just suddenly
appeared up there!
Did he teleport?
Yeah, he does!
You're talking about Ace, right?
Why do you wanna know?
I see.
So the rumors are true.
Yeah? So?
What's all this about?
What do you want?
Are you really a Warlord?
[KUMA] What I'm doing here
is none of your concern.
That guy is bad news.
What does he want with Luffy?
I've got to go warn him.
Gotcha, Moria!
You're mine!
You're not getting away
this time, you bastard!
I'm gonna beat
the crap outta you!
Give everyone's shadows back!
Now, Gum-Gum...
What?
I've been chasing his shadow?
[LUFFY]
Aw, dammit! He tricked me!
[MORIA]
Kushishi!
The morning sun will soon rise.
Careful! You will run
out of hiding places
if you dilly-dally.
[USOPP] Moria,
where are you hiding?
[MORIA]
Look carefully!
I'm right here.
[USOPP]
Now way!
Moria is inside Oars' stomach?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Oars + Moria.
The Most Heinous Combination
of Brains and Brawn.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!