[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY] "An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!"
[CHOPPER] Day three.
subject's bacteria count down by
seventy percent.
[LUFFY laughs]
[CHOPPER gasping]
Whoa! Amazing!
You are cool monster!
But what happens if I
do this? Tickle, tickle.
[gasps] What do you
think you're doing? !
‐‐[LUFFY chuckles]
‐‐[CHOPPER gasps, giggles]
That's funny!
Shut up! Get outta here!
Come on, let's you
and me be friends!
Please? I really really really
do like you, you know.
[CHOPPER gasps]
You. like me?
You'd make a great pirate!
[CHOPPER]
Did you slip and hit your head
while you were out on
the ice or something?
I don't wanna be a pirate
or your friend, see?
[LUFFY] Look, little guy, you
gotta say you'll be my friend!
My crew will love you!
Hey wait!
[CHOPPER] Why would I want
to be friends with you? !
Are you making fun of me? !
[CHOPPER pants, yelps]
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY] I think you're
the funniest guy I know!
Oh, yeah. we're gonna
be great friends!
I've prepared this extra
nutritious and fortifying
meal just for you so we
can get a healthy smile
back on that
beautiful face of yours.
[NAMI]
Thank you, Sanji.
Of course!
All though, you're as
heartbreakingly gorgeous
as ever, in spite of
your painful ordeal.
Hey, you.
I don't recall you asking for
permission to use my kitchen.
Madam, I made a dish
for you as well.
it's supposed to
make you look years‐‐
[KUREHA]
I'm not a "madam".
I'm a swinging single still
in the prime of youth.
Don't forget it.
[NAMI] Not a day over a
hundred thirty‐nine, right?
Doctorine, save me
from this lunatic!
[LUFFY] Wait! Hold on!
Come back! Hey!
[CHOPPER, LUFFY grunt]
‐‐[CHOPPER screams]
‐‐[LUFFY chuckles]
What are you doing? Luffy!
This guy's gonna join
us and be our friend!
Really? Great!
I didn't say I was
gonna do that!
[LUFFY]
Sure you did!
[CHOPPER]
No I didn't!
[LUFFY]
Did!
Be quiet! Both of you!
[yelling, chuckling continue]
Friend, huh? If he only knew.
.what friend means to
someone who's been through
what Chopper has.
[sighs] Poor guy.
When Chopper was out
there on his own,
there was only one human that
he ever really opened up to.
That man's name was
Doctor Hiriluk.
He was a crazy quack
but he named Chopper,
and called him his son.
[DOG howls]
Hey... you. Stop!
‐‐[GUARD A] Where'd he go?!
‐‐[GUARD B] Beats me!
[GUARD B]
He disappeared!
[GUARD A] Crazy quack!
We've got to get him!
Those are Lord Wapol's orders!
Now move out!
[GUARD B, GUARD C]
Right!
[HIRILUK breathes heavily]
[coughs]
[HIRILUK]
Damn.
[WIFE]
You can't go on like this!
We have to call a doctor!
We can't! There are
no doctors left to call,
except for the Twenty MD's
who belong to Wapol!
If we have to beg Wapol
on our knees for help,
then that's what we have to do!
I'll go get them!
[HIRILUK]
You don't need Wapol's charity!
I'll examine him!
Hiriluk! No! I'm fine!
It's just a cold!
Besides the last bunch
of patients you treated
ended up getting a
whole lot worse!
[HIRILUK] Now, there's no need
to be shy with your doctor,
I just developed a wonderful new
all‐purpose drug yesterday.
You're a lucky man,
now shut up.
[gasps]
Huh? Oh. That's not the kind
of gun you think it is.
It's a tranquilizer gun for
patients with severe pain.
I'm going to get the soldiers!
[door clatters]
[HUSBAND] Please go! If you
want money I'll be glad to pay!
[HIRILUK] I don't take money
from sick people!
I just want to help you!
Don't do it! Please!
I'm too young to die, stop!
[HUSBAND ribbits]
Huh? Okay, I gotta admit,
I wasn't expecting that.
I must have made a mistake
with the ingredients somehow.
Guess I shouldn't have
used frog extract.
Ah, sorry, there. My mistake.
[GUARD A]
Hiriluk! Are you in there?
[HIRILUK grunts]
[GUARDS]
Hold it!
[HIRILUK pants]
[HIRILUK]
Hm?
Are you happy now, quack?
The doctor hunt has
reached its final stage.
I hear you and I are the only
ones left in the country.
Wapol has his
hunters desperately
looking for us everywhere.
And even if they weren't,
you'd already be a
pariah in this country.
Since you're the worst
quack of them all.
[KUREHA chuckles]
[HIRILUK] I'm not gonna
get caught by some fool
"doctor hunt." And one day,
I'll end up saving this country
with medical science!
[exhales] Yeah, right.
I think you mean
"destroy this country"?
Look, there are people
on the bridge!
[KUREHA]
See you around, quack.
[HIRILUK] Not if I see you
first, you thieving sawbones.
[HIRILUK grunts]
Those tin soldiers aren't
gonna capture me!
I'm gonna go on helping
the sick and the injured.
[HIRILUK]
Hm?
[grunts]
[HIRILUK]
Looks like you've been shot.
We need to stop the bleeding
right away or you're dead!
[CHOPPER growls]
[HIRILUK]
Don't worry. I'll save you!
[VILLAGER A]
It's a yeti! Shoot it!
[gasps]
Actually you're pretty lucky,
because I just created
an ointment three days ago that
even works on broken bones!
[pants]
We can't let that blue
nosed yeti get away, men!
[VILLAGER C]
Shoot him down!
[yells]
Just what are you anyway?
You don't look like
a human being.
You must be that yeti everyone
is talking about in the village.
[CHOPPER shouts]
[HIRILUK grunts]
[shouting continues]
[VILLAGER A]
Yeah! We got him!
[VILLAGER C]
It wasn't enough! Finish him!
[pants]
[HIRILUK grunts]
How dare you.
Who do you think...
...you're dealing
with, creature?
[HIRILUK]
Hey! Wait!
I promise I'm not gonna
shoot you, see?!
My name is Hiriluk.
Doctor Hiriluk!
And I want to help you!
[CHOPPER grunts]
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
[sneezes]
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
[stomach growls]
[KUREHA]
That was the first encounter
between Chopper
and Doctor Hiriluk.
[NAMI]
So, what happened next?
Between Chopper
and Doctor Hiriluk?
[HIRILUK]
Wait. You can talk?
Why have you kept silent?
[CHOPPER] I thought you'd
hate me if I talked.
When I talked to humans the
other day, they shot at me.
You see, people think
I'm a freak for that.
So you can talk, so what.
Even children learn to talk.
I don't see what's so
damn special about it?
[HIRILUK]
Hm?
Aah! Run, Chopper!
Huh?
[CHOPPER, HIRILUK yell]
Aw. I thought for
sure that would work.
Hey, Chopper, are you okay?
[CHOPPER grunts]
Eh? Well, at least your
head was bandaged
to begin with, right?
[chuckles]
[CHOPPER] Mm? Hey, did you
call me Chopper?
That's your new name.
Tony Tony Chopper.
I picked it because I thought
you looked like you could
chop down a tree with
those antlers of yours.
Cool name, huh?
Anyway, that's what
I'm gonna call ya. [laughs]
Chopper... [chuckles]
[HIRILUK]
Now listen up, Chopper.
Always pay close attention
to your patients' symptoms
and give 'em proper treatment.
That's the way to
save a person's life.
Let's go! There are sick
people who need my help!
[VILLAGER D] Get outta here,
you crazy quack!
[HIRILUK, CHOPPER yell]
[HIRILUK] I thought lizard
eyeballs would work!
[VILLAGER E]
Don't ever come back!
[VILLAGER F]
Get lost!
[HIRILUK]
It's Wapol's guards! Run!
Chopper, it's time to
use the decoy plan!
[CHOPPER]
The what plan?!
[HIRILUK]
Good luck, pal!
[CHOPPER yells]
[CHOPPER]
Eh?
[CHOPPER] You almost got
me killed, you maniac!
[HIRILUK]
So what?
You already cheated death once,
you clumsy blue nosed caribou!
[CHOPPER] That's reindeer,
and don't call me blue nose!
[HIRILUK groans]
[CHOPPER groans]
[CHOPPER]
Doctor?
That's the first time I've
ever fought with anyone.
[laughs]
I can believe that, you have
to have an opponent to fight.
So is it your first time
for this as well?
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[HIRILUK]
That's for you.
A gift, as a memento
of our making up.
Gift? Making up?
[HIRILUK]
Ya' know Chopper,
it sometimes feels that
things are pretty rough,
but try not to hold a grudge
against us humans, okay?
This country is sick right now.
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
The people and the king both
suffer from a terrible sickness
of the heart, and conventional
wisdom has it that there is no
way to cure a sick country,
but that's wrong!
Once my invention
has been perfected,
this country will
be as good as saved!
You see, there used
to be a master thief
who lived in a country
in the far west.
He had a serious
heart condition.
He went to the greatest
doctors he could find
to receive treatment, but no
one was able to cure him.
They told him he
was going to die.
Frustrated and depressed, he
passed by a certain mountain.
There he saw something he
had never seen before.
[HIRILUK]
Blossoms!
He saw cherry blossoms all
over the mountainside!
And then, he went to
see another doctor
and got the shock of his
life because he was told,
"you're perfectly healthy!"
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
He was cured! It was
a miracle! Don't you see?!
But it also makes perfect
sense medically speaking!
By changing his
emotional state,
he was able to change his
physical state somehow too!
And if that's true,
there's no disease in this
world that can't be cured!
Let them laugh at me!
My medical skills will
save this country yet!
And that's why I raised
this skull and crossbones!
As a challenge to all the
diseases of the world!
[CHOPPER]
Skull?
[HIRILUK]
This symbolizes my belief.
That nothing is impossible!
I will save this country
with my doctor's skills!
By raising this flag, I vow to
fight just like the pirates do!
[LUFFY] Hey! Reindeer!
Join us and be our friend!
[LUFFY gasps]
Booty!
[LUFFY giggles]
I love being a pirate!
[CHOPPER]
Doctor, what are pirates?
[HIRILUK]
Pirates?
They're dashing
swashbucklers of the sea!
With great strength and
the eyesight of eagles!
Their voices echo
like rolling thunder!
[LUFFY chuckles]
Hey! Y‐You're really a pirate?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Well, yeah, of course I am.
It's like I've been
saying all along,
we do all kinds of fun stuff,
like fishing and singing!
Huh? P‐Pirates sing?
Sure we do and sometimes
we dance too!
[CHOPPER]
You call that being a pirate?!
Of course! And we
go on adventures!
You really do? Pirates really
do go on adventures?
Yeah, you bet we do!
Pirates risk their lives
to go on adventures!
And you meet the
most amazing people!
[HIRILUK]
It's great to be a pirate!
The most amazing
people sail the seas!
[HIRILUK] Chopper, some day
you've got to go to sea.
If you do, you'll realize just
how small your problems
really are in comparison to
the vastness of the oceans.
The island you were born on is
like this compared to the world!
[CHOPPER]
Really?
No, it's smaller! Like this!
Really!
[HIRILUK, CHOPPER laugh]
Your destiny lies beyond
that shining sea!
[KUREHA]
The good times passed
in the twinkling of an eye.
And then...
...it finally came time
to say farewell.
As it always does
in the end.
[HIRILUK]
It's taken a year,
but your treatment
is finally complete.
Your injuries
are healed, Chopper.
Yeah! Thank you, Doctor.
Well then, take care.
[HIRILUK] On your way!
Have a nice life!
I'm busy with my research!
So hit the bricks!
I'm no longer under any
obligation to care for you!
Doctor! I swear, I won't
cause you any trouble
if you'll just let me
stay with you!
I'll rub your
shoulders every day!
I'll make you tea and clean
the house! Please! Let me stay!
[CHOPPER]
I don't have any friends!
I don't have anywhere to go!
[CHOPPER] Doctor! Please!
Can you hear me? Doctor?!
[thudding]
Chopper!
I hurt my head. I... fell.
I'm injured!
Take a look!
[CHOPPER whimpers]
But why... doctor?
Go! Go to sea if you like!
Go anywhere you want!
Just don't come back!
‐‐[CHOPPER cries]
‐‐[HIRILUK whimpers]
Forgive me, Chopper.
[HIRILUK]
I'm... dying.
[KUREHA cackles]
Yes, you are.
[HIRILUK] Tell me the truth.
How many days do I have left?
[KUREHA] Excuse me?
This isn't a charity ward.
You don't have the
money to pay my fee.
Tell me.
You can't kill a person with
a tranquilizer gun, ya know.
All right, I'll tell you.
Ten days from now, you'll die.
So now ya know.
Ten? That'll be enough.
In two days, my research
will be done.
Now completed, after failing
for 30 years.
I will make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
You mean you've
wasted 30 years
researching freakin
cherry blossoms.
That's what your big
project has been?
The same cherry blossoms you
think saved your life back
when you were a master thief?
[HIRILUK]
That's right.
[CHOPPER]
What?
Damn. You idiot.
This is a winter island
where it's bitter
cold year round,
no cherry blossom
will ever bloom here.
No! I was nothing but
a worthless criminal
on the very brink of death,
but those flowers saved my life
and transformed my existence.
Every human being in
this world can be saved.
And I'm going to prove
it right here in Drum,
the land where I was born!
Right. You do realize that
what you're saying
has no basis in medical science.
or any other field of science.
And if you do get them to bloom,
there's no medicinal use.
[KUREHA]
Hiriluk!
Hmph.
[HIRILUK] Chopper, you and I
are alike. So before I die,
I'll at least teach you
that nothing is impossible
in this world, and that you
can do anything if you try!
[KUREHA] However, the story
of these two outcasts
doesn't have a happy
fairy tale ending.
[HIRILUK] I'll show you...
the miraculous cherry blossoms!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[SANJI]
Hey Luffy!
Are you really listening
to‐‐ hey, where'd he go?
[NAMI] Jeez, is he chasing
Chopper again? He said no!
[LUFFY] That's not true!
Are you stupid?
I'm gonna make him join us
and become our friend!
[SANJI] Come on!
That's what you want, not him!
[NAMI] Seriously, I wonder
if there's a medicine
that can cure fools.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms and
the Will that Gets Carried on!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!