It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
Riding atop Gomorrah,
four of the Straw Hat Pirates,
and the Franky Family,
raced to the Courthouse
Plaza in pursuit of Luffy.
You hear that, Gomorrah?
To the courthouse!
Gomorrah!
Damn!
Who the hell is that?
Don't get too cocky, scumbags.
All right!
The second one's down, too!
We can't even run away anymore!
What're we gonna do?
Meanwhile, Sniper King
was making headway
near the Main Island Front Gate.
All right!
Oimo and Kashii
are back on their feet!
We're screwed.
I don't have the strength to
fight these guys a second time.
We were so close!
You bastards.
How dare you...
...lie to us?
And now, with our bosses safe,
before we mourn all
those years we wasted--
We're going let out every
last ounce of our anger on you!
Are you ready,
King of the Snipers?
With the assistance
of Oimo and Kashii,
Sniper King is back
on the Straw Hats' trail.
Let us not waste words.
Hoist the signal
for the counter attack!
Soon we shall be
reunited with our comrades!
Gross.
Soon, you'll understand
the extent of your changes.
The birth of new Devil Fruit
users is always exciting.
Enjoy yourselves, but
I'd try to get those powers
under control
while you still can.
Meanwhile, Luffy was on
the rooftop of the courthouse
waging a fierce battle
against Blueno from CP9.
Iron Body!
Wheel!
Door-Door!
Was that a door on the ground?
Door-Door.
Whoa, wait a second!
Now there's a bunch of little
ones all over the place, too!
Damn it, I can't move!
This sucks!
Revolving Door.
Whoa, what?
I'm not moving
anywhere but I'm spinning!
I dunno which way is front!
Make it stop!
Tempest Kick!
Cook! See that?
Yeah. I saw.
You know what that means;
Luffy is already fighting CP9.
What?
Look.
We gotta run.
We can't wait here any longer.
Yeah.
Let's cut through
to the courthouse.
It's our only option.
Right! Let's go!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Wait! Nobody get off!
What? Why?
Everyone hold on tight!
That's-- That's
what Gomorrah says!
Go, Gomorrah!
Charge!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
Gomorrah!
What are you doing?
You're gonna knock us off
if you keep crashing like that!
Whoa!
Maybe he's too injured to go on!
What? No!
Gomorrah can't see!
His retinas were
damaged in that last attack!
He's blind!
What's that?
Gomorrah!
You can't see anything?
It started running like crazy!
Don't just stand there!
Shoot it!
We gotta stop that thing!
We can't let it go any further!
Fire the trench mortars!
Gomorrah, don't do this!
Please stop!
You're in no shape to go on!
You'll kill yourself!
He said that he made
a promise to Sodom.
He told Sodom
"Leave the rest to me!"
"I'll take on your share
and carry everyone
the rest of the way!"
Gomorrah.
They were in its stomach?
I'm full already--couldn't
eat another bite.
Let's take 'em
with us as back-up food.
Big Bro!
Come here, quick!
Some pirates gave Sodom and
Gomorrah a serious beating!
You pirates have
got a lotta nerve!
Never touch my family!
Hey!
Take it easy, you two!
You're still injured!
This is no time
for a dance party!
Look!
We're headed
straight for a dead end!
He'll crash into it and die!
Gomorrah! Stop it!
You'll never make it! Stop!
A dead end?
I don't see one.
Do you?
Nope.
Can't say I see
anything of the sort.
It's the Courthouse!
He did it!
You made it, Gomorrah!
All units!
The King Bull carrying the
pirates broke through Block D
and they are now at
the Courthouse Plaza!
I repeat!
The King Bull carrying
the pirates broke through--
Look at this, Funkfreed.
A Golden Transponder Snail.
Having this little
gadget is the same
as having the authority
to issue a Buster Call.
That means I have the
same power as a Navy admiral,
or someone even
higher up than that!
Admiral Aokiji
entrusted it to me.
The question is
"if and when will I use it"?
Just you wait!
Once I revive the
ancient weapons,
this won't just be something
that's "on loan" to me.
I'll carry it of my own accord,
along with the power
to control an army.
A Buster Call.
I will now initiate
a Buster Call!
All ships may
commence attack at once!
Target every last thing
on this island of archeology
and turn Ohara into ash!
With the single
push of a button,
an entire island will disappear!
Authority can be a
weapon unto itself.
Oh, the power.
Chief Spandam!
That was close!
What's wrong with you?
Can't you even knock?
I almost accidentally
hit the button!
I'm terribly sorry, sir!
But I'm afraid we've
got an emergency here!
There's an urgent call from
Enies Lobby's Main Island!
Idiots!
If there's an emergency,
why didn't they just
call my room directly?
What the--?
Hey!
Why is the receiver
off the hook?
This always happens!
Who's responsible?
Well, either way,
you were saying something
about an emergency, weren't you?
Yes sir!
Spanda.
Hey! Ms. Robin!
It seems we have an
urgent report coming in
from the marines
down at the Main Island.
Knowing what it's likely about,
I wouldn't call it an
"emergency," exactly.
Your friends tried their best
but only managed to take
down five of our soldiers.
I wonder how they
were ultimately defeated.
Did some of my other
men bring them down,
or was it the giant gatekeeping
team of Oimo and Kashii?
So many possibilities.
Why don't we listen to the
report about these idiots
who defied the World Government
and learn their fate together?
You're such a scumbag.
Shut up, you low-life!
This is Spandam.
I understand you have a report?
Chief Spandam!
Finally! Thank goodness.
I tried your direct line,
but I couldn't get through!
I'm-- I'm not really
sure where to begin.
Calm down!
Take it easy.
It's the Straw Hats, right?
Yes, what about them?
Whoa!
Hold on!
Listen.
Just pick up from where
your last report ended.
Give me the gritty
details loudly and clearly.
Right!
The intruders--
Did you accidentally kill them?
Pity.
It's their fault for
being such weaklings.
The intruders consist
of about sixty pirates!
They've pushed their way all
the way through the Main Island
and have reached
the Courthouse Plaza!
We can't stop them, sir!
All personnel on
Enies Lobby's Main Island!
Head to the Courthouse
Plaza immediately!
You did a good job, Gomorrah!
I swear, everything you
two did will not be in vain!
All right, we're breaking in!
It's time to save
Big Bro Franky!
Yeah!
I repeat: The pirates have
reached the Courthouse Plaza!
Can you see Luffy?
Nope.
But whether he's up
on the roof or not,
it's not exactly like we
can just jump up after him.
That's true.
Not much we can do.
How many members of CP9
did you see up there?
It was just that one
big guy with the bull horns.
It's hard to believe
that Robin, Franky,
all of them, are right
behind those doors.
In any case, we need
to catch up with Luffy!
Then we can save Robin together!
Hurry!
Get to the Courthouse!
The drawbridge isn't down yet!
Corner them!
Gero!
Whoa!
That frog's awesome!
That's the same ball
that took out Gomorrah!
Who threw it?
Look!
There're three of them!
And they're running away!
Why are they running away?
They're the ones
that attacked first!
Idiot cook!
We can't go chasing around every
enemy that runs off like that!
It's a waste of time!
Oh, pipe down.
It's confirmation.
Some of them need to
be chased, understand?
To find out who
we're up against.
That was amazing!
Who is this guy?
He must have superhuman strength
to swing something
like that around!
You think he's part
of some special unit,
like those guard dogs?
There're probably more of them
hiding out there somewhere.
Let's be careful.
We need to get moving.
It looks like the
reinforcements have arrived.
Surround them!
There's no way they'll be able
to open those heavy stone doors!
We'll have them cornered!
Move it!
He's right!
Now that I think about it, how--
--are we gonna open--
--those big, stone--
We're going in first!
Stay close-- don't fall behind!
He-- He cut right through
them, like it was nothing!
Hey! Zambai!
Let's split up!
We need to charge
both of those towers--
--'Cuz each side has a lever
to open up that drawbridge.
Yeah!
Good thinking!
I'm on it!
Right!
Looks like we need to
split into three teams!
Most of you go
with Kiwi and Mozu!
The rest are with me!
We'll crack some heads
in that courthouse!
Good luck, everyone.
Move!
Huh?
Also, the gatekeepers of
the Main Island Front Gate,
Oimo and Kashii, have
joined up with the pirates!
They're currently destroying the
central part of the Main Island!
Get outta the way!
After hearing all
the field reports,
our guard casualties total
must be over 2,000 men!
Wait.
Not five?
And the man who took down
over a thousand of those men
all by himself, the
notorious Straw Hat Luffy,
has suddenly disappeared!
We're still assessing
the situation here!
In the history of this island,
this is, without a doubt, the
absolute worst thing that has
ever happened at Enies Lobby!
It's Blueno!
What's he doing out
there on that rooftop?
What's happening here?
And why now?
What the hell's going on?
Finally!
My face closed!
Of course.
All open doors
will eventually shut.
I'm amazed you still managed
to dodge my Tempest Kick.
Yeah. No big deal.
How unsettling.
Jerk!
He's fast!
Finger Pistol!
Shave!
Iron Body!
Strong!
Now Gum Gum--
Bullet!
Iron Body!
Tempest Kick!
He's completely keeping
up with my speed.
He even changed the
course of my Tempest Kick!
His physical abilities
are unbelievable.
It's no good.
I can't stay like this.
It won't work.
When I lost to Aokiji,
I realized something.
I said to myself.
"You keep running into guys
that are stronger and stronger.
Unless you can
get stronger too,
you can't protect your friends."
And I want to.
They're not all strong like me.
But either way, they're my
friends and I wanna keep 'em,
so I have to get
stronger than anyone else.
Otherwise there's a
chance I could lose them.
Then what are you gonna do?
I thought of a new way
to fight with all my might,
so that I won't lose anyone.
So I won't let anyone
slip away from me.
What's happening to him?
What's going on inside his body?
That did it.
You won't be able
to stop me now.
What?
All my strength and techniques
just went up by one step.
Second Gear!
You know, truth is, I'm glad
I met you guys when I did.
And why is that?
Because thanks to you,
I won't ever lose my friends.
Ridiculous.
You certainly are
full of hot air.
Now Gum-Gum--!
On the next One Piece:
"Everything is to
Protect My Friends!
Second Gear Activated!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!