[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
After losing his brother, Ace,
in the War of the Best
against the Navy,
Luffy sent a message to his crew
in a way that only
they would grasp.
I hope they get the message...
wherever they are.
If anyone can understand
you, it's them.
They'll understand
if they see the article.
They are your crew after all.
[CHOPPER]
I got it, Luffy! Don't worry!
A change of plans, then!
Yeah, okay, okay!
So, that's it. Very well, then.
[ROBIN]
Interesting as always, Luffy.
Roger that, Captain!
[USOPP]
I've got it!
Yes, Luffy! Yes!
[NAMI]
But honestly, Luffy!
How about how I feel,
huh? You're so selfish!
I gotcha, Boss.
Hah. How very clever of you!
Normally, Luffy wouldn't
do something like this.
Rayleigh's with him, so it must
be some idea he cooked up.
There's gotta be a catch here.
[ZORO grunting]
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[NARRATOR] Now that
Whitebeard's era has ended,
ambitious pirates
all over the world
are starting to make their move.
[NARRATOR]
Trafalgar Law, however,
has something else in mind.
[PENGUIN] What? You don't
want to leave yet?
[SHACHI] Come on, let's
go to the New World!
[PENGUIN] We've been sitting
around here long enough already!
[SHACHI]
Yeah, what are we waiting for?
Like I said, we're gonna
leave when it's time.
Have some patience.
One Piece isn't going anywhere.
For now, we just bide our time.
But Captain!
Blackbeard's already starting to
make his move in the New World!
And in a big way, too!
I heard he's already taken down
at least one crew of pirates!
[HEART PIRATE A]
Yeah, and a bunch of rookies
are heading over there hoping
to take Whitebeard's place
as an Emperor!
[HEART PIRATE B]
If we keep wasting time,
all the other pirates'll
leave us in the dust for sure!
We're better off
letting them eliminate
each other before we get there.
That'll thin out
the competition, right?
Now why don't you
dispense with the whining
and do as I tell you for once?
We will get what we want,
whatever it takes.
[HEART PIRATES cheer]
Well, in that case,
we're with you all the way!
Aye-aye, Captain Law, aye-aye!
I got your back wherever we go.
[PENGUIN, SHACHI]
Are you sleeping?!
[BEPO]
I'm sorry.
[PENGUIN, SHACHI]
Don't apologize, just wake up!
[DRAKE PIRATE C]
I'm gonna freeze to death.
Are you sure this is the place?
[DRAKE PIRATE D] There can't
be anyone else out here.
[DRAKE grunts]
[DRAKE PIRATE C]
What's that?
[DRAKE PIRATE D] There's
something falling from the sky!
Hurry, get back!
[DRAKE PIRATES yelling]
[DRAKE groans]
[DRAKE PIRATES groan]
[DRAKE PIRATE E]
Everybody all right?
[DRAKE PIRATE F]
Yeah. I'm fine.
[DRAKE PIRATE H] Damn. What the
hell is wrong with this island?
[DRAKE PIRATE B] Captain, I
think we should get out of here.
There's no way anybody lives in
a dangerous place like this!
[DRAKE]
Are you sure about that?
In this sea,
anything is possible.
Take a look.
[DRAKE PIRATE I] That pile
of snow has a weird shape.
[DRAKE PIRATE J] Yeah, and
those icicles are stuck in it.
[DRAKE PIRATE K] Wait a sec,
it's some kinda metal dome!
What the...?
And now it's opening up?
[DRAKE PIRATE L]
Okay, you got me.
I wasn't expecting a whole
town to be in there.
[DRAKE PIRATES gasp]
[SCOTCH]
If you made it this far,
you should know this island
is very important to Kaido.
And I'm in charge of
security around here.
Yeah?
And what's your point?
Nothing really,
I just figured it was only
fair to give you a warning.
There's gonna be serious trouble
if a rookie like
you pisses Kaido off.
[DRAKE]
You mean, if I were to kill you
or harm you in some way,
that would get his attention?
You bet it would, pal.
So just take your
little friends--
[DRAKE] That makes
things easy for me then!
Whoa.
An ancient Zoan type, huh?
Don't see that every day!
[roars]
--[gunshots]
--[roaring]
[APOO]
One, two, Scratch and Boom!
That's how ya do it!
Holy crap, that took
a lot out of me.
That's Captain Apoo for ya!
Oh, yeah, he's got our backs!
[BOAR A growls]
[ON-AIR PIRATES]
Huh?
[BOARS growling]
[ON-AIR PIRATES gasp]
Uh-oh, there's too many!
[ON-AIR PIRATE A]
This is bad news!
[APOO]
Okay, not great.
No worries, everybody!
Just let Captain Apoo kick
their butts for us real quick!
All right, boys,
I've got a plan!
[ON-AIR PIRATES]
Yeah?
Run for your lives!
[ON-AIR PIRATES]
What?!
[BOARS growling]
I coulda beat 'em,
I just thought I'd take
the high road this time!
--[BOARS growling]
--[ON-AIR PIRATES whimpering]
[ON-AIR PIRATE B]
Captain!
We're headed straight
for a cliff!
[APOO] Open to suggestions
if you've got any!
[BOARS growling]
[ON-AIR PIRATE B] Oh, crap,
that means I'm a goner for sure!
[APOO]
Don't give up yet!
[ON-AIR PIRATE C] Oh, no!
We're gonna fall into the water!
[APOO]
Who cares, just go for it!
[ON-AIR PIRATES]
What?
[APOO]
Huh?
[ON-AIR PIRATE B]
Hey, that's pretty funny!
We're the On-Air Pirates
and we're running on air!
[ON-AIR PIRATE A] The boars
are running on air, too!
[APOO]
Yeah, yeah, I get it!
What the hell is up with
this crazy island anyway?
Too hot.
I'm beat, you guys,
I can't move.
One more step and my
legs'll fall right off.
Uh-oh, a fish just
bit me down there.
Stifle your bellyachin'
over there, Wolf!
It's because of you the raft
almost broke clean in two!
That's the reason
we're here, y'know!
[SHIRYU] You can blame it
on the giant if you like,
but trying to make it through
the New World on that
flimsy thing was a fool's
errand in the first place.
Guess we shoulda nabbed
ourselves a Navy vessel
back at Marineford
when we had the chance.
It wasn't our fault, that
raft had sentimental value!
None of you lot ever
prepare for anything.
You're all to blame for this.
Hey, I got an idea, Teach!
Maybe you oughta let me be
the Captain from here on meowt?
[chuckles] Oh, don't
make me kill you.
We're the Blackbeard
Pirates, remember?
Heaven only knows
what's going to become
of our miserable
souls after this.
[laughs] I need some more booze.
Can we find an island with
more liquor and less fire?
[laughs]
No kidding. A new ship's nice,
but I need a new outfit first.
These jailbird
clothes are just awful.
You'll have to
endure it for now.
Thick horizontal stripes make
me look heavy, you know.
Dah, do they? Maybe I'm
still too sober to notice.
You spy any Navy
ships out there?
I'll go and take a look.
Surely they know better
than to make us wait.
Let's hope so!
'Cause this old crew's gettin'
tired of roasting alive!
[BONNEY groans]
[BLACKBEARD] Ain't that right,
Miss Jewelry Bonney?
Poor Captain Bonney.
[panting]
And to think that a sweet
little thing like you's
racked up a bounty of
over 100,000,000 berries!
Only the strongest can hope to
sail the seas of the New World.
Ya might've come all the way
from the South Blue,
but I'm afraid your
voyage stops here.
[BLACKBEARD cackles]
[BLACKBEARD PIRATES laughing]
I'm afraid you're
not tough enough
to cut it as
a member of my crew,
but, hey, I might be
willing to let you tag along
if you promise to be my girl.
[BONNEY grunts]
That sound like
a deal to you? Huh?
No way, fatass!
--[BLACKBEARD groans]
--[BONNEY] I'll kill you!
[BLACKBEARD PIRATES laughing]
That sounds like a no.
What? I asked you nicely!
Women oughta have more decency!
This lousy crew's indecent
enough to begin with!
That's nice of you
to say, Captain!
[GROUP laughing]
Might as well leave the broad
with the Navy like we planned!
I was gonna keep her and steal
the ship, but screw that.
--[VAN AUGER] Captain.
--Huh?
[VAN AUGER]
The Navy is on their way.
About damn time! And do they
have our ship with 'em?
[VAN AUGER] They brought one,
but they're not giving it to us.
[BLACKBEARD]
What? How do you know that?
[VAN AUGER]
Because Akainu's on it.
[BLACKBEARD] Damn it! That's not
what I need to hear right now.
--[BLACKBEARD PIRATES shouting]
--[BLACKBEARD] Let's get movin'!
[BURGESS]
We screwed up!
[AKAINU]
Where's Blackbeard?
[MARINE A]
He's gone, sir!
[AKAINU] When I found out you
had escaped from the Government,
it nearly froze my blood.
[BONNEY grunts]
Oh, well. I suppose
it's all over now.
[gasps] You bastards!
I'm gonna make you pay,
do you hear me?
Disappeared?
Yeah, that's the best
way I can describe it.
So, Sengoku put you up to this?
I'll tear him apart!
Nah, think higher up the ladder.
[MORIA groans]
That ain't a figure
of speech either.
One minute he's there and
then poof, gone! [chuckles]
Not bad, huh? What can I say?
That Shadow Shadow
Fruit is tricky!
[NOBLE A]
It's not a joke!
Relax, buddy.
He was beat up
pretty bad anyway.
So, I guarantee you
he's dead by now.
Well, he's got that
zombie thing going on,
so he might come back
from the dead. [chuckles]
Now that would be ironic.
You shouldn't have done
such a sloppy job.
--[NOBLE A gasps]
--And you shouldn't
be getting cocky, my friend,
because the last time
I checked, you're not my boss.
No matter what kind of
authority you might have
as part of the World Government,
I'm still a pirate,
so I don't care.
[NOBLE A grunts]
And if I ever get
tired of doing business
with the likes of you clowns,
I can just give up
my title as a Warlord.
Don't you forget that.
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, in Birdie Kingdom...
[NARRATOR] ...the birds
and the natives have
bid their friend,
Chopper, farewell.
[NATIVE G sighs]
Me miss Raccoon already.
[chirps]
[BIRDS squawking]
Sound like birds sad
without Raccoon, too.
We hoping for Raccoon friend
coming back to visit one day.
Real soon!
[BIRDS squawk]
Okay, now everybody need
to finishing today work.
[BIRD D squawks]
[chirping]
[BIRDS squawking]
[NATIVE L]
Hmm? What that?
Bird come back!
[NATIVE H]
Wonder what happen?
[NATIVE I]
Yeah, too early return!
[NATIVE H]
Huh?
But where Raccoon friend go?
[NATIVE I]
Lost on trip?
Maybe too much windy,
poor Raccoon fall in ocean!
Big danger! We're going
and rescue little friend!
[ALL gasp]
[NATIVE I]
What? Who that up there?
[CHOPPER]
I'm glad you asked!
Sworn to protect all creatures
of this world from evil.
I am the hero
of peace and justice,
Chopper Mask has arrived!
Uh, hey, Raccoon, we know
we saying come back soon,
but maybe today too much early.
No! You guys've
got the wrong idea!
Chopper's a good friend of mine
and maybe we look alike,
but my name's Chopper Mask!
[NATIVE H]
You not fooling us.
You cover face so not look like
big wimp for come back early.
[CHOPPER] I already told
you guys, I'm not him!
[CHOPPER yells, groans]
[NATIVES gasp]
Raccoon fall down go ouch?
[CHOPPER] I'm not a raccoon.
I'm Chopper Mask, dammit!
Listen, we be nice to Raccoon
and play his pretending game.
If he want be Chopper Mask
so bad, then that okay.
We sorry we not
understand first time.
Yeah, we had some confuse.
Now we know you Chopper Mask
with wearing cool costume.
You not looking like
Raccoon friend at all.
It nice to meeting you,
Chopper Mask.
Oh, just forget it, I don't
need your stupid pity!
Hey! Raccoon back!
[chirping]
[CHOPPER gasps]
[chuckles]
You silly birdie! That tickles!
[NATIVES laugh]
[CHOPPER]
The truth is,
there's something
I need to take care of.
Can I stay here a bit longer?
[NATIVE L] You welcome
always. Reason not matter!
[CHOPPER]
There's so many different plants
growing on that tree.
Half of them I've never
even seen in books before!
I'd like to study them a little.
[NATIVE L]
We have good place for study.
I need to get stronger,
too, while I'm at it...
A lot stronger.
[NATIVE E]
Hello, Raccoon friend!
[NATIVE F]
You already come back so soon?
[NATIVE J]
We happy!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah.
Turns out I'm gonna
be staying on the island
with you guys for a while!
Here. Should help for learning.
[CHOPPER gasps]
Hey, where are we?
[NATIVE L]
Me show you.
[CHOPPER gasps]
[NATIVE L]
Village library.
You maybe can study in here.
[CHOPPER]
So many books!
[CHOPPER giggles]
[CHOPPER] Whoa, the walls
are covered in 'em!
Hey! You've got books on all the
plants I wanted to learn about.
This is exactly what I needed!
[CHOPPER]
Just look at all these.
[NATIVE L] Island have many
useful plant for make medicine.
We know how to make before,
but birds got in way.
Even though we have knowledge,
we stuck long time without
ingredients and
family got bad sick.
Wow, this is crazy.
I shouldn't have judged
them by their looks.
I guess their weapons
are pretty high-tech
now that I think about it.
I mean sure, they talk
dumb and look dumb.
--[NATIVE L gasps]
--But they're pretty smart
and their medical science
is the best I've ever seen!
I've got a lot to learn!
Stop, Raccoon!
Maybe you thinking
you talking quietly
so nobody hear you,
but you very loud!
And you not say
a very nice thing.
Makes me wonder...
How much can I accomplish
on this island?
[VILLAGER C] Hey, what is
that creature over there?
[VILLAGER D]
It looks like a yeti!
[VILLAGER E] It's dangerous.
Get the children inside quickly!
[VILLAGER C]
A gun! Bring me a gun!
--[VILLAGER D] Yeah, shoot him!
--[VILLAGER F] It's a monster!
[VILLAGER F]
See? I told you he was real.
[VILLAGER D]
Kill it!
--[VILLAGERS shouting]
--[CHOPPER crying]
[gunshots]
--[gunshot]
--[CHOPPER gasps]
A skull?
[HIRILUK]
This symbolizes my belief
that nothing is impossible!
By raising this flag,
I vow to fight just
like the pirates do!
It's great to be a pirate!
The most amazing
people sail the seas.
Chopper, someday you've
got to go to sea!
If you do, you'll realize
just how small your problems
really are in comparison
to the vastness of the oceans.
The island you were born on is
like this compared to the world!
[CHOPPER]
Really?
[HIRILUK]
No, it's smaller! Like this.
[HIRILUK, CHOPPER laugh]
[HIRILUK] Your destiny
lies beyond that shining sea!
Hey! You're gonna
to come on our ship
and be a pirate with us, 'kay?
[CHOPPER] Listen, maybe
I do want to be a pirate.
[CHOPPER]
But I can't ever be one of you!
I'm not a human! I'm a monster!
I can't be your friend,
and I can't join your crew!
So... I just wanted to say...
...I really
appreciate the offer.
It was nice of you,
so thank you.
I'm just gonna stay here but...
[CHOPPER] But if you wanted to
you could stop by here again--
[LUFFY]
Shut up! Let's go!
[CHOPPER crying]
[CHOPPER] Luffy's the one
who took me out to sea.
I was happy to follow
him anywhere.
[CHOPPER] But what have
I done to help him?
[CHOPPER] I don't want to
go through that again, ever.
It hurt, but I think maybe...
[CHOPPER gasping]
[BROOK screams]
[inaudible]
[SANJI groans]
[USOPP screams]
[inaudible]
[ZORO groans]
[CHOPPER] I think it must've
hurt Luffy more than any of us!
[CHOPPER] Now that I
have friends like him,
it doesn't matter
what people say!
It doesn't matter
if they're scared of me!
So, if Luffy's in
trouble or he's sad...
...I'll be a monster or whatever
else it takes to help him!
[LUFFY]
Chopper!
Chopper.
[crying]
Luffy!
I swear, I'm gonna get stronger!
I'm gonna be there
for you this time!
[NARRATOR] As Luffy's message
reaches Weatheria and Baldimore,
Nami and Franky decide to plot
a new course of
action for themselves.
Meanwhile, Sanji discovers
that the Kamabakka Kingdom
may have something
valuable to offer him,
as long as he's willing
to fight for it.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Living Through Hell!
Sanji's Fight for His Manhood!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!