[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[ONIGUMO] Those ranked
Lieutenant Commander or below,
stay put!
To the 200 elite
Captains and Commanders,
engage the enemy and
wipe them out immediately!
Destroy them!
[MARINES yelling]
[CAPTAIN 308A] Capture Nico
Robin and bring her here!
You don't have to worry
about protecting me anymore.
If the crew is fighting,
then I'm fighting, too.
Luffy'll be here soon--
We can't give up!
[MARINES yelling]
[LUCCI] So long as that woman is
wanted by the World Government,
I'll chase her to the ends
of the Earth if need be!
That is the
meaning of Dark Justice!
You won't be chasing anyone!
I'm putting an end to this,
right here, right now!
[LUFFY] Jet Stamp!
[LUCCI] Six King Gun!
[USOPP] Oh, no!
[CAPTAIN 308F] I got him!
[ZORO] Watch out!
Damn it, this is no time
for you to be spacing out, Us--
[USOPP] Luffy!
What the hell are you doing?
Get up!
Luffy!
[LUFFY] Fists Full of Emotion!
Luffy Unleashes Gatling
with All His Might!
[FRANKY] Weapons Left!
[FRANKY] Super!
[MARINE 309C] Commander!
Those Straw Hats
are no ordinary pirates!
They're insanely strong!
They're holding their
own against the Captains!
Huh! So that woman
has Devil Fruit powers!
Everyone attack on my command.
Go!
[MARINES yelling]
Now Cien Fleurs!
With a Flip!
Here we go.
Thunder Ball!
[NAMI]
Thunderbolt Tempo!
That'll teach you
to mess with us!
Guess these guys
are a bit stronger
than your average Marine.
Two-Sword Style...
[ZORO]
...Hawk Wave!
[ZORO] Who wants
their ass kicked next?
[ZORO] Usopp.
Luffy!
[USOPP]
Can you hear me?
Luffy!
Get up!
Usopp...
I didn't know
you were here, too.
[USOPP]
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just came here
to save Robin!
That's it, all right?
I didn't come to see
you or your stupid face,
understand me?
Come on. Enough.
What an idiot!
Hey, you!
The CP9 Boss Cat!
I know you hear me!
From here on out,
I'm your opponent!
Come and get some!
Yeah! That's right!
If you mess with Robin,
then you mess with me!
Now listen and
listen good, you bastard!
I'm a fearsome pirate!
A warrior among warriors!
And I command an army
of over 8000 men!
I am the great Captain Usopp!
[USOPP] I've sailed
all over the Grand Line.
I've destroyed
island after island,
wreaking havoc everywhere I go!
And if the World Government
wants to go toe to toe with me,
then I'll crush
every last one of you
with my little pinky finger!
Now come on up
here and fight me
if you've got the guts.
Or are you just a scaredy-cat?
No... No, wait...
Hey! Get back here!
You leave him alone!
This is between
you and me, got it?
[LUCCI] You've already lost.
I have no business with you.
I'm going to kill
every last one of them,
and save you for last
so you can watch it happen.
Come get me,
Boss Kitty-Cat!
I am gonna take you out!
You idiot!
Shut up, already!
He's gonna kill you!
You shut up!
What the hell are you
gonna do about it, huh?
You're almost dead!
That pigeon bastard's mine!
I'm gonna kick his ass
all over the place!
Then get up!
Show him what you're made of!
Stop lying around
coughing and bleeding
like you're about to die!
That is not the
Luffy I know at all!
Even though it's
filled with smoke,
we can still see the sky!
[USOPP]
We can still see the ocean!
[USOPP] This place isn't hell!
I can't believe you'd
let it end like this!
So stop acting like
you're about to die,
you stupid bastard!
What's wrong with you?
Why are you trying
to make us worry?
Get up and fight!
Finished with
your little speech?
Then I suggest you get ready
to show me what you've got.
[LUFFY]
You're right, Usopp.
[LUFFY] This place isn't hell.
It's not even close.
Luffy...
Finish him!
Then we can all leave
this place together!
I'll win no matter what!
I'm surprised you can stand.
I'm never gonna give up.
You hear me?
Until I defeat you,
I won't drop to the
ground ever again.
Now Life Return: Terminate.
This annoying farce of yours
has gone on long enough.
I'll crush you with a
single blow and end this,
once and for all.
Oh, and don't worry
about your little friends.
Just as you wished,
you'll all be reunited
once again very soon.
Once I kill you,
they're next,
then you'll spend
eternity together in hell.
Spots Attack!
[yelling]
How dare you!
You two can't treat
the marines like this!
As long as we stay clear
of those thunderclouds,
we got 'em.
Augh! There's
already another one?
All right, men!
We need to spread out!
Break formation and--
What is it? I'm busy here!
What the hell'd
ya do that for?
[NAMI] Hey, guys!
When the lightning
strikes this time,
try not to get too electrocuted.
Thunder Ball!
[NAMI] Thunderbolt Tempo!
[MARINES screaming]
Yeah!
Way to go, pirate ladies!
Meow! Meow!
[KOKORO] Nice work!
Listen.
We're all okay over here,
so go on upstairs
and help those boys out!
Your raccoon-dog will be
safe here with us, okay?
Meow!
Racoon-dog?
I'm a reindeer. A reindeer!
Okay, then!
We'll leave Chopper with you!
Take care of him!
Ready?
Yeah.
Everyone's fighting
as hard as they can,
and I can't do
anything to help them!
It's no fair!
Good luck!
Give it all you've got!
[MARINE 309C] Wait, what?
What do you mean "you're
running away?" We're guards!
We're supposed to be
guarding this place!
It's our duty as Marines!
[MARINE 309D]
The situation has changed!
This island's
going to be destroyed!
We're evacuating!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL 309A]
Click! Beep! Beep!
[MARINE 309C] Dammit!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL 309A]
Beep. Beep. Beep. Beep.
Bingo.
Luffy.
[LUCCI] Victory Bird!
[USOPP] Dammit!
What's up with these guys?
I can't hit any of 'em!
Hey! I got 'em!
I see!
My attacks were so fast
they didn't even
realize they got hit!
Oh yeah!
That's what you get
when you mess with
the king of the snipers.
Now everyone sing!
♪ Oh, the wind
carries my name... ♪
[BERRY GOOD chuckles]
[BERRY GOOD] That's the power
of the Berry-Berry Fruit.
It's Berry deadly!
Damn it all!
I can't even move here!
You're finished!
Hey! Thanks!
Whoa! Wait!
Just where do you
think you're going?
[FRANKY] If you like
flying around so much--
[BERRY GOOD]
No! Don't! Hold on a sec!
[FRANKY] Then, Weapons Left!
[MARINES exclaim]
Be careful!
Some of these jerks
have Devil Fruit powers!
They could say
the same of me!
It's time for Trienta Fleurs!
And Clutch!
[SHU] You must be Roronoa Zoro.
That's right.
What's it to you?
[SHU]
I'm here to eliminate you!
[ZORO] Good luck with that!
[SHU] I ate the Rust-Rust
Fruit and became a Rust Man.
You and your swords
will never defeat me.
Dammit! My Yubashiri!
[SHU]
That was just the beginning.
I'll turn all of your blades
into little piles of rust.
That's an interesting trick.
[ZORO] But it won't work twice.
[SHU] By the way, if you
think that's all I can do,
you're sadly mistaken!
No!
What happened?
Why can't I move?
[SHU] Because I rusted every
single joint in your body.
Now, let's get the
rest of you as well!
[ZORO] Dammit!
[USOPP] Firebird Star!
[USOPP]
Are you all right, swordsman?
[chuckles]
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Now Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
I won't fall
for that one agai--!
[LUCCI]
Ultimate Radius...
...Six King Gun!
[LUFFY yelling]
Until I defeat you,
I won't drop to the
ground ever again.
[growling]
Keep a close eye
on Nico Robin.
She'll grow to be more
than you can handle.
[LUFFY] Now Gum-Gum--
[ROBIN] No. It's over.
This is the last
time you'll see me.
This is World
Government business.
People like you
should stay out of it.
She did it all
for us, you know!
She's going to
sacrifice herself!
[LUCCI] Iron Body!
You're all going to die!
You morons can't
challenge the entire world
and expect to win!
So long as that woman is
wanted by the World Government,
I'll chase her forever!
I want to live!
Jet...
...Gatling!
What happened?
What the heck's
going on over there?
Luffy!
[MARINE 309L]
Whoa! Look at the tower!
[MARINE 309M] Hey. Wait.
What is that?
[MARINE 309N]
Down there! You see?
[MARINE 309G]
Attention aboard all ships.
I have an urgent report!
[MARINE 309G]
Just now, Rob Lucci,
the most powerful agent of CP9,
was seen lying face-down and
lifeless near the first column.
I repeat, Rob Lucci
has just been defeated
by Straw Hat Luffy!
Yes!
It's over.
We should be okay now.
We're all going back together!
Robin!
[USOPP]
So you actually came for us.
I should've known.
We can always count on you!
Luffy! The sea!
Jump into the sea!
We've got one more friend here!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
From the Sea,
A Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats
Share the Strongest Bond.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!