[NARRATOR] Luffy
accepted a challenge
from the Foxy Pirates
and wagered
his own crewmates in
a "Davy Back Fight."
[NARRATOR] However,
thanks to Foxy's trickery,
the Straw Hats lost the
first round, the Donut Race.
[FOXY] My first selection
is none other than...
...you! The doctor!
Tony Tony Chopper!
Boil me or cook me alive!
Give me your worst,
you bastards!
[NARRATOR] Now, an
unlikely duo must win
the second round, the Groggy
Ring, to get Chopper back.
Disappointed?
Not at all.
[CHIRP CHIRP]
Chirp, chirp!
[ITOMIMIZU] Our mighty
Groggy Ring combatants
have taken the field!
Opposing them, on
the Straw Hat's team.
Their meddlesome sidelined
supporter from the first round.
The savage chef Sanji!
I think you mean "stylish chef."
Puh-puh-puh...
[ITOMIMIZU] And beside him, with
a bounty of 60 million berries,
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro!
[PICKLES] Hardly
worth our time to squash
a couple of pipsqueaks like
these! Hehehe. Right, Big Pan?
Huh?
Puh-puh-puh...
He can't hear you.
Man, what do these guys eat?
[REFEREE] We'll start
this out with a coin toss.
Tails.
What about you?
[SANJI] Uhh... Kind of
has to be heads, right?
[REFEREE] Tails.
Hehehe...
[REFEREE]
Field or ball?
Ball please.
[ITOMIMIZU]
You heard them!
Our Groggy Monsters
have chosen the ball!
The Straw Hat's ball
man will now enter
the other team's mid circle!
[REFEREE]
Left or right?
[ZORO]
Doesn't matter.
[ITOMIMIZU] In case
you were wondering,
the ball men
are the players
with the silly little
hats on their heads.
Knock your opponent's
ball man into the ring
on their side of the field
and the game is yours!
[RANDOM FOXY C]
Just get on with it!
Hey ball man get
in position already!
Now listen. I never agreed to
be the ball in the first place.
You better shut your mouth
unless you want a
boot to the teeth.
How am I supposed to look cool
with this thing on my head?!
You gonna cry over a hat?
Hey! That looks good on you!
You think I'm gonna
fall for that, stupid?!
Zoro! Sanji!
I'm counting on you!
I'm sorry we lost the
last round, you guys!
It's up to you now!
Please get Chopper
back! You gotta!
Wow, would you look at
that! It's a real Wotan!
They aren't as large
as pureblooded giants
but he's still pretty big.
Feh-feh-feh!
Don't bother cheering for
your friends it's no use!
Those guys are more
than just muscle
they're Groggy Ring experts!
Oh, hey Split Head.
Did you want something?
He said it again.
Aw, Poor Boss!
[PORCHE] Why would you be so
cruel to this sweet, gentle man?
What's with that face?
If you're afraid
I'm gonna interfere again,
then don't worry!
I won't even need to in
this round! You babies!
Don't tell me you can
butt in on this game, too?!
Yep! It all depends on
how the captain feels!
Naturally some
pirates like to fight fair
and square so they can test
the strength of their crew.
Others will cheat
any way they can
to make sure they
never lose a match.
But I just do
whatever I want!
Feh-feh-feh!
I don't see why
you're complaining
about a little foul
play here and there.
If you're a real pirate,
you should be used to
these sorts of things, right?
The sea is treacherous.
Oh yeah. You would know.
[ZORO and SANJI] Three.
By the way,
your team looks
to be playing a
game of their own.
[ZORO and SANJI] Three.
They do know the match
is about to start, right?
[ZORO and SANJI] Three.
[NAMI]
Laugh while you still can!
They're just laid back,
'cause they know they can win!
I saw that, cheater!
You went too early
on that last one!
Shut up! You're just
mad 'cause you lost.
Like you always do.
What?! I always lose, huh?!
We'll just see about that!
Let's do best three out of five!
You'll just lose again.
So is the chef your
ball man, or what?
Hurry up!
[NAMI thinking] Is that what
those idiots are arguing about?
Sanji! That hat
looks great on you!
All right! Let's rock!
Ball Man's here
to kick some ass!
Gotta admit,
it does suit you.
You look like
a real prince.
From the kingdom
of lameasses.
You're wasting time!
Start the match!
[SANJI]
You suck.
[ZORO]
No, you suck.
[SANJI]
Hey, hold it!
No weapons on
the field, pal!
You gotta lose the swords!
Huh? Those the rules?
Yep! 'Cause this
is a ball game!
Can't have you slicing
each other up, now can we?
Fine! My fists
are all I need!
[SANJI] You sure you're
gonna be okay out there?
A swordsman without
his swords is just, well...
[ZORO]
What?
A normal guy. Only lamer.
That wasn't even a
good burn! Get over it!
[ITOMIMIZU] It certainly
took long enough,
but it looks like the
Straw Hat's Ball Man
is finally making his way
to the opponent's circle!
[ZORO] Hey cook, I hope
you get trampled out there.
[SANJI]
Up yours.
[CROWD cheers]
[ITOMIMIZU] The crowd
is hungry for action today!
Big Pan, are you ready to
make some grown men cry?
Huh?
Puh-puh-puh!
He can't hear you!
Eh... Heh heh heh...
Come on, man!
Hahahaha!
Pay attention for once!
Huh?
It's not that funny,
stop laughing!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What can I say?
The Groggy Monsters are
always up for a good laugh!
Now why don't we go
over a few quick rules?
There's no time limit, and
the first team to score wins!
[ZORO thinking] So all we gotta
do to win is knock jumbo's head
into the ring on
their side. Simple enough.
Hahahahaha!
[ZORO thinking] Hard part
is gonna be stopping them
from planting the
cook's head in our ring.
[swallows]
[ITOMIMIZU] Can
Team Straw Hat win back
the reindeer they
lost in Round 1,
or will they lose
another member?!
As you can see,
Foxy's returning champs
are laughing in the
face of their competition.
But will they be the
ones to laugh last?
The whistle is
about to sound!
[whistle]
[ITOMIMIZU]
Let the game begin!
We start with Ball Man
Sanji deep in enemy territory!
Will he retreat or attack?!
Let's do this!
[ITOMIMIZU] Tackle
Machine Pickles takes off
with a heavy charge!
Okay, just gotta head for their
ball man and finish them off.
Sling Tackle!
Get outta my way!
Let's see what
you got, big man.
I hope that fat head of
yours fits in the goal!
It's gonna be
a ball man fight!
Collier...!
Hey! What's going on here?!
His skin's all slimy!
The chef is
slipping and sliding
on Big Pan's massive arm!
But that's no surprise!
After all, Big Pan's
a Loach fish Wotan!
They have slippery skin!
What the heck are you doing?
Stop screwing around!
Run-and-gun!
Puh-puh-puh...
Get down here!
You better watch what
you wish for, sword man!
Punk Pass!
[ITOMIMIZU] This is it!
Big Pan's super-long pass!
Ahhhh!
Sanji!
[SANJI]
Ahhhh!
[ITOMIMIZU] Team
Captain Hamburg races
onto the scene
for the catch!
But Zoro is in
hot pursuit as well!
If that stupid
head of yours
makes it anywhere near the
goal, I'm gonna chop it off!
You talk big but just
wait 'til I get down there!
Now, my Sweeping Tackle!
[ITOMIMIZU] Pickles crosses
over the rival team's line.
Meanwhile, Hamburg flies
high for a fancy mid-air catch!
Perfect! And then.
Gorilla Throw!
Ahhh!
I got it! I got it!
[ITOMIMIZU] Pickles
dashes into position!
Get back here, damn it!
[ITOMIMIZU] Zoro goes
for an interception!
Spinning Tackle!
Uh-oh.
[ITOMIMIZU]
With his partner down,
ball man Sanji is sent
spiraling into the sky!
Ahhhh!
Sanji!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Bringing up the rear,
Big Pan storms
across the field!
And catches the
falling Hamburg!
[BIG PAN]
Punk Receive.
[ITOMIMIZU] Once again,
Hamburg nabs Sanji
with a perfect catch!
Incredible!
The ring is in sight!
Is this it?!
You can't go
down that easy!
Yeah! It's the
Hamburger Dunk!
Ahhhh!!!
Cut it out!
Hurry, do something!
Zoro! Sanji!
[ITOMIMIZU] The Straw Hats
are running out of time!
I know, I'm on it.
You don't need to remind me.
It ain't over!
I won't let you score!
Aaaahhh!!
[SANJI]
All right, you've had your fun.
Time to put me down, fat head!
I can't let Zoro
bail me out of this!
I'd never hear the end of it!
And stay down!
[ITOMIMIZU]
No goal!
No goal! Ball Man Sanji
is back on the ground,
and looks like's he's
ready for some more action!
Awesome! Kick that guy
in the face some more!
I can take care of
myself just fine Got it?
If you can stay
on the ground Ball!
[ITOMIMIZU] It seems
our Groggy Monsters
have finally found some
worthy adversaries in the ring!
This one will be a
match to remember!
Chirp, chirp!
The Straw Hats prevail
but can they do it again?
We've seen pigs fly once
today, so anything can happen!
The challengers seem to be
discussing their next move.
Let's get ready
for round two!
You're cramping
my style!
Go back to the
sidelines moss head.
Is it your "style" to get
pounded like a punching bag?!
Whoa dude, they're tough.
That guy picked up
Pickles and tossed him!
I've never seen
Hamburg go flying like that!
[ZORO] Stay outta the
way, and I'll win this.
[SANJI]
I can't stay out of the way.
I'm the Ball Man,
the only one that matters!
No! Hamburg, what are
you doing out there?!
If you lose, I'll never
ever forgive you!
Listen you good-for-nothing
playboy cook, you better get
those fancy eyebrows
outta my way in a hurry!
No, you listen you dumb oaf,
if you don't get your meat-head
off the field right now
I'm gonna fry it up!
[ITOMIMIZU] What this?
The Straw Hat team seems
to be having some sort of
disagreement with each other.
Both ball men are still in play,
so lets hope they can channel
some of that aggression
in a more productive direction!
Hahaha!
Those two sure are
funny, aren't they?
You idiots!
Now's your chance!
What're you doing?!
Their ball man's all alone!
Gang up on him and
knock him in the ring
while those other guys
are still out of the game!
--Hmm?
[loud crash]
[ITOMIMIZU] Big Pan stomps
in for a surprise attack
on the Straw Hats!
Whoa!
Grrrr!!! Too Bad Dance!
Don't run from the ball!
How are you
supposed to score?!
Hey, I'm doing my best here,
but that guy's got
knives on his shoes,
if we don't run away, he's
gonna make mulch out of us!
Hey ref! I thought you said
we couldn't use weapons!
♪ whistles ♪
What?! He's not
even trying, is he?!
And look how much
he's sweating, too!
You can't expect him to catch
every little thing, can you?
Stop screwing around!
[clunk]
Sanji, what were you thinking?!
You saw the whole thing!
I see you sweating over
there, you little cheater!
No, no way, I... I didn't
see nothing. Not a thing.
You liar!
Hey! That's the ref, Sanji!
You're gonna get in trouble!
Yellow card to Sanji
of Team Straw Hat!
You want another
boot to the face?!
Whoa! Hold on, you're
only gonna make it worse!
And there it is!
A yellow card for Sanji!
Just one more of
those and the chef
will be ejected from the
game once and for all, folks!
Shut up! I'll eject you!
[ITOMIMIZU] And the
threats keep coming
from the
foul-mouthed ball man!
Who knows who
he'll lash out at next!
Why don't you
come down here
and say that to my face?!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What is he, a gangster?
Worry about the boots.
The ref can wait.
Wait, an axe?!
You can't miss that!
♪ whistles ♪
I didn't see. Are you sure?
Of course, I'm sure! Look!
He's using a giant axe.
You can see for
yourself, stupid!
Give it up!
You're gonna get a red
card if you don't shut it!
Why are you siding with
them all of a sudden?!
We're gonna get
julienned out there!
I know, but they're trying to
make you do something stupid!
You're playing into their trap!
Who cares?!
If you won't do it for me
at least do it for Chopper!
Okay stand back
and let me handle him!
No! We don't need
the captain butting in
and complicating things!
Sanji, please!
Win the match for me!
I won't let you down!
[USOPP]
That was easy.
All right, now
back to the game!
Ahhh!!
If you're gonna do that
again, why even bother?!
[SANJI] Running around like
this is getting us nowhere!
[ZORO] Yeah, but now that
we know their game plan
we can come up with
a counter attack!
[SANJI] Get ready big
man. It's payback time!
[ZORO] Go back to the sidelines!
This bastard is mine!
There's plenty of him
for the both of you!
[ITOMIMIZU] And they're off!
All three are about to collide!
[SANJI thinking] If I attack
him where his skin's exposed
I'll just end up slipping
around like last time.
That leaves his hands, his feet,
his mask, and his underwear.
Loach Scooping Slide!
Loach Racing Circus!
Uh-oh! Here comes
Big Pan's signature move!
Things are about
to get slippery!
Ha! Bring it on! Who's afraid
of a little skating, right?
[ITOMIMIZU]
Now, there's no escape!
[SANJI]
I'm gonna lose my lunch!
C'mon! Pull it
together guys! Really!
[ITOMIMIZU] It looks
like Pickles and Hamburg
have finally recovered
from their earlier accident!
[RANDOM FOXY D]
Yeah! They're back in it!
[RANDOM FOXY E]
Slaughter them, guys!
[ITOMIMIZU]
And what's this?
It seems that they've
updated their wardrobe!
Their leader Hamburg is
sporting some iron knuckles
and elbow guards!
Where did those come from?
Meanwhile, Pickles has donned
spiked shoulder protectors!
Those clearly violate
the "no weapons" rule!
But by complete coincidence,
the referee seems to be doing
some stretches right now.
Oh well, you can't expect him
to catch everything, right?
Time for revenge
my friend. You ready?
Here goes! Loach Coaster!
Won't stop spinning.
Now we'll bring the pain!
Let's do it!
Spinning Tackle!
[ITOMIMIZU] The Groggy Monsters
launch a counter attack!
But this time, their
target isn't the ball man,
but his partner, Zoro!
This is about to get ugly!
Hamburger Hammer!
[loud crash]
No! Zoro!
[ITOMIMIZU] But the
assault isn't over yet!
Big Pan readies yet
another brutal attack!
Hamburg is brandishing
his mighty elbow guards
and preparing for an
air-to-ground strike!
Oh no.
This is bad.
[ITOMIMIZU]
The Straw Hats are about
to learn the
power of teamwork!
[pained grunting]
[ITOMIMIZU] Like an
arrow raining from the sky.
Hmm? Ahh!
[BIG PAN]
Punk Attack!
[crash]
[pained grunting]
No!
[ITOMIMIZU]
A direct hit!
He won't be
walking that one off!
By the way, fatalities
are a common occurrence
in the Groggy Ring,
in case you didn't know.
[SANJI]
So dizzy.
[ITOMIMIZU] And now
the Foxy Team turns
their attention to the
Straw Hat's ball man!
Human... Cannon!
[ITOMIMIZU] Pickles and
his spikes are closing in fast!
Sanji! Move!
[groans]
Sling Tackle!
[ITOMIMIZU] What,
you thought that was it?
They're just getting started!
[HAMBURG]
Size Attack: S!
[ITOMIMIZU] Hamburg
sends him flying back!
They don't even care
about scoring anymore!
[PICKLES]
M!
[BIG PAN]
L!
[crash]
[ITOMIMIZU] The
Groggy Monsters stomp
the competition flat with a
spectacular 3-man team attack!
[CROWD cheers]
Such a cruel way to win.
[LUFFY]
Get up, Zoro! C'mon Sanji!
[ITOMIMIZU] Both balls
are still in play,
but it looks like Team Straw
Hat is down for the count!
[RANDOM FOXY F]
Piece of cake! Nyahahaha!
[ITOMIMIZU] In fact, you
might say they're "Groggy"!
Now all that's left is to stuff
the ball man in his
coffin, I mean, goal
and it'll be two wins in
a row for the Foxy Pirates!
It just goes to show, you
can't keep a good monster down!
[RANDOM FOXY G]
Looks like we win again!
Hey, let's work together
for ten seconds
Okay, fine but no longer.
♪ ending song ♪
[NAMI]
What a joke!
They're using all the
weapons they want!
[ZORO] C'mon,
Prince Eyebrows, let's go!
[SANJI] Shut up
Moss Head, I got this!
[NAMI] Ugh! I'm so
sick of those two!
[ROBIN] As they say,
boys will be boys.
[LUFFY] I don't care,
as long as they win!
[USOPP]
Can't you work together
just this once
for Chopper's sake?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A Barrage of Red
Cards in Groggy Ring!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!