[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[LUFFY] The Worst Man
in the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!
[birds chirping]
[yawns]
[LUFFY]
This weather's perfect!
[LUFFY grunts, chuckles]
[LUFFY] So which way
is the Grand Line?
[sighs]
Is it that way?
[LUFFY chuckles]
Or maybe... this way?
That way. Over here.
Maybe there? I dunno.
Where could it be? I wanna
see this place! I wanna see!
You need to sit.
Geez... you bug me.
Oh, sorry. Heh! I'm just
excited that we
finally got a cook on board.
Now we just need Nami.
Then nothing will stand between
us and the Grand Line!
Nami, ah... I could just
sit around all day and
think about how,
beautiful she is...
I can't wait till I'll
get to see her again.
So. Are we getting close
to where Nami is?
You know, the island?
You're way too naïve
and way too young!
Don't you get it?!
Don't you realize every
second that passes
brings us closer to
the infamous Arlong?!
[YOSAKU] Nami couldn't stop
looking at Arlong's picture
when she saw it. And it
wasn't a normal kinda stare.
There was something different
about the way she was staring.
Something focused.
[birds chirping]
[YOSAKU] I'm telling you Nami's
planning on taking down Arlong
and then collecting the
20 million‐Berry bounty.
For all we know,
while we just sit here,
she's already making her
way through his compound!
[LUFFY yawns]
That's nice. Let's eat.
Sounds good.
[shouts]
Don't tell me you guys
are so clueless
that you have actually never
heard of the evil Arlong?
Uh, no. so who is he?
Yeah.
[gasps]
[whistling]
isten up, boys! Time for
your education
on the cunning Shark
that is Arlong!
Arlong is a fishman who used to
destroy everything in his path
up and down the Grand Line.
Fishman?
That's cool. I don't think I've
ever met one of those before.
I've heard, that the females
on Fishman island
are some the most
beautiful creatures in
the world to behold.
Fishman sounds weird...
Do they look like this?
[SANJI laughs]
[YOSAKU screams] Can't you focus
for just one minute, please!
Alright... I will start
from the very beginning.
The reason they call
the Grand Line
a pirate graveyard
in the first place
is because of Arlong and
the other two powers
like him who rule over it.
The first of the powers
are known as
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Seven Warlords?
The Seven Warlords are pirates
authorized by the government.
Seriously...?
Why would any pirate on the sea
want government approval?
[YOSAKU] For protection.
The Government
looks the other way
in exchange for a
cut of their treasure,
and they're allowed to exist.
'Course to other pirates
they're just government dogs.
But they didn't get to where
they are by being weak.
These guys are powerful.
[PIRATES shouting]
[YOSAKU] The man who defeated
Zoro is one of these Warlords.
His name is Hawkeye Mihawk.
That's so, cool!
I can't wait to meet all
seven of these guys!
They sound awesome!
Yeah... Well, the first
among the Warlords,
at least first you
should know about,
is Jinbei,
Captain of the Fishmen.
He is dangerous like
no one you've ever known...
Easily causing as much havoc
and destruction around
the Grand Line as Arlong.
Is this closer?
That looks just like your last
picture only standing up.
Arlong has taken control
of over twenty towns since
coming to the East Blue.
His strength easily
surpasses anyone you've
encountered including
that of Don Krieg's...
He's devastating.
So why do you think Nami
would go after this guy,
all by herself huh?
I told you already,
she wants to collect
the bounty on his head.
Oh, wouldn't it be great
if Nami was a mermaid?
I'd give anything to see that!
She'd look like this.
Tear that thing up... or die!
[YOSAKU] Have either
of you morons heard
a single a word that
I've said to you?!
[LUFFY]
Sure. Badass Fishmen.
Some guy's stronger than some
other guy. We get it.
[YOSAKU sighs]
No you don't get it.
You've never had to
face a Fishman.
Well, uh... we will
when we get there so
don't worry about it.
[SANJI grunts]
I guess I'll get lunch started.
'Bout time! Let's eat!
What? Food?
What're you in the mood for?
I want meat right off the bone!
I want sautéed bean sprouts!
[SANJI]
Okay, leave it to me.
This won't take long.
Meat and bean sprouts, no prob.
Man, having a cook is
the best! Huh? Huh?!
It sure is.
[LUFFY]
Bring me meat! Lots of meat!
[YOSAKU] Sprouts! I want
bean sprouts! Bean sprouts!
[NAMI] I can hardly
believe it. There it is.
My hometown.
[ARLONG] Here's this month's
take. I hope you enjoy it.
[cheeps] Ah, Arlong.
You are so much smarter
than your regular
run‐of‐the‐mill pirate.
You know how the world works.
[ARLONG laughs]
Likewise. There aren't
many Marine Captains
who know that
befriending me means
they can milk the
East Blue for eternity.
The fact that you understand
makes you more like me,
than any other marine out here.
Thank you very much.
[ARLONG laughs]
Don't thank me, thank money!
It's the only thing you can
count on in this world.
It's more reliable than people,
that's for sure.
Don't you agree?
[NEZUMI gasps]
Of course.
As a rule I hate all humans,
but you are the one tolerable
exception that I've found.
Well... if you'll excuse me.
Why not stay awhile and
have a drink with me?.
I would, but the longer
a marine cruiser
stays docked at a pirate island,
the quicker we get
unwanted attention.
[ARLONG] I'll kill
anyone who reports you.
Everybody knows that.
[NEZUMI] Thank you,
but still, we must go.
[ARLONG]
Hey, the captain is leaving!
Escort him back to his ship.
[HATCHAN]
Yes sir.
The pot's back
that way... Hop in.
Thank you!
That's very kind of you.
[HATCHAN]
When I see your face,
it always makes me want
to laugh. It's funny.
You look like a rat.
[laughs]
Hey, Hatchan watch
your mouth now.
The Captain's our honored guest.
[HATCHAN]
Oh, right,
Sorry about that.
[NEZUMI]
Don't worry about it.
[HATCHAN]
Here we go, men.
[NEZUMI] These Fishmen are
disgusting. Such a vile group.
But they sure do pay well.
[CHABO]
Hey you. Get outta my way!
Arlong's going to die today!
He killed my daddy and so now
I'm gonna have to kill him!
So move, or I'll have
to kill you too.
Hey!
[CHABO grunts]
Now...
You should know that Arlong
doesn't have time to deal with
whimpering little
punks like you.
You're too young. Go home.
[CHABO whimpers]
Take that with you
and use it to keep yourself
out of trouble, kid.
Go to hell.
[ARLONG]
Nami! You've returned!
I haven't seen you around
here for quite awhile.
So, how did you do this time?
[NAMI]
Heh. Who are you talking to?
You know I can't believe
the world is full of
such blind idiots... Wanna see?
[laughs]
You, girl, are one
excellent liar.
That's true.
[ARLONG] Listen up everybody!
Nami's finally returned!
Time for a party!
[FISHMEN cheer]
[chuckles]
All right. We're here.
That's Arlong Park ahead.
[USOPP] Arlong Park, huh?
So this is the hideout of
Arlong the Fishman Pirate
from the Grand Line?!
[gulps]
[USOPP]
I hope Nami's really here.
Big Sis Nami's ship
was the Going Merry,
so before we do anything stupid,
we should quietly check
to see if it stopped
on this island first.
Yeah. Good idea.
Let's attack.
But I just said we shouldn't
do anything stupid!
What?! Attack?! You idiot!
We know nothing
about this place!
Yeah, these guys
are the Fishmen!
We need some kinda
plan to do that!
[ZORO] While the two of you are
busy blabbering and wimping out,
I'm placing my thoughts on the
battle we're about to face.
Luffy told me to bring her
back and I'll do just that.
[USOPP, JOHNNY whimper]
Let's go!
[USOPP, JOHNNY grunts]
[USOPP gasps]
There it is!
Ha! Found it! The Going Merry.
It's right over there.
Then she has to be on
the island somewhere.
We just have to find her.
What do think you're doing?!
Would you idiots untie me!
I am not the enemy!
[JOHNNY] We're east of Arlong
Park, here at Cocoyashi village.
But it's strange.
Why would she have stopped
so far from the village?
Untie me dammit!!
Zoro, you're hurt way too bad
to be of any help we go ashore.
Just sit tight and relax.
[USOPP chuckles]
It's okay. Rest up.
You can help next time.
[ZORO] One of these
days I'm gonna skewer him
like a piece of meat!
Fear not, gentlemen. I will
bring the girl back safely!
[laughs]
[JOHNNY] Looks, like,
skipping Arlong Park
has sure cheered you up.
[USOPP]
Prepare the anchor!
Bring us alongside
the Going Merry!
Aye!
[USOPP sighs] Yes!
Now that we're under way,
its time to give a
name to this voyage.
I think I shall call it,
"The Great Adventures
of Captain Usopp."
[gasps]
What is it? What'd you see?!
[BOTH]
It's Fishmen!
[USOPP]
Full speed ahead.
[JOHNNY]
Okeydoke.
Why didn't we just
dock right there?!
[USOPP, JOHNNY]
Shh!
Didn't you see that?
There were three Fishmen
over there. It's Arlong's crew.
We can't stop here right now.
Do not yell at me!
If there are fishmen here,
this entire area must be
under Arlong's control.
So what now?
[USOPP] Huh. We could just
say we couldn't find her.
Untie me now, morons! Come on!
[FISHMAN A] Huh. Never seen
that boat before.
Suspicious.
[USOPP, JOHNNY gasp]
Let's run.
Okay.
Untie me! Damn it!
[JOHNNY, USOPP gasp]
[USOPP]
Bye.
[ZORO] Hey you two get back
here or you're gonna die!
[grunts]
There's just this one guy?
Maybe he just drifted here from
real far out or something.
Yeah right.
[ZORO] Those guys are dead
and they don't even know it.
Or maybe somebody just wanted
him to die real slowly.
[FISHMAN A] I think we
should take him to Arlong.
[USOPP gasps]
Forgive me Zoro.
I will tell Luffy that you were
courageous to the bitter end.
Please forgive me Zoro!
I'll never forget you!
Okay, now let's find some land.
[JOHNNY]
Right.
[JOHNNY grunts] I think this
place is called Gosa village.
[USOPP grunts]
[JOHNNY, USOPP gasp]
[USOPP]
Uh. What happened here?
I heard Arlong came
through here
a few weeks back but I
never thought that...
[USOPP]
Everything's upside down!
I've heard people say that
Fishmen can be stronger than
normal human beings by
a very wide margin.
I guess this is how
strong you have to be
to survive the Grand Line.
[JOHNNY gasps]
Maybe, but even the
street's upside down.
The monster Momoo
caused this destruction.
[USOPP]
Monster?
Don't tell me this
place has monsters.
We caught him out
on the grand line
and brought him
back here with us.
[USOPP]
From the Grand Line, huh...?
Wait... We?
[yelps]
You! You were with
that guy from the boat!
[USOPP yelps]
[USOPP]
Later!
[FISHMAN A]
Come back here!
[JOHNNY sighs] That was close.
I wish you luck.
I'll just hold my
position here
and wait here for our back
up from Yosaku and Luffy.
[USOPP laughs]
You may be a Fishman,
but there is no way you can
catch me on dry land.
[USOPP laughs]
I'm a very fast runner!
I'm a beautiful gazelle.
[USOPP grunts]
What the‐‐?
Got you stupid Fishman!
And now I'll avenge my
father by killing you!
[shouts]
[yelps]
[CHABO groans]
[whimpers]
[NOJIKO]
Honestly.
How many times do I
have to tell you, Chabo,
you do not mess
with the Fishmen?
It was just one person who
decided to stand up to them
and they responded by
slaughtering everyone in Gosa.
[NOJIKO] Hm. You look and
smell just like a Fishman,
but I can see that
you're human. Mostly human.
Ah! Mostly?!
[FISHMAN A]
Where'd you go? Over here?
Crap.
A Fishman!
And this time it's for real.
All right. Stand back
and let me handle this one.
Watch as Captain Usopp...
...takes out this Fishman
with a single shot.
Take this. It's my
Special Attack: Lead Star.
[grunts]
I guess he wasn't listening
when I said the Fishmen
would kill us if we
messed with them.
Come on, tough guy...
[screams]
What's wrong?
[NOJIKO]
A long‐nosed creepy guy!
Which way'd he go?
That way.
[FISHMAN A]
Now I gotcha.
Come on. If you help me out,
we can carry him back.
Aw, yeah. Looks great.
[YOSAKU]
Lemme see.
[birds chirping]
[HATCHAN hums]
[HATCHAN exhales]
That looks like it's ready.
[trumpet noises]
[HATCHAN]
Momooo! Lunchtime! Momoo!
Where is he? Kinda weird.
I've never seen Momoo
show up late to a meal.
I wonder what happened?
[YOSAKU]
Yummy. Thank you.
I don't care about you guys.
I'm just practicing for the
evening I get to make
dinner for Nami and myself.
[YOSAKU] I hope you can get
Nami to join the crew again.
She's the best.
Yeah, of course we will.
I mean she is our navigator.
[YOSAKU]
Ha, ha!
Hey, that's mine!
You just ate the other one.
I get to have one for myself.
[LUFFY]
But I ordered the meat!
[YOSAKU]
I don't care! It's mine!
[LUFFY]
Over my dead body!
[YOSAKU]
You'll have to catch me first!
[LUFFY] Give it back!
[YOSAKU]
I'm taking a bite!
[LUFFY]
Don't you dare!
[YOSAKU]
It's got my spit on it.
[LUFFY]
I'll cut that part off.
You fools are going to
make me spill my wine!
Honestly, I don't
know why I even bother
to give them good things.
[FISHMAN B]
Open the gates!
We have prisoner on
board this vessel!
One more time.
What was your purpose in
coming here to this island?
Like I said before,
I'm looking for a girl
you half fish bastard.
[ARLONG scoffs] Wow! For someone
I'd consider a good meal,
you are either really stupid
or you've got a
lot of guts in there.
We fishmen are, simply, the
next rung up the evolutionary
ladder from you
pathetic humans.
We are incredibly resilient.
We can breathe both on
land and underwater,
an ability which
clearly establishes our.
physical superiority over you.
I don't know if this will make
any sense to that puny brain
rolling around in your
head, but fishmen...
...are the lords
of all creatures
and to fight against us
is to defy nature.
[NAMI] I'm really sick
of listening to your
big ideas, Arlong.
[gasps]
Why are you always
so serious Nami?
You know that I wasn't
talking about you.
You are a very special human,
our greatest navigator and a
valued member of this crew.
You always have been.
Say what you will,
but I'm a lot smarter than
any of you, that's for sure.
Why did he call you
his navigator, Nami?
You can't honestly expect me
to believe you work for him.
Hold on, is this guy
a friend of yours, Nami?
[NAMI]
Don't be ridiculous.
This is just another fool who
thought I wasn't going to steal
all of his treasure right
out from under his nose.
To think he actually followed
me here without knowing that,
shows how stupid he is.
So this is the person
you really are.
All along I thought you
couldn't stand pirates.
You thought wrong.
It was all an act.
And you bought the whole show.
[ZORO]
That's...
[gasps]
I'm a pirate, plain and simple.
And a navigator... for Arlong.
[NAMI chuckles]
♪All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[USOPP]
Don't believe it!
Arlong and the Fishmen
rule this entire village.
[SANJI] Aww... don't tell
me seafood isn't allowed.
[LUFFY] I like to chew my
meat right off the bone.
Sanji, more meat!
[USOPP] I can't believe
she's teamed up with Arlong.
I thought Nami was our friend.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece !
"Witch of Cocoyashi Village!
Arlong's Female Leader!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!