[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest the of his crew,
Luffy has arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
Aided by new friends
and old enemies alike,
Luffy battles against the Navy
as he pushes
towards the scaffold.
Thanks to a final charge
from Whitebeard's associates
and a bridge built by Inazuma,
success is within
Luffy's grasp at long last.
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY panting]
Finally, I'm here.
I told you I'd do it!
Luffy!
Hmph. You really are crazy.
[MARINE EE]
Fire!
Blow them to bits
before they hit the ground!
[MARINE FF]
What is that?
It looks like
a tunnel of flames!
[ACE]
Ever since you were little,
you've never listened
to a word I said,
have you?
[LUFFY grunts]
Then you run off
and do something crazy.
Like old times, huh, Luffy?
Let's go!
[LUFFY] "Ace Rescued!
Whitebeard's Final Order!"
[PIRATES cheering]
[MARINE A]
That's... Fire Fist Ace!
[PIRATE A]
He's free!
Yee-haw! Ya did it,
Straw Hat! Yeah!
Hah, hah! You can suck it, Navy!
He hasn't slowed down once,
after all he's been through!
You can't... stop this guy!
Your papa would be so proud!
[crying]
[HANCOCK giggles]
I knew you could do it!
But this is only
the beginning of your
long, happy ending with
me at your side, of course.
Because as soon as you escape
this wretched battlefield...
...we'll be... married!
[HELMEPPO gasping]
[HELMEPPO]
See that?
He really did it!
That crazy little
bastard saved Ace!
Of course he did.
After all, he's Luffy.
Keep your cool!
This isn't over yet!
Open fire as soon as they land!
[MARINES]
Sir!
Let's split up for now!
Don't let your guard down yet!
Okay!
--[LUFFY grunts]
--[MR. 3] Wait, no!
Flame Commandment!
[MARINES gasp]
Fire Pillar!
[MARINES scream]
[MARINES screaming]
[MR. 3 grunts]
They're strong! Be careful, men!
Can you still fight, Luffy?
'Course I can!
Luffy! Ace!
Remember, Ace is a Logia type,
so he's gonna be
really tough to hit.
Never thought I'd need my
little brother to save me.
Guess I'll swallow
my pride this time.
I owe you one, Luffy.
[LUFFY chuckles]
Thanks, but I sure
couldn't've done it
if Whitebeard hadn't shown up.
You think we'll
let you get away?
[MARINE E] Consider this your
execution ground, pirates!
[MARINES gasping]
[LUFFY grunts]
Now charge!
I'll cut him to pieces!
[LUFFY]
Hm.
[MARINES grunting]
[ACE] That's my little brother
you're trying to murder.
I'll have to ask you to stop.
[MARINES gasp]
Fire Fist!
[MARINES screaming]
[LUFFY grunts]
Now, second Gear!
[MARINES]
Shave!
[MARINES grunt]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[MARINES]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
...Jet Stamp!
[MARINES groaning]
[ACE]
Fire Gun!
[MARINES grunting]
[ACE]
Hm?
You're dead!
[MARINE K grunts]
[MARINES gasping]
This is fun and all,
but the sooner we leave this
dump the better, right? Hmph!
Uh-huh!
Hah, hah, hah. They're
a fine team, I dare say.
We're pulling out, clear a path!
[PIRATES cheering]
We can't let them get away!
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINES gasp]
[ACE]
Heh. Firefly!
Fiery Doll!
[yells]
[MARINES scream]
This isn't over yet,
execute them both!
Now, Gum-Gum... Jet Gatling!
[MARINES yelling]
I gotta admit, you've
gotten pretty tough, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Hmph.
One of these days,
I'll be stronger than you!
--[ACE grunts]
--[LUFFY gasps]
All right, then I'll handle
things in the meantime.
"One of these days"?
Sorry, kid.
You're not gonna survive
to see tomorrow, I'm afraid.
Go finish 'em off, Admiral!
What a pain.
All right, Ice Block.
Stand back, Luffy.
And now, Pheasant Beak!
Flame Mirror!
[yelling]
[LUFFY grunting]
He vaporized Aokiji's ice.
Damn, I didn't know
you could do that.
[VISTA laughs]
Well, I can't blame Ace
for showing off a bit.
It's been a long time coming.
[PRISONER A]
Whoa!
A pair of brothers--
that's so cool!
Now's not the time
to be impressed!
Unless you're impressed
with me, that is!
In other words,
fix that transponder snail,
so I can show off again!
Uh, right! Of course, Captain!
[BUGGY growls]
[BUGGY]
Go ahead, Straw Hat.
Enjoy your time
in the limelight,
'cause everything's about
to come crashing down.
And the biggest crash
is gonna be Whitebeard
after I take his head
in all this chaos.
He's gotta be on
his last leg anyway.
[chuckles]
I'll be one of the
Four Emperors in no time!
[PRISONER A]
Wow!
No matter how dicey
the situation gets,
Captain Buggy always
greets it with a smile!
[PRISONERS]
Yeah!
[MR. 3]
Mr. 2...
I hope I could honor your
memory in my own humble way.
Any who, that's enough heroism
for a lifetime. I'm leaving!
[MARINE AA] Which platoon
is this traitor from?
Oh!
[MARINE BB] Hold on! He's a
prisoner impersonating a guard!
No! I was too slow!
[MARINES gasping]
You all right, sir?
This is the worst
blunder of my life.
We have to rectify this.
[laughing]
Huh?
Just let 'em go.
It makes things more
interesting, I say!
Cut the crap!
Those guys went toe-to-toe
with an Admiral!
What the hell are
we supposed to do?
[AKAINU]
Pull yourselves together!
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINES]
Admiral Sakazuki!
They won't make it out of
here alive, don't you worry.
Don't give up, men!
We've got this!
[MARINES gasp]
Great, what the hell is it now?
[MARINES shouting]
[MARINE CC] The enemy
ship is coming through!
Uh, on land somehow!
[MARINE DD]
Don't get close!
It's running on the
ground with it's paddles!
[PIRATES gasp]
Wait, who's on board?
I can't see!
It's Squard!
And it looks like he's got
his crew with him, too!
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
Make a break for it,
Pops! We'll guard you!
We'll show those bastards
the pride of the
Spider Whorl Pirates!
[PIRATES shout]
[WHITEBEARD]
Ah, damn it.
What're you thinking?
[PIRATES]
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
Don't be an idiot,
Squard. You'll die!
Yeah! You got a death
wish or something?
[SQUARD sighs]
[SQUARD]
Yes, of course.
After what I did to Pops,
this is the least I can do.
[SQUARD] I can't hope to atone
for my crime, but if I don't die
fighting here, I know
I'll never rest in peace!
I'm sorry for
bringing you with me.
This should be my fight.
What? Are you kidding me?
We wanted to follow you!
Yeah, you're our captain
till the bitter end!
If we all die here,
then that's our choice!
[PIRATE AA]
Let's not get sentimental here.
Lead the charge, Captain!
[SQUARD]
Thank you.
[SQUARD] Everyone else,
grab Ace, and make a run for it!
St. Elmo's Fire!
[MARINES yell]
[gasps]
[ACE]
Squard?
Those fools...
[MARCO grunts]
Squard, no!
You think anyone's gonna be
happy with a plan like this?
Hey! Hurry up and get
these cuffs off me!
You ready? We'll
fight to the last man!
[PIRATES]
Yeah!
All right, charge!
For Pops...
[yells]
[SQUARD, PIRATES grunting]
What the hell?
Did we run into something?
Huh?
[panting]
But why, Pops?
He... stopped it with one hand.
I thought he was
supposed to be dying!
[ACE, LUFFY gasping]
[MARCO grunts]
[panting]
[WHITEBEARD] You believe
you've done me a favor,
you poor, selfish child?
Don't you know how cruel it is
to force a father
to bury his own sons?
[gasps]
And show some humility!
You think I'm on my last legs
'cause of one measly poke?
It was settled long
before I came here!
Everyone has to grow
old and die someday.
[ALL gasping]
[SQUARD gasping]
[WHITEBEARD]
Our business is done.
Pull out now and I'll
stay here to make sure
I don't lose any more of
my boys to these bastards.
You're staying?
Whaddaya mean?
[WHITEBEARD]
Listen up, Whitebeard Pirates,
and listen well.
[WHITEBEARD] These are my
final orders as your captain,
so you'd better follow them!
You're kidding, right? That's
the last thing we wanna hear!
We're going back together!
[PIRATE L] Yeah! We can't
go on without you!
We didn't save Ace
to let our captain die!
[MARINES yelling]
[ACE]
Cross Fire!
[ACE grunts]
Let's go!
[WHITEBEARD] Even family
must part ways now and then!
You must, survive.
Return to the New World.
Continue your legacy without me!
No, you can't die!
We can find another way!
[WHITEBEARD] Make no mistake.
I'm a relic of a bygone era.
Long have I sailed, but no ship
can carry me into the new age.
[WHITEBEARD]
Now go and forge your own path!
[MARINES yelling]
Whitebeard!
There's no way
we can leave you here!
Look, I know how you feel,
but it's an order!
Old Guy, no!
What are you--?
[WHITEBEARD]
Don't look back boys.
A new age is coming.
[seagulls squawking]
[WHITEBEARD] Everything
started on those warm waters.
[PIRATE N laughing]
Aw man, what a haul!
Hey! You don't even care
about treasure, you weirdo?
Come check it out! There's
plenty to go around, buddy!
Tch! Forget it,
he's always like this.
[PIRATE C]
Huh? What does that mean?
We wouldn't even have
these treasures without him!
Whatever, it's nothin'
to complain about.
If he doesn't care,
then neither should we.
But it's weird!
Pirates live for the booty!
Why else would you
be in the game?
[PIRATE C] Well, what are
you looking for then?
Hey! You listening, Newgate?
[WHITEBEARD] It's been a long
journey, but a good one.
Let's finally
put an end to this!
You Navy bastards!
The Whitebeard Pirates
reluctantly follow
the captain's final
order to retreat.
However, Akainu refuses
to let his enemies escape,
and provokes Ace by
insulting his adoptive father.
Ace fights to defend
the honor of his crew,
but risks losing
his life in the process.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Power That Can
Burn Even Fire
Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!