[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
After losing his brother Ace
during the War of the Best,
Luffy was distraught.
Me? King of the Pirates?
[NARRATOR] He was soon surprised
by Dark King Rayleigh's
unexpected appearance
at the Maiden Island.
I may have another
suggestion for you.
[NARRATOR] After they learned
of Ace's death at Marineford,
the rest of the
Straw Hats made haste
to reunite with Luffy
and offer their support.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[ZORO grunting]
[NARRATOR] This is Gloom
Island, on the Grand Line,
home to the ruins
of the Muggy Kingdom.
An old castle remains from
the long-dead empire.
Despite its age,
a well-known figure has
made the castle his home.
Why did Moria have
to get himself killed?
[PERONA crying]
[MIHAWK]
You're being a pest.
Go and cry somewhere else.
How can you be so heartless
when I'm grieving?
Show some compassion,
ya big meanie!
Don't you have
anything kind to say?
Offer me a tissue!
I'm your guest!
Your manners are appalling!
[MIHAWK]
I never invited you.
The two of you showed up
and started living
here without asking.
Furthermore,
this article is not credible.
What?
But does that mean Moria
could still be alive?
He made it out?
A good question, now you ask.
If he died,
then I didn't see it.
Although, if he did escape,
then I didn't see
that either, I'm afraid.
[PERONA] But you think
he might have survived
and they're lying
about it for some reason?
--Perhaps.
--[door opens]
[ZORO panting]
Huh? What are you
doing out of bed?
You're hurt! Bad! Are you crazy?
And put those swords
down, you moron!
Don't tell me you're gonna
try and fight them again!
Give up. You're lucky you
survived the first fight.
Those baboons'll murder you.
[ZORO]
Shut up!
Keep your nose out
of my business, got it?
How could you say such
a cruel thing to me?
I dragged your stupid body
all the way back here!
Without my help,
you'd be monkey chow!
[ZORO]
Hawk-Eye!
[ZORO grunts]
[PERONA] Give it a rest already!
You can barely even walk!
You're wounded. Stay here.
Why are you in such a hurry?
[ZORO]
Have you forgotten?
You told me what
happened to my captain.
I have to go.
[MIHAWK]
He should still be alive,
but unfortunately, he appears
to be severely traumatized.
Fire Fist Ace died...
right before Straw Hat's eyes.
[ZORO] All this time and I never
even knew the war was happening.
But Luffy's all right.
Are you sure? Where is he now?
Can't you tell me anything else?
No. Alas, that's all I know.
Fine, then I'll leave you alone.
[PERONA]
Hey, stupid! Hold on!
You're never gonna
make it to the shore
without those baboon
things attacking you.
And even if you do get there,
how're you gonna cross the sea?
[MIHAWK]
If you want a boat...
[ZORO gasps]
...circle around
the castle, west side.
Thank you for that.
Are you kidding me? Dummy!
That's the last time
I save your ungrateful butt!
You can bury your own
corpse when they kill you!
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
Luffy,
although you just lost your
brother, no matter what,
I know that you'll
still keep your promise!
That's why I'll get
back to Sabaody, too.
At any cost!
[ZORO grunts]
[HUMANDRILL A screeches]
[HUMANDRILL A yells]
[HUMANDRILLS grunting]
[HUMANDRILL A screeches]
[ZORO]
It's about time.
I knew you guys weren't
gonna let me go that easily.
[HUMANDRILLS yell]
[HUMANDRILL B grunting]
--[ZORO gasps]
--[HUMANDRILL B grunts]
[ZORO]
That's my Bull Demon technique!
[HUMANDRILL A grunts]
[ZORO groans]
[HUMANDRILLS shouting]
[ZORO]
And that's the Dragon Twister!
They've learned to copy
my Three-Sword Style!
[HUMANDRILLS gasp]
[HUMANDRILLS yelling]
[ZORO]
Hey, chumps!
[panting]
Copying me? Pathetic!
How can you be satisfied
with yourselves?
You aren't real swordsmen!
[PERONA] Damn it! He can't
mess with me like that!
After all I've done for him.
He doesn't appreciate anything!
I hope he drops dead!
Yeah, that'd serve him right,
and I wouldn't care one bit!
If you're that worried about
Roronoa, go look for him.
You think I'm worried about him?
What gave you that
impression, huh?
[MIHAWK] In any case, I don't
think he'll die so easily.
Yeah? You're wrong!
By the time Kuma got to him,
he was already banged up,
and since he showed up at the
castle, he's only gotten worse!
And those baboons don't exactly
strike me as the merciful type!
[PERONA] Damn, damn,
damn! This isn't fair!
If Zoro gets himself
killed out there,
I'll be stuck with Hawk-Eye.
And he's downright rude
to my stuffed animals!
And as a host, he hasn't offered
me hot cocoa, not even one time!
You may be kind of an oaf, Zoro,
but you're still a lot more fun
to have around than
that old dirtbag!
So, don't get killed
out there, okay?
[ZORO]
Three Thousand Worlds!
But why?
Scars on the back are
a swordsman's shame.
Fine!
[PERONA] Yoo-hoo, Zoro,
are you still alive?
I haven't spotted a single
sign of him all day,
but he couldn't've set sail!
No. No, don't tell me
he got lost again!
[clanging]
[HUMANDRILL A yells]
[ZORO]
Oni...
[HUMANDRILL A yelps]
[ZORO]
...giri!
[HUMANDRILL A groans]
[ZORO panting]
[ZORO gasps]
You can't fix that
with your spit!
Who even taught you that
garbage? Your grandma?
[HUMANDRILLS yelling]
[pants]
Bastards, they may be stupid,
but, damn, they're strong.
At this rate, I'm never
gonna make it to the sea.
[yells, gasps]
[HUMANDRILLS gasping]
Hawk-Eye.
[MIHAWK] It's been quite a while
since you left the castle,
yet you've only
made it this far. Pity.
And the boat I offered you.
It seems it's not seaworthy now.
Shut up! It's fine.
I can just hold onto
a few planks and swim there.
I'm not one to give up
that easily, all right?
Your sentiment is admirable,
but you can't defeat them.
They're called Humandrills,
baboons that develop by
imitating human behavior.
[ZORO]
Humandrills?
Had they grown up among
peace-loving humans,
they would've turned
out differently,
but not on this island.
[MIHAWK]
Up until seven years ago,
this was the site
of a great war.
[MIHAWK]
When I first came here to live,
the entire island still
smelled of blood and smoke.
Everywhere, dead bodies
littered the ground.
As the battles raged on,
these baboons watched
the violence between
the humans unfold.
In time, they learned how to
use human weapons and armor,
becoming warriors of the forest.
Humans can defeat
ordinary animals
by using weapons and intellect.
But what happens when
animals don weapons, as well?
As you can see, they make
formidable opponents
for an arrogant young man.
You talkin' about me?
Well, who else?
Now, let's leave. It's late.
The Humandrills won't
set foot near the castle.
Yeah? You got no right
tellin' me what to do!
I've got to make it to the sea!
Of course.
Do as you like.
[panting]
I don't care if they're
"forest warriors" or monkeys.
I've already wasted enough
time stranded in this dump!
I'm cutting down
every single one of 'em!
Come on! That doof's gotta
be around here somewhere!
[HUMANDRILLS shouting]
[PERONA gasps] There! But
the baboons got to him first!
[HUMANDRILLS screaming]
Zoro! No!
[ZORO yells]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
in the land of Hungeria,
on Lazy Bones Island.
What is he doing? He's been
in that shack forever!
If Lord Satan's gonna help
us curse the Longarm Tribe,
then how come it's so quiet?
Lord Satan knows
what he's doing.
There's no doubt in my mind that
our savior is bringing forth
a powerful incantation
to deal the tyrannical
Longarm Tribe a fatal blow!
[BROOK laughs] Greetings,
everyone! Thank you for waiting!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER K]
Is the ritual finally over?
Atta boy, Satan!
[BROOK] My work is now complete.
I hope it will do the trick.
What is he holding?
[BROOK]
And here you go!
Oh. Thank you, Lord.
What is it?
Just a little ditty.
[SATANIC PRIEST]
Wait! No! Don't tell me!
Huh?
Our prayers have
finally been answered!
Satan has penned
a set of talismans
to help us kill
the Longarm Tribe!
Lord Satan has doomed the
Longarms to an agonizing death!
[BROOK]
Huh?
We're now as good as invincible.
Try as they might,
even those long-armed bullies
can't lay their hands
on us anymore!
I bet the mere sight of these
symbols will strike them dead!
[BROOK]
Not exactly.
How awesome!
That's Lord Satan for ya!
[SATANIC PRIEST] Come on,
men! Everybody grab a page
and find a place to nail it
up around town! Be quick!
--No. It's not like that,
--[SATAN WORSHIPPERS] Right!
you really shouldn't
separate them.
Oh, goodness.
Hello?
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS panting]
[SATAN WORSHIPPER L]
They're all posted now!
Yes! Excellent work, friends!
I finally feel safe now!
We all owe you our lives.
Thank you, Lord!
[BROOK]
Uh...
[SATAN WORSHIPPER G]
Sir! We have a problem!
[gasps]
The Longarm Tribe
is on their way here!
[SATANIC PRIEST]
Those simpletons
are like moths to a flame.
Now, we sit back and watch,
for as of today,
our enemies are history!
Hold on! Um, that thing?
With all the pages?
It's actually a musical score,
not a talisman at all.
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS]
Huh? What?!
[LONGARMS chuckling]
Welp, we're dead!
They'll take our food. What
few things of value we have,
they'll claim as their own.
People will be kidnapped.
Life will be miserable.
We have no choice.
[BROOK]
You always have a choice!
Lord Satan!
[BROOK laughs]
Please, lend me
your ears if you would.
[violin playing]
This song? What's it doing?
[SATAN WORSHIPPER M]
It's as if my body
is filling with
a brand-new energy!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS yelling]
[LONGARM BOSS] What the hell
is this? Some kind of spell?
[LONGARM TWINTAILS] Not only
do people with one joint
in their arm look funny,
but they think funny too!
What're they up to this time?
[LONGARMS laughing]
Huh? Well now, what's this?
From this day forth,
we no longer allow the Longarm
Tribe to terrorize our people!
Huh?
[SATAN WORSHIPPER N]
That's right!
We're finally fighting back!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER O]
Yeah! You're not taking
anything else from us!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER P] We're gonna
protect that which is ours
with our own hands!
Make your move.
We're not afraid of you!
[laughs] Now you've got it!
Hey, Boss, they're acting
kinda different than usual.
All right.
Guess we need to remind
these shortarms we own them.
Attack!
--[LONGARMS grunt]
--[SATANIC PREIST] Let's go!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS shouting]
You're truly
a blessing from hell!
Thank you, Lord Satan.
[laughs]
[SATANIC PRIEST]
It's unreal.
I never imagined that one day
we'd be able to fight
back like that,
much less beat them
and put them in a cage!
The music--something
about it changed us.
I've never felt
so uplifted before!
He's right! Courage and strength
welled up in our hearts.
We stood up and
defended ourselves
for the first time in our lives.
[BROOK grunts]
[SATANIC PRIEST]
Of course, we had no idea
how to use our weapons.
Ultimately, you did most of
the actual fighting by yourself.
But that's okay!
What matters is the people who
were abducted came back safely!
[BROOK laughs]
No, you're too modest!
I only helped a teeny bit.
Neither gods nor
devils will help those
who won't fight on their own.
In times like these,
it is important
to stand resolute against evil,
even if the odds
seem insurmountable.
You have the courage.
You proved that today.
Such a wise god!
You've inspired us.
We'll do our best
to make you proud!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS] Thank you
very much for your teachings.
Hail Lord Satan!
[BROOK] I hope that
repaid their kindness.
[BROOK]
Still, I can't believe the news.
Please stay strong, Luffy.
I hope you're all right.
I'll be there soon
to share in your grief.
If I had a heart,
it would be heavy!
Until I can return to your side,
all I can do is play a song,
and hope that it
reaches you, somehow.
Damn it! Guh!
I can't believe they got
the devil as their bodyguard!
What an embarrassment!
They should be the ones
in cages with those
freakish single-jointed
arms of theirs on display!
Actually, we could make a lot of
money doing that, couldn't we?
[SATANIC PRIEST chuckles]
Good idea.
[LONGARMS]
Huh?
We'll put their freakish
double-jointed arms on display.
They owe us and we can certainly
make a lot of money doing that!
[BROOK]
Wait, just a minute!
--[BROOK] That's wrong!
--[SATANIC PREIST] Huh?
And it's immoral! I'm certain
that you didn't appreciate it
when they were cruel to you.
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS]
Huh?
[BROOK]
Everyone, listen to me!
Let them go?
How could we, Lord Satan?
They'll just come back
and attack us again!
No, they will not.
I'll make sure of that
by binding them
to a devil's contract.
[LONGARMS gasping]
[BROOK]
Heed my words well.
If you break your oath with me
and commit a wrongful act
against the people
in this country again,
I will hunt each of you down.
And then I will eat your heart!
[LONGARMS scream]
Thank you, sir!
We promise you we'll behave!
We're going straight
back to our homes!
We'll never come back again,
oh, please don't hurt us!
[LONGARMS grunt]
You three are free to go,
but you must always remember--
Do not treat others poorly!
If somebody went
into your country
causing havoc and destruction,
then I'm sure you'd be unhappy.
It doesn't matter if you have
one or two joints in your arms.
Deep down, we're all the same!
So, treat each
other with respect!
[LONGARMS]
Yes, thank you!
--[SATANIC PRIEST sniffling]
--[BROOK laughing]
[LONGARMS]
Now, grab him!
[BROOK]
Ah! Woah!
Wha-- Huh-- What's
the big idea here?
[LONGARMS]
Away we go!
[LONGARM BOSS] Sorry, but
we don't believe in curses!
[LONGARM TWINTAILS]
Also, your speech was stupid
and you fell for the
oldest trick in the book!
[LONGARM A chuckles]
If we bring back
an actual walking,
talking skeleton...
[LONGARM TWINTAILS] ...we can
make a whole ton of money!
[BROOK]
Wait a minute! Let me go!
I have somewhere I need to be!
[SATANIC PRIEST]
Oh, no.
We have an emergency! Lord Satan
has just been kidnapped!
Everyone,
prepare to summon
another devil and fast!
Yes! We can still summon devils
with the magical
power of underwear!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS cheer]
[BROOK] Luffy, when you
feel sad, just sing a song!
Music is meant
to make you happy!
So sing as you wait for me!
I'll try to...
No, I will be there!
Till then, if you can hear me,
send help!
Well, then, that's it.
[gasps] I'm sorry.
What did you just say to him?
You heard.
You were right here
the whole time.
[HANCOCK]
Ugh. No!
I'm finding it difficult to
understand your intentions!
Surely, you know what's going
on in Luffy's mind right now.
Think of all he's been through!
Depending on your answer,
I may not be able
to forgive you!
[JIMBEI]
I agree.
How dare you suggest
such a thing,
and so soon after the war!
It's simply cruel.
I made a suggestion, that's all.
Only Luffy can decide.
So, what's your decision?
I don't know...
All my friends...
[LUFFY]
I never want them
to go through something
like that again!
[LUFFY]
If I do like you tell me to,
will it help me protect them?
No promises, but it's
certainly worth a shot.
That said, you do realize
you have a lot of work to do.
[LUFFY]
Okay.
I've made up my mind.
If you think I should,
I'll go back...
[LUFFY]
...to Marineford!
[NARRATOR]
After learning of Ace's death,
Sanji plots to
return to Sabaody.
However, his plans are
thwarted when Ivankov
makes his long-awaited return
to the Kamabakka Kingdom.
Burning with determination,
Sanji begins a fierce battle
with his pride on the line.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Disaster for Sanji!
The Queen's Return
to the Kingdom!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!