[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[LUFFY]
"Hawk‐Eye Mihawk!
The Great Swordsman
Zoro Falls At Sea!"
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU gasping]
[LUFFY gasps]
What'd you say?!
For real?! Nami sailed off
with the Going Merry?!
I need a straight answer!
Now, what happened?!
Well... It all happened
in only a few minutes.
[YOSAKU]
Hey, what's the matter, Big Sis?
Huh?
Say, I don't really
mean to pry or anything,
but whatcha looking at?
Oh well, it's nothing really.
Nice! Now that's a
big bounty pirate...
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
But Big Sis...
I think you're aiming a little
too high going after Arlong.
I'm not kidding, that
guy's really bad news.
He was playing it cool and
laying low for a while...
You know, staying out of sight.
[YOSAKU]
But these days,
that maniac is causing
all sorts of trouble.
It's kinda tough walking away
from a 20 million
berry bounty though.
[JOHNNY] That guy is so
powerful that there is the
slightest, tiniest chance that
we could lose and, well, die...
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Uh...
[YOSAKU]
Big Sis Nami?
Hey, would you guys
mind turning around
while I change into
something more comfortable?
Yeah, sure... I don't mind.
Changing? Like right now?
It's so hot...
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY gasp]
Yeah, you're hot‐‐ Uh, it's hot!
Have you ever met a
woman who's that daring?
Hey, what do you
say we turn around
and see if she's done yet?
[JOHNNY]
Good idea!
[BOTH gasp, scream]
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
I'm doing business, of course!
Use your heads, guys. I'm a
thief who only targets pirates
and my next score is this ship.
I never said anything about
being a member of this crew,
I was just traveling
with them, nothing more.
Even though I only spent a short
time with Luffy and the gang,
I sure had a lot of fun...
Make sure to tell
them that I said...
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Huh?
If it's truly meant to be,
I'll see them real soon.
Hey! Where are you going?!
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY scream]
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY gasp]
We're gonna be in
so much trouble!
Our only job was to
look after the ship,
and you're making
us fail miserably!
[PIRATES screaming]
So that's the story of how
Big Sis Nami took the ship!
Sorry!
[ZORO grunts]
Dammit! She just had to
make a bad situation worse!
The heartless thief!
Kaya gave us that ship!
[LUFFY]
Wait! I see a ship!
It's the Going Merry!
Tell me where your boat is!
We have it moored
to the restaurant!
Zoro! Usopp!
Don't just stand there!
Take their ship and go get Nami!
Calm down...
Let her keep the ship.
Trust me, that woman is way
more trouble than she's worth.
She's the only person I'll
accept as the ship's navigator!
Fine, I'll do it...
You're one high‐maintenance
captain, you know that?
All right, Usopp, let's go!
[USOPP]
Uh, okay!
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU] The ship's
ready for action, Big Bro Zoro!
Hey, what about you?
I should probably
stick around here till
I get this thing settled
with the restaurant.
Know what I mean?
Well, be careful...
The situation here could
get really bad really fast.
Yeah... Got that right.
[PIRATE A] We were
supposed to be safe now!
What's going on?!
[PIRATE B] The ship has
been broken to splinters!
Over there! It's that man!
[gasps] He came back!
[PIRATE OO gasping]
[PIRATE A]
Don Krieg!
The man who destroyed
our fleet is back!
What are we gonna do?!
[GROUP gasp]
That's... That's him...
‐‐[heartbeat thumps]
‐‐[ZORO gulps]
[thumping continues]
That man is...
[KRIEG]
That son of a bitch...
That psycho followed us back
here! He's gonna kill us all!
Everybody's gonna die!
Hey...
Who's that?
[ZORO] That's the man
I've been looking for...
Hawk‐Eye Mihawk.
So that's Mihawk.
Yeah... The greatest swordsman.
That's gotta be the guy
who destroyed Krieg's fleet!
He sunk 50 pirate ships out on
the Grand Line all by himself!
Looks like he came
back to finish the job,
but is that all he wants?
Wait a minute... He just
looks like any ordinary man.
He doesn't even appear to have
any kind of special
weapons with him.
He carries his
weapon on his back.
[PATTY]
That's impossible!
[CARNE] He couldn't have
destroyed a galleon like that
using nothing but a sword!
Hawk‐Eye Mihawk...
is a true master.
He is without a doubt the
greatest swordsman in the world.
[ZORO gulps] I never thought
that I would meet him so soon...
The time has come...
for me to fulfill my promise.
[PIRATE SS]
You... You monster!
Why are you doing this to us?!
What the hell have we
ever done to you?!
[MIHAWK]
Just killing time.
[PIRATE SS growls]
Bastard!
[PIRATES gasp]
What?! I missed?!
But I aimed straight for him!
He diverted them.
[PIRATE SS gasps]
He changed the
course of the bullets
using the tip of his sword.
[PIRATE SS]
That can't be!
Hold on! Who do you
think you are?!
He's got three swords!
It couldn't be...!
I've never see a sword handled
so gently, or with such grace.
There's no strength in
swordplay based on force.
[ZORO] Did you also use that
sword to slice up this ship?
[MIHAWK]
I did.
Then it's true...
You're the best.
I set sail for only one
reason‐‐ to meet you.
And what is your goal?
To beat you.
[MIHAWK chuckles]
How foolish...
You've got spare time,
so let's do this.
Whoa! No way!
It's him! Roronoa Zoro!
It's Zoro of the
Three‐Swords Style!
It is?!
Really? A pirate hunter?
He's a what?!
Hey Luffy, we'd
better hurry! Come on!
The Going Merry is about
to sail right out of sight!
Hey! Luffy!
A fight...
You're a weak, pitiful creature.
[MIHAWK] If you are in fact
a competent swordsman,
you should see the
disparity in our abilities,
even before we cross swords.
I must ask you why have
you challenged me?
Could it be your courage?
Or is it simply your ignorance?
My ambition drives me!
Also... I made a promise
I intend to keep.
The greatest
swordsman in the world
going up against Roronoa Zoro...
Two masters of swordplay...
What kind of a fight is
this gonna turn out to be?
There isn't a person alive
who can defeat Big Bro.
He's already the
best in the world!
[ZORO gasps]
Funny... What do you think
you're gonna do with that?
It'll be more than adequate.
After all, you wouldn't kill
a fly with a cannon, would you?
You may have quite the
reputation on the East Blue,
but that doesn't
mean much to me.
This sea is by far
the weakest of the four.
Unfortunately, I don't carry any
blades smaller than this one.
I have had just about
enough of your attitude.
[ZORO]
Now, you die!
You have no idea how
big the world really is.
[ZORO]
Oni Giri!
[metal clangs]
[ZORO gasps]
What the‐‐?!
Zoro!
What?! Big Bro's
Oni Giri was stopped?!
But that's crazy! That attack
never fails to stop an enemy!
What's going on here?!
[ZORO] I can't move my swords!
What has he done?!
No one's been able to defend
against that technique...
He stopped it with
a pocketknife!
No... Th‐This
can't be happening!
He can't be this much
better than me!
There's no way our skills
are this far apart!
[ZORO yells] I'm not that far
behind the world's strongest!
[ZORO grunting]
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY whimpering]
[ZORO groans]
[ZORO grunts]
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY gasp]
You're just toying with him,
right?! Fight for real, Big Bro!
Big Bro!
You can't be that
much better than me!
[ZORO yells]
[ZORO grunting]
Such ferocious swordplay.
[ZORO yells]
[PIRATE SS]
How can he defend against
Zoro's Three‐Sword Style
with such a small knife?!
[PIRATE VV] He's more
of monster with a blade
than even the great Zoro!
[ZORO] I did not devote my
entire life to swordsmanship...
to be dispatched
by a toy like this!
‐‐[KUINA] Zoro...
‐‐[ZORO gasps]
[ZORO groans]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO screams]
[KUINA grunts]
You're lucky, Zoro...
being born as a man.
All I ever wanted was to be
the world's greatest swordsman.
If only... If I'd
just been born a man!
[ZORO growls]
[ZORO]
Don't fly off at the mouth,
whining like that
after you beat me!
Because it's not fair!
You're my goal! Do you know
how this makes me feel?!
[KUINA gasps]
[KUINA]
Zoro...
Now promise me...
Promise me that someday,
one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman.
We'll see who gets there.
[BOTH]
It's a promise.
[ZORO]
To become the world's strongest!
[ZORO growling]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO] I ask that you
let me have that sword.
I'm gonna get stronger
than she ever was!
Strong enough that my name
reaches up to the heavens!
I am going to be the
world's greatest swordsman!
I promised her... I promised...
[ZORO grunting, panting]
[ZORO] I will defeat
this man... for her!
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO pants]
[ZORO grunts]
What is it then?
What weight do you carry
upon your shoulders?
Speak up, weakling!
How dare you call
him "weakling"!
You'll pay for that!
We'll teach you a lesson!
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY yell]
[LUFFY]
No!
Yosaku! Johnny! Get back here!
‐‐Just stay put!
‐‐[YOSAKU, JOHNNY growling]
Luffy...
[ZORO grunts]
No... I won't lose...
I refuse to be defeated!
[heartbeat thumps]
Tiger...
[LUFFY]
World's greatest swordsman...
Sounds pretty good!
The King of the Pirates
wouldn't have any less
than the best on his crew.
[ZORO]
...Trap!
You are defeated, yet
you won't step back...
Why not?
[ZORO]
I don't know...
But... I will not run...
Even if I retreat
a single step...
I would be shattering
the promises I've made.
I can't run...
I would lose my honor.
You see, without that,
there would be nothing
left for me here.
That's what defeat is.
[ZORO chuckles]
Then I won't accept defeat.
Then you'll die.
I'd rather die than give up!
[MIHAWK]
A strong heart indeed!
He chooses death before defeat!
[ZORO grunts]
Sir... State your name!
I am... Roronoa Zoro!
[MIHAWK]
I'll remember it!
No one as strong as you has
come around in quite some time.
So as a swordsman's courtesy,
I'll use the world's strongest
black sword to finish you.
Thank you... I appreciate it.
[PIRATE A]
Look! He took it out!
[PIRATE B] That's the sword
that sliced up the ship!
[ZORO]
So this is it...
Will it be the
world's strongest...
...or death?
[LUFFY growls]
Enough, Big Bro!
Stop it! Please!
[ZORO] Three‐Sword
Style Secret Technique!
[MIHAWK]
Fall!
[ZORO]
Three Thousand Worlds!
I've lost...
[ZORO] Never in my life
did I imagine I'd lose.
[ZORO] So this is the power
of the greatest in the world.
But why...?
Scars on the back are
a swordsman's shame.
Fine.
Zoro!
[MIHAWK] You shouldn't rush
these things, young man.
[USOPP]
Zoro!
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY]
Big Bro!
No!
[SANJI]
Why?!
[ZORO]
I devoted my entire life to
becoming the world's
greatest swordsman...
It was my choice,
so I'm the only one who
gets to call me stupid.
[SANJI]
He's insane!
His opponent was way
out of his league!
How this fight would end
was clear from the start!
Why choose death?!
Don't be stupid!
Give up your ambition and live!
So this is the power of the
Grand Line; it's terrifying!
The Pirate Hunter Zoro was as
helpless as a newborn baby!
[LUFFY]
Damn you...
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY]
Big bro!
[LUFFY yells]
He must be some kind of freak!
[SANJI gasps]
So that loudmouthed little twerp
has the power of a Devil Fruit.
[LUFFY]
Bastard!
[MIHAWK] Are you that
young warrior's comrade?
I'm impressed with you
for not interfering.
[LUFFY grunts]
[MIHAWK] There's nothing
to be upset about.
Your friend will live.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[YOSAKU]
Big Bro! Say something, please!
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
[ZORO groans]
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
C'mon let's hurry up and
get him out of the water.
[USOPP]
I've got some medicine! Here!
It's still far too
early for you to die.
My name is Hawk‐Eye Mihawk!
You're strong but there
is much for you to learn.
No matter how many years it
takes, I will hold this title as
the greatest in the world,
and wait for you!
Until that day, you
must hone your skills!
Then... seek me out!
Roronoa Zoro!
[YOSAKU]
Please say something!
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY]
Anything!
Not just anyone can earn
the regard of Hawk‐Eye Mihawk.
[MIHAWK]
You...
What is your goal?
To be the King!
Your ambitions are even
loftier than your friend's.
That's quite a task.
Yeah, well, you just let
me worry about that.
Bleh!
[USOPP]
He's alive!
He was just unconscious!
Big Bro!
If you're alive,
then say something!
[gasps] Zoro!
[YOSAKU]
Big Bro!
[ZORO]
Luffy...
Can you hear me...?
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
I'm sorry for disappointing you.
I know that you need
nothing less than
the greatest swordsman
in the world...
I've let you down...
Please forgive me.
Okay, okay! You can
stop saying things now!
Big Bro!
[ZORO]
I solemnly swear...
From this moment forward...
That I will never lose again!
[ZORO chokes]
Until the day comes...
...when I defeat him
and take his title...
I will never...
...never be defeated!
Is that okay...
...King of the Pirates?!
[LUFFY laughs]
Yup!
You're a good team.
I hope to see you
again... someday.
[KRIEG]
Hey! Hawk‐Eye!
I was under the impression that
you had come here
to take my life.
Weren't you here to kill Don
Krieg, ruler of the East Blue?
The thought had
crossed my mind...
But I've had enough
fun for today,
so I'm going home
to get some rest.
[bones cracking]
I don't care if
you've had enough.
I haven't even gotten started.
Um, but, sir...
Maybe it's not a good idea
to try to keep him here!
[KRIEG chuckles]
Now it's time to die!
[MIHAWK]
He just won't learn, will he?
[PIRATES screaming]
Aw, damn... He escaped.
[LUFFY grunts]
[COOKS scream]
[LUFFY]
Usopp!
Luffy!
Go on ahead!
I'll leave Nami to you!
[USOPP]
Roger that!
Don't you worry about a thing!
Zoro and I are gonna
get her right back!
And make sure you get that
cook to join our crew!
And then...
...on the Going Merry,
the five of us'll set sail...
...to the Grand Line!
[LUFFY laughs]
Yeah! Let's do it!
[KRIEG]
All right, men!
We ran into a little
distraction from our plan,
but the real fight starts now!
We're gonna take that ship!
[PIRATES]
Yes, sir!
[LUFFY]
Hey, Pops,
can I stop doing these chores if
I get those pirates outta here?
[ZEFF]
Suit yourself.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[USOPP] Krieg and his
pirates are on their way!
[LUFFY] Honestly, what an
ungrateful bunch they are...
They were given all
kinds of delicious food!
[ZORO] Come to think of it,
there's another ungrateful one
who took the
treasure and ran off!
[USOPP] Let me take care
of that, just get some rest.
[LUFFY laughs]
Hey, that guy looks funny!
[USOPP]
He sure has a lotta shields...
And fire! Ow, ow, ow...
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"The Deadly Foot
Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. The Invincible Pearl!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!