[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of the his crew,
Luffy struggled in vain to
rescue his brother Ace
from execution at the
hands of the Navy.
Marineford was then thrown
into chaos by Blackbeard,
who stole Whitebeard's
Devil Fruit power.
While attempting
to flee the scene,
Luffy and Jimbei were
critically injured by Akainu,
who continues after them on
a path of merciless destruction.
A splendid speech.
Touched my heart.
And though they were few,
those precious
moments of courage
you showed will
change this world.
Though only the
future will tell if
it's for the better
or for the worse.
[SHANKS] It's been
a long time, old friend.
Let's end this war.
Shanks, huh?
The bastard who turned my
grandson into a damned pirate.
[cackles]
Lookee here.
[gasps]
[MARINE G] The whole
Red Hair Crew showed up!
[MEDIC A]
Prepare for surgery!
This is serious, they're
losing a lot of blood!
Set up for a transfusion!
[BEPO]
Captain! Hurry up!
I know this is cool to watch and
all, but we're going underwater!
But how?
His crew had a run in with one
of the other Emperors
just yesterday.
I thought he and Kaido would
still be duking it out for sure!
So... what's he doing all
the way over here?
Wha...? Shanks? No way!
--Huh?
--[BUGGY] I got enough goin' on,
I don't need you here!
[SHANKS]
Buggy, catch!
Eh? Your hat?
[SHANKS]
Give it back to Luffy for me.
Huh? Why don't you do it?
Listen!
I've drawn enough
attention to myself today.
It's time to get out!
No more favors,
especially not for you!
That's a real shame.
I was hoping you'd stick around.
I've been holding onto this
treasure map for a while,
hoping I'd bump into you.
[gasps] "Treasure map"?
And I guarantee
it'll suit your fancy.
Oh, really?
I'm supposed to believe
we're such good pals
that you'll give me
a treasure map over a dumb hat?
[SHANKS] Oh, well. I can always
give it to someone else.
[BUGGY grunts]
Don't be so hasty!
I'll do it for old time's sake!
[ROUX]
You sure about this?
Huh?
[ROUX] You haven't seen
Luffy in ten whole years.
You gonna let him leave
without saying hi?
It's been that long, huh?
[PATRONS laughing]
[PIRATE Q]
Talk about a loser!
[SHANKS laughing]
Why are you all laughing?
What's so funny?
You should have
fought back, Shanks!
It doesn't matter
how strong they look
or how many of them there are,
if you just laugh it off,
you're not a man or a pirate!
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY crying]
You can't cry, you're a man now.
But, Shanks, your arm...
Your arm!
Luffy, It's just an arm.
I've got another one.
I'm just glad you're all right.
[LUFFY crying]
I wonder. What would he say?
[BEPO] Captain! We have
to close the door!
If we wait, they'll open fire,
but if we don't, you'll drown!
Please stop making things
difficult on us and get inside!
Yeah, okay...
[BUGGY yelling]
Actually, wait.
No! We're gonna die!
[BUGGY grunting]
Here, Straw Hat forgot this!
Now, take it and go!
What is he throwing at us?
[BEPO]
Huh?
[LAW]
I see.
Okay, okay, ya got the hat or
whatever, now c'mon, hurry up!
[LAW]
Right.
[BEPO panting]
It's still too soon, I'm afraid.
[SHANKS]
I'll leave this hat to you.
I want you to bring this
hat back to me someday,
in good condition,
and only once you've
become a great pirate.
That's our promise, Luffy.
I'll keep my word...
...and that means
I can't see you yet,
right, Luffy?
All right, shall we begin?
This one's been shot
through the stomach.
Amazing he's still alive.
Straw Hat's injuries
are fairly severe as well,
but I think his emotional
trauma is the real issue.
Do they need anesthesia?
Not in this state, no.
They're both unconscious
and Straw Hat is one
step shy of comatose.
In other words, no matter
how grisly this gets,
we won't hear
a peep out of them.
It's gonna be a fun
operation, yeah?
Damn it. Stop them!
Do whatever it takes!
Ice Age!
Ah! They're after the submarine!
The whole sea's freezing over!
Looking good.
His pulse is steady.
[MEDICS, BEPO yelling, gasping]
What was that?
[JEAN BART]
I dunno what happened,
but the water around
us is turning to ice!
[yells] It's gotta be Aokiji!
If we don't do something soon,
they're gonna grab us and
we'll be as good as dead!
Then do something!
[BEPO gasps]
We're diving deeper! Full speed!
[BEPO screaming]
[yells]
I think we're good.
[BEPO sighs]
Please, no more stress.
Ahh!
Now, Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
[gasps] What is it now?
Going deeper. Hold on tight!
[MEDICS gasping]
We got lucky once, but we're
dead for sure this time!
[LAW]
We'll be fine!
Keep moving!
No!
Jeez! Can't they just
give it up already?
Wait, he didn't
hit them, did he?
They can't die down there!
No way!
Aww, jeez.
If they're still
alive after that...
...I'm afraid Lady Luck
just isn't on our side.
But if we can't sink them today,
we'll sink them tomorrow.
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINE H]
Hey, that's one of our ships.
Why's it taking off on its own?
Hurry up, dammit!
Follow that submarine!
Okay, but I mean,
it's already underwater.
Also, I'm pretty sure
everyone on it is dead
after those attacks
from the admirals. Sorry.
[HANCOCK] They're alive.
I'm certain of it.
[HANCOCK]
Hear my words!
With my authority as
a Warlord of the Sea,
I shall pursue and capture Straw
Hat Luffy, no matter the cost!
[MARINES]
Yes, ma'am!
[MARINE I]
That's great, but, like, how?
Just shut up and go!
[MARINES gasp] It's so hot
when she yells at us!
[BUGGY] You scum-sucking,
red-haired sack of excrement!
You're telling me the
treasure map thing was a lie?
[BUGGY yells]
Just having some
fun, old friend.
It's been a while, huh?
Screw you!
"Oh, been a while, huh?" Blah!
What, did you think
that I'd forgive you
for what you did
out of kindness?
That I'd forget?
Forget about what?
Oh, don't give me that!
If you hadn't snuck up
on me back then,
I never would've
eaten that Devil Fruit,
and more importantly, I never
would've lost that treasure map.
In other words,
I'd be filthy rich instead
of running from the Navy!
Oh, is that so?
[BUGGY yells]
Playing it cool.
I should've known.
All these years and
you're still a prodigy
when it comes to pissing me off!
You've hardly been
here five minutes
and you've already
lied and cheated me!
You said you were
gonna stop the war?
Well, you're about to start
a new one, with me, right now!
Once a chump, always a chump!
You see that?
Sure did!
Even the Emperors can't
escape his trash talk!
He's such a pro!
[PRISONERS] Captain Buggy!
Could you be more perfect?
We'll follow you to
the ends of the world!
I really did miss you, though.
Oh, I'm sure you did!
Huh?
[BUGGY] But wait, these
guys are certified badasses.
If I can catch a ride
with my old crewmate,
I can get off this
island scot free.
[MARCO]
What now?
Marco,
there's nothing to gain
from fighting anymore.
Just walk away, nice and easy.
[grunts]
Hawk-Eye! Get back here!
I agreed to fight Whitebeard
and his allies, true,
but Red Hair is another
matter entirely.
[MARINES gasp]
[MIHAWK]
You should quit, as well.
[PIRATES gasping]
Your thirst for battle
is your undoing.
Every blow you land
upon your enemies,
you land upon your own men.
However, if anyone here
still hungers for battle...
...fine! Then come!
We shall be more than
happy to face you.
[MARINES gasping]
Well, Teach, you wanna try?
Sorry, "Blackbeard."
[laughs] Pretty as a picture,
aren't you, Red Hair?
Those scars are a nice touch.
[cackling]
[BLACKBEARD]
Y'know what? Fine.
[BLACKBEARD] I got what
I came for here, after all,
and I'm not looking for
a fight with you guys.
Well, not yet at least.
C'mon fellas, let's pack it up.
[BLACKBEARD cackling]
[SHANKS]
Accept your losses...
Honor the fallen...
Withdraw from battle
with your dignity intact.
I think it's finally over now.
[SHANKS]
As for Whitebeard and Ace,
I'm sure you won't
object to their friends
taking care of the burial.
[SHANKS] The battle was already
broadcast to the entire world.
I won't allow you to make
a further spectacle
of their deaths
by parading their corpses
around like trophies.
And why shouldn't we?
If they wanted a proper
burial so badly,
then perhaps they shouldn't
have defied the Navy!
We have every right
to string the bastards up!
And why should we listen
to a pirate anyway?
[MARINE J]
It's our victory! We earned it!
That's enough!
[BOTH gasp]
But, sir!
I'll allow it, Shanks,
just this once.
But why?
Let me take responsibility.
[DOBERMAN gasps]
Thank you.
Now go treat the injured,
before it's too late!
[MARINES gasping]
[SENGOKU]
This war is over!
The Navy has won!
[MARINES cheering]
If you can help
the medics, hop to it!
Get those with serious
injuries out of here first!
We've seen enough
suffering for today
and I won't lose any more men!
[NARRATOR] And thus,
what would later be known
as "The War of the Best,"
ended in Marineford.
The most fearsome battle since
the beginning of the
Great Pirate Era,
brought victories
and defeats alike,
leaving the world
uncertain of its future.
[NARRATOR]
The War of the Best
has thrown the entire
world into chaos.
Emboldened by the final
words of Whitebeard,
the pirates once
again envision a wave
they can ride into a new era.
However, in the vacuum
left after his demise,
the seas grow rougher
than ever before.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Mighty Leaders Face Each Other
Down! Heralding the 'New Era'!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!