[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention of
the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind
of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy is rushing to Navy
headquarters to rescue
his brother, Ace,
from public execution.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the Whitebeard Pirates
have successfully stormed
Marineford to save Ace,
and triggered an all-out
war with the Navy.
[ACE]
Oars!
[OARS JR.] Don't worry, Ace.
I can make it for sure!
[ACE whimpers]
Doppelman!
[MARINES gasping]
[MORIA]
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
[LUFFY]
"Justice for the Winners!
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
[MORIA cackles]
See?
Now that's how ya do it!
That is some good murder!
[ALL]
No! Captain Oars!
Damn you!
You Warlord scumbag!
Captain!
Oars! No!
[panting]
I'm here.
[OARS JR.]
[ACE whimpers]
Please, stop!
[groaning]
[OARS JR. groans]
[ACE whimpers]
Ace. I'm sorry.
[OARS JR. panting]
I'm here, Ace.
My... friend.
[ACE gasping]
[MARINES gasping]
[COBY gasps]
[ACE whimpering]
[ACE]
Oars!
[MORIA cackles] I'll have
to fix up that foot of his,
but that's a small price to pay
for another giant zombie!
[WHITEBEARD]
Oh, Oars.
[LONZ] Shouldn't drop
your guard, Whitebeard!
[LONZ grunts]
[WHITEBEARD growls]
[LONZ gasps]
[WHITEBEARD growls, yells]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[LONZ groans]
[MARINE AA]
Vice Admiral Lonz!
[MARINE BB]
Okay, uh.
Everybody just leave
Whitebeard alone, I guess.
[WHITEBEARD]
My son.
Now.
Climb up Oars' body and charge!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yell]
[ALL yelling]
[ALL grunting]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yell]
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
This is beautiful.
[ATMOS]
Doflamingo!
You're gonna pay for
what you did to Oars
and I'm gonna collect the debt!
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
What the hell're
you laughing at?
How are you not laughing?
We're standing on the
fulcrum of history itself!
The future and past
will be written here!
[ATMOS]
Quit your yammerin' and die!
Take 'im down, boss!
Stop dancing around
and fight for real!
[DOFLAMINGO]
Heh, heh.
[ATMOS yells]
[ATMOS]
Uh!
[DOFLAMINGO]
Heh, heh.
[YUKIMURA groans]
[COBY gasps]
[YUKIMURA groaning]
[COBY]
Wha...? Rear Admiral Yukimura?
[MARINE E, MCGUY grunting]
[MARINE F groans]
[MARINE G groans]
[ACE whimpers]
[COBY panting]
[COBY]
I can't do this!
I'm scared and I'm weak
and I'm useless!
Even our leaders are
falling one after another!
There's no way a loser like me
is gonna survive out there!
[HELMEPPO]
Wait, Coby!
I'm running away, too!
[AKAINU]
Get back to the battlefield!
[BOTH gasping]
[SCARED MARINE]
Just let me go!
Please, sir!
[COBY, HELMEPPO whimper]
[COBY] What's Admiral
Akainu doing here?
[SCARED MARINE]
I can't die like this.
I'm terrified to leave
my family on their own!
Please, I'm begging you,
Admiral! Please!
[AKAINU]
As soldiers of the Navy,
we carry the weight of
the justice of the world
on our backs, and we'll
gladly die to defend it.
Any man who turns tail
and runs doesn't deserve
to call himself a marine.
Let alone a man,
for that matter.
The most he could
be called is...
a waste of life.
[whimpering]
If you truly care about
your family as you say,
you'll only shame
them by living.
[whimpers]
[SCARED MARINE screams]
[HELMEPPO, COBY yelp]
[COBY]
N-no!
He killed one of
his own soldiers?
[MARINE H]
Admiral Sakazuki!
We're ready to proceed
with the operation.
Excellent.
It's finally time.
[HELMEPPO, COBY gasping]
[COBY]
"The operation"?
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE AA]
Ace!
[BABY cries]
Go!
Everyone get through
the space Oars made!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yell]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE BB]
The bay is ours!
Right!
Let's destroy the bay head!
Go open up another entrance!
Aim straight ahead and fire!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE G]
Dammit! Hardly a scratch!
[WHITEY BAY]
Leave it to me.
[MARINES]
Whoa!
[RANDOM MARINE C]
An ice cutter?
[MARINE DD] It's the
"Ice Witch," Whitey Bay!
I've cut plenty of glaciers
tougher than that.
All right! Let's move!
The path is open!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE G]
Right behind ya!
All clear! It's time
to move into the bay!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES cheer]
[ATMOS groans]
[DOFLAMINGO]
Heh.
Is something the matter,
Water Buffalo Atmos?
You seem like you've
gone a little stiff.
What-what'd you do?
My body. I can't control it!
Commander Atmos!
[ATMOS] Stay back!
Don't get anywhere near me!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE H]
What's wrong, Commander?
[ATMOS]
Now!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE B]
Let us fight, boss!
Stay away!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE B groans]
I don't understand, Commander.
Why?
He's got control of my body.
Doflamingo, you bastard!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES groaning]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE CC]
Stop it!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE DD]
Please, no!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES groan]
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
"Pirates are evil,
the Navy is just."
But that's only true because
history tells us so.
Children who've
never known peace
have different values than
children who've never known war.
[MARINES, WHITEBEARD
PIRATES grunting]
[DOFLAMINGO]
The one who wins will rewrite
the definition of
right and wrong.
They'll decide the future and
how the past is written.
Ah. Will justice prevail?
Why, there's no other way!
[ALL yelling]
[DOFLAMINGO] The winner will
define the meaning of justice!
[MARINE I] They've broken
through the bay head
at two different points, sir!
There's nothing left to
prevent Whitebeard's allies
from entirely flooding the area!
I'm afraid we've got no way
to hold them back, sir!
What should we do now?
[SENGOKU]
Don't worry about it.
[MARINE I]
Uh?!
We're ready. Put the
plan into action.
It's about time.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE J]
Outta the way!
Either stand down or die!
Move it, you old bag!
[TSURU]
Hm?
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES gasp]
I got washed!
And put out to dry!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE]
I feel so fresh and clean!
Sorry boys, maybe try again
in a couple hundred years.
Put a call out to all
ships and soldiers.
[TRANSPONDER SNAILS chirp]
[WHITEBEARD]
Mm...
[TRANSPONDER SNAILS chirp]
Of course. He's got
a plan up his sleeve.
You've always been resourceful,
"Buddha" Sengoku.
[BABY cries]
So his name is Gol D. Ace.
[footsteps]
[ACE gasps]
[ACE]
Old man!
What are you doing up here?
Not having second
thoughts, are you?
[GARP]
No, they chose to be pirates.
They brought this
upon themselves.
In that case--
[GARP]
Shut up!
I don't want to talk.
I just wanna sit here.
[GARP]
Little idiot!
[LUFFY]
Whoa, Ace!
What's wrong with you?!
You say you wanna
go out to sea?
Well now you've got my answer!
[ACE grunts]
Who're you to say I can't?
It's not like you're my father.
I don't have to listen to a
thing you tell me, old man.
I'm not "Old Man,"
I'm "Grandpa!"
Old man.
[GARP growls]
Do you want me to show you
how much I love you
with another punch?
[LUFFY laughs]
Grandpa!
[GARP]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Y'know,
I'm gonna get a lot stronger!
And when I do, I'm gonna go
out to sea just like Ace!
[LUFFY]
Ow!
Moron!
I don't want either of
you becoming pirates!
[ACE] Hey, don't hit Luffy!
Mean old fart!
[GARP]
Ah! What?!
Ace! You come here!
[ACE laughs]
[GARP]
Listen.
You never know when a
battle might spring up,
so you gotta eat when you
can to stay prepared!
And eat a lot!
Every Navy soldier should
live by that rule.
So both of you better
keep it in mind.
Yeah, well, you don't get to
decide that for us, old man!
Yes, I do!
[ACE]
I'm gonna be a pirate!
[GARP]
You're gonna join the Navy!
--Pirate!
--Navy!
--Pirate! Pirate!
--Navy! Navy!
Pirate!
[LUFFY]
Yum!
[ACE, GARP gasp]
No!
He ate it all!
[LUFFY]
I'm stuffed!
[GARP, ACE]
Huh?!
[LUFFY] I'm gonna be
the best pirate ever.
[ACE] Heh. Even if Luffy
does join the Navy,
he won't take orders,
and he'll eat all the food
supplies on whatever
ship they put him on.
Probably be less
of a nuisance to us
if he became a pirate, huh?
[laughs]
[GARP] I have no sympathy
in me for criminals...
[GARP]
but family's a different story.
[GARP cries]
Now what?
What am I supposed to do?
Ace, you fool!
Why couldn't you have
just listened to me
and done what I asked?
Ace.
Trust me on this.
You two really should
join the Navy. Okay?
[GARP] I know you'll make
a strong Navy soldier.
Old man.
If you're feeling any doubt
over what must be done,
I'm afraid I just can't
take pity on you, Garp.
[GARP] If I had doubts, I
would've done something already.
[COBY] Did you hear what
I just heard, Helmeppo?
What their strategy is?
Yeah.
They're gonna bypass the
schedule and immediately
execute "Fire Fist" Ace.
But if they do that--
[HELMEPPO]
Huh? What the...?
[SENGOKU]
Hm?
What is that?
Something's falling
from the sky.
[MARINES murmur]
It's gotta be another surprise
ambush from Whitebeard!
[PIRATES yelling]
[BUGGY] You just have
to overdo it every time.
[CROCODILE] This is because
of his death wink!
[IVANKOV]
Oh, so it's all my fault?
[LUFFY] Who cares whose fault
it is, we're gonna die!
It's all frozen down there!
[BUGGY, MR.3 scream]
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
[LUFFY yells]
Oh! Yeah, I'm rubber,
I'll be fine!
Hey! What about us,
you selfish jerk?!
Do something already!
This is not how I
pictured myself dying!
Somebody help me! Please!
I still care about
whose fault this is,
and it's all yours, Straw Hat!
Damn you!
[LUFFY]
I'm here, Ace!
[ALL yelling]
[NARRATOR] Luffy and
company fall from the sky
and land in the middle
of the battlefield.
With his brother in sight,
Luffy rushes forward
as fast as his legs
will carry him.
Yet even with his goal in sight,
the adversaries before him
may prove to be an
insurmountable wall.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Straw Hat Team Arrives! Tension
Grows at the Battlefield"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!