[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[BROGGY groans]
[gasps] Broggy!
[groaning]
Now...!
Let's get these
candles going faster!
It's time to turn these
people into beautiful,
artistic wax statues!
[NUMBER THREEE laughs]
This isn't good!
My hands won't move.
Can't we do something?
I don't wanna die like this!
[VIVI] My body's
beginning to turn stiff...
[ZORO]
Hey, giant.
[BROGGY]
Hm?
I say we take 'em down together.
What do you think?
[gasps]
All right, I'm in.
Let's cut them to pieces.
Don't be foolish!
What can you hope to accomplish?
[ALL yelling]
[LUFFY]
Hey! I'm gonna kick your asses!
Huh?
These guys messed up
the best duel ever!
And now they're
gonna answer to me!
We're here, Broggy.
Don't worry‐‐we'll pick up
where you left off.
Thanks, Usopp.
So, Luffy, what do ya think?
Could you go ahead and take
care of this pillar for us?
I think I've done enough.
No problem.
Hah! I wouldn't be so sure!
[NAMI] Hurry, will ya?
We're dying here!
[LUFFY]
"A Hex on Luffy! Colors Trap!"
Zoro... Why are you
standing like that?
If I'm gonna be a statue,
I prefer this pose.
This is no time
to be playing around!
Who said anything about playin'?
Do you think you could at least
do something about
all this blood?
I'm getting nauseous
just looking at it.
[ZORO]
So quit lookin' at it, then.
[NAMI]
It's kind of hard to ignore.
Do you still think
it was a bright idea
to cut your own legs off so
that we could escape from here?
[ZORO]
That wasn't the point.
I was going to cut them off
so that we could fight.
Oh, was that the plan?
'Cause that's an
even worse idea!
Whatever...
Seriously, sometimes
I think you were born
without any common
sense at all.
[VIVI] We're stuck here about
to be turned into wax statues,
and the two of
them are bickering!
They really don't seem
to understand the danger
of the situation at all.
Hey, sword guy...
Is that all the fight
you got left in ya?
Yeah, I think I'm gonna
have to let someone else
take over from here.
[BROGGY]
Heh! All right.
They don't seem terribly worried
about what's going to happen
to them, Mr. 3.
[MR. 3] And you don't
seem terribly worried
about making sure it happens,
Miss Golden Week.
[MR. 3]
Solidify already...
If you wanna die
in a cool pose, Nami,
you'd better hurry up.
I got other things
to worry about.
Mister Bushido, could you
please take this
a little more seriously?
Hey your pose could use
a little work, too.
Shut up about
the posing already!
They're acting so
careless like this
for no other reason
than to mock us!
This is very annoying!
They've been acting
this way ever since
he showed up...
Of course!
All right!
[MR. 3]
Though he doesn't seem to be
a very reliable man...
If you ask me.
[MR. 5]
Mr. 5.
[MR. 3]
Hm?
We'll be happy to take care
of the Straw Hat pest.
[MR. 3]
Hmph. Take care of him?
Please. Don't be ridiculous.
I sent you to take care
of him once already,
and look! He's standing in
front of us alive and well,
interfering with my
artistic process.
I think it's clear that
you can't handle him.
He's obviously too much
for you, wouldn't you agree?
[growls]
You two can deal
with the others.
If you think you're
up to it, that is.
I'll take care of him.
I think a Straw Hat Luffy
statue would make
an excellent addition
to my collection.
[MR. 3 laughs]
I think I've had way
more than enough of you.
And if you cretins know
what's good for ya,
you'll give up now.
[squaks]
Is that right?
Let's go!
[squaks]
'Kay, we're safely
in position now.
We got your back
from here, Luffy!
[squaks]
[LUFFY]
Hm? Did you say something?
[MR. 3] Now I've
got you! Candle... Lock!
[yelping]
[gasps]
What's he doing?
[squaks]
[LUFFY grunts]
[VIVI]
Luffy!
[ZORO]
Damn! He got caught already?
[NAMI]
Moron!
What is this thing?
Whatever it is,
it's nice and heavy.
[MR. 3]
Almost too simple...
All right, just once more.
[LUFFY]
Hm...
Yeah! This should be perfect!
Candle... Lock!
[yelps]
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
Hey, giant guy!
Excuse me!
Uh... What the...?
What is this weirdo doing now?
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
Mallet!
[yelps]
[VIVI, NAMI]
All right!
Woo‐hoo!
[VIVI, NAMI, ZORO scream]
[NAMI, VIVI screaming]
[VIVI, ZORO, NAMI whimpering]
Hey, the thing on my legs
broke at the same time.
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Um, but wait...
Why are they still there?
[panting]
We're okay now.
[sighs]
We didn't die.
We're still alive
but that really
didn't help at all.
That was a close one!
But why didn't
you guys run away?
[VIVI, NAMI]
Because we're stuck here!
Isn't that obvious?!
Oh, really?
So that's what's going on?
The only thing
you guys kept saying
was that I needed to
break the pillar...
So that's what I did.
Mister Bushido!
Do you really think it's
a good idea to put our lives
in that guy's hands?
Well, we don't exactly have
much of a choice, do we?
I don't know about you,
but I'm having a little bit
of trouble moving right now...
And you don't seem to be
bothered by it, somehow!
I... can't move...
What's happening?
My body... I don't know...
It... It won't move...
I can't move at all...
[MR. 3 cackles]
[MR. 3]
You fools!
All you did was move
the candles closer!
And by doing so, you only sped
up the solidifying process.
You'll become wax figures
even sooner, now!
Well done!
Ugh! That guy!
I wanna punch him,
right in his smug little face!
[squaks]
[LUFFY] Wait! You guys are
gonna turn into wax figures?
[NAMI] That's what we've
been trying to tell you!
[VIVI] Please just hurry up
and destroy this thing, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Right, yeah, I'm on it!
[MR. 3]
I don't think so, Straw Hat!
Now, get out of my way!
Wax‐Wax... Harpoon!
Exploding Star!
[gasps]
[MR. 5 gulps]
[LUFFY yelps]
That's not very flavorful.
Your gunpowder must
not be too good.
There's no way! He ate it!
[squaks]
[ZORO] This isn't really
looking good for us, ladies...
This damn thing is speeding up.
Good thing I've
got my pose ready.
Moron!
Come on, Luffy!
You have to hurry!
Right! So the pumpkin
thing has to go.
I'm on it now! Gum‐Gum...
[MR. 3]
It's no use! Candle... Wall!
Bazooka!
Hey! Outta my way!
I was just thinking
the same thing.
I would greatly appreciate it
if you would quit interfering
with my creative
activities. Candle Lock!
I got a mallet...
[MR. 3]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
No you don't! Candle Wall!
[LUFFY]
Mallet!
[MR. 3 whimpers]
[MR. 3 screams]
M‐Mr. 3?!
No way!
[NAMI] Luffy! Hurry up
and break this thing
before we die up here!
Um, no...
Quit joking around and hurry.
[LUFFY]
Nuh‐uh.
[ZORO gasps]
Quit being an idiot!
Now's not really a good time!
[VIVI]
Luffy! Please just do it!
Not now... I...
...just don't feel
like saving you.
[pants]
Luffy, what's wrong?
My Colors Trap.
[panting]
[ZORO]
Hey, Luffy!
There's no time
to space out now!
Do somethin' about this already!
[LUFFY]
Yeah... I know.
[VIVI] Then quit just
standing there, will you?
[NAMI]
Come on, Luffy!
I know what I should do.
But... I don't feel like it...
Damn it! Why do you
keep saying that?
We're about to be
turned into wax statues!
Do you understand me?
We're going to die!
[LUFFY]
Yeah...
But for some reason, I can't
get motivated to help...
[ALL] What do you mean,
"can't get motivated"?!
What's going on here?
What is wrong with him?
Our friends are gonna
die if he doesn't
do something to help them soon.
I'll snap him out of it.
Let's go, Karoo.
[squaks]
Huh?
[USOPP, KAROO shriek]
[USOPP]
Where did you two come from?!
Just give up.
Your friend has already
fallen into a nasty trap.
That's right.
Haven't you noticed
what he's standing on?
Standing?
[USOPP]
Let me take a look.
What's that? There's a strange
black pattern on the ground.
I don't get it.
What's so important
about that thing?
Yeah, you're right.
You really don't get it
at all, do you?
[laughs]
What's funny?
Paint... That's what's funny.
It's just paint...
You and your friends don't
stand a chance of escapin' now.
[USOPP screams]
[screaming]
[laughs]
[USOPP]
[KAROO screaming]
Karoo! Let's make a run for it!
[squaks]
Oh, great, now
they're running away.
Lets get 'em.
Full speed ahead, Karoo!
[squaks]
Hey, wait! I'm not on yet!
Slow down, Karoo! Let me on!
Hey, bird, do you hear me?
Let me on!
[squaks]
Just let me on, now!
[USOPP panting]
[USOPP]
Why are you afraid of me?
I thought you were
a duck, not a chicken!
Slow down, will you?!
Please, Karoo!
Miss Golden Week's responsible!
I know that this is your doing!
It's my Colors Trap.
Betrayal Black.
If you touch the paint,
you'll want to
betray your friends,
no matter what they might say.
Even if they beg
and plead for help.
What's she talking about?
I don't understand
what's going on here.
She's a painter.
She uses her paint to
create different emotions.
Each color is a feeling.
[NAMI]
Huh?
Her sense of
color's so complete,
she can manipulate your mind.
Just a splash of
one of her colors,
and you'll be
under her control.
Under her control?!
Well, that's not good.
That simpleminded oaf is
already too easy to control.
The last thing we need is
someone messing with his mind.
Does that mean that all
he needs to do is get away
from the paint
and he'll be okay?
Luffy! Move away
from there, quickly!
[VIVI]
No, don't! Luffy, listen!
Whatever you do,
please don't step outside
the black circle,
all right? I'm begging!
[NAMI]
What are you saying?!
[VIVI] We don't want
you to save us, Luffy.
Please, stay away from us!
No way.
[ZORO]
I get it now.
We just needed to say
the exact opposite
of what we wanted him to do.
Oh, hey!
What... What just happened?
I was acting really strange.
[VIVI]
Luffy! Help us now!
[LUFFY]
Okay! I'm on my way right now!
[giggling]
[laughing]
Never mind. I just
wanna laugh right now!
Luffy!
Moron!
What now?!
Colors Trap again.
Laughter Yellow.
[laughing]
You should not have
stepped out of the circle.
[laughing]
Now it's on his clothing!
Luffy! Quick!
Take off your shirt.
[LUFFY]
I'd love to, really.
But right now,
I'm too busy laughing.
[laughing]
[ZORO grunts]
It's getting bad.
If the wax keeps
falling at this rate,
we'll be lucky to stay
alive for five mintues.
[USOPP, KAROO screaming]
[ZORO] Did you guys come
here just to play tag?!
[USOPP, KAROO scream]
[NAMI]
Look! When Usopp ran into Luffy,
the paint smudged!
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY] Jeez! What's going on?!
I felt all weird again!
Hey, painter girl!
Would you stop messin'
with me already?!
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK] But you
were having such a good time.
Wasn't it funny?
Well, yeah...
it was kinda funny.
But stop!
I've gotta see about
breaking that pumpkin now.
Gum‐Gum...
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK]
Another Colors Trap!
Time for Bullfight Red!
[LUFFY]
Bazooka!
[ZORO]
What were you aiming at?
I just can't let you break it.
Mr. 3 wouldn't be
happy about that at all.
What'd you do?!
During a bull fight,
a bull can't
control his urge to
attack the red cape.
Likewise, you can't
do anything now
but attack that red circle.
That's what I did.
[screams]
'Kay, that does it!
I'm mad now!
Gum‐Gum...
Bazooka!
Having fun?
Aw... Oh, great...
At this rate, he's never
gonna be able to beat her.
Now all of his
strength is useless.
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK]
Now to finish up!
We'll mix the Laughter
Yellow on your back
with some Sadness Blue!
The last Colors Trap:
Tranquil Green.
[sighs]
Ah... That's some good tea!
[NAMI, ZORO, VIVI]
Luffy!
So... What happens now?
See, I told you,
you should have posed,
but you wouldn't listen to me.
And now it's too late.
You're gonna die like that.
Are you really still
talking about that?
Damn. How can they just
keep runnin' like that?
Nose Fancy Double Cannon!
[KAROO squaks]
[USOPP laughs] You missed us,
jerk! Way to go, Karoo!
[KAROO squaks]
My turn now!
Special Attack: Lead Star!
[USOPP] We need to get back
to Luffy and the others now.
[KAROO squaks]
Chasin' them around
isn't gettin us anywhere.
I noticed.
I hate to use this on
useless pests like them,
but it looks like we may
not have a choice now.
This little beauty
should be quite handy.
A .44 calibur, six‐shot
flintlock revolver.
It's a new model out
of the South Blue.
Continuous fire.
And when I shoot it,
the bullets are invisible.
[USOPP] When Luffy was acting
so strange back there,
those two agents mentioned
something about paint.
The paint must have something
to do with Luffy's behavior!
There was also some
yellow paint on his back
when we crashed
into him earlier.
That's gotta be the key!
We just have to do
something about the paint
before it's too late!
[USOPP]
Hurry!
[KAROO squaks]
[LUFFY sighs]
This really is some nice tea.
Really nice.
Luffy!
Hey! Wake up!
It's nice tea...
So nice... Very nice.
[USOPP growls]
Why are you just drinking tea?!
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[USOPP]
They haven't been hard for long.
We still have time to save 'em!
[LUFFY]
Really?
[USOPP]
We're coming now, guys!
I'm counting on you,
Karoo. Let's go!
‐‐[KAROO squaks]
‐‐[LUFFY] I'm not gonna let
[LUFFY]
anyone else die today!
[USOPP] It'll be hot,
but it's the only way!
[LUFFY]
Wake up, everyone!
[SANJI]
This is really strange...
Why hasn't anyone come back?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Time to Fight Back! Usopp's
Quick Thinking and Fire Star!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!