[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[MERRY] I'm sorry.
[MERRY]
I wanted to carry everyone
just a little bit further.
[MERRY] I had so much fun.
I wish our adventures
would never end.
Merry!
[MERRY]
But I'm sorry, I can't--
[LUFFY] No, Merry!
If anyone should apologize,
it's us, not you!
[LUFFY] I'm no good at steering.
I ran you into icebergs
and all kinds of stuff.
I took bad care of you
and ripped your sails.
Zoro and Sanji are idiots, too.
They were breaking
your stuff all the time!
[LUFFY]
Usopp tried to fix you,
but he wasn't any good at it.
We all know that.
If anyone's sorry,
it's--it's us!
[LUFFY crying]
[MERRY]
I don't mind. I was happy.
[MERRY] I know you always
treated me with love.
Thank you.
[MERRY] Even if the time
we spent together was short,
I'm glad that I could
spend it with you.
Merry!
[LUFFY] Peace Interrupted!
A Navy Vice Admiral
with a Fist of Love!
[CHILDREN laughing]
[ANNOUNCER WOMAN 313A]
Attention, we've now arrived
at Water Seven's Blue Station.
Please check all
of your belongings
before departing the sea train.
If you want to take it,
I'll give it to you for free.
Since you're a real swordsman.
[ZORO] Damn it.
[CITIZEN 313A] How's it looking?
[CITIZEN 313B] Everything's
still a mess over here.
[CITIZEN 313A]
This year's Aqua Laguna
did a real number on the city.
Everyone's giving it their best,
but I don't think we can
repair this on our own.
[screaming]
Wait. Is that--?
[CITIZEN 313A]
It's Paulie from Dock 1!
[CITIZEN 313B] What's he
doing here in the backstreets?
[GIRLS] Paulie!
[PAULIE] Quiet down!
We're here to work, not play!
Now move it!
[screaming]
[PAULIE] Dock 3, I'm leaving
this side of the bridge to you!
[SHIPWRIGHTS] Yes, sir!
[PAULIE] Dock 5,
you get started with the houses
next to Scrap Island.
[SHIPWRIGHTS] Yes, sir!
I know we still
gotta do our day jobs,
but I wanna see this whole
town in tip-top shape
by the end of the month!
[SHIPWRIGHTS] Yeah!
Let's go!
[SHIPWRIGHTS cheering]
Thanks guys!
We love you, Galley-La!
[CITIZEN 313C]
They never let us down!
Aw, geez!
Building stuff
sure is hard work!
I admit, we're a lot
better at breaking things!
Guess we're sleeping
outdoors again!
[FRANKY FAMILY MOONHAIR]
There you go.
Good! You take it easy!
Just a little rest and
you'll be better in no time!
[FRANKY FAMILY SPLITHEAD]
Doctor Reindeer said
Gomorrah's eyesight
should return
if he takes it easy for a while.
[FRANKY FAMILY BANDANNA]
Oh really? That's great!
[ZAMBAI] Hey guys, could you
gimme a hand for a second?
I need to pick up an important
package from the station.
A package?
It finally came, huh?
Yep.
I can't wait.
This is gonna be fun.
[CITIZENS complaining]
[CITIZEN 313C] C'mon!
Let us meet the pirates!
[CITIZEN 313D]
We wanna apologize
for treating them so bad before!
No way.
The Straw Hats aren't
meeting with anyone today!
Our company prepared them
a thank you package.
At least let us give it to them!
I'm with Water 7 News.
Can I please get a comment with
the heroes who saved the mayor?
No means no!
They're busy, okay?
[REPORTER 313B] At least
let me take a picture!
All of you, go home!
[SECRETARY 313A] Do you need
a secretary to replace Kalifa?
I'm highly qualified!
Stop keeping the
pirates to yourselves!
Would you shut up already?
[loud stomping noise]
Awesome!
Now that's what I call "power!"
Is this where you wanted it?
[CITIZEN 313E]
Yeah, that's perfect! Thanks!
Wish we had you guys
around all the time!
This kinda stuff
is a piece of cake!
If you got more,
then bring it on!
[laughing]
You're making everyone
else look bad, guys.
[KASHII]
By the way, Sniper King.
You sure you're happy here?
'Cause we were just thinking.
If our bosses are still fighting
like you said they were,
there's no point in us
joining up with them
'til it's all settled.
[OIMO] We'll stick
around here and help out
while they need it,
but after that,
we planned to
head back to Elbaf.
[KASHII] Long story short...
You wanna come along with us?
[chuckling]
I dunno.
[USOPP] Wherever I go,
it's my business.
[USOPP] I'm leaving the crew.
This is goodbye.
[USOPP]
I challenge you to a duel!
Damn it all.
[ICEBERG] I see.
So in the end,
you burned the blueprints.
I think it's
better that way.
[ICEBERG] You've made yourself
an enemy of the government.
Yeah, I guess.
So spill it.
What are you so busy
drawing over there, bro?
Aqua Laguna was
powerful this year.
I'm sure it's weighing
on everyone's minds.
It may not be long
before this island
is completely
swallowed by the sea.
You're right.
Soon we're gonna have more
city underwater than above it.
We can't keep up
this fight forever.
So, what's the plan?
[ICEBERG] I'm going
to make this city float.
What?
You're gonna make
Water 7 a... boat?
Do you really think
that's even possible?
Have you forgotten already?
We grew up watching a man
who could make the
impossible possible.
Now I'm going to do the same.
If you're a man,
show some gusto!
[MOUSE squeaks]
[FRANKY] He did always
do everything with a bang,
didn't he?
Well, it's worth a shot.
You are his student, after all.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[ICEBERG'S TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
Hello?
[ZAMBAI] Oh, is that you, Bro?
[FRANKY] Hey, it's Zambai!
What's up?
You're gonna love this.
It finally came in!
We're picking it up here at
the train station as we speak!
Your 200 million Berry treasure!
This is gonna be sweet!
[knocking]
Hope everyone's decent!
[SANJI] Oh, hey, Kokoro.
Yo, we're comin' through!
[SANJI] Sure. Good to see ya.
Meow! Meow!
Gero!
[KOKORO] I think
you better wait outside.
Gero! Gero!
[KOKORO] You boys have
been sleeping for days!
You musta been awfully pooped!
Not that I blame you,
after all that fighting.
Well!
Mister Pirate King
is back on his feet, too!
Uh, actually, not so much.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Even though he couldn't
move after the last fight,
he didn't wanna miss dinner
'cause he was sleeping.
[SANJI] So he developed
the sleep-eating technique
you see here.
[KOKORO] He's still asleep?
Whoa! That's so cool!
Meow!
[KOKORO] That's what
you call multitalented!
[laughing]
By the way, your
Log Pose should be set
after another 2 or 3 days here.
[KOKORO]
Oh goodness, what happened?
Even if the Log Pose is set,
it's not like we can
go anywhere without a ship.
All the money we
saved up to buy a new ship
is gone forever.
Our clothes, furniture,
even Bellemere's precious
tangerine trees were lost.
Aqua Laguna
carried it all away.
I'm so depressed,
I can't even move.
[KOKORO] Sorry I said anything.
We left our stuff in
one of the backstreet hotels.
Oh, so that's what your
guests are here about.
Our guests?
[knocking sound]
[CITIZEN 313F]
Um, so, funny story.
My trees!
Oh my gosh!
I thought I'd
never see them again!
--I'm so happy!
--Yeah...
Sorry about
kicking you out,
but we thought you tried
to assassinate Iceberg.
We treated your belongings
as pirate loot,
so we confiscated everything.
[CITIZEN 313F]
I hope you're not mad.
Of course I'm not mad!
Thank you so much!
[laughing]
Well, there you go!
[CHOPPER] Hi!
Doctor Chopper, reporting in!
How are you?
[SANJI] I'm great
now that you're here!
Such a heavy bag!
Please, allow me.
If you must.
I treated the
Franky Family's wounds,
but I didn't let Robin out
of my sight for a single second!
[SANJI] Mission Complete!
[laughing]
I already told you
I'm not going anywhere!
[CHOPPER] You promise?
[ROBIN]
You have my word, soldier.
[NAMI] Guys, look!
Can you believe it?
My tangerine trees are okay!
We got our money back
and our stuff, too!
[CHOPPER] Really?
Once we buy a ship,
then we'll be good to go!
[CHOPPER]
All right! That's great!
[laughing]
Wow, baby!
You guys feelin super or what?
Oh. Some folks aren't here.
Whatever.
What's with the big entrance?
Something going on?
[FRANKY] You bet!
Now, better
listen close, brother.
So there's this island
that's always at war.
[SANJI]
Wait, stop. I don't care.
If you're here to tell bedtime
stories, go bother someone else.
[FRANKY] Shut up!
This is important--Listen!
For years, fire has
rained on that island.
Death and destruction
are the only things
that its people know.
[FRANKY] Houses burn down;
cities fall to ruin.
There's no place to
run from all the chaos.
And in the midst of all this
madness, there's a single tree.
[FRANKY] No matter what
happens, it never falls,
and no matter how much
the island is destroyed,
its people gather around
it and build it all up again.
[FRANKY] It's the strongest
tree in the world.
As far as anyone knows,
only a few exist.
It's known as
the Jewel Tree, Adam.
Huh?
Okay. So what?
[FRANKY] Every so often a
piece of wood from that tree
shows up on the black market.
I've wanted one
for a long time now,
but the going price
is 200 million Berries.
Too expensive for me.
That is, until a bunch
of pirates showed up,
flailing their money around
and begging me to take it.
Bastard!
You used our money
to buy some stupid log
and then you brag about it?
I told you, shut up!
[FRANKY] A long time ago,
I decided that I was
done building ships
for the rest of my life.
And yet, I couldn't help
but follow in the footsteps
of my old master.
And soon enough, I found
myself designing a ship.
Now, my hope is to use
that special wood to build it--
To put all my heart
into one last ship.
A ship of dreams that
can sail across any sea!
[FRANKY] I've had the
blueprints for ages.
Now I finally have the wood.
All that's left is to make it.
So what I'm saying here
is it would be my honor
if you'd take my ship
and sail the world!
Wait, so does that mean--
You--You're gonna give us
the ship, free of charge?
Uh-huh!
'Cause that way,
I'll know my masterpiece
is in good hands.
Trust me, that's
all I could ask for.
[FRANKY] Well, that, and you
kinda paid for it already.
Gold Roger is
the only man in history
who's sailed
across the whole world,
and his ship, the Oro Jackson,
was made from
a jewel tree, as well.
Mark my words.
I'll show you the best
damn ship you've ever seen!
Heh. You're a
shipwright after all.
You can pretend all you like,
but in the end, you're
just like old Tom, ain't ya?
[chuckling]
Guess you're right.
I get it now.
It took a while,
but I think I finally understand
the pride Tom felt when he died.
[ALL cheering]
[CHOPPER]
You're the best, Franky!
Thank you!
We'd be happy to take your ship!
[SANJI] All right!
Now on to the next island!
[NAMI] Luffy! Did you hear that?
We have a new ship!
Gero! Gero!
[YOKOZUNA]
Gero!
This is bad.
I didn't think those bastards
would come after us so soon.
Damn it, and I bet
Luffy's still sleeping, too!
[ZORO] I gotta warn 'em
before it's too late!
No way!
The ocean?
Can't remember.
Is it the other way?
What?
Not again!
Damn! Stupid ocean's everywhere!
This sucks!
[CITIZEN 313E] It's the Navy!
They're here
to arrest the pirates!
[CITIZEN 313G] Even after
they saved the mayor's life,
they won't show them any mercy?
Hey! You see that over there?
That's Vice-Admiral Garp's ship!
Straight from Headquarters!
[CITIZEN 313F]
Wait, did you say "Garp?"
The same Garp that
nearly captured Gold Roger
over and over again?
He's a living legend!
[CITIZEN 313G] They're not
messing around if they sent him.
[CITIZEN 313H] If they don't
run, those pirates are finished!
What the hell's going on here?
Don't tell me this
is the same beach?
[ZORO] I don't have time
for this crap right now!
Well!
Would you look at that!
I guess he's lost!
Heh!
Well, that's too bad!
[MICHAEL] Hey pal, are you lost?
You new around town?
[HOICHAEL] Turn around.
Let's see your face.
Huh?
[SHIPWRIGHT 313A]
Now hold on, sir.
The only person here is
our president, Mr. Iceberg.
[GARP] Move it!
I know you're
hiding those pirates.
[SHIPWRIGHT 313A]
I swear, we're not!
[SHIPWRIGHT 313B] Hey!
You can't go inside!
Hold on!
The Straw Hats are heroes!
--They--
--Shut up!
All right, you two.
Wait here.
[COBY and HELMEPPO]
Yes, sir!
[chuckling]
[shrieking]
What the hell?
What's going on?
[GARP] Pardon me,
but are you folks
the Straw Hat Pirates?
You see,
I have some friends here
that would like to share
a word with Monkey D. Luffy.
--The Navy?
[snoring]
Dumb kid. Never learns.
Just as careless as ever.
What?
Damn, he's fast!
Rise and shine!
No!
Ow! That hurt!
--Ow!
--What happened?
Why would one little
punch hurt you so much?
You're made of rubber!
It's because there is no
defense against a fist of love.
You've been getting
in a lot of trouble lately,
haven't you?
Luffy.
G-G-G-Grandpa?
[SANJI] Huh?
[ALL] What?
[CHOPPER] A Marine Vice
Admiral is your...
[FRANKY, NAMI, SANJI, CHOPPER]
...grandpa?
[SANJI] So all this time,
Luffy's grandpa was
some kinda Navy hero
and he never told us?
[CHOPPER screaming]
[CHOPPER]
Forget about that, Sanji!
Luffy's in trouble!
[SANJI] What the hell
is with his family?
Clearly, they have issues.
[ZORO] Damn it!
This is a waste of time!
I gotta get back to
the rest of the crew!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
The Strongest Family?
Luffy's Father Revealed!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!