It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
It's all right, Robin.
We'll be fine.
I understand what's going on.
You're still hiding
something from us, aren't you?
There's one last thing,
you can do what you want
but a pirate...
...isn't allowed to
leave their crew,
unless they have their
captain's permission.
So no matter what, you
can always believe in Luffy.
Dumb frog!
Gero!
Poor kid.
It's been eight years now.
Eight long years since
Tom was taken away from us.
I've watched you challenge
the sea train every day
since then again and again.
You were trying to get
stronger, weren't you?
So you won't ever have to lose
the ones you love ever again.
So you'll have the
power to protect them.
Don't cry.
Now's the time for you
to put that training
to the test big boy.
Gero?
Anyway, we're in trouble now.
The government's got
exactly what they want.
The only woman with the know-how
to bring back an ancient weapon
and the man with the only
known blueprints for one.
Don't that beat all.
But still, there's no point in
me making it out of here alone.
You gotta find some way to get
back to Straw Hat, all right?
I can't.
If I'm with them, it will
only bring them suffering.
Those government
bastards may tell you
that your existence is a crime,
but no matter how
dangerous you may be,
just being alive, just being
who you are is never wrong.
There's no right or
wrong in who you are.
Open the main gate!
Huh?
Whoa!
What the hell is
this crazy place?
A waterfall?
What?
I can't see the bottom!
You sure are a noisy one.
It looks like Lucci and the
others are headed this way.
And they've brought me
the best souvenir I could
ever possibly wish for.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
We gotta hurry!
Can't you bulls go any faster?
So big bro Franky sacrificed
himself to save you guys?
And now he's--?
Yeah.
That's right.
He was trying to rescue Robin
and help us escape with her.
Our Big Bro is such
a kind-hearted guy!
We need to hurry or
we won't make it in time.
Look!
The lights of the
"Nightless Island"!
It's Enies Lobby!
Really?
I can't believe we made it!
All right!
Now we can rescue bro!
"Nightless Island"?
Yeah!
The sun never
stops shining there.
So it's "nightless".
They sometimes call the Judicial
Island a "Daytime Island", too.
Is that so?
We found them!
The giant yagaras!
Ahoy!
Luffy!
Hey! Sanji!
And--Who the heck it that?
It's Straw Hat!
Looks like we
caught up with 'em.
No problem.
Well, now that
we've found the others.
It's time for our date
with the World Government!
Hell yeah, it is!
Okay! This is it!
Now approaching Enies Lobby!
All hands!
Get ready for a showdown!
Yeah!!!
At last.
After five long years,
the time has finally come
for all eight members
of CP9, to be reunited.
This should be a
time of celebration.
But instead I'll ask,
"What's the meaning of this?"
Your orders were to assassinate
the leaders of the revolution!
But according to this article,
not only did you
kill those three, but
twenty others, as well!
What happened?
If you have an excuse,
I'd like to hear it!
Yoyoi!
My most sincere apologies
and pardons, Chief!
Everything is entirely,
unreservedly,
completely, my fault!
Stop that, Kumadori!
A real man doesn't bow
his head to anybody!
I'll explain everything
that happened to the Chief,
so shut up and get
a hold of yourself!
Yoyoi!
I can't apologize enough!
And so if need be I'll shoulder
the blame by taking my own life!
Don't be so melodramatic!
Yoyoi!
It happened like this, Chief.
We followed the
plan to the letter.
We infiltrated their forces
and were all ready
for the assassination.
But somehow the enemy managed
to find out about our plans!
Probably 'cause I was talking
about them all over
town, Chapapa!
You again?
What's wrong with you?
And what's the point in
having a zipper on your mouth
if it you don't even
use the damn thing?
This little blabbermouth problem
of yours has got
to stop, understand?
We're secret agents!
We've got secrets to keep!
I didn't do it on
purpose, Chapapa!
Don't you "Chapapa" me!
Can't do anything
about it now, Chapapa!
There's no need
to blame Fukurou!
I will take full responsibility!
Seppuku! Iron Body!
I can't even die right!
Oh just get it over
with, you bastard!
You'd be doing everyone a favor!
I accidentally talked
about it, Chapapa!
Shut up!
Enough.
I understand.
Hot, hot, hot!
I spilt my coffee again, dammit!
Oh, by the way, I heard
Nero didn't work out.
Whatever.
♪ Oh, the wind
carries my name. ♪
♪ From Sniper Island,
far away. ♪
♪ When I aim,
it's straight and true. ♪
♪ Lulu lala lu ♪
♪ Whether you're a man
or a mouse, Lock on! ♪
♪ I will put your
heart in my sights! ♪
♪ And lock on! ♪
♪ No one knows
the secrets hide ♪
♪ beneath this
mask and my cape. ♪
♪ Lululu, lulu lala. ♪
♪ There is no escape! ♪
♪ Sni-papa snipapa. ♪
♪ Sni-per-king aims true! ♪
Sniper King from Sniper Island?
For real?
That's right!
I'm a close friend of Usopp's.
I'm here because he asked me
to aid you on this
perilous journey!
He's a super hero!
I knew it!
I could totally tell
'cause of the mask and cape!
Amazing!
I've never seen one before!
So wearing a mask and cape
means he has super powers?
'Course!
Everybody in a mask
and cape is a super hero!
Really?
Well, yeah!
Isn't that Usopp?
I'm glad you're safe, Usopp.
That's the long-nose guy that
busted into the Franky House.
That's the guy that got
taken away with bro.
Totally.
No question.
It's-- It's nice to meet you!
Likewise.
That's one of the guys
we met at the Shift Station.
Meow!
Can I have your autograph?
Sure.
But that makes me
wonder--Where did Usopp go?
He's safe.
There's no need
to worry about him.
Anyway, he told me the most
important thing right now
is saving your friend Robin.
Then he left.
Yep.
He's absolutely right.
So, uh--So where exactly
is this Sniper Island?
I'll tell you.
♪ Oh, the wind
carries my name. ♪
It's inside of your heart.
Wow!
♪ From Sniper Island. ♪
♪ Far away. ♪
Seriously. Where?
♪ Oh, the wind
carries my name! ♪
♪ From Sniper Island,
far away. ♪
Sing it!
♪ From Sniper Island, far
away! ♪
Hey, Nami.
Huh?
Yeah? What is it?
Just a second.
The rest of you idiots
should hear this, too.
Before we go to rescue Robin--
There's something
you need to know.
If there's a Buster Call,
you'll be obliterated.
Long ago, an island was erased.
Five vice admirals
and ten battleships
are a terrifying force
for anyone to behold.
But for a child to see
them destroy her home,
well, it's nothing
short of a nightmare.
Those thoughts have
haunted her for years
and now that her old
nightmare bares its fangs
at her companions she no longer
has the will to resist us.
You bastards!
You knew and you used that.
Of course we did.
So there you have it.
Those CP9 guys
are controlling Robin
by using her childhood
fears against her.
I'm not making excuses for
not being able to save her.
I just wanted to make it clear
that even if we march in
to get her back, it doesn't
necessarily mean
that she'll be willing
to return with us.
No.
It's over.
This is the last
time you'll see me.
None of that matters!
I won't stand for this!
Damn Robin!
It's not her fault!
Of course it is, Nami!
Why doesn't she
want us to rescue her?
It doesn't make sense!
Because she doesn't
wanna feel responsible
for all the awful things that'll
happen to our crew once we do!
I don't care about all that!
If we don't rescue her, she's
gonna be killed, isn't she?
There's no way she wants to die,
so we're gonna save her!
Well of course she doesn't
want to die, but still!
Let it go.
This doesn't change
what we have to do.
We'll save her either way.
I'm gonna beat up
every last one of them!
There's a new move I wanna try!
Hey, guys, take a look at this.
I came to this island once
before to do some
maintenance on the railway.
I drew this from what
I could remember.
It's a rough sketch of the
overall layout of Enies Lobby.
The Gates of Justice are located
at the back of the island.
The only way to get to them
is through the Tower of Law.
What's that big black thing?
It represents the waterfall.
Huh?
Yeah.
Once we're inside, you'll see.
If we don't rescue
Franky and Nico Robin
before they pass
through the Main Gate
and into the Gates of
Justice, then that's it.
It's over.
And why's that?
It doesn't matter
where they take her to,
we'll just keep on fighting
them until we get Robin back!
I explained this before
we left Water 7, remember?
Once we pass that gate,
the only two places
we can go are Navy Headquarters
or the deep-sea prison.
No matter what happens,
we have to settle this before
they reach those rear gates.
Yep. Pretty much.
On top of that,
even if we all rushed the
island at the same time,
the only ones capable of going
up against those CP9 guys--
--are you Straw Hats.
After seeing what you can do,
I know how strong you are.
That's why I think you should
stay behind once we get there.
Give us five minutes,
then charge through to the
main island in Rocketman.
The Franky Family and
Galley-La will go in first
and break open the Main Gate
and the Main Island Front Gate
so the train can pass through.
I'm sure we'll suffer
a lot of casualties,
but remember: Once you're in,
keep going no matter what.
Don't look back.
We've only got a
little over 60 people.
The enemy forces
probably have somewhere
between 2 and 3 thousand.
Our best chance for victory
is for you Straw Hats
to concentrate on CP9 and leave
the rest of the marines to us.
Right, I got it.
Okay, folks!
We're pulling up to
the front of the island!
While we're here, take a look
at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
Behold!
The Gates of Justice.
Whoa!
That's huge!
It's not a good idea
to open them all the way.
When it comes time to
send a criminal through,
they only unlatch them
just enough to let 'em pass.
Behind that gate are
some big sea kings.
That part of the sea is
a lot like the Calm Belt:
An eerie body of water cutting
right through the Grand Line.
No normal ship would
dare to sail there.
They'd be lost forever.
I don't know how
they managed to do it,
but somehow the Navy figured out
a way to make it through safely.
In other words, it's
like the pirate girl said:
You can't take
back a criminal once
they pass through those gates.
Any chance of a rescue is gonna
have to happen before they open.
Go!
Hop to it!
There's no time to lose!
We'll head in first
and clear a path for you,
just like we planned!
Give 'em hell, Straw Hats!
Hey!
You two over there!
Aren't you supposed
to be with us?
Hm?
Wait, where's Luffy?
Huh?
He was here just a second ago.
Look!
Isn't that Straw Hat?
What?
Why the hell is he
going in on his own?
That crazy Straw Hat didn't
understand the plan at all!
There goes our strategy.
He said "Right! I
got it", didn't he?
He's really not the
wait-five-minutes type.
Damn. Should have known.
He's an impatient one, isn't he?
Yeah!
Go, Mister Pirate!
Meow!
Gero, gero!
Too late now!
Let's move!
Sodom! Gomorrah!
Jump over that iron fence and
then break open the main gate!
Yeah!
Gum Gum--Rocket!
What the--?
Something just flew over!
Whoa!
What's up with this place?
What a huge hole!
It looks like the island's
floating or something!
I see a town, too!
Huh.
I wonder if Robin is down there.
There's someone up
on the flagpole!
Shoot him down
before he gets away!
Whoops!
Guess they spotted me!
He went inside the main gate!
Get back here!
This is the Main Gate!
I have an urgent message
for the Chief Officer at
the Main Island Front Gate!
This is the Main Gate!
It's an emergency!
This is Spandam.
What's going on?
An intruder somehow managed
to pass through the Main Gate
and is heading toward
the Main Island, sir!
One intruder?
That's what all
this fuss is about?
Surely you can manage
to take care of him.
But, sir!
You don't understand, it's--
This is the Main
Island Front Gate.
Intruder sighting confirmed.
Don't worry.
We'll take care of
things from here.
Hey there, buddy!
That's far enough!
Do you have the slightest
idea where you are?
Don't take this guy lightly!
Unless my eyes deceive me,
then I'm pretty sure that he's--
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
What?
What was that you just said?
The man with the
100 million berry bounty!
It is him!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Where's Robin?
Tell me where
Robin is right now!
I'm afraid Straw Hat Luffy has
entered the main island, sir!
What?
Why the hell did
you let him do that?
What's going on over there?
Get out of my way!
Any idiot should know what it
means to attack Enies Lobby!
And if they don't,
we'll have to teach them!
We're coming, Robin!
On the next One Piece:
"Luffy Cuts Through!
Big Showdown on
the Judicial Island!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!