[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
The battle of Marineford
ended with a Navy victory.
Unable to save Ace's life,
Luffy fell into despair.
But this is a story
from another time.
Ten years ago,
when the brothers ran wild
with dreams of a world
full of adventure.
[LUFFY]
"To the Sea Someday!
The Pledge of the Three Brats!"
[LUFFY yells]
Here I go!
All right, Gum-Gum...
...and Pistol!
Huh?
[gasps]
Would you pull it
together already?
Why do all your moves
suck so much, huh?
That's one for Ace.
[BOTH grunting]
[ACE]
I won't lose a fight to anyone.
Sorry, Sabo, but that
goes for you, too.
[SABO]
I'm still too weak.
I can't stop till I'm
stronger than Ace--
till I'm the strongest
in the world.
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
I guess that's two
wins for me. Heh.
[SABO yells]
[SABO groans]
Dammit!
D'aw! It's always so
close when they fight!
What's the deal?
Sabo! You and me--let's do this!
Last chance to turn back!
This is gonna hurt, you know!
[LUFFY chuckles]
Gum-Gum Shield!
Not this again.
Here goes!
What, does he think I'm
just gonna run into him?
--This should be fun.
--Whoa, whoa, wait!
No, that's cheating! Stop it!
[LUFFY groaning]
[sighs] Just give it up
with the rubber crap.
Or at least learn to fight
like a normal person first.
No way! I was so close!
Just you wait, it's gonna be
awesome when I get it right!
C'mon, one more try!
Sorry, man.
You know the rules--
a hundred matches a day.
You can try it tomorrow.
[SABO] Luffy lost 50
times to both of us.
Me versus Ace
looks like 24 to 26.
Lost by two points. So close!
You just win 'cause
you're older.
I'm telling you, when I turn
ten, I'm gonna kick your butts!
You do realize we'll
be 13 then, right?
Anyway, let's go look
for something to eat.
That looks yummy.
I could eat crocodile every day!
Okay, but make sure he
doesn't eat you this time.
You're lucky you got
swallowed whole before.
Better safe than sorry, huh?
You can't swim, so stay
up here and watch.
Crocodile meat!
[SABO screams]
If you don't die,
I'm so gonna kill you!
[NARRATOR] The harsh
environment of Mount Corvo
made the three boys
grow stronger each day.
[NARRATOR] To the north of
their forest playground,
the dirty dealings of Gray
Terminal continued as usual.
[NARRATOR] And even
further north than that,
there was a city with
a solid stone wall,
handily keeping the nearby
criminals at arm's length.
[NARRATOR] The only entrance
from the junkyard below
is called the Great Gate.
Twice a day, mountains
of discarded trash
from all over the country
are carried through it
and dumped into Gray Terminal.
--[SCAVENGERS chuckle]
--Here it comes.
Let's go! Treasure huntin' time!
[NARRATOR] From time to time,
residents of Gray Terminal
will enter the city to sell
what they call "recycled goods."
[GUARD A]
Huh? Hey, wait!
What's in that package?
Crocodile skin. Want it?
[GUARD A]
What?
[GUARD A gasps]
G-Go ahead!
[NARRATOR] Beyond the
Great Gate is a boulevard,
through which everyone
entering the city must pass.
It leads to Edge Town.
[NARRATOR] Edge Town, populated
by thugs and criminals,
lacks the refinement seen
in the rest of the city.
Hey there, buddy.
Need some help with
that heavy package?
[HOODLUMS chuckle]
Hey! Answer me
when I speak to you!
[ACE]
Buzz off.
What?
[HOODLUMS gasp]
You're dead!
Gotta pick your targets
more carefully!
You might get more than
you bargained for.
[HOODLUMS gasp]
Aw, damn it, not them! Look out!
[ACE]
No mercy!
[SABO, LUFFY]
All right!
--[thudding]
--[HOODLUMS groaning]
[CROWD chattering]
[NARRATOR]
In the middle of the city,
another stone wall
reaches to the skies.
This one encloses High Town,
which separates those
with noble blood from
their "lessor" neighbors.
[NARRATOR] This is the shining
jewel of the Goa Kingdom.
Said to be the most beautiful
country in all of the East Blue,
not a hint of trash can
be found on its streets.
[NARRATOR] Windmill Village
can make no such claim.
And although it's technically
a part of the Goa Kingdom,
the fact is often
swept under the rug
by its more wealthy inhabitants.
[CROWD chattering]
[SABO] I told you they'd
love that crocodile skin.
Our pirate savings
are really piling up!
[LUFFY]
Fine, but I'm hungry!
[ACE]
Hold on, we're almost there.
I hear this place has
the best ramen noodles
you've ever tasted.
[SABO chuckles]
Well, that's not saying much.
I've never even
heard of the stuff.
[LUFFY] I'll eat dirt
at this point! Just hurry!
We're here.
Hello, may I help you?
[gasps] Oh, my goodness,
this will not do, sir!
Forgive my bluntness,
but we simply do not
serve your kind.
[SABO]
The VIP room, please.
But that mark-- It can't be!
Please excuse my
impertinence, sir.
We would be honored to have
a noble such as yourself
grace our establishment.
Give me but a moment and
I'll gladly prepare a room.
That's pretty handy!
Where did you get that thing?
Oh, uh, yeah, it's weird,
I found it lying on the street.
[WAITRESS A] Three bowls of
ramen. Thank you for waiting.
Enjoy your meal.
So, this is ramen, huh?
Whoa, looks good!
Well, eat it already!
Took the words
right outta my mouth!
Seconds, please--
Ahem. We require seconds.
Three more bowls, post haste!
[WAITRESS A]
Yes, sir! On the way!
[SABO]
Three more!
[WAITRESS A]
Uh, yes, sir!
[SABO]
Three more!
[WAITRESS A]
Uh, right, just a moment!
[WAITRESS A panting]
[SABO]
More!
[WAITRESS A panting]
[WAITRESS A sighs]
[WAITRESS A]
May I come in?
[screams]
[WAITRESS A panting]
You might wanna see this!
[RAMEN MAN A]
Are you sure?
Sir, I think we need to talk.
[SABO, ACE, LUFFY gasp]
[ACE]
They found us out!
[SABO]
Yeah! Book it!
[RAMEN MAN A]
It's a dine and dash!
Catch those criminals!
Ahh. Wow, ramen sure is good!
[ACE]
I know, right? Worth it!
[LUFFY]
Mm-hmm!
[MAN E]
"Criminals"?
[MAN F]
They're just kids!
[CROWD gasps]
Damn it, how did
those little pests
sneak through the gate again?
I've had enough of their
antics for a lifetime!
Don't let them get away!
I don't care if they're kids!
They belong in a damn jail!
[WAITRESS A] Did they realize
they were on the fourth floor?
Because that is a long fall.
The window is a mess.
but we lost 26 bowls
of ramen, too!
Sir, look at this.
Those kids left a weird note.
[RAMEN MAN A gasps]
[RAMEN MAN A]
What is a "treasure tab"?
Huh? Wait, Sabo?
I can't believe it's him!
Please, come back!
It's you! You're alive!
[SABO'S DAD]
Let's go home!
The hell is this?
Are you friends with
that old dude, Sabo?
I think he knows you.
He's confusing me with
someone else, that's all.
[gasps] No! Sabo, come back!
Sabo.
You're wrong!
I'm not hiding anything!
[LUFFY]
Oh, that's cool, then.
Come on, how stupid can you get?
He's full of it!
Dammit, Sabo, we can't keep
secrets from each other!
[BOTH]
So, talk!
There's nothing
for me to tell you.
You trying to pick a fight
with me? Spit it out already!
[SABO] Okay, okay,
just stop killing me!
[LUFFY]
Huh?!
[ACE]
The son of a noble?
[ACE, LUFFY]
Who is?
I am!
[BOTH]
Hmm. So?
If you don't care,
then why did you ask me?
[SABO] The truth is, both my
parents are still alive.
So yeah, I'm not an orphan.
That means I lied about growing
up in Gray Terminal, too.
And that guy who was
calling out to me...
[SABO]
That was my dad.
[gasps]
[SABO]
I'm sorry.
I know I've been lying to you
guys for a long time now.
Well, he said he's sorry,
so we gotta forgive him.
I'm not forgiving anyone
till I hear the whole story.
If you're really
from a noble family,
why would you want to live
in some crappy junk heap?
'Cause I ran away
from home, that's why.
[ACE, LUFFY gasp]
[SABO'S DAD]
You understand, don't you, Sabo?
[SABO'S DAD] A noble must
be a gentleman, educated,
well-mannered, and wise.
And then, when you're older,
you can marry a girl
from a royal family.
That will make Mommy
and Daddy very happy.
Of course, I'm sure
you'll be very happy, too.
All I have to do is study
and meet the right girl?
Then everybody will be
happy as long as we live?
[SABO'S DAD]
Mm. If you work very hard at it.
Good boy, Sabo.
Okay!
[SABO]
I'll do my best!
[SABO'S DAD]
That's ridiculous!
What do you mean
the cargo ship sunk?
I don't give a damn
about the crew!
Those supplies weren't
cheap, you know!
Someone will pay for this!
Hello? Hello?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL A]
Cah-lick.
[SABO'S DAD groans]
I cannot afford this.
What a mess.
[knocking]
Hey, Dad! Look at this!
I drew it for you!
[gasps]
Your father is having
a trying day at work.
Sabo, if you have time to draw
this, you have time to study.
[NOBLE BOY A]
Hey, you!
[SABO]
Uh--
[NOBLE BOY A]
I'm from the royal family!
And that means you have
to do everything I say!
Carry me back to my house.
[NOBLE BOY A gasps]
How dare you!
I'm related to the king and I
want a piggyback ride right now!
Stop! Get offa me!
You nobles think you're
so hot, don't you?
This oughta teach you!
[gasps]
[SABO]
No!
[crying]
My son has royal blood--
I won't stand for you spilling
it on the pavement, you oaf!
[SABO'S MOM gsps] Sabo, tell me
you didn't get in a fight
with this boy from
the royal family!
Well, kind of.
I mean, he attacked me
with this scary knife, so...
[SABO'S MOM grunts]
My son can be such
a little beast!
I blame myself--
I do hope you weren't hurt!
It's terrible, I know.
Please forgive us.
I assure you, he will be
punished severely for this.
I'll do anything I can
to make things right.
Shall we go to the doctor
to make sure your
son isn't injured?
[SABO] Then I realized,
they love their money...
...their property...
their status...
[SABO]
...but not their son.
[SABO] If I couldn't
marry into a royal family,
I was useless to them.
They tried to teach me
culture and literature
and all that stuff...
...but I guess I didn't
learn fast enough,
'cause they were always
arguing and getting mad.
That family had no place
for someone like me.
I know you guys have it worse,
but even if I had parents,
I was still alone.
[SABO'S DAD] I heard that you've
been sneaking out behind my back
going goodness knows where.
I shouldn't have to
tell you this,
but stay away from Gray Terminal
if you know what's good for you.
We nobles are privileged
to live in High Town
with the king and his family.
It's a life the people down
there can only dream of.
By the same token, you do not
belong in their world.
[HOODLUMS laughing]
Hm? What? You again?
I dunno where your parents are,
but someone's gonna string you
up by those suspenders of yours
if you keep hanging around here.
[HOODLUMS laughing]
Please, tell me another story!
I wanna hear about all the
different countries you've seen!
And about all your
adventures on the high seas!
[MEN]
Hm?
[MAN C laughs]
[MAN C] You're a weird kid,
but I'll give you a pass.
[MAN D]
Yeah, take a seat.
Okay!
Well, at least the
people in Gray Terminal
know what it means to be free.
If the nobles in High Town
didn't spend their whole lives
licking the boots
of the royal family,
maybe they'd look up and see
that there's more to the world.
Man, I had no idea.
[SABO]
Ace, Luffy, listen.
The three of us,
we're gonna leave this country.
We're gonna sail the seas
and see the world.
And once I've done it all,
I'm gonna write a book
for kids like me.
'Cause studying is fun when
you're learning about adventure!
And we're gonna
have lots of 'em.
We're gonna be pirates!
[BOTH chuckle]
[ACE]
You don't gotta tell me!
I'm gonna be a pirate anyway!
I'll be so tough that
all the other pirates
and all the Marines
will bow at my feet.
Everyone in the world
will know my name!
That's gonna be the legacy
I leave behind when I die!
I don't care if people hate me.
I don't care if they wish
I'd never been born.
But they won't ignore me.
That's what it
means to be strong!
To be a great pirate!
I won't ever lose and
I won't ever run away!
Who cares if the world fears me
or respects me or whatever.
I'm gonna be a legend!
[chuckles]
[LUFFY] Then I know
what I'm gonna be, too!
The king of the pirates!
[BOTH gasp]
[laughing]
You dork.
Just gotta try and
show me up, don'tcha?
[SABO laughs]
I dunno if you'll
be a king or not,
but you're gonna do
something crazy,
I know that much for sure!
Uh-- We all wanna be pirates
together, though, don't we?
We're only saving for one ship,
but what if all three
of us wanna be captain?
Damn it, I never
thought of that.
Sabo, I always figured you'd
be the navigator on my ship.
You guys are welcome
to join my crew!
[ACE, SABO]
No thanks!
Huh? But I was nice
about it and everything!
Also, I'm gonna be the king,
so I gotta be the boss!
[ACE] Who wants a
crybaby captain? Not me.
[SABO]
Me neither!
[LUFFY]
What did you call me?!
Whatever.
[ACE chuckles]
You gave up?
[SABO laughs] Man, you're always
good for a laugh, aren't you?
[ACE, SABO, LUFFY laughing]
[ACE] Well, we'll figure it
out when the time comes.
Maybe we'll leave on one ship
and maybe we'll leave on three.
[LUFFY] Ooh! You stole
that from Dadan, huh?
Lemme tell you guys a secret.
[ACE] All it takes to become
brothers is to share some saké!
Whoa, really? That's so cool!
[ACE]
We may sail in different seas,
with different crews
on different ships.
But wherever we go and
whatever adventures we have,
we'll always be brothers,
and nobody can take that away.
[giggles]
[ACE]
Heh.
From now on, we're honest
to goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
[ALL]
Brothers!
[NARRATOR] The antics
of Luffy and his friends
began to test Dadan's patience,
and when Garp
unexpectedly pays a visit,
the situation becomes desperate.
Determined to stay
on their path,
the three boys must learn to
stand on their own two feet.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Leaving the Dadan
Family For Good?!
The Kids' Hideout
Has Been Built!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!