Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR]
After the battle with Duval
and the Flying Fish Riders,
the Straw Hat Pirates
continued their journey
toward Fishman Island.
Uh, so, do you
like them, Nami?
Listen. Don't think
I'm going to forgive you
'cause of something
silly like this.
Nooo!
No, of course not!
That's not what I meant!
I just wanted to know if ya
think it tastes good, honestly!
It's really delicious!
Nyuuuuu!
You think so?
Do you mean that?
There are actually
two separate routes
one can travel
to reach the New World.
But for outlaws
such as yourselves,
only one of them
is a viable option.
The passage you'll be taking,
ya don't have to
get rid of your ship.
And that passage is the
great Sea Floor Route,
straight through Fishman Island!
The Red Line may
be the most massive wall
in the whole world.
But it's not totally solid,
and there's one small hole
that passes through it.
And inside that hole
is Fishman Island!
[NARRATOR] In order to prepare
the Sunny to travel underwater,
Luffy and his crew set sail
for a certain island
not far out of the way.
[PAPPAGU]
This is it!
The Sabaody Archipelago!
[LUFFY]
So cool!
A bubble popped
out of the ground!
How weird is that?
[LUFFY]
I'm riding it!
Wow!
So, Hachi.
What's our objective
on this island anyway?
Nyuu!
We'll meet up with one of the
island's coating specialists
and have him slap a coat
of this resin on your ship.
That's all it takes.
After that, your ship
will be fully equipped
for underwater travel.
Seriously?
[NARRATOR] Intending to meet
with the coating mechanic
Hachi spoke of,
the Straw Hat Pirates set out to
explore the Sabaody Archipelago.
[LUFFY]
Tyranny!
The Rulers of Sabaody,
the Celestial Dragons!
Everyone else went to town.
Why didn't the
two of you go with them?
We used up a lot of cola
in that battle with Duval.
Damn near all of it.
It's my job to take
good care of the Sunny.
That's right.
And I like helping out with
all things ship-related, too.
Once we're done, all three
of us can head out together.
What do you say? Sound good?
[SANJI]
Sorry.
Thanks for the invite,
but I can't do my shopping
until a certain
someone comes back.
[USOPP]
Wait, what do you mean?
Well, you see...
...my beloved Nami was in a jam.
Now what to do?
We have a ton of
treasure on board,
and I can't leave the ship
knowing it's unguarded.
If only there was a
valiant knight around
to keep an eye on it.
That's me!
She's got you wrapped
around her finger, doesn't she?
[SANJI]
I am a slave to love!
[USOPP] You admitting it
saves me the trouble.
[USOPP]
Hey! Zoro!
[SANJI]
Zoro! Wait!
[USOPP and SANJI]
Where do you think you're going
all by yourself?
[ZORO]
For a walk. That okay?
[USOPP]
Of course not!
You're gonna get
yourself lost, moron!
This is an archipelago!
We won't be able to find you!
Screw you!
I'm not gonna get lost!
Only an idiot would get turned
around in a place like this!
All of these trees
have numbers on them, okay?
That way it doesn't matter how
bad your sense of direction is.
Whoa!
Nice job!
You actually put
some thought into this.
Yeah, good call!
All right, then! Have fun!
[USOPP] Ask for directions
if you get confused!
[SANJI]
Don't trust your instincts!
Screw these guys.
I'll be all right.
I just have to remember
the number on this tree.
And that number is one.
What, do they
think I can't count?
You'd have to be brain dead to
get lost in a place like this.
I'm not taking
anymore crap from them.
The World Nobles I mentioned
are also known as
the Celestial Dragons.
They think they're so much
better than everyone else
they wear masks to avoid
breathing the same air as us.
Now remember what I said:
No matter what they do,
just stay out of their way!
I need you to promise me that!
[LUFFY]
Uh-huh.
[HACHI]
Aside from that,
there are a couple
of other things
you should probably
keep an eye out for.
Remember, this is the
place everyone gathers
before heading to the New World.
In other words, like you,
there're a lot of big
name pirate crews around.
Which means marines and bounty
hunters are out to catch them.
[HACHI] Also, the law
won't protect pirates
from being bought and sold here.
Kidnapping happens all the time.
So try not to stand out.
If people realize
how much you're worth,
the whole island'll be on you
and we'll never
get the ship coated.
And fair warning, the marines
here aren't pushovers.
We're right by
Navy Headquarters,
so you never know which
powerhouses might show up.
The bounty hunters here
are pretty ferocious, too.
They're a lot tougher
than what you're used to.
Oh, yeah!
And one more thing.
Oh, come on!
We're gonna be just fine!
Hold on. When did you get
that wound on your head?
Huh? Oh, that.
Don't worry about it, okay?
And by the way, Camie isn't a
mermaid and I'm not a fishman.
Not while we're here, anyway.
Just pretend
we're humans like you.
What? Why would we do that?
[HACHI]
It'll just be easier that way.
When traveling,
it's best to honor the
local culture, Luffy.
Let's just do
what the octopus asks.
[BIKE SHOP GUY]
That's it. Slowly...
Look, I'm inside!
--Ooh, me next!
[ROBIN]
How mysterious!
[LUFFY] I can get
my whole body in here!
And none of the air
is coming out, either!
[BIKE SHOP GUY]
You ain't seen nothing yet!
Here, pull this thing
inside there with you.
Like this?
[BIKE SHOP GUY] As long
as you can reach the pedals,
you can drive it
around all over the place.
[LUFFY]
It's moving!
Cool!
[LUFFY laughing]
Here goes! Woohoo!
The bubble isn't breaking!
[BIKE SHOP GUY]
These Bubble Bikes
are the most convenient
way to get around
--the Sabaody Archipelago.
--[CHOPPER] Come back!
--They're affordable, too!
--Let me ride it!
[BIKE SHOP GUY] They rent
for 500 berries a person,
but you can own it for
only 10,000 berries.
So how about it?
We'll just rent one.
[LUFFY]
Wait!
I got the money.
I'm gonna buy one!
Me, too! Me, too!
Nyuu, no you don't.
There's no point
in buying, just rent it.
It's my money;
I'll do what I want!
Yeah! So there!
Well, uh...
Look, take my word for it.
I'll explain everything later.
Two rentals, please!
I take it you're a local, then?
Such a shame, such a shame.
Wow! This is fantastic!
I love it!
Feels great, doesn't it?
There are all
different kinds, too.
Suddenly, I have
the urge to sing!
♪ Yohohoho!
You can't stop me.
I'm gonna buy one of these!
Listen, Straw Hat.
Think back to when you rode
that bubble up into the sky
right after we got here.
Do you remember
what happened to it?
Uh, yeah!
I hopped on a bubble, flew up
past the tops of the trees,
and tried to jump around to
other ones to go even higher.
[LUFFY]
But outta nowhere,
all the bubbles around me
started popping.
And the one I was
riding on popped, too.
[LUFFY]
And then I fell down.
[HACHI]
That happened because you left
the Sabaody Archipelago's
unique atmosphere.
This area has a distinct
climate specifically suited
to the Hustle Muscle Mangroves.
Once you leave that climate,
the resin in the
bubbles starts to change.
Not long after that, they pop.
Really?
That means someone
would only be able
to ride one
of these bubbles
if they stayed
in this area, correct?
Yeah.
See, you get it.
People who come here
for the first time
are always eager
to buy a bubble bike.
Since they only work here,
it's a rip-off.
Just renting one
is all you really need.
I don't care!
I wanna buy one!
All I heard was "blah,
blah, blah, bubble bike".
How many ways do we have
to spell it out for you?
Once you leave this island, the
bubbles aren't strong enough.
They just pop.
It's quite the
mystery, isn't it?
Whoa, what the hell?
They're "Mystery Bubbles"?
Why didn't you say so before?
[NAMI] We did!
Why don't you ever listen?
Oh.
You can use bubble bikes on
Fishman Island too, if you like.
The ocean floor has
the same kind of bubbles.
You'll love it.
[LUFFY] Ooh, I can't wait
to get to Fishman Island!
It's gonna be awesome!
In that case,
you should meet
the Mermaid Princess!
So graceful. So beautiful.
Sometimes...
It's all you can do
to not stare at her!
Yohoho!
I look forward to it!
I have an excellent eye
for appreciating beauty.
Though, being a skeleton,
I don't actually have any eyes.
Yohohohoho!
Do you get it?
[LUFFY] Whoa!
That stuff looks yummy!
[CHOPPER]
What's a "Graman"?
They're Grand Line Steamed Buns!
They're called
"Gra-man" for short.
Care to try a sample?
As you can see,
it's got "Grand Line
First Half" written into it.
They're meant to be a
souvenir to return home with.
Shelf life's three months.
Plenty of time
to make it back with them.
[BROOK]
Delicious!
Would it be all right if I
sampled another box or two?
Aren't you gonna buy any?
[ROBIN]
Grove 35.
There seem to be a lot
of hotels around here.
Those are the living
quarters of the sailors
who're waiting for permission
to pass through Mariejois.
Building all these hotels
is easier than you'd think.
See?
They simply coat the giant soap
bubbles with a metal alloy,
and voila!
Instant foundation!
That's how all the round
buildings are made!
Wow!
[NAMI]
Robin! A mall!
I bet they have all sorts
of stuff--let's check it out!
Stop by anytime!
Grachoco and Grackers, too!
A keychain!
And a pennant!
Hold onto those
precious memories!
You guys bought
a lot of stuff!
It'll be tough to carry
all that junk around.
Go have him bubble pack
it up for you.
What's a bubble pack?
Awesome!
It's so light!
Carrying around stuff
in this place is super easy!
[CHOPPER]
Hey.
Where are Robin and Nami?
Don't worry about them.
They went to the
shopping mall on Grove 30.
They said that they
wanted to leave
the coating
of the ship to us.
[LUFFY]
Oh yeah?
Right! Leave it to us, then!
So where are we
headed next, Hachi?
We're going to Grove 31.
Even by bike, it's a long trip.
So we should prob'ly get moving.
[ROBIN] I wonder
why Camie didn't join us.
We invited her.
Yeah, she's been
sort of nervous and quiet
ever since we
got here, hasn't she?
Something's bothering her,
but I don't know what.
Perhaps it's Sabaody itself.
There could be a "bad history"
tied to the island.
A "bad history", huh?
[yelling]
[LUFFY chuckling]
[HACHI]
Nyuu!
We're going so fast!
Hey! Straw Hat!
Where'd you go?
[LUFFY]
Right over here!
[HACHI]
Oh yeah?! Nyuuuuu!
Yeah!
I'm winning,
I'm winning, I'm winning!
Don't get so cocky!
We've still got
a long way to go!
Yeah, keep it up!
You can do it, Hachin!
What the heck is
wrong with you guys?
When did this turn
into some kind of race?
[yelling, cheering]
Oh! I'm so sorry!
Wait! What are you--
No! I didn't mean to!
Stop it, please!
[BIG MAN]
You gotta help me!
I'm begging you!
Get it off!
Get this thing off of me!
I just...
I just wanna leave!
I just wanna go back home!
[CROWD murmuring]
Hey. What's all
that yelling about?
[CROWD screaming]
Anybody! Please!
Get me outta this damn thing!
Bring me something!
Somebody bring me a damn tool!
An axe, a saw, something
to get this thing off of me!
All I want is to go back home!
I don't wanna hurt anybody!
Please, sir.
Let go. Don't kill me.
I give up!
I don't wanna go to the
New World anymore!
Please! I've got a wife
and kid back home!
I'm begging you here!
Somebody help me!
My little boy...
I left when he was just a baby.
He doesn't even know
what I look like!
Help me, please!
Who's that?
[BIG MAN]
I wanna go home!
That's all that matters now!
I won't hurt you!
Let's stay out of this.
He's probably just some pirate
who was caught by kidnappers
and sold into slavery.
His owner must've
brought him to this island
and then he made a run for it.
But he must know
what happens to slaves
who try to get away!
[ticking noise]
[CROWD screaming]
What's that sound?
Why's he ticking?
[BIG MAN]
This collar!
If I could only get
this thing off my neck!
Stop it! Please!
Stop ticking!
Damn it! Damn it!
Get off me!
[CROWD screaming]
Help me...
Every slave has one
of those metal collars
put around their neck.
And if they try to take it off
or run from their master,
it'll explode.
Just let me go
home to my family.
I don't wanna be a pirate
in the New World anymore.
[CROWD screaming]
[RANDOM SCARED MAN 391A] It's
a slave that tried to escape!
[RANDOM SCARED MAN 391B]
Everybody stay back!
Ignore him!
I can't believe
what just happened!
We have to help!
Idiot! You guys promised
not to get involved
no matter what, remember?
What's with this crazy place?
What're we gonna do, Hatchin?
The Celestial Dragons
will be here any minute!
[HACHI]
It's all right.
Just stay calm, Camie.
Listen, Straw Hat.
You need to get off
that bubble bike.
What for?
Hurry up and do it!
Fine. Just this once.
They're here!
That's not a dragon.
[HACHI]
Bow down!
Aw, but why?
No matter what happens,
don't look them in the eye!
Same goes for you guys!
[BROOK and CHOPPER]
Right!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Salu!
Come now! Don't be vulgar!
Those are Dragons?
Yeah.
Oh, look, father.
Another one of our
slaves has broken down.
Did you give it
its daily sedative
like you were supposed to?
Of course I did.
But it seems it had no
effect on this poor fool.
I don't even
want it anymore.
Would you buy me a new one?
[WOMAN'S FATHER]
Honestly!
You're terrible
at taking care of them.
You're decimating my precious
ship captain collection
one pirate at a time!
[WOMAN]
It was useless to begin with!
"Family!" "Children!"
Stop crying!
Pathetic! You're nothing
but a lowly human slave!
He can't even move.
You make me want to vomit.
[gunshots]
You--
Calm down!
Control yourself!
[WOMAN] I think I'd like
a giant for my next slave.
[WOMAN'S FATHER]
Perhaps something smaller,
like a human child.
[WOMAN]
Ugh, I detest the weak ones.
Whatever you're thinking,
don't think about it.
[CHOPPER]
The Marines!
We need to get the
hell away from here, fast.
Would you care for some tea?
It'll calm your nerves.
I feel terrible.
Thanks, though.
[LUFFY] You think
he's gonna be all right?
Maybe so, but If he lives,
he'll go to prison for piracy.
I don't understand!
An old man and a woman are no
match for a pirate like that!
What's going on here?
If anyone hurts
a Celestial Dragon,
Navy Headquarters
sends an admiral
and a fleet of battle ships
to handle the situation.
An admiral?
You mean Aokiji?
It could be him,
or Akainu, or Kizaru.
No telling which one
of them will show up.
Remember, we're right by HQ.
What makes those
Celestial Dragons so special?
The Dragons are
from the bloodline
of the creators of
the World Government.
Are you serious?
800 years ago,
a group of twenty kings
came together to create
the organization
that's now known as
the World Government.
The Celestial Dragons
are their descendants.
As the years go by,
generation after generation,
they grow more and more
reckless with power.
Celestial Dragons.
[BOUNTY HUNTER 391A]
It's him.
[BOUNTY HUNTER 391B]
Yeah, Straw Hat Luffy.
[BOUNTY HUNTER 391B] With a
bounty of 300 million berries!
[CHOPPER]
Shakky's Rip-Off Bar?
[SHAKKY] Welcome,
Monkey D. Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Wait, you've heard of me?
[SHAKKY] A man with a
300-million berry bounty
has quite the reputation.
But there's another rookie
visiting the archipelago
with an even higher bounty.
[CHOPPER] He's worth
even more than Luffy?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"New Rivals Gather!
The 11 Supernovas!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!