Eheheh!
Ah!
So, how much do you think
the repairs are gonna cost?
We've got plenty
of money to spend.
And no price is too
high for our Merry!
Her battle scars are
far worse than you think.
Uhm... Then you're
saying it's gonna
take a long time
for you to fix her?
No, Ma'am. It's
not about the time,
it's not about skill, either.
I'm saying no one can
fix her. Not even us.
No way.
We... We've gone everywhere
without any problems until now!
In theory, even if we
did everything we could.
The probability of your ship
lasting till the next island...
[gulps]
[KAKU]
...is zero.
Merry tell me.
Is what he said true?
You'll never sail again?
This sucks.
I'm sorry, Sanji.
I was so focused
on the books
that I didn't
notice when she left.
There's nothing you
should have to apologize for.
I just assumed that the
person I saw walking with Robin
had to have been you
in your human form.
Which begs the question:
"Who was that masked man?
And how were they able
to disappear so suddenly?"
Yeah. Even Robin's
scent disappeared.
I hope everything's
all right. I feel uneasy.
Do you need an examination?
No! That's not what I meant!
It's what Aokiji said.
His words keep repeating.
What did he say
that worries you?
It was all that terrible stuff
he said about Robin's past.
And that very soon we'd
regret her being on our crew.
Oh yeah, right. So do you
think what he said might
have had something to do
with her disappearance?
I don't know.
But I know we're getting
nowhere looking for her.
Let's head back
to the ship for now.
If nothing's wrong,
she'll come back on
her own eventually.
Yeah, you're right.
[SANJI]
Hurry back to the Merry.
What? You can't fix the
Going Merry? Why not?!
I thought all of
you were supposed
to be awesome shipwrights!
Don't worry about the money!
Look! We've got plenty!
[KAKU] It's not
about the money, son.
No matter how much you pay.
That ship can't be restored
to how she used to be.
To be honest,
I'm rather impressed
you were able
to get that ol' girl this
far considering the condition
that she's currently in.
What's that supposed to mean?
What exactly is going
on with the Merry?
Do you know what the
"keel" is, Immoral Girl?
[NAMI]
Immor--?!
The thing at the
bottom of the boat?
Yeah.
It's the most important
piece of lumber on a ship.
It crosses from stem to
stern and provides support.
When you build a ship, you
start off by placing the keel.
Then, you set the wood for
the stem, the stern, the frame,
frame brackets, and deck beams.
All of the pieces are
carefully assembled together,
with the keel
serving as the core.
It's the very
backbone, framework,
and life of every
vessel constructed.
And when it's severely damaged,
then that's the end of her.
You can't just replace
it with a new one.
That would be the same thing
as building a new
ship from scratch.
That's the reason we, or anyone,
won't be able to fix her.
Your ship's just a bunch of wood
stuck together awaiting her end.
Hey, you! Don't say
such horrible things!
Horrible or not,
it's the truth.
Okay, fine then!
Just rebuild her from the
ground up, like you said before!
Build another Going Merry!
Coo coo! Sorry, not possible!
Why not?
We could build you
a very similar ship.
But no one could build you one
that would be exactly the same.
Nowhere in the world are there
two completely identical ships.
It simply can't be done.
What do you mean? Why?
Tell me, are there
any trees in the world
that grow exactly the same way?
Huh?
A sailing ship is mostly
built out of lumber.
So the overall size
and shape of a vessel
is determined by
the type of wood used.
That's why an exact duplicate
of your ship can't be built
by us or anyone, even when
using the same blueprints.
If we made a ship like that,
with those specifications.
The ones who would
notice the difference
and feel that it's a
completely different ship
would be all of
you guys! Coo coo!
No way. So, you're saying
it's absolutely impossible
for us to continue
sailing on the Going Merry?
Unfortunately, yes.
You can either wait
around for her to sink.
Or you can dismantle
her immediately.
[NAMI]
A real caravel!
[LUFFY]
What a cool ship!
Have you guys seen the front?
It's totally awesome!
Okay! It's all done!
Now the Going Merry
has everything she
could possibly need!
[ICEBERG] Mmwell, your
ship is on her last legs.
Why don't you look at
this as an opportunity?
You happen to be in the
best place in the world
to buy a new ship.
You have money, right?
I understand that
your ship was a caravel.
Sailing on the Grand Line
in an old ship like that
would be difficult
to begin with.
No way. We're not
getting a new ship.
[NAMI]
Luffy...
The Merry is...
The Going Merry is the ship
of the Straw Hat pirates!
If she's repaired,
then she can still sail!
She'll be fine! You'll see!
She got us here
today, didn't she?
And you tell us out of nowhere
she can't sail anymore?
I can't believe that! I won't!
You guys are saying that
because you don't know her.
You have no idea
how strong she is!
Then your plan is to keep
sailing her until she sinks?
I'm shocked.
So, this is the decision
of a ship's captain?!
This discussion is over
for now. Just think about it.
If you decide to buy
a ship, let me know.
My people can help.
If you're able to
spend 300 million,
we can build a state-of-the-art
ship for you. Kalifa!
Here, if you'd look
this over, please.
It's a catalogue of our
new and our used models.
Use it as a price reference.
Hey, Iceberg!
There's someone at the front
gate who wants to see you.
There doesn't
seem to be anyone
on your appointment
schedule for today.
It looks like those World
Government Officials again.
Should I tell them
you're unavailable?
Mmwell, yes please.
Say I'm gone.
By the way, Lulu. You've got
quite a case of bed-head.
Oops! How embarrassing!
My apologies.
Anyway, I'll ask them to leave.
Uh, thanks! I appreciate it!
[CORGY] Hold it
right there, Iceberg!
[CORGY] Looks like
you're here after all!
Hey! You two need to hide!
Government Officials are here!
What? Uh, okay.
Mmwell, hello again, Corgy!
As you can see,
I'm not here today.
[CORGY] Yes, you are!
Come now! I've come all the
way out here by Sea Train.
Don't turn me away.
It's impolite!
[sniffs]
For some reason,
I detect the scent of pirates.
Whatever, in any case,
I want to talk to you.
I don't like you! Go away!
Are you a child?
Nuh-uh. I'm totally an adult.
Then start acting like one.
There's something of
special importance
I need to discuss with you.
I would appreciate it
if you would hear me out.
Come, let's talk
this over in private.
Those Government guys
are so damn persistent.
What the hell do they
want with Iceberg, anyway?
Look, it has
nothing to do with us.
Probably political
stuff. Coo coo!
[LULU]
Should I beat them up?
I wouldn't, I mean they're
Government guys, after all.
What? What's wrong?
Something seemed
weird about these bags
when I grabbed them.
They're really light.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Oh, come on!
Stop kidding around!
How could they be with
all of that money inside?
[loud screams]
Hey. Who's that?
What's with the screaming?
Idiots! What
the hell are you--
Hey, lady! If you sit like
that, everyone can see your--
[NAMI]
Don't tell me. There's no way!
[LUFFY]
I don't wanna look!
200 million!!
Gone! It's really gone!
Wait! Look at these bags!
They're not even ours!
[LUFFY and NAMI scream]
[LUFFY]
Wh-Wh-What are we gonna do?
Hey, hey! Keep it down!
What's wrong?
Our money. Our money's gone!
Vanished! Gone! Disappeared!
[PAULIE]
What?!
Paulie! Was it you again?!
Huh? No!
Honest?
[PAULIE]
Why would I lie?
[HATTORI]
You mean it?
They're so noisy.
Hey Kaku, question for ya?
Why were you hanging out with
the Franky Family earlier?
What are you talking about?
I haven't been anywhere
near a single member
of the Franky Family all day.
That's strange. Huh.
I was so certain that
I saw your long nose.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on a sec!
That's Usopp!
You saw him with
the Franky Family?!
Well, you could
say he was with them.
Or maybe you could say
he was being dragged away.
That's called kidnapping!
Luffy! We gotta find him!
[LUFFY]
Right!
[NAMI] Hey! Hold on!
Where are you going to look?
Wait for me, Usopp!
Wait for me, money!
I'm coming!
Hey! Where can I find the
Franky Family's hideout?
It's not really a hideout.
It's more like a workshop.
From where your ship is docked,
it's way up the seashore
to the northeast.
It's off by itself.
You can't miss it.
It's called the Franky House.
[NAMI] Luffy! Luffy!
What was he thinking?
There's no way he
could find Usopp
in this place all by himself.
I can't keep looking
for him right now.
Before I do anything else,
I need to take this
money back to the ship.
If I march in there demanding
our 200 million back
while holding 100 million,
I'd be asking them to
steal that money, too.
Yagara, please take
me to the bull shop!
Shortest route possible!
I'll take Zoro and the others
with me and teach them a lesson!
Stealing from pirates?
Franky Family, that makes
you the lowest of the low!
[ELEVATOR GIRL A] First Floor:
Backstreet Shopping District.
Please proceed with caution.
Thank you and
have a wonderful day.
Hurry! I'm counting on you!
What's her problem?
Hey! Watch where you're going!
I'm sorry, Sir!
[thinking] I hope Usopp was
able to escape from them...
...somehow...
[CITIZEN AA]
This is terrible!
[CITIZEN II]
Where's this guy from?
[CITIZEN U] Hey! Does
anybody know him? Who is he?
What's with them? Yagara, wait!
Hold on a second! Stop! Stop!
[NAMI]
Usopp!
Hey! Say something!
Are you all right?
Open your eyes! Usopp!
Hey! Usopp! Wake up!
Excuse me. But are you
two pirates by any chance?
Shut up! Stop staring
and mind your own business!
Oh, no. Usopp,
who did this to you?
Was it the Franky Family?
It was. It happened
because I'm weak.
They took... They took
all of the money.
[USOPP]
Nami...
Huh?
How can I face the others now?
We were finally
able to fix the Merry.
I'm so ashamed.
Dammit!
Usopp, I understand.
Don't worry about the money.
We'll get it back together.
[thinking] He's been
beaten pretty badly.
I probably shouldn't move him.
[NAMI]
Look. Stay right here, okay?
I'm gonna go back to the ship
to get the others
to come and help.
Chopper will have you fixed
up good as new in no time.
And listen, don't worry about
the stolen money, all right?
From what I've heard,
their hideout
isn't too far away from here.
We'll crush them and that'll
be the end of it. Okay?
Hey! You think this is
some kind of show? Get lost!
Stay put, okay? I'm going
to you some get help.
I'll be right back!
Hurry, Yagara! Go faster!
[OLD GUY A]
A runaway bull!
We were finally
able to fix the Merry.
No matter how much you pay.
That ship can't be restored
to how she used to be.
[thinking] Whether we decide
to give in and buy a new ship
or we have someone else manage
to fix and improve the Merry.
If we don't put the entire
300 million into this,
our future journeys together
will be difficult, for sure.
We need that money.
All of it!
We have to get it back!
What? Is that true?
[ZORO] Well, that's
what the shipwright said.
This ship.
It can't be fixed?
Even if we have money?
Then... Then what's going
to happen to the Merry?
Beats me.
Honestly, it really
just depends on how Luffy
and the others react after
hearing the assessment.
Either way, I'm sure
they'll get it sorted out
while they're
at the shipyard.
It just seems so extreme!
I mean, look at her!
Same old Merry that
she's always been.
We've traveled
together on this ship
all the way from the East Blue
to this place! Why now?
You just answered
your own question.
Human beings become stronger
hardship after hardship.
But ships are different.
Their wounds just pile up.
[SANJI]
It's so hard to accept.
And what is Usopp gonna say
when he hears about all of this?
[CHOPPER] I don't wanna
leave her! I love the Merry!
I know, we all do.
But her wounds are too deep.
There's nothing we can do.
[SANJI] The Merry's in trouble
and Robin's still missing.
I'm worried about both of them.
[NAMI]
Hey! Everyone!
Look! It's Nami,
and she's alone.
[SANJI] Hmm?
That's weird.
I wonder what happened
to Luffy and Usopp.
Hi, Nami!
Is everything all right?
[FRANKY]
Ow! Ow! Ow! 200 million?!
[FRANKY FAMILY]
Yes! 200 million!
What do you think, bro?
Awesome, right?
[FRANKY] Incredible!
You guys are amazing!
Now that we have
this much money
we'll be able to get
what we've always wanted!
We actually did it, didn't we?
After three years,
our perseverance
has finally paid off!
I'm stoked!
[FRANKY]
Me, too!
Every time we'd
have a little money
we'd bet it all
on the Yagara races.
And lose every time!
Each time we'd collect
a criminal's bounty,
we'd party and drink!
And spend it all!
We could never ever save up
the 200 million
berries that we needed.
Until now! We finally
have enough to get it done!
[FRANKY] And then some.
You guys did a hell of a job!
[cheers]
[FRANKY] Now then.
I know it isn't much,
but here's 5 million berries
to show you how grateful I am.
Eat, drink, and have a blast!
Hahaha! That's our bro!
Party time!
[RANDOM A]
What the hell?!
Huh?
What was that?!
Show yourself!
What fool would dare to
oppose the Franky Family?!
Huh? It's that weakling
we ran into earlier!
How did you manage
to even stand up?
Give us our money back!
[FRANKY] "Give us our
money back," you say?
Hmm, does that mean
you're one of the Straw Hats?
That's right, bro!
He totally is!
I was expecting all
of the Straw Hat crew
to be really strong,
but this one's not at all!
Hahahaha!
Yeah, he's a complete
weakling! What a joke!
Mind your own damn business!
[FRANKY]
Whoops!
[jeers]
What's he doing?
[FRANKY]
You've got some guts trying
to take back the
money all by yourself.
But I'm afraid
I can't let you have it.
Give it back!
We need the money...
...to fix the Merry!
Her scars are deep.
That's our money.
It's to heal her wounds,
understand me?!
You can't have it!
Give it back to me right now!
♪ ending song ♪
[USOPP]
Give it back!
[LUFFY]
Usopp!
[USOPP]
Give me back that money!
[LUFFY]
Chopper! How is he?
[CHOPPER]
He's hurt pretty badly,
but I know he's
gonna be all right.
I'll find a way
to save him somehow!
[LUFFY] Right. Hang in there,
Usopp! Don't worry.
We're gonna wipe that
house right off the map!
On the next One Piece :
"Rescuing Our Friend!
Raid on the Franky House."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!