There's a... There's a
frog doing the front crawl!
[LUFFY]
What?
See for yourself!
It's headed to your side!
Really?
Come on, Luffy.
Are you really
gonna take anything
that goofy Admiral
told you seriously?
There's no way a frog
would do the front crawl.
It's... HOLY CRAP!
THERE'S A FROG DOING
THE FRONT CRAWL!
Come on! After him!
[ZORO, USOPP, and CHOPPER]
Aye-aye!
Now what's a lighthouse
doing way out here?
I wonder if anyone lives there.
[ZORO, USOPP, LUFFY and CHOPPER]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
[LUFFY]
It's flying!!
Quick! Don't let it get away!
Let's get up ahead of it
and block its course!
I guess we ran
ashore or something!
Huh?
What is that sound?
[bell clanging]
[distant whistle blow]
[bell clanging and
chugging noises]
[NAMI]
Full reverse! Right now!
Turn 180 degrees!
[whistle blow]
What the hell is that?!
Turn the ship around! Now!
[NAMI]
Hurry!
Aaaah!
Ahh!
AAAAAAHH!
[LUFFY]
Whoa! That was close!
[USOPP] That hunk of
metal's trying to kill us!
[CHOPPER]
Is it a ship?
No way! Something
that big and heavy
shouldn't even
be able to float!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Get out of the way!
[growls]
Oh no! Froggy!
It looked like it was
spitting out smoke!
[CHIMNEY]
Pirates?
Granny! Granny!
Look! We got pirates!
[KOKORO] What?
Izzat true, Chimney?!
Okey dokey then, in that case.
Better bring Granny
the Transponder Snail!
It's gonna be big pain
if they call for help
and the marines show up.
What should we do?
[CHIMNEY]
Here it is, Granny!
[KOKORO]
Uhm... hello?
Who is this?
Sorry, you got the wrong number.
She's totally drunk!
[KOKORO]
Oh! Paille, huh?
That stuff goes
good with booze!
[CHIMNEY]
Mm-mm! Yummy!
My name's Chimney.
This is our kitty cat, Gonbe
and that's Granny Kokoro.
You fellas wouldn't happen
to be train robbers, would ya?
Wahahaha!
My name's Luffy and I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates.
Really?
Yep.
Hahahaha!
I like you, you're funny!
By the way, Chimney. That
thing's a steam boat, right?
Seems awfully long to me.
Can't imagine it
getting very far.
[CHIMNEY chuckles]
You've probably never
seen anything like this.
Seeing as it's the
only one in the world.
It's not a steam boat,
it's a sea train
called the Puffing Tom.
[NAMI]
How does it work?
It uses a steam engine to turn
its paddlewheels
and run on a railway.
Railway?
[CHIMNEY]
Uh-huh! If you look close,
you can see the tracks
right below the waves.
The train goes the
same route every day,
taking people from
one island to the next.
It carries ships and
packages and other stuff, too.
Oh wow, funny we
didn't notice it before.
No kidding,
we ran right into it.
You should be more careful!
Didn't you see the signal?
There's a bell
ringing and everything!
Is that what that thing is for?
I thought it was just
here to welcome us.
How were we supposed to know?!
And if we couldn't figure it out
then that frog sure
wouldn't get it, would he?
It was awful rude of
you to hit him like that.
We were gonna catch him
and cook him, you know.
Oh, you saw the frog?
That's Yokozuna.
[LUFFY]
He sure was an awesome swimmer.
[CHIMNEY] Either way,
I wouldn't worry about him,
he's pretty tough.
In fact, that
wasn't the first time
he's challenged
the train and lost.
He's really kind of a pain.
If you want to see him again,
just hang around here
and I'm sure he'll pop up.
That's why he didn't run.
Wow, I thought
that frog was stupid,
but it turns out he was
just being super manly.
[CHIMNEY]
Easy for you to say!
You don't have to put up
with him all the time!
I can't even count
how many times
he's broken the rail guard.
And just imagine what it's like
for the passengers when
he slams into the train!
That's pretty crazy.
Okay, since that
frog's a fighter like me,
I'm not gonna eat him after all!
Who would want to eat that
gross thing in the first place?
Anyways, after this, where're
you folks headed off to?
The sea train runs
to all sorts of places.
There's the town of the
Spring Queen, St. Poplar.
There's the gourmet town, Pucci
or the Carnival town, San Faldo.
They're all fun places to go.
And if you happen to
work for the government,
you can take a special train
that's even fancier
than the Puffing Tom.
The gourmet town, Pucci?
Oh! That's the place
those people we met
on the island
were talking about.
[LUFFY]
Hey! You're right!
Good, then that's the
place we're gonna g--
Give it up!
Thanks, but there's no reason
for us to take the train
when we have our own ship.
We'll just follow the log.
Oh? Where's it pointing to?
Should be someplace
east of here.
I see. Well, in that case
it's Water Seven for sure.
The train you saw
on the way here
just came from
Blue Station on that island.
They call it
the City of Water.
I think you'll like it!
Water Seven, huh?
They got great shipyards.
You might say that's
their claim to fame.
When it comes to boats,
they're first class!
They're always
coming up with some
fancy new technology to build
boats for the World Government.
Whoa, then they must have
some awesome shipwrights, too!
[KOKORO] Some? More like
damn near all of 'em!
City's like a regular
shipwright's convention!
Ah! You hear that?!
Yeah!
All right then. It's settled!
We're gonna find the best
shipwright in Water Seven
and get him to join our crew!
Oh, is that so?
In that case, hold on a sec.
Upsey-daisy, you can do it.
Where's she going?
Dunno.
I got a present for ya.
This is a little map of the
city and a reference letter.
Just give this to a
fella named Iceberg,
and I promise he'll
fix yer ship up good.
Water Seven's a
pretty confusing place,
be sure not to get lost.
You have a big
heart, don't you?!
We really owe you one!
[CHIMNEY] We'll be heading
back to Water Seven soon,
so maybe we'll see you there.
[KOKORO]
Sounds like a plan to me!
And if you like,
I can even give you folks
a tour of all my
favorite drinkin' holes!
Ha ha ha!
Sounds good! We'll try
to keep a look out for you!
It'll take 'bout a
week for the Log
to lock onto the next island,
so you'll have plenty of
time to do some sightseeing!
[LUFFY]
Great! Should be fun!
[LUFFY] Okay! Everyone
ready?! Time to set sail!
[CREW]
Yeah!
Thanks again for the map
and reference letter.
I sure am glad we
ran into you on the way!
[CHIMNEY]
Have a safe trip!
Better keep an eye out
for all those government
types down there!
[LUFFY]
Yahoo! Let's go!
City of Meat,
here we come!
[USOPP] Did you forget
where we're going already?
[NAMI]
What a nice wind!
We might make it
out to Water Seven
even faster than I thought!
I'll be happy either way!
[SANJI] Don't worry
about finding a shipwright.
I got it all under control.
I'll get the hottest girl
in town, guaranteed.
What do I care if
the shipwright's hot?!
I want a huge, manly dude--like
even bigger than a bear!
16 feet tall!
A guy that size couldn't
even fit on the ship!
And who knows how much
food he would need to eat!
All that matters is
that he's good at his job.
If you ask me, the
real problem's gonna be
finding someone crazy enough
to go sailing with
a bunch of pirates.
Size doesn't matter!
I'm just glad we're
gonna make a new friend!
We're lucky we ran into
that train station on the way.
This map should be a big help!
All we have to do is
follow Kokoro's directions
to that Iceberg guy
and we're set!
I see.
Stupid drunk!
Whoa, looks like Luffy's art.
Okay, let's try to
find a shipwright
that looks
something like this!
If I saw a guy
like that, I'd run.
I wouldn't just run,
I'd jump into the sea to
get away from that freak.
But he looks like he
might be part-octopus,
so even that
might not save me.
Don't you have anything
better to talk about?
[NAMI] Okay everybody, since
we're gonna be at Water Seven
for a whole week, let me
give you your allowance.
[CHOPPER] Ooh! Me first!
Me first! Ah! Stop shoving!
[sounds of arguing]
[LUFFY and USOPP]
Allowance! Alowance! Allowance!
[LUFFY] Why're you hugging
the ship, Usopp?
I know all these tin plates
might not look like much to you,
but they bring back a lot
of fond memories for me.
I almost hate to see them go,
but it'll all be worth it
if the Merry can finally
get the repairs she needs!
[SANJI]
I feel the same way.
I'm proud of her battle
scars like anyone else,
but she's taken a real beating
since we've entered
the Grand Line.
The deck squeaks and we've got
leaks popping up everywhere.
Nobody wants to admit it,
but if we don't fix this soon,
we're as good as sunk.
[LUFFY] Yeah, but even if
we can't get a shipwright
for the crew, we still
have plenty of money!
We can do more
than just fix her;
we can power her up, too!
[USOPP] Ooh!
Then let's get more cannons!
[LUFFY]
Yeah! And a big statue!
[ZORO]
Hey, I think we're there.
Huh?
[LUFFY] He's right!
I can see Water Seven!
[LUFFY]
All right men, time to row!
[SANJI]
The wind's enough.
Don't wear us out
before we even get there.
Lovely.
Wow.
[LUFFY] Nobody told me
it was gonna be this cool!
[LUFFY] Whoa!
Check that thing out!
I didn't know they
made fountains that big!
OHHH!
That's nuts! I've never
seen anything like it!
And I thought the
sea train was a big deal.
Oh, wow. That's a lot of water!
Do you think it all
comes from the ocean?
That's what it seems like.
Then it pours out
of the fountain,
goes through the canals
and falls back into the sea.
Hey! Once we get there,
let's have a race on
those water slides!
Water slides?
I think I'll pass.
Even if that was a water slide,
you still can't swim.
Oh, good point.
By the way,
do you have any idea
what those numbers mean?
[USOPP]
Hmm... Good question.
[SANJI] They look like walls but
they could be some kinda gate.
Duh, those are
special entrances
where all the 16-foot
shipwrights go in.
How many of those guys do you
think there are out there?!
At any rate, that's
the station up front.
[NAMI] Must be the same one
Kokoro was talking about.
Still, I wonder
where the harbor's at?
Inside the town, maybe?
[FISHERMAN A]
Hey! Hold on!
Pirates shouldn't
sail in the front,
you gotta be more discreet!
Use the backstreet entrance
over there, instead!
[NAMI]
Oh, okay! Thank you!
Whoa. Look,
there's so many boats!
Awesome! The city's floating!
I wonder how it works?!
[CHOPPER] But everything's
flooded everywhere!
Aren't all the buildings
gonna be full of water, too?
Not at all. The houses
here were built
with a submerged
foundation in mind.
[CHOPPER]
Hmm?
If you look beneath the
walkway, you'll understand.
[CHOPPER]
You're right!
It's like the city's
sitting on stilts!
I see. Certainly
lives up to its name.
Hey, hurry up! Dock the ship!
Whoa, hold on a sec!
What do you pirates think
you're doing here in town?!
You're not looking to
plunder, now are you?
Nuh-uh! We just wanna
get our ship repaired!
[USOPP] He just asks that
like it's no big deal?
In that case there's a
little cape just ahead of here.
Anchor your ship
over there for now!
[NAMI]
Okay!
[LUFFY]
Thanks for the help!
[USOPP]
They keep waving us off.
[ZORO] Of course they do.
We're flying a pirate flag.
[USOPP] Should be okay
to anchor here, right?
[SANJI]
Can't see why not.
It's certainly far
enough from the city.
[LUFFY]
Works for me! Furl the sail!
[CREW cries out in surprise]
AAHHH!
Are you trying to
break the ship?!
No!! All I did was pull
the rope like I always do!
Holy crap! If the Merry's
falling apart this easy
we're lucky we
made it here at all!
By the way, they're not scared
of pirates here, are they?
Don't you think
that's kinda strange?
It's cause we're shipyard
customers just like anyone else.
Stop yapping and start
fixing the ship already!
They probably aren't
concerned about pirates
because they have enough
security to deal with them
if they misbehave.
Bet there's plenty
of Marines here, too.
Comes with the territory, huh?
What, are you kidding me?!
You mean they're gonna
have us arrested?!
I don't think
that'll be a problem,
since we're paying
customers and all.
[USOPP]
I guess so.
[LUFFY and USOPP] Well, that
settles it! We'll see you later!
Hold on one minute, you two!
[NAMI]
I need you to come with me
to take care of some business.
What business?
First off, we're going to
take Kokoro's reference letter
to this Iceberg guy--assuming
we can find him.
Hopefully, he'll be
able to take care of
the Merry's repairs for us.
After that, we'll
have to find a place
where we can trade in
our gold for some Berries.
[LUFFY]
Okeydokey. Works for me!
So what are
we waiting for?
Let's go! To Water Seven!
[NAMI] Okay, but aren't
you forgetting the gold?
[USOPP] Try to have that mast
fixed before we get back, Zoro!
[SANJI] Be careful out
there, Nami, Sweet!
Aww! It looks like I missed
my chance to go with them.
You can go with me
later, if you like.
Really?! Can we
go to a bookstore?
Yes, of course.
[USOPP] Maybe we should trade in
the gold before anything else.
That's boring. I wanna
go to the shipyard.
It might not matter to you,
but I'd feel nervous
walking around a crowded city,
dragging a giant bag
of treasure behind me.
If we trade it, we'll still
be dragging Berries around.
I know, but it'll
be a lot smaller,
so people won't
notice it as much.
I mean, what if we
run into thieves?!
[LUFFY]
Ha! We are thieves!
Well, that's true
but if we cash it in,
you won't be the only
one carrying the money.
I don't know if
I like the sound of that.
It's almost like you don't
want me taking care of the gold!
Yep! Only you could
lose that much gold!
He already forgot
it once today.
[LUFFY] You guys don't
trust me, your own captain?!
[NAMI and USOPP]
Nope!
[LUFFY] Awww... Hey, that
really hurts my feelings!
I don't know if
I can keep sailing
with a crew that...
Wait, what's that?
[NAMI]
Huh. That's funny.
Is that the only
entrance to the city?
What's a rental bull shop?
[LUFFY]
Beats me.
Obviously they must
rent out something.
Yeah, but what's a bull?
I dunno like a bulldog?
That can't be right.
[LUFFY] Excuse me!
We'd like to rent some bulls!
Find out what
they are first!
[SHOP MAN A] Hi, looking
for some bulls, you said?
How many people?
We've got three.
[SHOP MAN A]
What kind would you like?
There's three ranks.
"Yagara," "Rabuka," and "King."
For your little group,
I'm thinking two
Yagaras will do just fine.
Gimme one rare
and one well-done.
You don't know what
you're saying, do you?!
[SHOP MAN A] Oh? You
followed a Log to get here?
[LUFFY]
Yep!
[SHOP MAN A]
That's quite an achievement,
but if you're not
from around here,
this is probably the first
time you've heard about bulls.
Uh-huh.
[SHOP MAN A] Well, to make a
long story short there they are!
Yagara bulls, you can
find them all over town.
As you can see, it's a
type of fish that swims
with its head above the water.
Since the whole city is flooded,
we have a lot more
canals than walkways.
Because of that,
pretty much everyone
here uses the bulls
in their daily life.
If you want to go sightseeing,
you'll need one too.
So they use the bulls
to pull those little boats?
Actually, the boat part's
mounted on their back.
In other words,
it's not much different
than riding
horseback on land.
Go ahead and take a look
at the bullpen over there
if you want to pick one out.
They don't bite.
It'll be 2,000 Berries for
two two-passenger Yagaras.
[NAMI]
They're cute!
They even look like horses!
Ugh! That's gross! What's
wrong with you, horse fish?!
Ha! Since that one seems to like
you, I'll mount him for you.
Is he all right
carrying heavy stuff?
Yeah, these guys
are built for power.
The people here use them
for moving all the time.
That's a big bag.
Can I ask what's inside?
[LUFFY]
Gold.
That's a good one. Well,
whatever it is, it'll be okay.
See?
Whoa! Gimme!
Yeah, right!
I guess he thought it was
worth asking, at least.
This is why I said I don't
trust you with the money!
I had to show him...
He didn't believe me!
Wow, I sure
wasn't expecting that.
Like I said,
that'll be one million Berries
for the two Yagara bulls.
Don't try to change
the price on us!
Oops, I mean 5 million Berries.
It went up even
more that time!
Ha ha ha!
Can't fool you!
I knew I'd have to
watch out for thieves...
[NAMI]
Here... 2,000 Berries.
[SHOP MAN A]
Thank you.
Speaking of gold, do you know
where we can get ours cashed in?
Well there's quite a few places,
but you'd probably
clean them all out trying
to trade in that much
treasure in one shot.
If I were you,
I'd check out downtown
on the shipbuilding island.
We're not really
familiar with the area.
Think you could give
us some directions?
It's right over there.
Here, take this.
Oh! A map!
Thanks for the help!
[LUFFY] Hey, we can find a
shipyard downtown too, right?
Yep! Best one in the world!
That'll be perfect.
We can head straight
to the shipyard soon
as we trade in our gold!
Well you're not gonna
hear any complaints from me.
As long as the Merry
gets repaired, I'll be happy!
Then we'll find a shipwright.
Oh man, I can't wait!
Well?
Shall we?
Yeah! Go Yagara!
[SHOP MAN A]
See you later!
Thanks for your business
and have a safe trip!
[LUFFY] Downtown,
full speed ahead! Yahoo!
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY]
All right! Let's go!
[USOPP] These Yagaras
sure are fun, aren't they?
[NAMI] And they're
surprisingly comfortable, too!
[LUFFY] Look! The canals go
to the top of the buildings!
[USOPP] Hold on
Luffy, slow down!
[NAMI] Yeah, this isn't a
roller coaster, after all!
[LUFFY] Of course it is!
Let's race to the bottom!
On the next One Piece :
"Adventure in the
City on the Water!
Head to the Mammoth
Shipbuilding Plant!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!