Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in intrigue and danger,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison Impel Down.
[NARRATOR]
Together with Captain Buggy,
as well as former Baroque Works
agents Mr. 3 and Bon Clay,
Luffy was able to make his way
to Level 4:
The Burning Heat Hell.
[NARRATOR]
But as soon as he arrived,
he was poisoned by Magellan,
the Warden of Impel Down,
and taken into custody.
[NARRATOR] After Luffy
was imprisoned on Level 5,
the Freezing Hell,
Bon Clay did everything in his
power to find a way to save him.
[BON CLAY (HANNYABAL)]
No freaking way!
I mean, uh... what do you mean
you can't make an antidote?
What's the hold up?
A miracle?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Oh, yeah! I forgot about him!
He's in Impel Down! My hero,
"The Miracle Worker"!
Come on, we need to find out
where they're holding him now!
[LUFFY]
"A Paradise in Hell.
Impel Down Level 5.5"!
Uh-oh. I think we're surrounded.
[ARMY WOLVES growling]
[grunts] Well, then,
we have no choice.
We should lock ourselves inside!
Right, I'll try to distract
the mutts. Make it quick!
[BUGGY]
Chew on this!
My special Muggy Ball!
[laughs] Good riddance!
[ARMY WOLVES roar]
What the hell?!
[MR. 3]
Now I've done it!
Yeah, you did?
[MR. 3 crying]
[MR. 3]
Yep, I broke the key!
Why are you so useless?!
[ARMY WOLVES growl]
[BUGGY]
Eh. Crap, it's too late!
Take this! Candle Shield!
[ARMY WOLVES yelping]
[sighs] That was close!
Come on! Move! Let's make
a run for the cell, pronto!
[sighs]
I don't think that we'll
need to. I just had an idea.
[BUGGY laughing]
[BUGGY]
Stupid wolves!
Try and eat us now,
you frozen fleabags!
[MR. 3]
It's no use trying
to bite your way
through, mister wolf.
This Candle House
is as hard as iron!
Even with fangs so big
and powerful as yours,
there's no way you'll break it!
You said it! Let's head out!
[MR. 3]
But of course, my friend!
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
One, two! One, two!
[BUGGY]
Maybe you're not useless!
[MR. 3] I'm so happy right now
I'll take that as a compliment!
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
One, two.
[BUGGY, MR. 3 groan]
[BOTH panting]
After a while,
it gets kinda heavy.
That makes sense.
I made it thicker
than usual to protect us.
Oh, yeah? Well, good thinking!
How fast we move doesn't really
matter, as long as we're safe.
All we've gotta do
is make it to the stairs
and we can get out
of this hell hole.
Indeed! And, while we
remain inside this cell,
we keep out of the wind, too!
It's a win-win!
Let's move!
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
One, two! One.
[MR. 3]
Wait!
Take a few steps back,
would you?
[BUGGY]
Huh?
Something up?
Something is odd.
Look, outside. What happened
to all of those wolves?
You're right. They're gone!
[MR. 3]
You don't suppose they gave up?
[cracking]
Do you hear something?
[BUGGY]
Huh?
[cracking]
[BOTH]
Uhh... Uh-oh.
[ARMY WOLVES roaring]
[BUGGY, MR. 3 screaming]
[BUGGY, MR. 3] Since when
do wolves dig underground?
[BON CLAY shivering]
[PRISONER A]
Who the hell is that?
He's covered in blood.
[LUFFY groaning]
Before... I--
[BON CLAY] I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen!
Running is the only answer!
I'm sorry, Straw Boy!
I'm a coward! Forgive me!
I ran away!
Hey, pal, how do you know him?
[BON CLAY]
He's my friend!
Straw Boy, I'm not
letting you die!
Come on. We better go.
--[click]
--[door squeaks]
He left the keys?
I never thought about
breaking out of here until now.
[BON CLAY] I gotta find Iva
before it's too late!
Iva, huh? I have no idea
where that twinkle-toes went.
Who the hell wants
to know, anyway?
[LUFFY groaning]
Emporio Ivankov? Oh, that guy!
Yeah, he's prob'ly dead.
What're you staring at?
[PRISONER F] Huh? That guy's
been missin' for ages.
What do even want with him?
And how did you
get out of your cell?
Get me out of mine, too!
[BON CLAY groaning]
Do you know where they're
keeping a man named Iva?
Hey, you! What's wrong?
Hey! Speak up! Answer me!
[PRISONER G]
Don't bother.
Didn't you notice? Everyone
in that cell is frozen stiff.
[BON CLAY]
How 'bout you, then?
Yeah, I heard ya.
Said you're looking
for Ivankov, right?
Yeah, do you
know something?
Look, over there.
You see that forest?
Yes.
[PRISONER H]
There's an abandoned jailhouse
way beyond the tree-line.
A while back,
I saw this strange guy
just dancing around out there.
Really?
Yeah, I think it was him.
It's worth a look.
[BON CLAY]
Thanks, friend.
[PRISONER H]
We're all in this together.
That forest, it's where
the wolves live.
[PRISONER H]
Oh, is it?
[PRISONER H laughing]
[GUARD H] Every so often,
people disappear in Impel Down.
We're sure they didn't
just break out,
as some of the missing
could barely move.
They just vanished
without a trace,
and no one seems
to know the cause.
We've come to call it,
"demoning away."
[GUARD H] All the guards here
have come to fear
these unnatural and
strange disappearances.
We believe that those missing
have been dragged
to the gates of hell,
hence why we call it what we do.
[BON CLAY]
"The gates of hell"?
"Demoning away"?
Quit pulling my tail!
No way Iva disappeared
because of some
superstitious mumbo jumbo.
I've never met him myself,
but his reputation
certainly precedes him.
Even in a hell like this place,
I'm sure he can still
make a miracle happen.
[BON CLAY] Because Iva
is our queen! Our god!
Somehow, I know
he can save Straw Boy.
[BON CLAY] If we can't count
on an antidote anymore--
[BON CLAY panting]
[BON CLAY]
He's his only chance.
Iva, I swear I'll find you!
No matter what!
[ARMY WOLVES growling]
[BON CLAY]
Eh?
--[BON CLAY grunts]
--[ARMY WOLF yelps]
[ARMY WOLF roars]
[ARMY WOLVES growling]
[BON CLAY panting]
[ARMY WOLF roaring]
[gasps] No!
[ARMY WOLF yelps]
[ARMY WOLF whining]
[BON CLAY grunting]
[BON CLAY groaning]
[roars]
[BON CLAY screaming]
[LUFFY groaning]
[ARMY WOLF growling, yelps]
[BON CLAY screams]
[BON CLAY]
Straw Boy!
[LUFFY] What do you think...
you're doing to my friend, Bon?
[ARMY WOLVES whine]
[LUFFY]
Leave him...
...alone!
[gasps]
[LUFFY coughing]
Whoa! Straw Boy, how did you--?
[thud]
[snow crunching]
[NARRATOR] "The public
execution of "Fire Fist" Ace
will take place in 26 hours."
[HANNYABAL]
Damn it all.
Where did you go?
[sighs] This place
is like stupid hot.
It's so steamy!
[HANNYABAL] Young!
Gorgeous! Just my type!
Woo-hoo! She's hot enough
to light hell on fire!
[HANNYABAL]
Wait a minute. Priorities.
Where's that pansy prisoner
who beat up all the guards?
He's gotta be around
here somewhere.
[HANNYABAL]
Wait, who are you?
[BON CLAY (NAMI)] Who I am
doesn't really matter right now,
lover-boy. Could I get
some assistance, here?
[HANNYABAL]
Uh?
Whew! Can't you see
how sweaty I am?
Oh, surely you can help me
out of these rags! Please?
[BON CLAY (NAMI)]
We can do it in here, right?
[HANNYABAL
Yep! One sec.
Ca-chink! Ladies first!
[HANNYABAL]
Oh my, it's dark in here.
No need to be shy! Ha, ha, ha.
Where did you run off to?
[BON CLAY]
I'm right here.
[HANNYABAL]
Huh?
[gasps]
[HANNYABAL]
This is the worst day ever.
I'll just blame it on
the warden, of course,
but I can't believe that
a prisoner outsmarted me!
[HANNYABAL groaning]
[HANNYABAL]
When do I get to be the warden?
[MAGELLAN farting]
[MAGELLAN groaning]
I used too much poison.
Oh, my tummy!
[SALDEATH] That's right.
We got the riot shut down.
All of the prisoners have been
returned to their cells,
and we've retrieved
the keys, but--
I think some are missing.
Damn it. What a pain.
Listen up! You've got to...
[giggles] ...find him!
[SADIE] He must be
somewhere on this floor!
Find him and I'm going to whip
[giggles] the sass
right out of him!
[GUARDS]
Yes, mistress!
[NARRATOR] Several hours later,
Bon Clay starts to wake up.
Where... am I?
[gasping]
[thud]
Straw Boy!
Where did he go? Straw Boy!
[BON CLAY] I think I hear
people talking somewhere.
[distant chatter]
[distant chatter continues]
This is it!
[gulps]
[gasps]
So bright!
[laughing, chatter]
[gasps]
Well, you decided
to join us, did ya?
You were sleeping forever.
Want a drink?
Raise them for the newcomer,
everyone! Cheers!
[PATRON A, PATRON B]
Cheers!
We've been watching you guys
on our monitors.
Bravo! Quite the show!
What the--?
I'll seat you. What floor
did you come from, by the way?
We've got plenty to eat here.
I'd guess you're hungry.
Wait, where am I?
Where's Straw Boy?
[laughs] What, do you think you
somehow magically made it out
of the prison?
Don't worry. You're still
in Impel Down, sweetie.
No way! That's a lie!
No one's wearing
any prison clothes!
Everyone's drinking
and having fun!
Did I wake up
in some kind of paradise?
What's the deal?
Hold on... I remember.
[BON CLAY] I was chased down
and attacked by those wolves.
Then, Straw Boy
woke up and helped me.
After that, I passed out.
[thud]
[BON CLAY]
Then, maybe I am dreaming!
Or wait! What if I died from
the cold and I'm in heaven now!
[WOMAN]
Close, but no cigar.
[BON CLAY]
Huh?
You've been sleeping
like a baby.
Out cold for ten hours now.
Ten hours? Are you kidding me?
And who are you?
[WOMAN]
My name is Inazuma.
Hm. Mind your manners!
I'm the one who fetched you from
that bitter cold, after all.
You're lucky you two
didn't die from exposure.
Wait, did you say "you two"?
So you brought
Straw Boy here, too?
Well then, where is he?
Speak up! Answer me!
Damn you! There's no time!
[sighs] Patience now.
Let him explain things to you.
Him, who?
[PATRON F] Oh, the lights
are down! It's time!
[PATRON G]
The show's starting!
You'll want a front row seat.
[CROWD cheering]
What is this?
[PERFORMER] Did you sleep tight,
little candy boy?
[PERFORMER]
Or should I say little Bon Boy?
How do you know my name?
[CROWD cheering]
[PERFORMER]
Thank you for coming.
Are you ready?
Shake it! Sexy!
[PERFORMER]
To get here,
you have to pass through
the sewers of Impel Down.
[PERFORMER] Following paths
that shouldn't exist
to a place beyond imagination.
It's a prisoner's paradise!
We've got every pleasure you
could ever beg for, right here!
Drinks!
Weapons!
Games!
But most of all,
we have freedom!
Yeah, you said it!
We got our freedom!
[PERFORMER]
Looks like the jailers
are flipping their tops again.
"Prisoners have disappeared!"
"They've been
pulled down into hell!"
Those silly little fools
couldn't be more wrong!
We're here and we're queer!
[CROWD cheering]
[PERFORMER] I wouldn't exactly
call this hell, would you?
[PERFORMER]
Well, who knows? Maybe it is.
But, if so, at least
it's a gay one!
The secret underground
where dreams come true!
[PERFORMER]
I bid you welcome.
To Impel Down
Level 5.5, bitches!
A secret garden
for all y'all prisoners! Ahh!
This is New Kama Land!
[ALL]
Hee-haw!
[CROWD cheering]
They're... all queer like me.
[CROWD]
Yeah! Iva! We love you, Iva!
Wha?
Iva!
That's Iva?
The-The legendary
Miracle Worker?
The Queen of
Kamabakka Kingdom?
[QUEEN singing]
[CROWD]
Hee-haw!
[BON CLAY]
Emporio Ivankov?
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
[NARRATOR] Rescued by Inazuma,
Bon Clay is relieved to hear
that Iva will cure
Luffy's poison.
However, when he
discovers the toll
that it will take
on his friend's body,
his joy quickly turns to dread.
Now, the battle
for Luffy's life truly begins.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Luffy's Treatment Begins.
Iva's Miraculous Power!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!