Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR]
While on the ice-covered sea
known as the Frozen Highway,
the separated members
of the Straw Hat crew
face off against a
group of bounty hunters
known as the Accino Family.
[SALCHOW] Here goes!
[SALCHOW, ARBELL]
Love Throw!
A gorgeous rocket of
beauty soaring into my arms!
Not what I expected!
[LIL] Today's our
Papa's big birthday party.
That's why everyone's
out trying to get him
the best present they can!
[ROBIN]
So the flag's his present?
No. Bad guess.
[LIL] These are the presents.
There's an 80 million
bounty on your head.
Isn't there?
[NARRATOR]
With a little help from Puzzle,
Luffy and the others
managed to capture
the eldest son of the
Accino Family, Brindo.
Dammit!
No!
[coughing]
[CHOPPER] Luffy!
[BRINDO] And as for the
rest of you pirate scum,
your time is coming, too!
[JIRO] Captain Puzzle!
[SUTTON] Puzzle!
They still haven't caught them?
You got their
flag though, right?
[CAMPACINO]
It'll be here soon, Papa.
You just relax.
What the hell's this
place 'sposed to be?
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Nami and Franky
fought against the Accino
family's third son, Hockera.
They were defeated and captured.
--Damn it, let us out!
--Let us out of here,
--you stupid jerk!
[SALCHOW] Get back here,
you long-nosed bastard!
[USOPP yelling]
Usopp! What's wrong with you?
How could you shoot
a lady like that?!
Are you kidding?
She was trying to kill us!
[SALCHOW] How dare you do that
to my sweet honey, Arbell?
[SALCHOW]
Get back here!
I can't just
leave her like that!
[SALCHOW]
Take this!
Gunpowder Star!
[USOPP] Look out!
Ow! My head is
killing me! I mean...
Hahahahaha! Operation Usopp
Headbutt Attack was a success!
Mission complete!
[SANJI] Dearest Arbell,
are you all right?
Salchow...
Lemme go!
[LUFFY] Hot Full Throttle!
The Twins' Magnetic
Power Drawing Near!
[sneezes]
So cold!
Hey! You were the one
who saved me, right?
Thanks a lot!
[CHOPPER] How is it? Any pain?
A little,
but I think I'm okay.
You!
How dare you try to turn us
into your own personal slaves!
Too bad. You underestimated
the Phoenix Pirates.
It's payback time!
Not so fast.
Don't forget about my brothers.
They'll hunt you down
if anything happens to me.
Bring 'em on!
Your days of telling us
what to do are over!
That smart mouth's gonna
get you in trouble, kid.
Whatever!
I swear, if you think you can
still push us around, then--
[PUZZLE] Enough!
[JIRO] Captain Puzzle!
You've all got the wrong idea.
I didn't capture him so that
we could keep him locked up here
as our prisoner.
[GUYLE] What?
If possible, I'd like
to make a deal with you.
A deal, huh?
[PUZZLE] Yeah.
I'd like you to let my crew
leave this place peacefully.
In exchange,
I'll surrender myself.
What? No, Captain Puzzle!
You can't!
What the hell
are you trying to do?
[laughing]
Well, well!
You're not as dumb as I thought!
Would you think about this?
If you leave, what's gonna
happen to the Phoenix Pirates?
Stop it, Jiro.
The Captain has spoken.
He's made up his mind.
But--!
[PUZZLE] Jiro.
Listen to me.
You little rat!
Do you really think
you can deceive me?
Well, you'll pay for trying!
[coughing]
Stansen!
[JIRO] Captain!
Why're you standing here?
Hurry up and beat
the crap out of that guy!
C'mon, captain, please!
Ohohohoho!
Captain!
What's wrong with you?
You aren't acting
like yourself at all!
C'mon!
Help him!
Do something, captain!
Damn it!
We're not pirates anymore.
It doesn't matter, okay?
How can you say that?
[laughing]
You're a smart
captain after all.
All right, then.
In exchange for you
and your bounty,
I promise the rest of
these guys will be free to go.
You can't!
I won't let you!
I'm a Phoenix Pirate!
Hold it!
Just watch!
I'll take care of him!
Jiro. Stop.
That's enough. It's over.
Ohohohoho!
Come on! Just try it!
If you even touch me,
your entire pathetic
crew will be doomed!
You bastard!
Ohoho! Ohoho!
What are you doing?
Whoa! You heard
what I said, boy!
If you even think about hurting
me, this entire crew will--
Where's our flag?
Easy, Luffy.
Your flag?
Maybe you haven't noticed, but
this crew is in no position to--
This has nothing
to do with them.
Gimme back my flag
before I beat it out of you.
Even if, on a whim,
I felt like giving you back
your flag, it doesn't matter.
It's not here.
[LUFFY]
Take us to where it is. Now.
Hey! Just calm down!
The guide will be
here shortly, all right?
[BRINDO] Once he's here,
we'll be led deep
inside the Frozen Highway
until we reach my family's
stronghold: Lovely Land.
And the moment you and this
joke of a crew set foot there,
all of you will be done for.
It's just a matter of time.
[ACCINO] What's taking
that flag so long?
Answer me, Campacino!
Papa!
Take it easy!
Lil's flying fish will
deliver it any minute!
No need to worry!
And what of
my birthday party?
When will that happen?
[CAMPACINO] Just as soon
as the others return.
Campacino!
How long are you
gonna keep me waiting?
Papa! There's no
need to be angry!
Just a little further,
then we'll be home.
So as of right now...
This person and this person
are also headed to your house?
[LIL] Yep!
My brother Hockera should arrive
there with them at any minute.
Huh...
Ke ke! Papa is
going to be so happy!
Come on!
Can't you do something
to warm it up in here?
What exactly do
you expect me to do?
The controls are frozen solid.
Though if you'd like,
I suppose a little taste of my
Fresh Fire might do in a pinch.
Are you insane?
You'll burn me and
everything else to a crisp!
[FRANKY]
You got any better ideas?
[NAMI]
Come up with something
that doesn't
involve me in danger!
[FRANKY]
Holy crap, are you demanding!
[NAMI] Not wanting to
die is not "demanding"!
Dammit! Are these
guys annoying or what?
Oh, Arbell.
What could you possibly
see in that guy?
You clowns might've
gotten lucky once,
but you'd be fools to
think we'd lose that easily!
Salchow, let's show
them something special.
How about our Supreme Attack?
Crap! They're about to
hit us with something big!
Good.
That'll be the perfect
chance to show off my skills
in front of Arbell.
[USOPP] I don't like
the looks of this!
They're spinning even faster
than they were last time!
Once I do,
she'll be so impressed,
she'll dump that jerk for me.
Fine. Whatever prevents
them from killing us.
It's up to you!
That's fast enough!
Are you ready, Arbell?
Yes, Salchow!
[SALCHOW, ARBELL] High Jump
Great Rotation Ultra Love Throw!
[SANJI] Dammit! It's the ice!
It's too slippery!
Sanji...
If those two hit me again, I
think it'll be the death of me.
Come on!
You're always exaggerating.
I've got bruises
and I'm covered in blood!
Is that an exaggeration?
Salchow! This is the best!
Agreed, Arbell!
Let's do it one more time!
Right!
Usopp.
Let's show them
our cooperative attack.
So you figured out a plan?
Sure! I'm happy to help!
What the--?
How is this supposed to help?
It keeps me from slipping.
[SANJI] Collier Frit!
[SANJI] Dearest Arbell!
Seems fate's given us
a second chance.
So what do you say?
Can it, you womanizing jerk!
Have your lover's
quarrel somewhere else!
Get off me!
[ARBELL]
Salchow! Can you hear me?
Say something!
--Oh! Arbell!
--[USOPP laughing]
Now you get it!
Whatever attack you throw at us
will be rendered meaningless
against our boundless strength!
Sanji! Get up already!
You're gonna make us look bad!
If you'd like to surrender,
now is the time.
That last attack only revealed
ten percent of my true power!
[ARBELL and SALCHOW chuckling]
[ARBELL] Oh, how cute,
you probably think
we've been skating in circles
this whole time just for fun.
[USOPP] Eh?
Wait, what? What do you mean?
[SALCHOW, ARBELL]
Funny you should ask.
This is what we mean!
[USOPP screaming]
[USOPP] It's freezing!
[ARBELL]
I think you should surrender!
[USOPP] Never!
Now don't be like that.
If you behave, and come along
quietly, we'll save you.
What do you say?
[USOPP] Hey... What's that?
[screaming]
If you two don't give up soon,
you're gonna freeze to death.
You shut up!
Hey! Snap out of it!
Usopp, I--I think I
feel like sleeping right now.
Are you kidding me?
We're in danger!
We're gonna die!
[USOPP]
Okay! Okay! I'm sorry!
I surrender!
Please, save me!
Salchow! Look!
I think I caught one!
[SALCHOW] I did too, Arbell!
[USOPP] Dammit. So cold.
[kissing noise]
Where is he?
I thought there
was a guide coming.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL RINGING]
--[JIRO] Huh?
--[BRINDO] There. Finally.
Hey, kid, there's a
transponder snail in my pocket.
Pull it out and answer it.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL RINGING]
[CAMPACINO]
Brindo, what's wrong?
Where are you?
Where are the presents?
Papa's getting angry.
[CAMPACINO] Did you hear me?
What's going on? Say something.
Brindo has been taken
prisoner by the Phoenix Pirates!
If you try anything stupid,
he'll be executed!
No! Jiro, wait!
[laughing]
Oh, boy! Now you've done it!
Huh?
My brother's coming.
[LUFFY] Your brother?
[laughing]
[BRINDO]
Looks like the deal's off!
Just you wait. Our powers
are going to crush you!
[laughing]
What do you mean "your powers"?
What are you gonna do?
What's happening?
I'm not gonna let you do
anything weird, got it?
Whoa! Cool!
How'd you make yourself shiny?
Wow! Awesome!
This is just the beginning.
[laughing]
What's that?
[chuckling]
Wait... He was
chained up, wasn't he?
How'd he escape?
No way!
[laughing]
What's going on here?
Now there's two of him?
[CAMPACINO]
How dare you try to kidnap
my adorable little brother.
My brother!
Brother!
It's been quite
some time since...
...we used our
Combination Play!
That's cool!
How'd you do that glowy stuff?
We're merely using
a bit of magnetism.
Observe.
We can cover a greater
range by separating.
And then we can
return together instantly
for close-range assaults.
It's the magnetic power that
links our brotherhood together!
That's how we show our...
...brotherly love!
Cool! Did you two eat
a Devil Fruit or something?
[CAMPACINO chuckling]
Our power doesn't come
from anything like that.
We have these abilities...
--...because we are twins!
Haha! Twins are awesome!
That doesn't explain it!
It's still weird!
Brindo, which ones
are today's targets?
Well...
First we have
Captain Puzzle, the Phoenix,
with a bounty of
100 million Berries.
Next, we have Straw Hat Luffy,
with a bounty of
300 million Berries.
[CAMPACINO] Really! That guy?
[BRINDO] And this is their
cotton candy-loving pet,
Chopper, with a
bounty of 50 Berries.
[CHOPPER]
50?
50 Berries?
Really? Why bother?
I know, right?
It's almost nothing.
[CHOPPER] Don't gimme that crap!
I object to 50 Berries!
Never mind.
Now, let's see if you can
think of a way to escape
from our Combination Play!
--[BRINDO] Straw Hat!
--[LUFFY] Hm?
Look over here!
[CHOPPER]
Luffy, be careful! Behind you!
Behind me?
[BRINDO] Repulsion Pass!
[chuckling]
Right into the sea!
These punks are no
match for our brotherhood!
Luffy!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum... Rocket!
Brother, no!
Nice one!
Wow!
You'll pay for that.
Haha! Ready to give up?
[ACCINO] Campacino!
Who said that?
Hello? Is somebody in here?
[ACCINO] How much longer
do I have to wait?
Where's my party?
Where's my flag?
Ugh. It's hot.
What is this place?
[ZORO] Who are you?
My mistake--thought you
were my boy, Campacino.
I was saving this for
the party, but want some?
All right. Sure.
[ACCINO] Make yourself at home.
Will do.
I'm waiting for my
family to get back here
for my birthday party.
And now, the party
organizer stepped out
and hasn't returned yet, either.
It's kind of annoying.
Well, what a coincidence.
Everyone in my crew stepped out,
and I can't seem
to find them anywhere.
I've been looking for hours.
We're in the same situation.
Seems so. Thanks!
I wish I knew where those
nitwits wandered off to.
I bet.
I'm also curious as to
where you wandered in from.
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum... Bell!
Doctor!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
[LUFFY] Listen up, you two.
If you don't give us
back our flag,
we'll beat you up for real!
Brindo. Papa is getting
angrier and angrier.
We need to end this now.
Let's use his Devil
Fruit powers against him.
Throw him in the sea.
That should stop him.
Enough! Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
[BRINDO] Combine!
[LUFFY screaming]
Luffy!
Captain!
I can't! He's too far!
Like I'd fall!
[BRINDO, CAMPACINO]
Magnetic Repulsion Pass!
Whew! That was close!
Listen, Straw Hat.
Just give up already.
It's impossible
to escape from us!
So? I'm not gonna escape--
I'm gonna beat you up!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum... Twin Pistol!
--Repulsion!
I'm on my way, Luffy!
[loud crashing noise]
What's going on?
Jiro! Be careful!
[CHOPPER] Jiro!
Are you all right?
Yes. Thanks, Captain.
Quick!
Turn the ship around now!
We gotta go back for Luffy!
But that's impossible.
We're on the
Frozen Highway, remember?
It won't let us turn.
Luffy...
[ACCINO laughing]
Forget about them.
They forgot about you, right?
Nah, these things happen.
They're probably just screwing
around in the ice somewhere.
We'll find each other
soon enough.
Ah! You noticed!
My collection I'm so proud of.
What do you think?
[ZORO] Collection?
[ACCINO] That's right!
These are the pirates
we've hunted down.
Quite impressive, yes?
That's an annoying
little hobby you have there.
Come on!
Don't say such things.
Finally! It's here.
Maybe if you see this one, we'll
understand each other better.
[ACCINO] The flag of the
notorious Straw Hat Pirates,
whose collective bounty
is more than 600 million.
Isn't that right...
...Mr. 120 million Berry
bounty, Roronoa Zoro?
[ZORO] You!
What the hell are you doing
with our flag, you bastard?
This particular one may
be the prize of my collection.
[NAMI] It's even colder here!
You were planning on imprisoning
us all along, weren't you?
[USOPP]
Even the walls are made of ice!
But all this cold is
making me kind of sleepy.
[NAMI] No sleeping!
If you do,
you'll freeze to death!
[USOPP] Where the hell
are Robin and Zoro, anyway?
Help us!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Mansion of Great Chaos!
The Enraged Don
and the Captured Crew!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!