[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Demon Aura Nine-Sword
Style Asura!
Sky Slicer!
[ZORO]
You did well.
I commend you!
Suffering is welcome on
the path to bloodshed!
Asura Silver Mist!
[LUFFY]
Second Gear.
Jet Whip!
[LUCCI]
Shave! Finger Pistol!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[LUCCI]
Iron Body!
...Jet Bazooka!
Franky!
You gotta save her!
Just super leave it to me!
[SPANDAM]
Stupid woman!
Don't you get it?
This is useless!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
There's no hope for you
so just give it up now!
[ROBIN]
I'm not going anywhere!
They're coming!
They're all coming to rescue me!
[LUFFY]
"Spandam Frightened!
The Hero on the Tower of Law."
Hey! Look! They're opening!
The Gates of Justice
are really opening!
You're right!
In all my years here,
this is the first time
it's ever happened!
[MARINES] I've never even heard
of it happening before!
[MARINES] They must be
letting the battleships
from Headquarters through.
[MARINES] The Buster Call's
about to let loose!
Ah, crap.
I don't like this.
Granny Kokoro said
the Gates of Justice
never open all
the way like that.
[KIWI] This Buster Call
thing must be really bad.
Even the Marines are in
a panic to get out of here!
[MOZU] The Straw Hats picked
a fight with the whole world.
They might really burn
the whole island
down to get at them.
[TILESTONE]
Those bastards!
Hang in there, Bro! Don't die!
Yeah!
You too, Straw Hat!
Good luck!
Robin'll be fine.
I know Franky
can take care of her.
[LUCCI]
I was careless.
This new power of his
took me by surprise.
Whatever you're doing
seems to be taking its toll.
Shame.
The fight was just
getting interesting.
[LUFFY]
I don't care what happens,
as long as I can beat you.
I see. How stubborn.
Almost there!
Don't you dare
leave yet, Nico Robin!
Would you look at yourself?
I've never seen such
a pathetic sight! Really!
Now that's enough.
Stand up! Stand up, damn it!
Gimme a break!
The gate is right over there!
We're so close.
It's so annoying!
[MARINE]
Guards, onto the bridge!
[MARINES]
Yes sir!
All right, men. Ready? Good.
Because Chief Spandam
is on his way as we speak.
He's delivering an
especially heinous criminal
across the bridge
from the Tower of Law.
This doesn't happen often,
so I want all Marines
from the escort ships
and all guards from the
gate here in top form!
Give him the best
damned salute you've got!
[SPANDAM]
Would you look at that!
All lined up and ready to sail!
Not a thing left to stop me!
Oh, I almost forgot.
There's a surprise waiting
for your little friends.
You see, before we
crossed the bridge,
I set up a landmine at
the top of those stairs
right over there.
So, in the unlikely
event that someone
actually does come to save you,
they and the stairs
will both go boom!
Quite the elegant solution,
don't you think?
Well, I'm excited at least.
Though I suppose neither of us
should get our
hopes up too much,
seeing as how
no one will be coming
to help you in the first place.
[ROBIN]
I won't go through that gate.
[SPANDAM]
What?
I still believe they'll
come to save me.
They're not coming, okay?
Jeez! Shut up!
They'll be burned to a crisp
just like everything else
in the Buster Call's path.
You got that?
Rather convenient, really!
Every humiliation I've suffered,
including them
shooting down our flag
will be erased as well!
Just like before, 20 years ago,
when that marine giant
attacked us in Ohara.
Now it's time to walk!
That means on your
own two feet, damn it!
[ROBIN]
Saul.
Hurry up!
Are you okay, Chief?
Do you need help?
No, I don't need
any help, damn it!
I'm a friggin hero!
If you thought I didn't
know anything about that,
then you're dead wrong!
Your old friend Jaguar D. Saul
was a Vice Admiral
before he betrayed us.
Your mother, Olvia,
was an archaeologist.
And I know about your
hometown of Ohara as well.
Quite the tragic tale, isn't it?
And why do I know all this?
Well, it's quite simple.
Because the man who
commanded the raid on Ohara,
uncovered their crimes,
then blew the island to
smithereens with a Buster Call,
was the Chief of
CP9 who preceded me.
Otherwise known as
my father, Spandine!
Well, scholars of Ohara.
I'm afraid your death sentence
has already been decided.
Kill him!
Professor!
[ELDER STAR B]
You left us no choice.
Ohara knows too much.
I invoke the Buster Call!
And that's a wrap.
Hurry. Take her and go, Saul.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Stop it!
I wanna stay with
you! Mommy! No!
[OLVIA] I was happy to hear
you call me that again.
Thank you.
From now on,
for my sake as well--
You must live, Robin!
At the time, they thought
that everyone in Ohara
had been nicely eliminated.
But they found out later
that one little brat
had slipped through
their fingers.
So, how was it?
Running from one money-grubbing
adult to the next,
hoping you weren't
either killed or sold out?
Not a single person
you could trust,
no matter where you went.
Nowhere to lay your
little head down in peace.
Nothing to eat.
What a vile and wretched
existence you've had.
Why it's too appalling
to even think about.
Sad enough to make you cry, huh?
20 years ago, my old man
put that bounty
on your little head.
All for world peace!
Show some gratitude, will you?
Now we finally have
our happy ending.
The son completes the father's
crusade
against the devils of
Ohara, and the wrongs
of 20 years ago have
been made right at last!
Ohara is dead!
Don't cry, Robin! Be proud!
Your mamma's a wonderful woman!
Ohara's a wonderful place!
You gotta remember that!
It's up to you to
pass it on, okay?
Ohara was so brave they
fought against the whole world!
Ohara won't die as long I live!
Yeah?
And how long is
that gonna be? Huh?
Whoa! It went off!
[SPANDAM]
C-Cutty Flam!?
What is he doing here?
Well, no harm done.
He fell for the landmine. Idiot!
Serves you right!
[ROBIN]
He came to rescue me.
Still, that was close.
It's a good thing
I had my backup plan.
Come on, let's go!
[ROBIN]
I'm so angry I can't even speak.
All right, marines, set sail!
We're getting out of here now!
Understood, sir.
Everyone, move!
Yes sir!
[ROBIN] I can't hold
back the tears anymore.
Watch carefully, men!
Because you're about to witness
the first step of a
hero that is destined
to go down in history!
[SPANDAM]
Watch carefully, men!
Because you're about to witness
the first step of a
hero that is destined
to go down in history!
Are you okay, Chief?
What happened?
He was hit! We're under attack!
There's no one on
the bridge but us!
No, they must be
hiding somewhere!
Everyone start searching!
But where?
Hey! What's wrong with you?
Fight back! Don't
just stand there!
We're trying, sir,
but we don't know
where the enemy's at!
There!
Don't look back, just go!
If you say on this
island, you'll die!
Take my raft and go out to sea!
But what about you?
He's got me, little lady.
I'm afraid this is
the end. Hurry!
No!
Everybody I care about is here!
Now you listen to me.
You may be lonely at first.
But one day you'll
find true friends.
True friends?
Yeah, the sea's a
vast place, so I guarantee.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
No matter who you are,
ain't no one born into
this world to be alone!
It's time to go, Robin.
This is goodbye!
When things are bad,
do like I taught you.
You know the laugh, don't you?
Look out! He's behind you!
Dereshishishishi...
Now. Ice Time.
Saul, no!
Dereshishishishi...
Your friends are out there
at sea waiting for you, Robin.
All you gotta do is find them!
[SAUL] Share your life with
them, and never let them go.
[MARINE]
Chief, over there!
What? Over where?
[MARINE] He's standing on
top of the Tower of Law!
What's he doing up there?
It's so far away!
How the hell's he hitting us?
[USOPP]
Shing!
[MARINE U]
Is he using a slingshot?
[MARINE V]
This guy's a monster!
The wind's blowing like crazy
and he's all the way over there,
but he's still hitting
his mark every time!
Thank you, Long Nose.
Bam! Eat that!
Our sniper is number 1!
Serves you right, bastards!
C'mon Robin, run!
I could do without
the singing, I think.
Chief!
Damn it!
What are you idiots doing?
Shoot that guy already!
We're trying, sir,
but he's too far away
for our bullets to reach,
let alone actually hit him.
I hate to say it,
but he's got us
totally outclassed!
Nico Robin is getting away!
Then stop her! Shoot her down!
Sir!
Shoot her just dead
enough to keep her alive!
Fire!
[MARINE]
Who the hell is that?
Franky.
Bullets are no problem
when you're made of iron.
But that landmine
wasn't very nice, Spanda.
Franky!
Come in Franky, do you read me?
This is Sniper King.
Huh?
Yeah, I can read you
loud and clear, but--
How?
I got the snail from Nami.
Anyway, turn around.
There should be a red bundle
on the ground next to you.
Red bundle? Oh, I see it.
Good. It has two keys inside.
Together with the ones you have,
that should be all of them.
How did they get the keys?
And my mission is complete.
Nice work.
All right, then. Let's go.
Number one. Number three.
Number four. Nope. Number five!
We got it!
No way!
This can't be happening to me!
[FRANKY]
Whoa! Hold on.
We're not in the clear yet.
But wait-- that
means--They really did it?
A bunch of useless pirates
beat every last member of CP9?
No, that can't be right!
They must've just stolen
the keys and run away!
Buncha cheaters!
Okay, we got it!
Hey! You hear me?
We got the handcuffs
off Robin, no problem!
Yes!
[ROBIN]
Thank you, Long Nose.
That was wonderful.
[USOPP]
It was the least I could do.
The true heroes are those
who fought to retrieve
those keys from the enemy.
The Straw Hats will be
proud to have you back.
Hold your head up high
and meet them with a smile
when all of this has ended!
Right.
Heh.
Now Seis Fleurs!
Huh? What the--?
[ROBIN]
Slap!
[ROBIN] I've been waiting
a long time to do this.
[MARINES]
Are you okay, Chief?
All right. Let's move!
Get your asses over here!
I'll get everything
ready for ya.
We're gonna bail!
[USOPP]
Roger!
[SANJI] Get down here
already, Sniper King!
[MARINE BB]
The prisoner's escaped
from the Sea Prism
Stone Handcuffs!
Regroup and recapture her!
[USOPP] Everything went
according to my plan.
[squeaky, squealing noise]
[USOPP]
What's that?
I swear I heard something.
[LUCCI] It's obvious that you're
pushing your body too far.
And I doubt that you
could take much more.
You're shortening
your own lifespan
just for a few
minutes of strength.
[LUFFY] It's better than
letting you take away
everything I care about.
I'll do anything to keep
that from happening!
On the next One Piece:
"Robin Freed!
Luffy Vs. Lucci, Showdown
between Leaders."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!