[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NAMI]
Well, we're finally here.
I'd ask if you're relieved, but
I guess it's too early to know.
Do you have any plans for how
to deal with the rebellion?
Yes, I do have a plan.
But... I don't
really know for sure
how well it's going to work.
So hungry.
And hot.
[VIVI] Please... just hang
on a little longer.
[LUFFY]
"Off to the Desert Kingdom!
The Rain‐Summoning Powder
and the Rebel Army!"
[CITY FOLK chattering]
So this is an Alabasta city.
[LUFFY]
Is there food?
[NAMI]
Listen carefully, guys.
I want you all to do your
best to control yourselves
while we're here.
Of course, Nami.
You do realize the one who needs
to hear that warning the most
has already abandoned ship.
[LUFFY]
Feed me now!
[NAMI]
Get back here!
He doesn't know the
meaning of control.
What now?
He's easy to find.
Just look for the area
with the commotion
and that's where he'll be.
He's right.
Uhg. I wish he'd
at least remember
that he has a bounty on
that rubbery head of his.
Especially while we're in
a big country like this‐‐
[ZORO] Forget about Luffy,
He can take care of himself.
Now let's go find some food.
We can get to work after that.
They're all the same!
[VIVI]
I guess I should let you know...
Karoo and I
can't go with you.
What's wrong?
Don't feel up to it?
We'd both be way too
recognizable here.
Makes sense.
No worries!
I'll take care of all of
your shopping, Vivi, my love!
[KAROO squawks]
What's wrong, Karoo?
[VIVI]
Mr. 3's ship!
[USOPP groans]
I thought we took care of
that creep for good already.
I'm certain it's him.
That ship couldn't
even run without Mr 3's
Wax Wax Fruit powers.
The bastard's here.
This isn't good...
...'cause he's seen
most of our faces.
Usopp has a plan.
It's gonna be all right.
[CITY FOLK chattering]
[USOPP]
There's no telling where he is,
so we have to move
without standing out.
[NAMI] This is your
idea of blending in?
Hah! Looks like it's
safe to come out, guys.
Thanks, we figured that one out.
It looks like my ingenious
disguise worked like a charm!
Oh yeah, I'm sure
that's what it was.
Well then.
it looks you should be
safe from prying eyes
for a while, my dear.
Hello there?
Uh, yes!
Sanji, what were you saying?
[SANJI] What is it Vivi,
is something wrong?
Sorry for that...
...but, I'm just
really relieved now.
If nothing else...
from what I've seen so far,
I know that at least
this town is doing all right.
I can't exactly
start resting easy...
...but it's a good sign.
[CITY FOLK chatter]
[NAMI] It does seem like this
is a really peaceful town.
[ZORO]
Vivi.
[VIVI]
Huh?
You said you have a plan
for stopping the rebel army,
didn't you?
Well, what are you going to do?
And what do we
need to do to help?
If you really want to stop
this thing before it starts,
it's better to act quickly.
Well, I agree with that,
but the only agreement I made
was for you to bring
me here to Alabasta‐‐
Quit it!
Are you still
thinking like that?
Nami...
We traveled this far
together, after all.
We're not gonna run away
and leave you now.
Yeah, Vivi, come on.
You're practically
one of us now.
[ZORO] And I wanna see
this Warlord of the Sea.
You didn't need
to bring that up.
Now listen!
We're not going to abandon you.
They're trying to kill us too.
Well, everyone except for me.
Yes, but...
It's settled then!
Besides, if this
country gets destroyed,
then we'll be out
a big reward for
bringing you here in the
first place, you understand?
[VIVI]
Uh, yes!
Okay good!
You're such a good friend.
[NAMI]
Thank you, Zoro!
I haven't forgotten about
your debt to me, either.
[ZORO]
You‐‐
Even as a ghost, I'd still
haunt you for my money.
You lousy‐‐
[NAMI] You better pay me
those 400,000 Berries.
[ZORO]
What?! It went up?!
[NAMI] It'll go up even higher
if you don't pay me quickly!
[ZORO]
Usopp, do you think you could...
Thank you.
[SANJI]
Nami's right about this.
[ZORO]
What?!
[VIVI] A little Northwest
of the city we're in now
is an oasis called Yuba.
That's where the rebel army
is based at the moment.
I'd like to go there first in
order to head off the rebellion.
But, in order to get to Yuba,
we're going to have to cross
through the desert first.
We'll need all the
necessary supplies to make it.
We can find everything we need
easily here in this town.
But if Mr. 3 is out there
somewhere waiting for us...
[SANJI] If that guy's
the only obstacle,
we shouldn't have a problem.
He's never seen my face before.
Yeah, you really haven't
run into many of
the Baroque Works agents so far.
There's someone else, too.
[NAMI]
That's right, Chopper!
[SANJI]
That'll be perfect.
We're going to have
a lot to carry.
That all right?
Yeah, I got it.
[USOPP]
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I want to do whatever
I can to help out.
[gasps]
I should blend in fine
like this, shouldn't I?
[USOPP] All right! Now that's
what I call a brave reindeer.
[VIVI]
I really appreciate your help.
[SANJI]
Just leave it to us.
[VIVI] I made a list
of everything we need.
Oh, and we'll need
some clothes, too.
[SANJI]
Huh?
[VIVI] Normal clothes,
so we won't stand out.
[SANJI]
Ah.
[NAMI]
And perfume too?
[SANJI]
Of course, Nami.
‐‐[ZORO] And food and water.
‐‐[USOPP] Tabasco.
‐‐[ZORO] Remember the food.
‐‐[USOPP] And Tabasco‐‐
‐‐[SANJI] Who cares about you?
‐‐[USOPP] Tabasco!
[ZORO]
Shut up with that!
[NAMI]
And keep an eye out for Luffy.
Damn it... Where could that
idiot have run off to now?
[LUFFY sighs]
[LUFFY] Doesn't really
seem like there are any
restaurants in this place.
Aww man.
Where the heck have
I ended up, anyway?!
[LUFFY]
Oh well.
I guess I'll just
go back that way.
Mm!
[LUFFY]
That's smoke.
If there's smoke, there's fire.
And if there's fire...
...there might be cooking!
[CITY FOLK chattering]
‐‐It's venison.
‐‐[CHOPPER gasps, whines]
That's what's great
about traveling around.
They have all sorts of
interesting ingredients to try.
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
[SANJI]
What's wrong, Chopper?
There's a strange scent mixed
in with the smell of the food.
In what way?
Oh, what you're smelling
is just perfume.
[CHOPPER]
Perfume?
[SANJI] Yeah, that shop
over there sells it.
[CHOPPER]
Uck...
I just don't like
that smell at all.
Can we get out of here?
Sanji!
Hello, my darling.
Your outfit's ravishing.
But nothing in the world can
possibly compare to your
amazing eyes and your
beautiful smile.
What do you think?
We could go somewhere‐‐
[WOMEN, SANJI yell]
‐‐[WOMAN A, WOMAN B laugh]
‐‐What was that, Chopper?!
‐‐It was getting good‐‐
What are you doing, we came
here to shop for supplies!
Yeah, I know that!
It's getting to be too much...
I can't stand the smell anymore!
Now, now. Relax, it's okay.
Just let me take
care of the shopping.
You can wait over there, 'kay?
Darling! Wait for me!
[CHOPPER]
Is he actually going to shop?
[CHOPPER panting]
[CHOPPER]
This isn't good.
I think I'm starting to get
symptoms of heat stroke.
I need to find someplace where
it's cool and shady, quickly!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[CHOPPER panting]
[CHOPPER exhales]
[CHOPPER]
Ah... that's nice.
I'll just take a quick nap
until Sanji gets back.
That'll be okay, I'm sure.
It‐‐It'll be fine...
Is it closed?
Yeah, it's good.
All right, then let's get going.
[SANJI]
Hm...
‐‐[CITY FOLK chattering]
‐‐Where did my reindeer go?
[CHOPPER snoring]
[VIVI] Nanohana is famous
for selling perfume,
but the perfume itself
is actually made at an
oasis called Katorea.
It's to the west of here a ways.
[LUFFY]
Hm...
I dunno, this doesn't really
look like a restaurant.
Is anyone here?
A fire's going,
but no one's here?
Hey! Water!
[groans]
[LUFFY] Come on, is a
little water too much to ask?
What are those things?
[LUFFY]
Hm.
Just a bunch of green powder.
I wonder if it's food?
Doesn't look very tasty,
that's for sure.
[LUFFY]
Bleh, that's so gross! Yuck!
Who would eat this stuff,
it's disgusting!
Oh, that's perfect!
[grunts] This stuff's
obviously some kind of poison.
But now it's gone!
Well, that was a big waste
of time, but there's gotta be
a restaurant around
this place somewhere.
[THUNDER rumbling]
What is that?
It's rain.
Oh, this is good!
‐‐[KAMONEGI gasps]
‐‐[LUFFY] I can have some water!
What's this!
[KAMONEGI screams]
The bags! Where are they?!
What the hell did you
do with my bags?!
What's the problem?
[KAMONEGI] Shut up and
tell me what you just did
with all that green powder!
[LUFFY]
Oh that? It's all burned up now.
You what?!
My precious dance powder!
It was my treasure!
[LUFFY]
Hey, what's the matter?
What are you so sad about?
You burnt all my powder!
Do you have any clue
how much that cost me?
No, and why would you
want that poison anyway?
[KAMONEGI]
That's none of your business!
Now shut up and
give me my dream back!
Wait, that stuff was your dream?
That's right!
That powder was going to
help me achieve all my goals!
[LUFFY]
I'm sorry.
Sorry's not good enough!
You have to pay me for it!
Can't do that.
I don't have any
money I could give‐‐
[KAMONEGI]
Bastard!
I've come so far...
I even...
built this cabin here...
[LUFFY]
Hey, don't be so down.
Can't you just buy some more?
It's not all that easy to get.
The World Government
has outlawed the powder,
it's illegal to
make or sell it!
[LUFFY]
Illegal?
Oh really?
So you're a criminal?
[KAMONEGI chuckles]
That's right!
Now you die!
[CHOPPER]
Mm?
Hey, what is this place?
What's going on?
[CHOPPER gasps]
[MAN B]
Hm?
[CHOPPER]
Oh no! Who are those guys?
And what am I doing here?
[gasps] Rifles!
[MAN A]
What's wrong?
[MAN B]
Thought I heard a voice.
It's nothing, never mind.
[CHOPPER]
I don't know what's happening,
but they seem dangerous.
I should probably get
out of here quickly!
That didn't feel good...
Well done, men.
That took a while.
[MAN B]
Yeah...
[MAN A] The weapons
dealer raised his prices,
so we had some
negotiating to do.
It makes sense.
If he ever gets discovered,
he'll be in as much
trouble as we will.
[MAN B]
Where's Koza?
[MAN D]
Inside.
[MAN B]
We picked up some food, too.
It's in the back.
[MAN D]
Got it.
[yawns]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[MAN D]
What's this all about?
They went and bought
an entire deer?
[MAN B]
Koza.
We were able to
get some weapons.
A few, at least.
[KOZA]
Well done.
I know it was a dangerous
job to give you.
[MAN B]
It was fine.
Koza... is something the matter?
[KOZA]
Just the usual.
Our country is doomed.
[MAN B] If it doesn't
collapse from the inside,
one outside attack
will finish us.
Whatever the case, this peace
right now is temporary.
Now that 300,000 of the royal
army have switched to our ranks,
we have enough men.
But we're still falling short
on weapons to arm them.
[KOZA]
And food to feed them.
We are all running out
of the strength to fight.
There's no reason for shedding
any more unnecessary blood here.
We need to settle everything
for good with our next attack.
This country has got to change,
and it's up to us rebels.
[gasps] Hey, wasn't
there some venison
in the back here earlier?
[MAN D]
Yeah.
Are you sure someone didn't
take it out already?
[LASHES grunts]
Damn... we can't afford
to lose any food now.
[LASHES grunts]
What is it? Water?
There's some in that
trough over there,
‐‐[LASHES whinneys]
‐‐drink that.
Hey, let's get the rest
of this stuff outta here.
Give me a hand!
[REBELS]
Right!
[CITY FOLK chatter]
[LASHES grunts]
So... am I safe now?
Oh, thank you! That's a relief.
But why did you
even help me at all?
[LASHES whinneys]
"I don't really have a reason...
...I'm just cool
like that, I guess."
[laughs] I agree, that's cool.
[LASHES grunts]
Thanks a lot, mister camel!
[LASHES whinneys]
He may be a little strange,
but he sure is really nice!
I wonder if I'll see him again.
More importantly
than that, though,
I wonder who all
those people were.
Hm. Well, now I'll
just find my way back.
Uhg, this way.
Haha, well you certainly
are a strong one, aren't you?
Sure am, no one can beat me.
Yeah I'm not surprised.
Your fighting style is
very unique! Sorry about that.
Oh no, no, no.
I'm the one who burned
up your powder stuff.
‐‐[LUFFY] I'm sorry.
‐‐[KOMANEGI] Uh, no!
Why don't we just go ahead
and say we're even.
Oh, and...
...if you think you could avoid
telling anyone about the powder,
that would be just great!
Wait. What was
that powder stuff?
What? You don't know?
Well, it sure was gross.
[KOMANEGI exclaims]
Well it isn't food!
It's a very special substance
known as Dance Powder.
What's Dance Powder?
[KOMANEGI] Well there's
another name for it.
It's also called
Rain‐Summoning Powder.
That's what caused the
sudden downpour we just had.
Uh... would you like
me to explain more?
I wouldn't understand.
I guess you wouldn't, would you?
[BOTH laugh]
Hey, don't be so rude, old guy.
Like I was saying, this
powder is very special.
It can be used to artificially
produce rain, right?
Good, all right.
Dance Powder works like this.
When you burn it, you
release it into the air,
and it's like planting a
type of seed, a rain seed.
[KOMANEGI yammering quickly]
Well, does all that make sense?
So... it's mystery powder.
[KOMANEGI] Yes,
well done, that's it exactly.
You being rude to
me again, old man?
Why would you wanna
use the powder
to make rain in the first place?
[KOMANEGI] You don't
even know the first thing
about this country, do you?
[LUFFY] Nope. I just
landed here by boat.
[KOMANEGI] Well you
see here in Alabasta,
we're constantly
battling drought.
[LUFFY]
What do you mean?
[KOMANEGI] Drought is
when there is no water
and the land dries up.
[LUFFY groans] I know that much!
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[KOMANEGI groans]
[KOMANEGI] Anyway, our country
never gets much rain.
But it's become much more
scarce in recent years.
[LUFFY]
That sounds bad.
[KOMANEGI] And most of
the oases have dried up.
[LUFFY] So just use the
mystery powder, then.
That's what you would think!
But as I told you, the
World Government has now made
Dance Powder illegal.
Use of the powder is a crime
punishable by execution!
[LUFFY]
Mm.
[KOMANEGI] The powder
is also supposedly what
started the country's rebellion.
[LUFFY]
Really?
[KOMANEGI] I don't know
much about that, though.
[LUFFY]
Oh.
Hey, I think I get it now!
Was it your dream to
help save your country
by using that powder?
Earlier you said the powder
was really important.
Uh... yeah...
...but that wasn't exactly
what I had in mind for it.
Then what was?
Well...
...I thought by selling
water in these hard times,
I could make a lotta money!
‐‐[LUFFY] Yeah, you're right...
‐‐Ya know?
You must be really smart.
Oh well. I don't
really care about that.
I just need to find
someplace to eat.
But, but, but, but, but, but!
Please don't tell
anyone about this.
Let's keep it between us, okay?
Sure, whatever...
makes no difference.
[KOMANEGI]
Please just don't tell!
I'll give you anything
you want! Anything!
Ooh, anything?
[KOMANEGI]
Anything at all!
Well, it was fun!
And thanks a whole lot for
the food, weird old guy.
Sure! I only hope you enjoy it!
Oh, trust me, I will.
See you around, rude old guy!
Remember not to
tell anyone, okay?
[LUFFY] Yeah, you got
nothing to worry about.
Besides, I couldn't even
turn you in if I wanted to.
Huh?
After all... I'm a pirate!
See ya! Thanks again
for the lunch!
Hey... Not fair.
[NAMI]
Wow! This is beautiful!
Oh yeah, love it!
Uh... well...
I know I asked you to pick
out some clothes for us,
but these were meant
for dancer girls.
Oh, Vivi! You're a vision.
But commoners
wouldn't wear this.
But aren't dancers common?
We're crossing a desert!
Hey, don't worry!
If you get tired, my darling,
I'll just carry you!
[SANJI laughs]
This is pointless.
‐‐[USOPP, ZORO chewing]
‐‐[SANJI] Now then,
‐‐let's take a look at you guys.
Compared to the lovely ladies,
you two look like
sloppy bandits.
You might wanna
look in a mirror.
Hey Chopper!
‐‐[KAROO slurping]
‐‐What are you doing?
‐‐[CHOPPER groans]
It's that smell!
Oh yeah, where did
you run off to?
Just somewhere.
[NAMI]
Is he not feeling well?
Yeah, it's just the perfume.
Chopper can't stand it.
‐‐[NAMI] Perfume?
‐‐[VIVI] Oh, yeah...
Tony has an incredibly
sensitive nose.
This stuff?
Some of it does have
a really strong smell.
Oh...
[CHOPPER screams]
[SANJI] You smell
just like an angel in a
field of fresh flowers!
You're an idiot.
[SANJI yells]
At any rate.
At least we've managed to
gather all the supplies
that we're gonna need
to cross the desert.
Yeah...
This oasis... you said
it's called Yuba, right?
Yes, that's correct.
But first we'll have to
travel through the desert.
That trip... will most likely
be a lot more difficult than
any of you can even
begin to imagine.
There's no telling what
might happen out there.
One wrong step at any moment
in a desert land like this one,
and there's no guarantee
that we'll all survive.
I'm still a little reluctant
about asking you to
follow me into such
a dangerous place.
But more than anything,
I want to bring peace
back to Alabasta Kingdom.
So I guess...
I guess I don't really
have any choice but to ask.
Help me! Please, help me
bring peace back to my country.
Please help...
[NAMI]
Well you finally said it.
[VIVI gasps]
It's about time.
There's no telling what might
happen on the sea, either.
We're used to it. Am I right?
Yeah, it'll be just
like any other day.
Cool! I can't wait
to see the desert.
[KAROO squawks]
Okay, you guys! Are you all
ready to head out for Yuba?
[ALL]
Yeah!
Thanks...
Are we missing someone?
[ALL]
Luffy!
Good food... want more.
[NAMI]
That idiot!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[NAMI] Where in the world
do you think that idiot
could have run off to now?
[ZORO]
Oh no! Hide! It's the Marines!
[USOPP]
What's all the fuss about?
Did something happen here?
[SANJI] Some idiot pirate must
be on the loose in the area.
[LUFFY]
Hey you guys!
[ALL]
Luffy!
[ZORO] Aw, jeez,
it's that evil look alike!
I'm outta here!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Heroes' Reunion!
His Name is Fire Fist Ace!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!