Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
20 years ago, everything
was taken away from me.
And many innocent
lives were lost.
With one push of a button,
they summoned a terrible demon.
Now it rears its head again.
Aiming its sights on the friends
I've searched so hard to find.
The more that I wish
for us to be together,
the more my ugly fate
bares its fangs at you!
Even now, no matter
how far we sail,
there's an enemy that
haunts me at every turn!
Because I'm facing the world,
and all of its darkness.
First it was Aokiji,
and now CP9.
I've dragged you into
my troubles twice already!
If it goes on and on like
this, no matter how kind
you may be, someday,
you'll see me as a burden.
Someday you'll be forced to
betray me and throw me away!
That's what I'm most
afraid of! Understand?
That's why I didn't
want you to rescue me!
If that's the
only future I have,
I'd rather die
to save me the pain!
There you have it!
Yep! Right on the mark!
What a sorry case!
Even if you make friends,
all you can do is drag them
through the mud with you!
You can't win, pirates.
Look at this flag!
This symbol represents the
unity of over 170 nations.
A power that spans the
four seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world itself!
No matter how loud
your bark may be,
you can't stand up to an enemy
like that! Just face it already!
Do you realize how
strong our organization is?
Do you realize how devoted
we are to capturing her?
If that's Robin's enemy,
then I know what to do.
Sniper King.
Hm?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger.
This my new weapon, a massive
slingshot by the name of Kabuto!
Behold its awesome power!
Special Attack Firebird Star!
No way!
Mission complete.
Now they've done it!
Those idiots!
You can't fire on a
government flag! That's crazy!
Those pirates just declared war
against the World Government!
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win!
Yeah? Bring it on!
Robin! There's still something
I want to hear you say!
Tell me you want to live!
Robin.
I can live?
I never dared to wish
for something like that.
The world had
denied me that hope.
The sea's a vast
place so I guarantee.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
Believe in Luffy.
But now.
If I'm allowed to say my wish,
just this once. Then I--
I want to live!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
You guys! You're
so awesome! I love you!
Let's go!
"I'm Not Gonna Hand
over the Blueprints!
Franky's Decision."
All right!
We pulled the lever!
Bring down the bridge!
Looks like Mozu took care
of things on her side, too.
Go, Straw Hat!
Look! The drawbridge
is lowering!
Our reinforcements pulled
it together after all.
And just in time, too.
I'm trembling with excitement!
Come on, hurry up!
Lookin' scary there, Zoro.
Hey, Robin! We'll save you!
No matter what!
Stay away!
They're in high spirits!
They've sure got guts
burning down our flag.
They're just idiots.
They dug their graves the
second they set foot here.
No, stay over there!
That got it! Go, Straw Hat!
The rest is up to you!
Damn you, pirate scum!
We'll never let you though!
Prepare the mortar cannon!
Don't let them cross the bridge,
even if you have to destroy it!
Yes, sir!
No way I'm gonna
let you do that!
Pipe Hitch Knives!
You've got three heads
too many! Dismantler Chop!
Chief Justice Baskerville, no!
Psych! Joke's on you!
We're actually the
Chief Justice Trio!
Known as the Left Baskerville,
my true name is Bas!
Known as the Right Baskerville,
my name is Kerville!
And as for me, the Center
Baskerville. Call me Princess!
What is wrong with you?
You mean all this time it
was three dudes stuck together?
Why would they do that?
'Cause we're the
best of friends!
That's just weird!
Now, fire the trench mortar!
Fire!
What happened? Why'd it stop?
Damn those marines!
They really piss me off!
Stop getting in the way!
We got it, Chief Spandam!
Evacuate the Tower of Law!
Good work. And also good advice!
This should buy me enough time
to get to the Gates of Justice.
All right, move it!
Someone grab Cutty Flam
and bring him too!
Robin!
They're nobodies.
Just a bunch of scum.
As long as I've got CP9 here,
I'm practically invincible!
Better yet, I've also
got the only person
who can revive the
ancient weapons, Nico Robin.
Not to mention the man
who inherited one of their
blueprints, Cutty Flam.
I'm not letting this
slip through my fingers!
I'll crush as many
pirates as it takes!
What? What the hell is it?
Is that-- No-- It can't be.
Those aren't the real
blueprints for Pluton.
Oh, they're real.
Don't believe me?
Lucci, Kaku, you
guys can tell, right?
Suppose we should've
seen this coming.
If you can hide soda
and weapons in your body,
you can hide blueprints
just as easily.
So, they are real?
They're really real?
That's great!
Then hand them over!
Saves me the trouble
of searching for them!
Nico Robin.
I gotta admit,
the rumors I heard about
you were about as
wrong as they could be.
While the government was
dragging us to this crap hole,
I realized that you aren't
the monster that's gonna
use the ancient
technology for evil.
I know the shipwrights from
Water 7 have been passing down
these blueprints from
generation to generation,
but we're not doing
it to revive a weapon.
Tom had achieved so
many wonderful things.
But he gave up everything
to keep these blueprints
hidden from the world.
As long as the risk
remains that a woman
named Nico Robin can figure out
how to restore the weapon,
then the world
needs these blueprints
to be able to fight back!
Hey, Spanda.
The reason why Tom and
Iceberg risked their lives
to protect this is simple.
Just give me the blueprints!
If an ancient weapon
fell into the hands
of some power-hungry
dumbass like you,
who knows what might happen.
In other words,
the shipwrights passed
this blueprint down to create
a possible countermeasure
against another weapon.
Now I agree that
Robin's a dangerous woman.
As long as people
like you are around,
even if she has the best
intentions, her knowledge
could still be used to wreak
havoc on the whole world.
But now she's got
friends who are willing
to risk their lives to
make sure that never happens.
And I think they're up to
the job. So I'm making a bet.
Now that everything's
gone to hell,
I have to get a little
creative if I'm gonna uphold
the wishes of the
original architects.
Just shut up and hand
them over already!
Those blueprints are mine!
Tom, if you were here, I'm
sure you'd do the same thing.
Now that everything's
gone to hell,
I have to get a little
creative if I'm gonna uphold
the wishes of the
original architects.
Just shut up and
hand them over already!
Those blueprints are mine!
Tom, if you were here,
I'm sure you'd
do the same thing.
What the hell are you doing? No!
My dream! It's
been burnt to a crisp!
We spent five years
on our mission for this?
The only reason we were keeping
those blueprints was to
create a countermeasure.
So if you took 'em away,
that would defeat the purpose.
Now that it's come to this,
destroying 'em is all I can do.
But I'd rather sacrifice my own
plan than help you with yours.
If you end up making
a weapon after all,
we won't be able to
fight back anymore,
and that's possible
if you're able
to take Nico Robin through
the Gates of Justice.
Everything's resting
on the Straw Hats,
and if they're able
to get her outta here,
then you'll be left
with nothing at all.
I've placed my bet.
I think they can do it.
You've made a mockery
of me for the last time.
Laugh it up while you can,
because you're not
leaving this island alive!
Big Bro!
Hey! Look! We're all
down here, Big Bro!
Look guys! Big Bro's
right over there!
That means we're not too late!
Oh! You're right, I can see him!
Don't worry, we'll
save you no matter what!
We came with the Straw Hats!
Sodom and Gomorrah
fought hard, too!
We're all going home
together! I promise!
They didn't hurt you, did they?
What? No way!
Aw, damn it you guys.
I didn't ask you save me.
I didn't ask you
but you still came!
I'm not crying!
You hear me, you bastards?
Shut up! That's enough!
Whoa, Luffy!
Calm down!
Robin's waiting! Hurry up
and bring down the bridge!
Oh yeah, right.
What the hell are
you waiting for?
No kidding! Get moving already!
Don't make me come down there!
Uh, yes ma'am.
Wow Nami, you're sexy
when you boss people around!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Thanks for helping out my men
while I was gone, but now
that the gang's all here.
The one and only
Franky will show you
how super his gratitude can be!
I don't need your help!
I'm still mad about
what you did to Usopp,
so don't think we're friends!
He's, uh, right
next to you, ain't he?
Cutty Flam, how dare
you burn my blueprints!
I'm gonna make you pay!
Bro!
Big Bro's falling
down the waterfall!
Franky!
Hey! Straw Hats!
Huh? Granny Kokoro?
I heard everything. Why are
you all just standing around?
We're not "standing around"!
The bridge broke--there's
no way over!
It's halfway down, isn't it?
That's more than enough!
Hang on - I'll be there
in about four seconds!
Jump into the waterfall! Give
it all you've got! Trust me!
Oi, look! Here it comes!
Monster Granny?
What did she say?
Well she said "Jump
into the waterfall".
Holy crap! Is that a train?
What's it doing
inside the courthouse?
Chimney! Sound that
whistle as loud as you can!
Okay!
Look, it's the sea train!
Hey. What's up with
that devious chuckle?
Chief Justice!
Get out of the way!
Don't you dare!
Let's go!
Rocketman's as fast as
the day it was made!
I'm gonna show you
why Tom's Workers is
the most legendary ship-building
company in the world!
Is that Rocketman?
It's flying!
Please, go away!
Waterfall!
Brings back memories,
don't it, Tom?
Giving a hand to that Roger guy
is something I'll never forget.
In fact, it's something
I take great pride in!
My name's Luffy and I'm gonna
be King of the Pirates.
Really?
Yep.
That boy may have a screw loose,
but come to think
of it, so did Roger.
It's funny, all those years
ago you helped him out,
and now Tom's Workers
is coming together again
to help out this Straw Hat Boy.
We sure didn't learn
our lesson, did we?
But I gotta feeling you woulda
done the same thing, Tom.
We're gonna crash!
Hey! What the hell are we doing?
We've come a long way,
but Robin's still in trouble.
We'd better do something
before they take her
through the Gates of Justice.
Guess there's no way around it.
We're gonna have
to take out CP9.
We don't have much time,
so we'd better split up!
Everyone, you gotta win,
even if it kills you!
On the next One Piece:
"Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!