Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] While making
their way to the New World,
the Straw Hat crew were
confronted by the Accino family,
a clan of bounty hunters.
[FRANKY]
Coup de...
...Burst!
[NARRATOR] The Sunny managed
to escape the Accino family
and free itself from the Frozen
Highway for a brief while.
But then the very soul
of the ship, the pirate flag,
was stolen from them.
[USOPP] Shimmering
behind a pirate fla--fla--
What the hell?
[NAMI] Our flag! It's gone!
[NAMI] Huh? What's that?
[NARRATOR]
The seemingly sentient icebergs
turned out to be controlled
by the strange Domo Penguins.
[USOPP yelling]
He's too far!
[NARRATOR] And with the
Straw Hat crew split up
and effectively weakened,
the Accino family
made their move to
pick them off one by one.
[LIL laughing]
[LIL] Will you play with me?
It'll be fun.
[BRINDO] Oh, how rude of me.
I am the second son
of the Accino family.
The name's Brindo.
[BRINDO]
Ohohohoho!
Ohoho! Ohoho! Ohohohoho!
[LUFFY] The Straw Hat's
Hard Battles!
A Pirate Soul Risking
it All for the Flag!
[LUFFY]
What the heck's Lovely Land?
Lovely?
[BRINDO] Ohohohoho!
What is it?
Well, it's your flag's new home.
The fortress stronghold
of the proud Accino family.
[BRINDO] A place so splendid...
...that even our
prisoners are turned over
to the marines with
a smile on their face!
Yes!
The great Lovely Land!
I don't care
about your house!
But I haven't gotten
to the interesting part--
[LUFFY] Quit running!
[CHOPPER] Luffy!
Well...
You caught me off-guard
earlier, but trust me.
It won't happen a second time.
Hey, raccoon dog!
I'm a reindeer!
[BRINDO] Your captain's
quite the fool, huh?
I mean, what kind of pirate
leader lets his flag get stolen?
[BRINDO]
And the rest of you scum?
You have a world
of hurt coming to you.
I'm going to personally
escort you to hell
for covering up that
cowardly captain of yours.
All right.
I see you won't listen.
A shame, really.
You'll never know what
happened to your flag now.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
[BRINDO] Damn.
I thought I could wear him out,
but this guy
has energy to spare!
[BRINDO] He seems
to be speeding up, too!
I can't keep dodging
like this forever!
Your ship is really cute.
Does it have a name?
Of course.
It's the Thousand Sunny.
Thousand Sunny?
[giggles]
And you? What's your name?
Oh, my name?
My name's Robin. Nico Robin.
Robin, huh?
[ROBIN] Yes.
I saw you earlier, didn't I?
[LIL] You noticed me?
Of course I did.
You surprised me the way
you appeared all of a sudden
out of nowhere.
So, Lil.
Do you happen to know
any of this ship's crew?
Thousand Sunny's crew?
I don't think so.
I see.
--Then perhaps you could
--But I do know where the crew's
--tell me a little something--
--flag is being hidden.
[gasps]
[LIL]
You're looking for it, right?
Mm-hmm, So where is it?
[ROBIN]
Won't you please tell me?
Maybe. If you...
If I...?
[LIL] If you play with me!
Play a game with me
and then I'll tell you.
All right. I'll play.
[LIL] Really? Awesome!
Y'see, my big sister
won't play with me lately.
She's busy playing with Salchow,
so she ignores me
to be with that jerk.
[laughing]
Yes! Beautiful!
Salchow! Look at us!
Our form is a work of art!
[USOPP] What's goin' on
with these two weirdos?
They're not even
bothering to attack.
All they do is
spin, spin, spin,
spin around us!
[SALCHOW] Jump and kick!
[SALCHOW]
Arbell...
...this rink today...
The surface is...
...quite exceptional!
Dammit!
--[ARBELL] Jump and kick!
--[USOPP] Ooh! The pain!
[ARBELL] You're right,
Salchow, darling!
Skating on this ice...
We're flawless!
Doesn't look like
they're planning on
letting us out of here.
Hey, Sanji.
Huh?
We're gonna be in trouble
if we don't get back
to the Sunny, right?
Yeah.
Then why aren't
you doing anything
to stop these two?
[ARBELL] La-la!
Wahhhh!
[SANJI] I can't take
how sexy she is!
It's killing me!
[USOPP] I should've known.
It's always the same
with this guy.
One-track mind.
That's it!
[USOPP] Hey, you two!
You were the ones who
stole our flag, weren't you?
Tell me where you
stashed it, right now!
--[SALCHOW] We're just glorious!
--[USOPP] Answer me!
[SALCHOW, ARBELL]
La-la-la-la-la!
[USOPP] Geez. I'm
surrounded by lunatics.
I have a feeling we're
about to make Papa's day.
He'll be so happy once
we collect their bounties.
But of course, Salchow.
He'll be so proud.
By the way, I think we're
properly warmed up now.
Our bounties, huh?
So that's what this is?
[SALCHOW] Here goes!
[SALCHOW, ARBELL]
Love... Throw!
[SANJI] Arbell--
[SANJI] Ow.
[SALCHOW] Once more!
[SALCHOW, ARBELL]
Love... Throw!
A gorgeous rocket of beauty
soaring into my arms!
Not what I expected!
Damn.
Hitting me with a flying lady?
Now that is unforgivable.
[HOCKERA]
Hoh-ke!
[NAMI] He's one of
the guys from before.
[FRANKY] Yeah.
[NAMI] You're the creep who
stole our flag, aren't you?
Hm? Someone stole your flag?
Eh... Now who would do that?
Hoh ke ke ke!
You didn't?
Huh... Let's go.
This is a waste of time.
Okay.
And besides,
it's too cold out here.
[HOCKERA]
Whoa, whoa, hey, time out!
You can't just abandon a match!
Fine, I admit it!
My family's responsible
for stealing your flag, okay?
Then where is it?
Where?
Hm... Where did we put it?
We're not staying
unless you know.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Time!
Don't go! Not yet, at least!
I'll tell you where
the flag is if you stay!
Tell us now.
Now? Where was it again?
I'm done with this guy!
[HOCKERA] Time!
Time, time, time, time!
I didn't know they had missiles!
Shooting rockets is
not a fair fight, dammit!
If you fight like a real man,
then I'll tell you!
I'm way too cold.
You handle him, all right?
--[FRANKY] Heh heh. Sure!
--[whistle blows]
[HOCKERA]
Now, let the game begin!
If it's a missile match,
you're gonna lose!
[FRANKY]
As if it wasn't cold enough.
Maybe I should've worn pants.
[FRANKY] Come on!
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke ke ke!
[FRANKY] Dammit.
It's getting harder to
see with all this smoke.
I thought this guy
seemed like a joke earlier.
But I can't hit him while
he's flailing around like that.
And the cold is starting
to limit my movements.
I'm in trouble if
I don't hit him soon.
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke ke!
This is starting to get boring.
What's the point if I can't
even see your stupid face
when I beat you?
Huh?
Wait! You're shooting
blind, just like me!
You're gonna run
outta ammo at this rate!
[HOCKERA babbling]
I liked it better
when he couldn't see me.
Well I like it this way.
[HOCKERA]
Ke ke ke...
[ROBIN] So, which hand
do you think the coin is in?
Gimme a second.
It's this one!
So, Lil.
What?
[ROBIN] Where do you think
they could be hiding the flag?
[LIL] I don't know.
[ROBIN] Or you just
don't wanna tell me?
I don't know.
[laughing]
Okay! Stop!
I'll tell you where it is!
--Really?
--I'll tell you where it is!
Yes! Really, really!
They keep the
flags in Papa's room.
[ROBIN] Papa?
Yep! And he's got a pretty
big collection of 'em, too--
A whole room
full of pirate flags.
That many, huh?
[LIL] Today's our Papa's
big birthday party.
That's why everyone's
out trying to get him
the best present they can!
[ROBIN]
So the flag's his present?
No. Bad guess.
[LIL] These are the presents.
[LIL] He's got
a 300 million bounty.
This one has a hundred
and twenty million bounty.
There's a 44 million
bounty for this guy.
And then you.
There's an 80 million
bounty on your head.
Isn't there?
Now Gum-Gum Pistol!
You care that much about a flag?
Of course we do!
That flag is a symbol
of our pride!
It's the most
important thing we've got!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum Axe!
Quit butting into
our conversation,
little raccoon dog.
This is a private talk
between men.
Shut up!
I'm more of a man than you are!
Really. You're just
annoying me now.
And what're ya
gonna do about it?
--[CHOPPER] Shut up!
--[BRINDO] So close!
You almost had me that time.
[BRINDO] What're ya doing?
How're you gonna get that
flag if you defeat me here?
C'mon, just think about it.
Who's gonna take you to
Lovely Land if you knock me out?
Careful!
[LUFFY] Don't worry,
he'll still be able to talk.
I'll break everything
but his mouth.
[BRINDO]
I should've expected this
from a man
worth 300 million.
The only way
I can make this work
is if I can get them to
follow me to Lovely Land.
All right now.
Let's stay calm.
I'll talk--
Where's the flag?
You bastard!
Wait! Please...
No! Stop! Please, I give up!
White flag.
See, the truth is that I've
actually got the flag on me.
Here, I'll give it to you.
Luffy!
Give us back our flag!
Dammit!
[LUFFY yelling]
No!
He fell for
that one, literally.
If you wanna get your flag back,
you're going to
have to chase me down!
[BRINDO] And as for the
rest of you pirate scum...
Your time is coming, too!
[JIRO] Captain Puzzle!
[SUTTON] Puzzle!
[muffled screaming]
[CHOPPER] Luffy!
[SALCHOW, ARBELL]
Love Throw!
There's no doubt that these
are the guys who stole our flag.
It's obvious.
You've brought the wrath of
the Great Usopp upon yourselves!
Stupid lovebirds!
And now... Flame Star!
[ARBELL] My head's on fire!
Arbell, no! Oh! No, no!
And now you know
the consequences
of hurting a
pirate's pride! Ha!
[SALCHOW] Nobody sets
my honey's head on fire.
We were perfectly
synchronized, you fool!
[SALCHOW]
You long-nosed bastard!
[USOPP] I'm sorry!
Luffy! He fell into
the sea! Save him!
If he can't swim,
why'd he jump?
'Cause of the flag?
[CHOPPER] Luffy!
Come on, you can't
swim either, remember?
Ah! I forgot!
[TROFF] What? You idiots!
How can we head out
to sea without our flag?
Find it right now!
[ALL] Right.
Hey. You should put it back now.
The crew's gonna tear the
ship apart searching for it.
All right.
This is the flag that's gonna
make me the King of the Pirates.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
Still, I think you can do it.
I mean, after all,
you are our captain.
Nobody's ever
gonna take us down.
[cannon fire]
[laughing]
[RANDOM PIRATE 330A]
The Phoenix flag! Ahhh!
What? Really?
You gotta be kidding me.
You're clearly not
cut out to be a pirate
if you're that afraid
of a little fight.
"A little fight," huh?
They know the beat down
that's in store for them
when they see that flag.
[PUZZLE] Yeah.
[LUFFY coughing]
[CHOPPER] Luffy!
--I thought you were done for!
--He's all right.
[CHOPPER] Don't ever do
something like that again!
You really scared me!
I'm so happy you're alive!
[chuckling]
[CAMPACINO] For you.
They still haven't caught them?
You got their
flag though, right?
[CAMPACINO]
It'll be here soon, Papa.
You just relax.
Do I not look relaxed?
[CAMPACINO]
Oh no, of course you do.
But everyone seems to be
dragging out the fun a bit,
so I hope you don't mind, Papa.
Wait.
Did somebody just walk by?
[CAMPACINO]
No. I don't think so.
Maybe you've had too much wine.
[ACCINO] Hm...
Well, hurry up with that flag.
[CAMPACINO] Sure.
I'll check on their progress.
Hey.
[CAMPACINO] Yes?
I want Straw Hat's bounty.
Don't worry, Papa,
you'll get it.
What the hell's
this place 'sposed to be?
Ha! The next duel
will be decided by speed!
Speed, huh?
All right, if that's
how you wanna play.
Coup De Vent!
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke!
[whistle]
[HOCKERA] Game over.
Super!
Oh... Guess that
was the last of my cola.
What's taking so long?
It's too cold to be out here.
[FRANKY]
Well, that was some fight.
Sorry. That took a while.
[NAMI] I was gonna see if
I could find a warmer place
so I tried to make this thing
work, but it won't even turn on.
It's no use.
[FRANKY]
What's the problem here?
I have no idea.
That rumble was so annoying.
And it's too
cold to think clearly.
Just get this thing working.
Rumble?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, crap.
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke ke ke!
There! It's frozen over!
Your fault.
Never let your guard down.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
Yeah? What is it?
Right. Yeah.
Two?
Well, that's pretty good.
Sure. Okay.
I understand.
[sighs]
[LIL] Go! Flying fish!
Okay, let's get
back to the game.
[ROBIN] What happened?
That was one of
my older brothers.
He said he captured
two of the bounties.
[LIL] This one, and this one.
[LIL] But forget about that.
I wanna play some more. C'mon.
Right. Of course.
But wouldn't it be more fun
if we played at your house?
Huh? You actually
wanna go play at my house?
[ROBIN]
Sure, will you take me there?
Yeah!
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke ke! Hoh ke ke!
--Let us out of here,
--Damn it, let us out!
--you stupid jerk!
[HOCKERA] Hoh ke ke!
Hoh ke hoh ke hoh ke ke!
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke ke!
[LUFFY] Whoa, what's going on?
How can there be
two of the same guy?
[CHOPPER]
Oh, is it a Devil Fruit power?
[LUFFY] Maybe it's some kind
of cool fighting technique.
Hey, Chopper! Let's try it, too!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah! I want another me!
But how do we do it?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Hot Full Throttle!
The Twins' Magnetic
Power Drawing Near!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!