Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of
pirates go to battle
across the seas in search
of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will
cut a path across
the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison Impel Down.
[NARRATOR] While Buggy and
Mr. 3 escaped from Level 4,
Luffy, who had been poisoned
by Warden Magellan,
was whisked off to a mysterious
haven for prisoners
known as New Kama Land.
There, he received treatment
from its leader, Ivankovs.
I know what's going on
in the world right now.
There's been a shift in the tide
and big changes are coming.
The Navy and the Whitebeard
Pirates are taking center stage.
Even so, the "big man's"
still waiting things out.
I'm of course referring
to my comrade,
the leader of all
revolutionaries in the world.
You may know him as Dragon!
Oh, you're talkin'
about my dad.
[IVANKOV]
What?
[IVANKOV groaning]
Your dear papa.
And I never knew! Goodness!
[NARRATOR] After hearing
that Luffy is Dragon's son,
Ivankov decided to join him
in his efforts to rescue Ace.
[IVANKOV] The Vivre Card was
pointing down, which means
he's still here and still
alive, thank goodness.
[MAGELLAN]
This is it, Portgas D. Ace.
You're going to be
transferred to Marineford.
Upon your arrival there,
you will be taken to
the execution grounds.
[LUFFY]
"Ace's Convoy Begins!
Battle on the Lowest Floor,
Level 6!"
--[footsteps]
--[LUFFY] Ace!
--[LUFFY yells]
Hurry up!
Don't let them get past us!
[LUFFY growls]
--Ready?
--Move it, I'm in a hurry!
[GUARD A]
Aim.
[LUFFY]
Now, Gum-Gum. Pistol!
[GUARDS scream]
[GUARD A whimpers]
Oh yeah? How do you like this?
[LUFFY grunting]
[IVANKOV] What a bothersome
little trap. Ha! Death. Wink!
[GUARD A screams]
--[IVANKOV] Heehaw!
--[applause]
We're short on time.
Huh? Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
--[GUARD A groaning]
--Huh?
[GUARD A grunts]
[GUARD A] W-Who are you
people? How did you--
Hello, there.
I'm going to need to
borrow you for a moment.
[GUARD A protesting]
--Take it easy.
--[GUARD A] No wait!
--It won't hurt, I promise.
--Stop it! Lemme go!
[INAZUMA] Almost there. Let's
just hope we're not too late.
All right guys,
don't let 'em through!
[GUARDS yell]
I don't have time for this!
Now, Gum-Gum. Ricochet!
[GUARDS screaming]
[HANNYABAL growling]
[GUARD D]
The trap didn't work, sir!
And all the jailers
are out cold!
[HANNYABAL growling]
[GUARD D] Straw Hat Luffy,
Ivankov, Queen of the Queers,
and Inazuma, the revolutionary!
All three criminals are
now entering Level 6!
What are we gonna do?
[LUFFY]
Ace!
We made it. This is Level 6.
It's known as the Eternal Hell,
where only the most legendary
of criminals have been held.
Hey, Ace! Where are you?!
It's your brother!
I'm here to save you!
Can you hear me?! Ace!
[IVANKOV]
The direct approach is a no-no.
[GUARD A whimpers]
That's where you
come in, sweetie.
Mind telling us where he is?
Uh-uh! No way!
Oh! Whatever shall I do?
[GUARD A]
Ah!
[IVANKOV]
We need to be more open,
with each other,
and with ourselves!
Ah! What are you doing?
[IVANKOV]
Emporio...
--...Female Hormone!
--[screams]
Is this me?
[LUFFY]
Whoa! He turned into a girl!
[IVANKOV] It's the you, you were
always afraid to be. Look.
I'm... beautiful.
[IVANKOV] You've been
reborn, my dear.
You're no longer a jailer.
You're a New Kama now!
Oh! Thank you!
What have I been doing all
of these years? My gosh.
I don't know how I can
ever repay you, Iva!
[IVANKOV] Oh, it's nothing.
Don't mention it.
Ah, there is one thing--
Where is Ace?!
Down that way!
--[foot steps]
--[JIMBEI] Mm?
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[LUFFY panting]
This one?! Ace?!
[panting] He's gone!
Are you absolutely certain
that this is the right cell?
Yes, I promise you!
He-He was just here, I swear!
We're a bit late, it seems.
[JIMBEI grunting]
[JIMBEI] A straw hat?
Then it's him. It must be.
[ACE gasps]
She said that my
brother is here.
[JIMBEI]
She was telling the truth!
I never thought anyone could
penetrate this fortress,
let alone make it all
the way to Level 6!
[LUFFY]
Uh?!
[JIMBEI] You there!
You're Straw Hat, aren't you?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
[JIMBEI] You're a moment
late! He was here!
They took him to the elevator
for the prison transfer!
Go! There's still a chance
you can catch them!
Thanks, but who are you?
My goodness it's you.
All right. Let's move. Thanks
for the help, whoever you are.
[LUFFY IVANKOV panting]
[JIMBEI]
Who is this boy?
To brave the impossible, to
accomplish the inconceivable,
and to charge into yet another
struggle more hopeless
than the last? And Ace knew.
[ACE] My brother really
would break into here!
He does stupid things without
thinking all the time!
Since we were kids,
he's always been reckless
and made me worry
about him! That idiot!
[JIMBEI]
Mm...
[LUFFY, IVANKOV panting]
[INAZUMA] They took that
elevator to the upper floors.
Let's go!
[INAZUMA] Thankfully,
they've left the gate open.
[LUFFY]
Nice!
[IVANKOV groaning] It seems
like the operation system
is locked up! It won't budge!
[LUFFY]
Uhh. Well, that sucks.
All right.
We'll just have to climb up.
There's no other way!
--Do it!
--Sir!
[LUFFY grunts]
Oh, man! That was close!
[IVANKOV pants]
Ah, I see.
They can't let things be
convenient for us, now can they?
We'll just have to find
ourselves another way.
They're watching us.
[SECURITY SNAIL grunting]
[IVANKOV]
Let's go back to the stairs!
[LUFFY]
M-Uh?!
[LUFFY grunts]
Oh yeah, just try it.
[ALL gasp]
Hey! Those jerks
blocked the staircase!
They're trying to trap us.
We'll just have to break
through then, won't we?
[LUFFY]
Sounds good!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL grunt]
[INAZUMA] That's an awful lot of
gas. Do you think it's deadly?
[PRISONER A]
Poison gas, again?
[PRISONER B]
Hey, you! Listen up!
I don't know who the hell you
punks are, but if you're gonna
get yourselves killed,
don't take us with you!
Shut up! Nobody cares!
Doesn't matter if it's
poisonous, I've gotta go!
Wait!
[LUFFY growls]
Well, there you have it.
Sleeping gas.
The boy didn't even give
it a second thought!
At least try to stay alive!
Get outta here already! Move!
[PRISONER C] This is the
last thing we need! [groans]
I see. They're hoping to
stop us without a fight.
How cowardly.
[GUARD C] Vice Warden. Level 6
is now blocked off completely.
The sleeping gas
is highly effective,
and there's nowhere to run.
Just in case,
keep the guards on standby.
Did you report all this
to Warden Magellan?
[GUARD E]
Yes, sir! Just now.
[HANNYABAL]
Good!
That means I get
to keep my job!
Now to place the blame for this
entire fiasco on Magellan, then,
I'll become the Warden!
Uh, Sir,
the microphone's still on.
C'mon man!
[MAGELLAN growls]
What do you know,
Straw Hat made it to Level 6
just after we left,
unfortunate timing for you.
[ACE gasps]
L-Luffy!
I wasn't in the mood for a nap,
but it seems we're
out of options!
[snoring]
It's all over.
The emergency sleeping
gas has flooded Level 6.
It's only a matter of time
before they catch Straw Hat.
Apparently, the Freezing Hell
wasn't punishment enough
for him. Since the cell you
were in now has a vacancy,
Straw Hat will have
a taste of the torment
reserved for our most
heinous criminals.
[ACE gulps]
Luffy.
[GUARD G] No one told
you to stop! Keep walking!
[ACE sighs]
--[ACE grunting]
--[GUARDS groaning]
--[GUARD H] Why you...!
--[ACE grunts]
[GUARDS groan]
[MAGELLAN growls]
[GUARDS groaning]
[ACE grunting]
[ACE growls]
[MAGELLAN growls]
[ACE groans]
I assure you,
resistance is futile.
[ACE groans]
Luffy!
[MAGELLAN]
Your brother's a pirate.
His fate was sealed the moment
he stepped in this prison.
[ACE] Damn it, Luffy.
I'd hoped Hancock was lying.
[MAGELLAN]
But this troubles me.
No matter how strong he is,
he shouldn't have recovered
from my poison, and so quickly!
How did you do it, Straw Hat?
How did you survive?
We made it back to Level 3!
--[BUGGY sighs]
--[MR. 3 groans]
But that's only halfway home.
[MR.3] Sadly, I think we moved
faster on the way down
thanks to of all those times
we fell through the floor.
[BUGGY] I'm so thirsty. I think
my legs are going on strike.
[screams]
[BUGGY]
What is it?
Hm... Let me rest for a
minute, will ya?
[yelps] What the...?!
[SPHINX growls]
Hello!
Gnocchi.
[MR. 3 yelps]
[BUGGY]
You're still here?!
[SPHINX grunts] Penne!
Buckwheat noodle with egg!
[MR. 3 yelping]
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
Let us go!
[SPHINX] Buckwheat
noodle with fried tofu!
Wheat flour noodle with curry!
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
Shut up!
Come on! Do something!
The whole floor's
filling with gas!
Someone, help!
Who the hell is this guy?!
He's cutting a stone floor
like it's made of paper!
Huh?! Now he's flipping
it up like a ribbon!
Well, that's one way to deal
with the problem, I suppose.
I don't get it, but I like it.
[IVANKOV]
Inazuma ate the Snip-Snip Fruit,
so now he's a scissor-man.
[IVANKOV] He can manipulate
whatever he cuts
as though it's made of paper.
[LUFFY grunting]
Really? That's cool.
--[LUFFY snores]
--Don't fall asleep!
If you doze off on me,
I might get drowsy.
But... I never sleep!
[LUFFY]
Stop doing that!
Good morning.
[LUFFY] We gotta keep
going up, crab guy!
Thanks for blocking out the gas,
but now I can't go up
the stairs to get to Ace!
This is the only way to
prevent the sleeping gas
from filing up the room.
If you're unconscious,
you can't save anybody, can you?
I'll save him whether
I'm unconscious or not!
I'm not gonna let him die,
you understand?
[INAZUMA]
Don't be ridiculous.
It was a simple plan,
but it defeated us nonetheless.
As much as I hate to admit it,
we're trapped here on Level 6,
at least for the time being.
Sorry, buddy. Well,
this is all I can do.
At least the jerks
can't watch us now.
Well, we gave it a good shot.
But no time for regrets.
I'm sure that by now, they've
made their way to the top floor
to hand off Ace
for the transfer.
Even if we could get out,
we'd have quite the mélange
of obstacles in our way.
The Navy's convoy is quick, too.
Take a look at the Vivre Card.
[LUFFY grunting]
[IVANKOV] It's not pointing
straight up anymore, is it?
[LUFFY]
Uh...
[IVANKOV]
That means that Ace
has already been handed
over to the Navy.
You're right on time. Very good.
Impel Down hereby transfers
custody of the criminal,
Portgas D. Ace, to the
Navy forces present today.
[GUARD I sighs]
--[ACE] Here.
--[LUFFY] Huh?
But it's just a scrap of paper.
[ACE] Do yourself a favor
and always hang on to that.
That scrap of paper
will reunite us one day.
[LUFFY]
Yeah?
[ACE]
You don't want it?
No, I'll keep it.
Luffy. [grunts]
C'mon! It's time to start
thinking of ourselves.
The first step is
your escape. I promise.
I will do my very best to break
you out of this prison safely.
As far as Ace Boy
and the Navy goes,
that ship has already
sailed, literally.
Give up on him, 'kay?
Or rather, put your
faith in Whitebeard.
There's no way he'd give
up on one of his own!
He'll come up with something.
--I'm leaving.
--Huh?
I'm going to Marineford.
[IVANKOV groans]
Don't be stupid!
A massive battle is
about to take place
between two of the most powerful
forces in the entire world!
Do you have any idea
how strong Whitebeard is?
What about all the admirals,
vice-admirals, and the
Warlords on the Navy's side?
Remember them?
[IVANKOV] And are you
also forgetting that how
close to death you were after
the fight with Magellan?
Do you have that
many lives to spare?!
[IVANKOV]
What is it?!
Look. If I give up now,
I'll regret it.
[IVANKOV gasps]
[IVANKOV] I know that face.
I've seen it many times before!
It's the face of his father.
Staring at me, unflinching.
[INAZUMA] You can do as
you like, but first of all,
how do you propose we
get off of this floor?
[PRISONER chuckles]
[IVANKOV, INAZUMA, LUFFY]
Huh?!
If you want out that
bad, then set me free.
I'll make a hole in the ceiling
and you'll be free to go.
--Sound good?
--[chains rattle]
[PRISONER chuckles]
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY] No way!
They've got him down here, too?
--Crocodile.
--[CROCODILE chuckles]
Just like old times, huh?
Did ya miss me?
[NARRATOR] Luffy and his
friends recruit Crocodile
and Jimbei, forming a
plan to catch up to Ace,
and escape from Impel Down.
Meanwhile, Hannyabal
hatches a plan of his own,
with the intent of
intercepting them on Level 4.
With nowhere left to run,
a full scale battle breaks out
inside the walls of the prison.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Ultimate Team is Formed
Shaking Impel Down!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!