Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] As Luffy and his crew
journeyed to Fishman Island,
they passed through a
patch of Sea Snake Currents
to reach the Red Line,
the halfway point
along the Grand Line.
[LUFFY]
It's the Red Line!
I can't even see the top!
It's huge!
So this is the Red Line.
[LUFFY] Anyway,
we're halfway there!
[NARRATOR] Their victory
proved short-lived,
for even though they
had seemingly reached
their destination,
Fishman Island
was nowhere to be found.
[NAMI] Even if we know
which direction to go,
that doesn't tell us
how to get there.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Rifle!
Hey! Something flew
out of its mouth.
A fish?
Whoa!
Hell yes!
[NARRATOR] Emerging from the
belly of a giant Sea King,
the mermaid Camie and the
starfish fishman Pappugu
find themselves on the deck
of the Thousand Sunny.
[LUFFY] He Hates
the Straw Hat Crew!
Iron Masked Duval
Makes his Appearance!
[CAMIE]
Are you all right?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm great!
[screams]
Oh my gosh!
There's a bunch of humans!
Uh, yeah?
Okay, let's all stop screaming!
[CAMIE] I'm sorry,
I was just startled.
Anyway, thanks
for saving my life.
It feels like I'm always
getting swallowed by sea kings.
This was probably the 20th time.
You gotta stop that! Jeez!
There has to be some way
to pay you guys back.
Oh! Octopus fritters!
You have some?
Ooh, gimme gimme!
Sure thing!
They're 500 berries each--
how many can I put you down for?
[ALL]
Huh?
You're not selling 'em!
I'm not, am I?
[SANJI]
I finally met a real mermaid!
Mermaids!
Loved by sailors
the whole world wide!
Mermaids!
The jewels of the sea!
And she's adorable!
Just like I imagined!
I'm kidding, you're
even better than I imagined!
You said your name was Camie?
This is the best day
of my whole life!
I've never seen a
real mermaid before!
[USOPP] Come on,
that's not true. Remember?
You met Granny Kokoro,
didn't you?
Gigantic monsters? Zombies?
That was nothing.
That's not fear.
My heart already felt
the true meaning of terror
when I saw her.
--[SANJI] I--
--[USOPP] It's okay!
I know just how you feel.
Let's just forget that
ever happened, Sanji.
She's the first
mermaid we've met!
Could you be any more rude?
Huh?
Are you saying that Granny
Kokoro was a mermaid?
But she could walk and stuff.
[FRANKY]
I see.
Guess you never
found out, did you?
You were busy
fighting that Lucci guy
when she saved us from drowning.
[KOKORO]
Everybody freeze!
Don't you die on me!
Granny Kokoro
was cool and all,
but thinking of her as a
mermaid is really gross.
[NAMI]
You'll be old someday, too!
[LUFFY] That hurt!
Why are you so strong?
[NAMI]
Jeez!
I've had enough of you men and
your gross mermaid fantasies.
But still, she is
rather cute, isn't she?
[BROOK]
Yohoho!
This is my first
encounter with a mermaid,
as well. Yohoho!
Pardon me,
but would you be so kind
as to lend me some money?
What the hell, Brook?
A skeleton!
Look! Now you're
scaring her, you big freak.
Get out of here!
Hey, I can open my head.
Pretty cool, huh?
That is cool!
[USOPP]
And now she's fine.
So I gotta know.
How do you poop?
[SANJI]
What is wrong with you?
Oh! Poop, yeah--
She doesn't poop!
--You're the one pooping here,
--[CREATURE] Uh, hey, Camie?
--on my dreams!
--Hello? Camie?
Aren't you forgetting someone?
Like a friend that you might
have neglected to include
in your fun little chat?
Someone like me?
So, uh,
one question, Camie.
What is this thing?
Like a talking glove, maybe?
Oh, no, no,
this guy is my pet.
His name is Pappagu.
He's a starfish,
and also my teacher.
Teacher?
Yep! That's him!
This guy?
Yep!
Wassup?
Is it normal for
starfish to talk?
As normal as it is for
your pet to be your teacher.
I let her take me in.
We have our reasons.
[PAPPAGU (SONG)]
♪ Camie!
♪ She feeds me clams,
what can I say? ♪
♪ I am what I am!
[NAMI]
That's your pet food?
[guitar playing]
[PAPPAGU (SONG)]
♪ A starfish is a star,
♪ and when people don't
know who you are, ♪
♪ it's so rough.
♪ Will I stick around?
♪ Well, I'm no sucker but my
suckers are sticky enough. ♪
♪ Does anybody need a hand?
♪ Don't sweat,
I've got plenty! ♪
♪ But as for fingers,
♪ Baby-cakes, I don't got any.
♪ No fingers! Wahoo!
Yeah! Thanks, everybody!
C'mon, this is the part
where you guys're
supposed to laugh.
[PAPPAGU laughing]
[CAMIE] My T-shirt
is made by "Criminal".
They're a really popular
fashion label on Fishman Island.
[CHOPPER]
That's pretty cool!
And Pappagu is
their lead designer.
I wanna be one, too, someday,
so that's why he's teaching me.
[SANJI]
You can do it!
Whatever it is, you can do it!
[CAMIE] Aw, thanks!
That's so sweet of you!
No one listens to me.
[SANJI] You know you
could be a model, too!
You should put on
a fashion show for us!
[CAMIE]
Oh, no. I don't think so.
[LUFFY] So, glove guy,
how can you talk?
I'm so glad you asked!
He got over that one quick.
[PAPPAGU] See, back when I was
a kid, I was a little confused.
I thought I was a human.
But by the time I figured
out I was a starfish,
I already knew how to talk!
Wow, I didn't know
talking worked like that.
The brain is a powerful
thing, my friend.
They say you can do anything
you put your mind to.
Anyway, whatever.
I'm Pappagu, the Starfish.
Up-and-coming fashion designer.
Thanks for saving me.
Seriously, you guys
are the best.
[NAMI]
We're lucky we met you.
The truth is, we're a bit lost.
Since you're from
around here, can you t--
No, Nami!
Octopus fritters first!
Right, I forgot.
I won't charge you, either.
Hold on, let me call Hatchin
and we'll work out
a meeting spot.
Who is Hatchin?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL dialing]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
Hey, it's Camie.
Are you doing okay, Hatchin?
Sorry, I got kinda lost.
So where are you right now?
[MALE VOICE] Oh,
so it's Camie, is it?
Muhahaha!
[CAMIE]
Hatchin?
[MALE VOICE] You don't know
who you're talking to.
This ain't your buddy Hatchin.
[CAMIE] What?
You're not Hatchin?
[MALE VOICE]
Of course not!
Listen, this is Macro from
the big, dumb Macro Gang!
Wait. I shouldn't
say that, myself.
My goodness,
this sounds like trouble.
What are you doing with
Hatchin's transponder snail?
[MACRO]
Muha!
We beat him up
and stole it from him--
what do you think?
Muhahahaha!
[CAMIE]
Yeah, right. Don't lie to me.
There's no way Hachin
would lose to you!
[MACRO]
Normally, you'd be right.
We aren't really
a match for him,
but this time we teamed up
with The Flying Fish Riders
and he didn't stand a chance!
Muhahahaha!
The Flying Fish Riders? Damn it!
[HACHI]
Nyuu! Camie, you're all right.
Well, that's a relief!
[CAMIE] Hatchin, don't tell
me they really beat you!
[HACHI] Nyuu.
I let my guard down.
Anyway, no matter
what they tell you,
don't come to save me.
I'll beat these guys somehow
and get out on my own.
I'll meet up with you later,
so don't worry.
Hatchin...
[MACRO] Muhahaha!
You know, Camie,
we were planning on
selling your friend here.
Octopus fishmen
fetch a high price,
so if you want to save him,
you'd better hurry.
Oh, for the record, we're
at the Sabaody Archipelago,
5 kilometers east of grove 44.
And did I fail to
mention this is
the Flying Fish Rider's hideout?
Because it is.
[HACHI] I'm telling you,
Camie, don't come here!
[MACRO] Shut up suckerface,
no one cares!
[punching noise]
[MACRO]
Ha. See you there!
Hatchin...
Uh, hey...
Camie.
So... the fritters...
--This isn't the time for that!
Hold on a second.
Her friend on
the transponder snail
sounds awfully familiar to me.
And they said he was
an octopus fishman.
It's my imagination.
There's no way, right?
[CAMIE]
Sorry, Luffychin,
but can I give you your octopus
fritters some other time?
It's just that I have to save
my friend before it's too late.
[LUFFY]
Uh...
[SANJI and FRANKY]
Hey!
[NAMI]
So, Camie,
I know this might come
across as meddlesome,
but if you're going
to rescue your friend,
you don't have to do it alone.
You can leave that to us.
Wait. I said that wrong.
What I meant is that
you can leave it to them.
Hey!
--You're not our boss!
In return, you can show
us the way to Fishman Island,
which is a good deal,
since you're probably
headed back there anyway.
Are you sure? Really?
[NAMI]
Of course!
Right, Luffy?
Huh? Sure.
You'll beat up all the bad guys
for me, Luffychin, really?
And you'll save Hatchin?
[LUFFY] I guess, but
who is this Hatchin guy?
[CAMIE] He runs the octopus
fritter shop where I work.
He makes the best snacks
in the world--promise!
Battle stations, men!
We're gonna save
those octopus fritters
even if it kills us,
you hear me?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ALL] Octopus snacks!
Octopus snacks!
Well now that
they're motivated,
can you show me the way?
Let me see.
[PAPPAGU]
Grove 44 is a tiny island
right here on the east
edge of the Archipelago.
They said 5 kilometers
east from there,
so I'm guessing the Flying Fish
Rider's base is in this area.
As for us, we're
about here right now,
so if we head due west,
toward Sabaody,
we'll hit it on the way.
Bam. Simple as can be.
We can ask some
fish for directions
before we set off.
Right. Sounds good.
Let's do this!
Hey!
[CAMIE's call echoing]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[LUFFY] Look! All the
fish are coming up!
We need directions from you!
[CAMIE's call echoing]
They're scared of the
Flying Fish Riders
so they won't get too close,
but they will show us the way.
Oh wow!
I didn't know you
could talk to fish!
Maybe the men are right!
Mermaids are really something!
You know,
if you stick around,
we can eat all the fish
in the whole world--
You need a time out?
Huh? Watch your mouth!
[NAMI]
Hmm.
But one thing is bugging me.
How are we supposed
to follow fish?
Check it out for yourself!
Awesome!
Man. I guess fish
are a lot smarter
than I give them credit for!
See? Check it out.
They're drawing
an arrow in the water!
Perfect!
We shouldn't have any
problem following that!
That's just--
Wow, so cool!
Oh, stop.
Any mermaid could
do the same thing.
Don't be so modest!
We don't know any better!
[USOPP] Okay! I'm gonna
take the helm!
[ROBIN]
Four o'clock, Usopp.
Got it!
All right!
We ready?
Go!
[MACRO] So there you
have it, Master Duval.
Everything's going
according to plan.
They fell right into our trap.
The mermaid's on her way
here even as we speak.
[DUVAL]
Good.
Hey, men.
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Yeah, boss?
[DUVAL]
Go greet our new friends.
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Yes, sir.
[MACRO]
Uhm, one little thing.
She's worth a lot of money,
so try not to rough her up
too much if you don't mind.
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Hmph.
Man, this is gonna
work out great.
Hate to break it to you,
Hachi old pal,
but you and Camie
are done for this time.
It's all right. You can cry.
I was just kidding,
you big baby.
I didn't think
you'd really do it.
Muhahaha!
Hey, Zoro.
I noticed the
Sunny is setting off.
Did we finally find
a way to Fishman Island?
Forget that! Check it out!
It's a real-life mermaid!
Her name's Camie.
Isn't she cool?
Nice to meet you!
She's a mermaid, huh?
[ZORO]
Never seen one before.
It's gone!
He erased his memory!
She has a friend that makes
real good octopus fritters,
so we're gonna save him
first so we can eat.
I'm kind of worried.
Hatchin didn't sound like
himself at all when we talked.
I'm afraid they've done
something awful to him.
[PAPPAGU]
Ehh, he's tough enough to cope.
I wouldn't worry 'bout it.
You guys, on the other hand,
were awful quick
to offer your help,
but are you positive you're
not in over your head on this?
You kidding?
[PAPPAGU] All right,
well fair warning,
these guys aren't the
only kidnappers in the area.
There's a whole bunch
of crews just like them.
[PAPPAGU] The Sabaody
Archipelago's a hotspot
for kidnapping.
Human trafficking is
big business around here.
You mean like
slave trading or something?
Pretty sick stuff.
And seeing as mermaids
fetch a high price
on the market,
a trio of fishmen that call
themselves the Macro Gang
have been targeting
Camie for a long time.
[PAPPAGU] We were stuck in that
sea monster's belly for a while.
Hachi probably
got worried about us
and figured the Macro Gang
kidnapped you or something.
then he went after
them to rescue you
and got kidnapped himself.
Yeah. That must be it.
Hachin's so kind, and he's
always looking after me.
This is all my fault.
Guy's named Hatchin, huh?
Reminds me of that dumbass
octopus from way back.
If it's that guy,
there's no way I'm helping him.
But what're the odds, right?
Usually Hachi
can take those guys,
or anybody else,
for that matter,
but with the
Flying Fish Riders involved,
it's a whole
different story.
[FRANKY]
'Kay, but who are these guys?
[PAPPAGU] They're another one
of those kidnapping crews
I mentioned.
They've really been
running the place lately.
Word is, once they target you,
you're as good as done for.
[PAPPAGU] Their boss Duval
is this scary guy
with an iron mask.
Nobody knows what
his face looks like.
Anyway, it seems like
they're looking for someone.
They've been stopping every
ship that comes by here
and checking out their crews,
member by member.
Man. They sound
like a real pain.
Eh, how tough
can they be? It's fine.
Don't worry, Camie.
We'll get the octopus
fritters back for sure!
That's fritter "salesman!"
I-I'm sure you're
right, Luffychin!
[LUFFY]
Of course I'm right!
Hey Brook! Why dontcha play
a song to lighten the mood?
Yohohohoho!
With pleasure, Captain!
[violin playing 'Binks' Brew']
[violin continues]
Whoa! What?
[USOPP] Hey, guys!
We're in trouble!
Did something happen?
What's the matter?
The fish said they're sorry,
but they can't
take us any further.
They're scared.
Wait, what? Someone's here?
Ah!
Look! It's the
Flying Fish Riders!
[LUFFY] Where?
I can't see anything!
Hey! Camie!
Where are you going?
You have to hide!
They're in the sky,
not the sea!
Look up!
Wow, they really can fly!
That's awesome!
They're our enemy, remember?
Damn it.
Attacking us head on!
They have seats and handlebars
and everything! Whoa!
Hey! It's them!
[FISH RIDER 386B]
Yeah! You're right!
Those are the Straw Hat Pirates
down there, no doubt about it!
Let's contact the boss!
[FISH RIDER 386B]
You got it!
[FISH RIDER 386A] I thought we'd
only make it out with a mermaid.
This is our lucky day!
[FISH RIDER 386B] Master
Duval is gonna be thrilled
when he hears this!
Here they come again!
They're dropping bombs.
Buncha jerks.
--Now, Gum-Gum...
--72 Caliber...
--[LUFFY] ...Pistol!
--[ZORO] ...Phoenix!
That was a close one!
They're not finished!
Once they're out of the water,
flying fish can stay in
the air up to five minutes!
[FISH RIDER 386B] Yep,
that's right, Master Duval,
there's no doubt in
my mind that it's them.
Huh? Wait.
Sorry, sir,
I missed that last part.
Turn around!
He told us to go
back to base!
[FISH RIDER 386A]
But that's ridiculous!
[FISH RIDER 386B]
Boss's orders. Who knows?
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Fine, but I don't get it!
They're gone?
[DUVAL]
Macro.
[MACRO]
What is it, Master Duval?
[DUVAL] That mermaid
you were luring here
is on a pirate ship right now.
Were you aware of that?
[MACRO]
Huh? Camie? No!
[DUVAL] The very pirate ship
I've been searching for
all this time.
All my suffering,
all my waiting,
will finally
come to an end.
[DUVAL]
I'll have my revenge!
I'll kill that bastard
that ruined my life!
[HACHI] Nyuu! Camie, run!
This is a trap!
[ZORO] That voice, and that
silhouette. It's gotta be him.
[LUFFY] Ugh!
I don't want to save him!
Even if octopus fritters
are at stake,
we can buy 'em
somewhere else!
You stay in that cage!
[HACHI]
Nyuu!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Fated Reunion!
Save the Captive Fishman!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!