[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy raided Navy HQ to rescue
his brother Ace from execution,
only to see him
killed before his eyes.
[NARRATOR] Although he
escaped to Amazon Lily,
he found himself
consumed with despair.
[LUFFY] I couldn't save
my crew or my brother!
[JIMBEI grunts]
[LUFFY grunting]
Boy, you can't see
a thing. You're blind.
There is yet joy
beyond your sorrows!
What's gone may be gone,
but you still have something
left in this world to treasure.
Don't you?!
[inaudible]
My crew...
I still have my crew!
[sighs]
[LUFFY]
I wish they were here right now.
I miss them.
I miss my crew!
[cries]
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[NARRATOR]
Along the Grand Line,
there lies the ruins
of Muggy Kingdom,
found on a place
known as Gloom Island.
Yikes, we're in trouble now!
[HUMANDRILLS growling]
Whoa, they're angry!
[HUMANDRILLS chattering]
[HUMANDRILL D grunts]
What did that one just say?
How should I know?
Either way, I'm not chattin'
it up with these guys.
There's no point!
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO grunting]
[HUMANDRILL D yelling]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO]
Three-Sword Style...
...Bull Demon...
...Bold Hooves!
[HUMANDRILLS yelling]
Oh, no! How many of
these things are there?
[ZORO]
Damn. They're smart.
They're using weapons
just like a human!
[HUMANDRILLS yelling]
[ZORO]
Three-Sword Style...
...Dragon Twister!
[HUMANDRILL D grunts]
[HUMANDRILLS yelling]
[ZORO]
Whoa!
[ZORO grunts]
[HUMANDRILLS grunting]
[ZORO groans]
[ZORO]
They reopened my wound.
Is that what they
were aiming for?
[ZORO groans]
[yells]
[ZORO panting]
[HUMANDRILL J growling]
[ZORO pants]
[ZORO grunts]
[HUMANDRILL J growling]
Um, you're not dead, are you?
[ZORO]
Shut up.
This is no time
for you to annoy me.
What? How dare you accuse
me of being annoying
when I'm genuinely
concerned for your safety!
Whatever, I don't care,
get eaten by the evil
monkeys, why don't you?
[ZORO grunts]
[HUMANDRILLS chattering]
Tch. Well, I'm screwed.
[HUMANDRILLS yelling]
[footsteps]
[HUMANDRILL K gasps]
[HUMANDRILLS yelping]
[footsteps]
What's that aura?
[ZORO gasping]
It... It's him!
There's no way!
It's Hawk-Eye.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, in Birdie
Kingdom in the South Blue,
where the birds are constantly
at odds with the humans.
[yelling]
But I don't wanna
be your dinner!
We catch raccoon
again for hot pot!
Raccoon taste good!
I already told you idiots!
I'm not a raccoon!
[CHOPPER yelling]
Hey, Papa, why yummy raccoon
saying he not raccoon?
You making no sense.
Raccoon no can saying words.
I'm saying words right now,
you overgrown potato!
Maybe you'd hear them
if you'd shut your fat mouth!
I'm a reindeer and I can speak
like a proper human, unlike you.
Oh, and I'm a doctor, too!
That's stupid.
No way can be talking
doctor raccoon.
Then how you know
what he saying, Papa?
Wha-wha-wha?!
I'm glad we're on the same page,
can you get me down now?
[DAD NATIVE A]
Me helping.
[CHOPPER gasps]
[CHOPPER laughs]
Awesome!
This is special cream
for fixing burns.
We using many
plants for medicine
that help making better
all kinds of sickness!
[gasps] Is there more
where this came from?
I'd love to see it!
We no more have them.
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
Big tree on mountaintop
growing plants we
needing to make medicine.
But last year, mean birds
make nest on mountaintop.
Never letting us get more plant!
Almost have no
good medicine left.
But more and more people sick!
[coughs]
[BOY A]
Friend have big cough.
This is awful.
[GIRL NATIVE A panting]
No can breathing.
[CHOPPER]
She could easily die from this.
[DAD NATIVE A]
No more do nothing!
We fix bird problem forever!
We only doing what have to do!
Me not afraid!
Go helping my family!
[GROUP yelling]
[BOY A]
Papa!
Son. Me sorry.
You protect mama now.
[MOM A whimpers]
[NATIVES chattering]
Hey! Wait a second,
you guys! Don't rush this!
As a doctor, I can't turn
my back on sick patients.
Don't worry, I'll
go talk to the birds
and ask them to stop
picking on you, okay?
Raccoon can talk bird?
I sure can! All I gotta do
is ask them nicely, right?
But first, I am not a raccoon!
Don't make me say it again!
[grunts]
Seems like I got along okay
with the baby bird at least.
Should be no problem. I hope.
Hey, raccoon!
Me not want to say
me no trust you,
but me not thinking mean birds
gonna listen so well
to nicely asking!
When bird get angry,
then we go do attacking!
[NATIVE B]
Mm.
[CHOPPER grunts]
[gasps]
Yo!
[squawks]
Listen up.
I have a really important
favor to ask of you!
The humans in the
forest have a problem
and a bunch of them could
die without your help!
[squawking]
Huh? You say you're not letting
them take the treasure?
And what treasure is that?
[CHOPPER screams]
Bird angry!
[CHOPPER]
Was it something I said?
[gasps]
[CHOPPER screams, groans]
Ugh.
Oww.
[BIRD A growling]
Rumble...
...Arm Point!
[CHOPPER grunting]
[CHOPPER] What treasure
are you protecting?
Why do you hate humans?
Why do you want them to suffer?
[BIRD A squawks]
[CHOPPER]
You're here!
Talk no good against mean bird!
[BIRD A squawking]
One choice left!
[BIRDS squawking]
[squawks]
[DAD NATIVE A grunts]
[BIRDS squawking]
[DAD NATIVE A gasps]
[CHOPPER]
Guard Point!
Raccoon, no!
[BIRDS squawking]
Oh, man!
I can't get the
humans or the birds
on this stupid island to listen
to a single word I'm saying!
[BIRDS squawking]
This sucks!
[gasps]
[BABY BIRDIE A chirping]
[CHOPPER]
It's you!
The chick from the other day!
You sure grew up
fast, didn't you?
[caws]
[CHOPPER]
All right, listen up this time!
[squawks]
[BIRDS squawking]
[BIRD screeches]
[BOTH gasp, squawk]
[BIRDS squawking]
[CHOPPER laughing]
[CHOPPER]
I get it now!
What happen?
Raccoon make friend
with birds after all?
[grunts, gasps]
[BABY BIRDIE A chirping]
[CHOPPER]
Here's the deal.
Turns out the birds have
a good reason to act this way.
They like to collect
sparkly stuff,
so they gathered treasure
from all over the world
and stored it on
their home island.
But when some bad guy
humans found out about it,
they came to their nest to steal
their stuff and chase them away!
They were scared that the
same thing might happen here,
so they were just
protecting themselves!
[FEMALE NATIVE A gasps]
This plant!
Use for medicine!
[CHOPPER grunts]
Guess that oughta do it.
I'm glad this worked out,
'cause I'm gonna need some more
of that ointment
as soon as you've got it.
[BOY A]
Uh, oh! Raccoon sleepy!
[gasps]
It doesn't hurt.
--[BIRDS chirping]
--[NATIVES chattering]
Shiny. You can keep!
[BIRD A squawks]
[laughs] You guys
already hit it off, huh?
[NEWS COO squawks]
[CHOPPER]
Hey, a News Coo!
Thanks for the newspaper, buddy!
[NEWS COO squawks]
Now, let me see.
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
on the Sky Island of Weatheria.
[NAMI sighs]
You're supposed to put your
back into farm work, you know!
Goodness, you're such
a lazy young lady!
I'm not lazy, you old
sack of wrinkles!
I wanted to learn about
weather, not do manual labor
in your stupid field
while you lecture me!
I'm getting sick of this!
There's no reason you can't
do both at the same time.
This isn't ordinary farming.
This Weather Field is where we
grow all of our Weather Balls.
Hard labor is essential to any
scientific discovery, my dear.
Okay, you could've
told me that before.
[NEWS COO squawks]
Well, well! It's a News Coo
with today's paper!
Why, thank you kindly!
My, what's all this
nonsense about pirates?
What? Let me see that!
[NARRATOR] On the
Grand Line's Bowin Islands...
[NARRATOR] ...Usopp has
been rapidly gaining weight
by eating everything
he can get his hands on!
How do you like these muscles?
[HERACLES] The bounty
of the forest is delicious,
but you must stop, Usopp'n!
Also, that's not muscle.
It's nothing but flab!
What if you get diabetes'n?
[USOPP]
Who cares, I'm strong now!
[HERACLES groans]
[HERACLES]
I tried to warn you.
[NEWS COO squawks]
[HERACLES]
Newspaper'n?
[USOPP]
Aww, yeah!
Chicken!
[NEWS COO squawks]
[HERACLES] You are
completely out of control!
[USOPP grunting]
[NARRATOR] On Peachy Island
in the Kamabakka Kingdom...
[MEN, SANJI laughing]
[SANJI]
Oh, stop it, you!
Look at that gorgeous sunset.
[NEWS COO squawks]
[SANJI]
Hey there, Mr. Bird!
Thank you, sugar.
Now, how's my horoscope today?
[SANJI gasping]
Check mine, too!
What the hell is this?
[NARRATOR] At Tequila Wolf
in the East Blue...
Here, Nico Robin, take this.
[ROBIN gasps]
Thanks for your help,
but mind if I ask
how you know my name?
[BUNNY JOE] Heh. Every soldier
in the Revolutionary Army
knows who you are.
Now if you'd be so kind,
I would like you
to come along with us.
A kind offer,
but it's imperative that
I see all of my
friends again soon.
[BUNNY JOE]
I see. That's a shame.
Ah. when you say your "friends,"
are you referring to
the Straw Hat Pirates?
Because we happen to have
a bit of information
about them that might
be of interest to you.
What?
I thought that
might get a reaction.
Shall I tell you now?
Oh, yes, please do.
Anything at all would
mean the world to me.
[NARRATOR] On the Mechanical
Island of Future Land Baldimore.
[FRANKY]
Finally!
Woo, cola sure does
goes down smooth!
I missed the way it
makes everything tingle.
I gotta say I wasn't expecting
to see a mechanical animal
inside the laboratory, though.
It was a polar bear,
and it was a jerk!
But it punched me straight into
a fridge that was full of cola!
And then I torched him!
So I'd say everything's
pretty cool.
[beeping]
Huh? What the heck?
[NARRATOR] On the Lazy Bones
Island Hungeria.
[BROOK singing]
That's the most terrifying
lamentation I've ever heard!
That howling can only mean
that Lord Satan is
summoning his demonic legions
to place an unspeakable curse
upon the entire Longarm Tribe!
[BROOK gasps]
[BROOK] Drat, I just
lost my train of thought.
[BROOK singing]
[SATAN WORSHIPPER A gasps]
That sounded like it came
straight from the pits of hell.
Forty-five degree slant!
Wait, no! Should it be 60?
[groans]
How could I fall into
such an awful slump?
Is this my punishment
for all those panties?
[gasps] Oh, my.
[ZORO grunting]
[MIHAWK] Save your
strength, Roronoa Zoro.
Your wounds are too severe
to ignore any longer.
And to be quite frank,
you have no hope of defeating
me if you lost to those apes.
[ZORO]
Yeah, well.
What the hell are
you doin' here?
[MIHAWK] I've been living in
that castle for a while now.
What brings you here?
That would be one of
your Seven Warlords pals.
Kuma sent the whole crew flying.
I see. That explains
things, then.
Straw Hat was fighting with
a different group in Marineford.
[ZORO gasps]
Hold on, did you see Luffy?
Is he all right?
What was he doing?
[MIHAWK]
He should still be alive,
but as he left the battle,
he appeared to be
severely traumatized.
[ZORO]
Why's that?
Don't you know?
His brother is dead.
[ZORO gasps]
[FRANKY groans]
It can't be!
And you're certain that's true?
[SANJI gasping]
Oh, no!
No way. Really?
How can this be happening?
I can't believe it.
Fire Fist Ace died...
right before Straw Hat's eyes.
[ZORO]
Luffy.
[ALL]
Luffy!
[NARRATOR] Determined
to return to Sabaody and
keep his promise to his crew,
Luffy prepares for depature.
However, when Dark
King Rayleigh appears
and makes him
a surprising offer,
Luffy is forced to make
a decision that could alter
the fate of his entire
journey on the Grand Line.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Reunited with
Dark King Rayleigh!
Decision Time for Luffy!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!