[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[USOPP gasps]
[pants]
[NARRATOR B] After stepping foot
on Upper Yard's Lost Forest,
Luffy, Sanji, and Usopp
braved the random and vicious
Ordeal of Spheres unleashed
by the priest Satori.
[NARRATOR B]
On the other side of the island,
the Sky Knight Gan Fall was
defeated by Priest Shura.
[CHOPPER]
I'll save you!
[ZORO]
Hey, Nami!
Can you see anything up there?
[SATORI]
It's you! Get off me!
How are you still alive?
[SANJI]
So I'm proposing this.
Ordeal of love.
Then, you must brutally
and without hesitation
tenderize the meat.
[yells]
[LUFFY]
"Light the Fire of Shandora!
Wyper, The Warrior!"
[WYPER]
So Gan Fall, the former God,
made his way into
the Upper Yard alone.
This will not sit
well with Eneru.
You think Gan Fall's trying
to take back what he lost?
No way.
That old fart's never had
the guts to try before.
Why would he now?
[gasps, screams]
[AISA whimpers]
[screams]
What's the matter, Aisa?
Two voices. They're gone.
What did you say?
Huh? Your Mantra?
Yes. It just happened.
[WYPER growls]
You're saying that
you heard two voices
and then they
disappeared suddenly?
You need to be honest with me.
Is this true?
[AISA exhales]
I assume that's 'yes.'
We should believe her.
Ever since she was born,
she has been able to use
her ability of Mantra
to sense people, even those
who are far away from her.
There's no mistaking her gift.
You sure you don't hear them?
They're not there anymore?
Yeah. I think it's stopped.
But...
It seemed like Gan Fall was
fighting a priest and they--
Killed each other?
Nicely done, old man.
There're only three left now.
Which is good for us.
I guess Heaven's actually
answered our prayers.
It's time for us to crush those
priests once and for all.
Yeah!
On your feet!
We're launching a full scale
attack on the Upper Yard.
[OTHERS grunt]
[LAKI]
Hm?
Wyper still makes you
nervous, doesn't he?
You have to grow up
sooner or later.
[AISA gasps]
[groans] Laki, wait, please!
What is it?
It wasn't Gan Fall who
defeated that priest!
There are others on
that side of the island
and they're the
ones that did it!
[LAKI]
Other people?
You mean the ones who entered
Skypeia from the Blue Sea?
I don't know who,
but they're really scary to me.
So...
...be careful.
[sighs]
[LAKI]
I'll try.
Now be a good girl
and hand over your bag.
[AISA]
No! I can't!
This is my special secret bag!
It has treasure in it!
I know that.
[AISA groans]
And it will have even more
inside when I bring it back.
--Yeah?
--Yeah.
[SANJI] He couldn't have
shut up any sooner.
Nothin' worse than
being humiliated
by a guy who looks like that.
At least he had
some neat tricks,
like predicting our moves
before we even knew them.
--[USOPP] Hey! Guys!
--[LUFFY] Huh?
Luffy! Sanji!
I found the boat, but you
gotta move! I'm serious!
If we don't get to it right now,
we're gonna be stuck
on this stinkin' island!
[SANJI]
I guess Usopp's okay.
[LUFFY] He's yelling
something about the boat.
[USOPP pants]
Kick it into gear!
The boat's leaving this place
and we gotta get on it now!
[pants] Get up here!
You just hold on to my body.
Your what?
Here goes.
Usopp-- [yelling]
Now that's what I
call marksmanship!
[LUFFY]
Ha! Usopp, you're my hero!
[USOPP] Do you try to kill
all your heroes like that?
[LUFFY]
I don't think so.
[USOPP]
Ya threw my back out, ya jerk.
--[cracking]
--[LUFFY] You fixed it!
[USOPP]
I can do anything.
I'm surprised you
pulled this off.
Yeah? Well, no more
underestimating me!
[ALL]
Huh? Uh...
[LUFFY]
Hey...
[ALL grunting]
[SANJI]
What are you doing?
[USOPP]
I'm not doing anything!
The rope is tightening!
--[LUFFY] Oh, no!
--Hold on!
[ALL yelling]
[ALL groaning]
That... hurt so bad.
[SANJI] I will never
let you forget this.
You know...
...I could've stretched my
arm and grabbed the boat.
[USOPP] Look, we're on the
boat and out of the forest.
That's all that matters.
[USOPP gurgling]
[CHOPPER]
Oh, yeah. I can't swim.
The Sky Knight...
[CHOPPER]
And his weird bird, too,
who also has the power
of the Devil Fruit.
[CHOPPER]
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't save anyone.
[CHOPPER]
This is it.
I can feel myself slipping away.
[GEDATSU]
Satori has fallen.
Losing control over his Mantra
only shows his
inexperience with it.
It seems the intruders this
time are from the Blue Sea,
but they behave strangely.
The sacrifices are now
moving around freely as well.
However, even if we
leave them alone,
they won't find their
way off this island.
More importantly...
[HOLY THE DOG panting]
[OHM] Do you hear the voice
of a sorrowful warrior, Holy?
[woofs]
[OHM] It doesn't matter how
many times we walk this road.
Things always end the same.
Shura defeated Gan Fall, but the
Ordeal of Spheres was broken.
That's where luck will end
for our new challengers.
For them to attempt to see God
is insolence at its greatest,
and their punishment at my hands
will have things a bit unsettled
this evening in the Upper Yard.
No one here gets out alive.
[FUZA screeches]
[SHURA] The ones who escaped
sacrifice are off my list.
It seems there are
others roaming around
who are more worthy of my anger!
All of you, listen up!
Today we catch Upper Yard
at her most vulnerable.
This is the opportunity
of a lifetime.
We move full speed ahead
and don't stop until
we reach God's Shrine!
And do not fear Eneru!
The Great Warrior Kalgara
is our one and only savior!
Only to him are we true!
[WYPER]
Braham!
Ready!
[WYPER]
Kamakiri!
[KAMAKIRI]
Hmph.
[WYPER]
Genbou!
[grunts]
[WYPER]
Laki!
Right.
[WYPER]
Be careful.
We split up here.
[WYPER] We vow to the
Great Warrior Kalgara
to light the fire of Shandora!
[SHANDORIAN WARRIORS cheer]
[GEDATSU, OHM, SHURA]
So the Shandorian's
have come for a fight?
No... It couldn't be.
[explosions]
[ZORO]
Hm?
Uh, guys?
[ZORO]
That sounded like an explosion.
[ROBIN]
I thought I heard some earlier,
but this one seemed bigger.
[gasps] Well, either way, we
have to keep moving forward.
[ZORO grunts]
Are you in some
kind of hurry, Nami?
You've been acting
odd for some time.
What did you see?
[ZORO]
Please tell me it wasn't God.
It wasn't.
If I explained it, you still
wouldn't understand--[screams]
[panting]
This is so stupid!
Why can't I just
stay on my feet?
You said we should go this way.
Something about it being faster.
Enough with the mystery, Nami!
Spit it out!
Tell us what you saw!
[NAMI] Quit ordering me around
and just do what I say!
We have to get to the
seashore--[screams]
Would one of you please help me?
[ZORO]
You're the leader.
Why don't you help yourself?
The seashore?
[NAMI]
Yes.
It's the only way we
can get close enough
to check this thing out.
[ZORO yelling]
'Cause to be honest,
I won't believe what I saw
until I see it up close.
--[ROBIN] Me, too.
--Huh?
[ROBIN] It's been bothering
me for a while now.
[NAMI yelps]
But I still can't
prove anything yet.
[NAMI]
Huh?
[ROBIN] Of course a theory is
only a theory until proven.
But if what I dreamed up
turns out to be true,
it would be interesting.
Very interesting.
The one thing I
always wanted in life
doesn't seem so far
out of reach anymore.
Although, it's only a theory.
[CHOPPER groans, gasps]
[CHOPPER]
What's going on?
I'm alive!
What happened? [pants]
Ow! My neck's killing me!
[CHOPPER gasping]
Sky Knight!
Hey! Doc! Oh! Wait, that's me.
[GAN FALL groans]
He's alive. That's good.
[PIERRE groaning]
[sighs]
[CHOPPER] This makes no sense.
I jumped in after him.
I figured we'd
sink to our deaths.
I wonder who could have
pulled us out of there?
[gasps] Hey. What was that?
Hello? Is someone there?
[gasps, screams]
[groans]
[CHOPPER screams]
[BIRD squawks]
[CHOPPER gasping]
--[BIRDS squawking]
--[CHOPPER screaming]
But why?
[ROBIN]
We're almost there.
[ZORO]
Hm?
I can hear the waves
breaking on the shore.
Listen.
[waves breaking]
[NAMI panting]
Yeah! Almost. Almost!
Just a few more steps.
[ZORO] Would you mind
telling me what you saw?
[NAMI cackles]
Or at least shut up.
On second thought,
I'm hearing more than just
the tide rolling in. You?
Yeah. It sounds like
a charging army.
[SHANDORIAN WARRIORS yell]
And some explosions thrown
in for good measure.
With any luck,
it's a distraction
from what we're doing.
[ROBIN]
Or they're attacking our friend.
[ZORO] Chopper? Aw, he's
tough for bein' so fuzzy.
When the time comes,
he can handle himself.
[ROBIN]
And what about the others?
[ZORO]
You mean Luffy?
[ROBIN] He won't sit still after
knowing what happened to us.
[ZORO]
Right. And he's the one
who wanted to come
here to begin with.
[ROBIN] I don't know what this
God has hidden out here,
but I doubt he'll let our
captain just walk through.
[ZORO grunts]
Between that, your theory,
Nami's mental breakdown,
and this other battle.
[ROBIN] This whole thing has
gotten more complicated.
[ZORO]
That's what I was gonna say.
Anyway, our shipmates are used
to being neck deep in trouble,
so I'm not worried.
Getting bent out of shape over
things that haven't happened
is a waste of time.
[ROBIN chuckles]
Good point.
[NAMI groans]
Huh?
[ZORO]
Hm?
Nami, wait. Nami!
[LUFFY laughs]
Let me do it again.
But this time,
don't make me laugh!
[USOPP laughs]
All right.
Zoro, would you wake up already?
Huh? You're a dead man.
[USOPP laughs]
That's the best!
[USOPP coughs]
This is no time for goofing off!
Nami and Robin are
lost out there
and for all we know they
could be in trouble.
[LUFFY] Zoro and Chopper
are with 'em, you know.
There're three more priests
waiting in the wings.
We may have more
challenges ahead of us.
--[USOPP laughing]
--[LUFFY] Ordeal of love.
[SANJI groans]
Whatever the case is,
we've got to get to that altar.
Don't you think?
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Okay. We're sorry.
[panting]
[ROBIN] I wonder why
she took off so fast.
Figures.
Sees what she wants and she's
got no problems on her feet.
I was right. It's exactly
what I thought I saw.
[ROBIN gasps]
Unbelievable.
[ZORO]
Hey, Nami.
If you don't tell me what it
was that you saw, then I am g--
[gasps]
[NAMI]
Speaks for itself pretty well.
Look at it. It's almost unreal.
[NAMI]
But it's no fairy tale.
We've all seen
what it belongs to.
How did it get all
the way up here?
[ZORO gasps]
[ZORO]
That doesn't make any sense.
Why would this be here?
It looks exactly the same.
It's like a copy.
[ROBIN]
But it's not.
[ZORO]
How do you figure?
This is the other half
of what we saw before.
[ZORO]
Go on.
It's bugged me for a while.
Why is it that we walk on soil
here instead of island cloud?
This dirt.
There's nothing in the makeup
of the White White Sea
that would allow
for its existence.
So... the ground that
we're walking on
shouldn't exist up here.
Upper Yard was originally
on the ground.
[NAMI] I knew that house
was off when I saw it.
Thing is, it's a
two-story house,
and there was no staircase
leading up to the second story.
And what would make you build
a house on the edge of a cliff?
But then again,
it wasn't a cliff at all.
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Whoa! Amazing!
[ZORO grunts]
Look closer.
It's really unattractive.
A guy's gotta have some serious
guts to build a house that ugly.
[CHOPPER]
What's that?
[screams]
[LUFFY]
This isn't a palace at all!
[NAMI] This is the half of the
island that was ripped away.
[NAMI] This island
used to be part of Jaya.
[ZORO] So what that means
is a few hundred years back,
the island below
us split in half
and one side of it
rose into the sky.
[SOUTH BIRD squawks]
[ZORO] Either of you know
how that coulda happened?
[SOUTH BIRDS squawking]
They're--South Birds.
A whole flock of 'em.
They're huge.
I didn't know they got so big.
It had to have been the Knock
Up Stream that did this.
Sounds ridiculous,
but that's the best I can do.
You guys are the ones
who saved our lives.
Thank you.
[SOUTH BIRD squawks]
[CHOPPER gasps]
What do you mean he's God?
[CRICKET]
My name is Montblanc Cricket.
I'm sorry I attacked you.
I thought that you were more
bandits coming for my gold.
You mean there's no
sky island? Are you sure?
I know of only one who claims
to have seen the island himself.
But that man is considered
a liar of epic proportions.
Hey! What are you lookin' at?
[NAMI]
It's called Noland the Liar .
"I saw a city of gold on
an island in the great sea,"
declared Noland.
And the courageous king decided
that he must have this
treasure for his kingdom.
The king set out with Noland and
2,000 of his finest soldiers.
And all they found
for their troubles
was a normal island covered
with an ordinary jungle.
[CRICKET]
As the story goes,
Noland's last words
were as follows:
"I can only assume that the city
of gold sunk into the sea."
Unable to find the ruins,
Noland insisted that the
ancient city had submerged
due to shifts in
the earth's crust.
But everyone dismissed this
as a last ditch excuse
of a doomed man.
[CHOPPER] That's what made you
keep diving until you got sick.
[CRICKET]
All I'm doing is
following what I
believe is my destiny.
This is between me and Noland.
I'm facing what I fear,
and whatever the outcome,
the act is all that matters.
Let's settle this, Noland.
Once and for all.
[SOUTH BIRD squawks]
[WYPER yells]
[SHANDORIAN WARRIORS yell]
[LUFFY, USOPP]
♪ Take my hand, honey. ♪
[SANJI]
No singing!
[SOUTH BIRD squawking]
[NAMI] The City of Gold that
Noland discovered on the ground
didn't sink into the
ocean like he guessed.
This part of Jaya...
It's been floating in
the sky for 400 years!
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[LUFFY]
To the sacrificial altar!
[USOPP] We're on the
way to save the day!
[SANJI]
This is no fun cruise, you two!
[LUFFY]
Jeez! Touchy.
Why don't you just relax, Sanji?
[USOPP] Yeah. Be calm like
those guys headin' toward us.
[SANJI] Those are guerillas,
you idiot, and they're after us!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
What?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Jaya, City of Gold in the Sky!
Head for God's Shrine!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!