[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Wait! Now I get it!
Get what?
We can save Robin.
As long as I'm here we
can save her, dammit!
Whoa, okay.
Do you really have to get
so carried away about it?
[USOPP]
C'mon, let's go!
[SPANDAM]
You are just determined
to keep making me repeat this.
There isn't even a microscopic
residue of hope left for you.
Sure, we might've heard what
could've been a voice earlier,
but I haven't seen
anyone, have you?
If there was anyone back there,
Lucci is probably killing
them right about now.
Get it?
I doubt that we'll
ever agree on this.
So there's no sense
in us discussing it.
And I don't have time
for talking anyway.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Stamp! Whip!
Spear!
I'm a wolf, you dolt.
I won't stop chasing you
until you're in my jaws.
[JABRA]
Still hanging in there, huh?
[SANJI]
I'm not going anywhere pal.
I'm not about
get killed, either.
And I'm not gonna forgive you.
Forgive me?
Upset with the way
we've treated Robin?
Gettin' all emotional
will only clutter up
your mind during a fight.
Don't waste all of your
precious time pitying
that hopeless fool of a woman
when you should be
busy trying to think up
a way to get out of here alive.
[SANJI]
Watch your damn mouth, wolf.
You don't wanna see me mad.
I tend to overheat when I'm mad.
The heat of its destructive
power burns hotter
than the flames of hell.
Diable Jambe!
Wait!
Flambage--
Shot!
God may have created food.
But the Devil created spices.
If you think that kick was hot,
my heart was
burning even hotter.
[LUFFY]
Oni Giri!
What's Moss Head doing up there?
He's gonna bring the
whole damn tower down.
[Gates of Justice
Underground passage]
Who wrote this?
It says "Gates of Justice."
Guess I might as well follow it.
Nami and Usopp are probably
on their way to Robin already.
If this is the key they need,
I can't keep them waiting.
Better hurry.
Can't you move any faster?
This is it!
At long last, the
Bridge of Hesitation!
Look, Nico Robin!
That's right.
The Gates of
Justice are opening!
It took long enough,
and I admit, it was
scary for a while there,
but I finally made it.
Once I step through those gates,
I'll be the
government's hero. No.
I will be a hero to
the entire world!
The bridge leading to the
gate is rising as we speak.
Can you hear it?
It's calling out to its hero!
It's beautiful!
A path into the horizon as
radiant as my shining future!
Although, for you it must look
like a path straight to hell.
Right? That's what you're
thinking, isn't it?
Well, take a good look!
No!
Hey, stop squirming around!
Ow, that hurt!
Stupid woman. Come back here!
Enough!
I'm sick of chasing
you around, damn it!
For the last time,
you can't escape,
so give it a rest,
you obstinate cow!
Are you stupid?
Do I need to remind
you who I am?
Huh?
I'm the hero of
the entire world!
The whole damn world!
And that means
I'm different than you,
better than you!
While I have a
bright future ahead,
you're condemned to die
without a shred of hope!
You're nothing but a
stepping stone to me!
Have I finally gotten that
through your thick skull?
Or do I need to keep
grinding it in for you?
[ROBIN] Luffy. Everyone.
I still believe in you.
C'mon! Hurry! Hurry!
There's no point if
I don't make it in time!
Is that the exit?
Ten minutes until we arrive!
All hands are ready, sir!
[OFFICER]
All ships confirm positions
and prepare for attack!
[CREW]
Yes sir!
Now get up! Show some dignity!
You're not going
to ruin this for me!
Did I make it?
Whoa, calm down, Straw Hat!
Huh. It's Franky!
I got enough jerks to
deal with--get lost!
What?
You mean you're
still playin' tough
after all we've been through?
We're bros now!
Just deal with it!
Lucci, huh?
He givin' you a hard
time, or something?
By the way,
I brought you two keys.
Though I guess Robin's not here.
Should I lend you a hand?
No.
Leave this guy to me.
You should go after Robin.
You can get to the
Gates of Justice
through that door
behind the pigeon guy.
Robin left a while back,
so we're running out of time.
Keep going and don't look back.
You can super count
on me, brother.
Listen, just so
we're straight here,
despite my appearance,
I prefer meat.
Well, just so
we're straight here,
I really don't give a damn!
Hm?
[ZORO]
Anyway, enough small talk.
I gotta get that key.
If I can't make it in time,
this is all for nothing.
Two Sword Style Nigiri.
Are you supposed to get stronger
when you wear that
bandanna on your head?
Let's find out.
Tower Climb!
Tower Climb Return!
Flash!
Ripple!
[KAKU] You've given
yourself a blind spot!
Giraffe Scythe!
Iron Body Edge Wise.
What?
There's no blind
spots on a square.
So what?
If you can't move, who cares?
You're so naïve!
Perhaps I should
remind you of something.
Yeah?
Unlike humans, giraffes
have four legs. Tempest Kick!
Are you gonna fight me,
or just sit there?
What do you mean?
Take a look!
My attack has already begun!
First the slashes go up,
they deflect off the ceiling,
and then finally,
they come raining down!
Giraffe Shower!
Iron Body.
There's too many of them.
Damn it! I can't block!
Nose Pistol!
Bastard.
You're quite resilient for a
human. But I'm a giraffe, boy!
That your superhero name?
"Giraffe Boy"?
Giraffe Boy?
It's just "Giraffe", fool!
[ZORO]
Now it's "Giraffe Fool?"
You're the fool!
I'm the giraffe! Got it?
[ZORO]
Listen to yourself.
[KAKU]
Hm?
[ZORO] Who the hell cares if
you're Giraffe Boy or whatever?
If you're a swordsman, then you
let your blade speak for you!
If you think you can
get under my skin,
you're just wasting your time.
I'm not getting under your skin.
I'm gonna cut
straight through it.
And if you use your Iron Body,
I'll cut through that, too!
[KAKU]
Hmph.
You're quite the
comedian, aren't you?
So, you'll cut
through my Iron Body?
I can't imagine how.
Just sit back and watch,
Giraffe Boy. I'll show you.
One-Sword Style Sword Draw.
Lion Song!
Tempest Kick! Dragon Cut!
Iron Body isn't the issue.
If you can't cut me at all,
it doesn't matter
if my body's iron or not.
[ZORO]
You're right.
I'll have to take a
different approach.
One Gorilla! Two Gorilla!
Now again!
Three-Sword Style.
A test of strength
this time, is it?
Sounds fun to me!
Nose Pistol!
Two Gorilla Slash!
[KAKU]
This is truly a fearsome attack!
[ZORO] You never thought
you might lose, did you?
You can't even imagine that
I might be stronger than you.
Well, it's time to wake up!
I'll make you face the truth.
I could say the same thing!
Eat this! Gum-Gum Gatling!
Paper Art.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Shave!
Straw Hat!
Tempest Kick!
Weapons Left!
Shave!
[FRANKY]
Uh-oh!
Gum-Gum Rocket!
What happened?
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Hey, you got him! Good!
Hold him right there
and I'll blast him!
Forget it!
I said I'd take care of him,
right? Come on! Go!
Stick to the plan and
leave this guy to me!
Get serious, man!
This dude's too strong!
We gotta work as
a team on this one!
That's enough!
This is my fight, not yours!
I can't lose to him!
For the last time.
You gotta get out of here
and find Robin now!
I'm counting on you!
If you can't help her,
she's gone for good!
This is the only
chance we're gonna get!
Straw Hat.
You hear me?
Stop now, sea train!
Give me Tom back!
[LUCCI]
Ridiculous.
You can't escape.
[FRANKY]
Are you sure?
Of course I am! Go!
All right then. Good luck!
I already told you.
You can't escape!
Moon Walk!
Shave!
Damn it!
Finger Pistol.
Get back here. If you
wanna fight, then you fight me!
[KAKU] You still haven't seen
the true, wild,
strength of a giraffe.
[ZORO] Then stop talking
and show me already.
It would be my pleasure.
Observe, for this is
the power of nature!
Giraffe Cannon!
[ZORO] There's nothing
natural about that.
Extreme Nose Pistol!
Giraffe Blast!
[ZORO]
It stretched!
But it's like I said. That neck
of yours is your weak point!
Keep telling yourself
that!
Tempest Kick! Spinning
White Blade!
Why don't you worry
about your own weak
points instead of mine?
What's with this guy?
These attacks just
keep getting weirder.
You won't get away
next time. Giraffe Cannon!
[KAKU]
Damn it!
I pushed my neck in so far, it
made my arms and legs pop out!
What kind of messed up
body have you got?
It's like when you
cram dough through
a little hole and it
comes out as noodles!
Like a pasta machine!
[ZORO]
Hm?
Pasta Machine!
[ZORO] Don't act like you
did that on purpose!
A long neck is nice,
but long limbs like
these are handy as well!
A pro like me can turn even
the most unexpected situations
into fresh opportunities!
Behold as I unleash
a devastating new
long-range technique!
Giraffe Blast!
That's the same
attack you did before!
I've had enough
of this nonsense.
Three-Sword Style Tatsu Maki!
Iron Body!
It's too strong. Shave!
Moon Walk!
[ZORO] Now what?
He can't be running away.
Pasta Machine!
Thank you for waiting.
Never mind the neck.
If I can control the
reach of all four limbs,
my blades will be unstoppable!
Perhaps you were so distracted
by my Giraffe Powers,
that you forgot I'm a master
of the Four Sword Style!
You've done well thus far,
but this battle is over now!
[ZORO] Even if you have the
power of a wild animal.
Even if you can attack
with that long neck of yours.
Even if you can use
the Four-Sword Style.
What? He deflected
all four blades?
None of those
things will give you
the strength it
takes to defeat me!
[ZORO]
Nine Sword Style!
[KAKU]
There's no point in trying!
You'll never defeat me!
No matter where you hide,
you won't escape the power
of my strongest attack!
The Sky Slicer!
[ZORO]
I commend you.
Suffering is welcome on
the path to bloodshed.
[KAKU]
What? I must be seeing things!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Demon God Zoro!
An Incarnation of Asura
Born from Fighting Spirit."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!