Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit, sets sail
to become the next
King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer
numerous obstacles, they capture
the unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After landing
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
Luffy and the Straw Hat crew
succeeded in rescuing
the kidnapped mermaid, Camie.
Soon afterward, however, a
battle with the Marines began.
We'll help you guys
get outta here!
[NARRATOR] After a wild
scramble they found themselves
in the clear, for
the time being.
[LUFFY]
Roger and Rayleigh!
The King of the Pirates
and His Right Hand Man!
[HOUND PET 400A]
Peterman! Boss, Say something!
How dare they do this to you!
Damn those guys!
You know what...
I never expected Duval to be
so handsome under that mask.
[DUVAL laughing]
Well, see ya! Feel free
to call us anytime!
We'll be there whenever you
need us until you're safely
on your way to Fishman Island!
[LUFFY]
Sounds good! Thanks, you guys!
Hey, ain't no thing, buddy!
Yeah. Enough with the winking.
Oh, I forgot.
For you, Miss Mermaid.
[CAMIE]
Hey, you found my backpack!
[DUVAL] Indeed! That
idiot Peterman had it.
[CAMIE giggles]
Thank you!
Alright! Let's go,
Rosy Life Riders!
[FISH RIDERS]
Yes, Handsome Rosy!
They sure shout a
bunch of weird stuff.
Probably trying to find
something that clicks.
Here we are. Let's hurry inside.
[CHOPPER] Sounds good.
We need to get Hachi to a bed.
[RAYLEIGH]
Hey, Shakky! Are you here?
Open up!
[SHAKKY]
Oh, it's Ray! Welcome back!
I wasn't expecting you.
Or rather, I wasn't expecting
them to find you so fast.
Hachi was seriously
injured in the escape.
Do you have a bed?
That looks terrible! Hold on.
I'll throw something
together for him.
Hey, old guy.
You said you had something
to tell me, right?
Hm?
[LUFFY yells]
You were on Gold Roger's crew?
I was. In fact, I served
as his vice-captain.
The name is Silvers Rayleigh.
It's nice to meet you.
[ALL]
Vice-Captain?
Hm?
[SHAKKY]
Why didn't you tell them?
Slip your mind?
[HACHI] We only needed
him to coat the boat,
so I didn't think about it.
Wait. You didn't
know who he was?
Not his face. But I
sure know his name!
[NAMI sobbing] He's in so
many books. He's legendary!
It's definitely a name
everyone's heard at least once.
Gold Roger...
I seem to remember a rookie
with that name long ago,
but I'm not sure, really.
So how do a big-shot
pirate and an octopus
know each other?
Hachi rescued me.
I was stranded at sea
and he found me.
That was over 20 years ago,
but I'll never forget it
for as long as I live.
[SHAKKY] Hachi was still just
a little kid when it happened.
But he saved Rayleigh's life.
[RAYLEIGH] We remained good
friends after that incident,
until he joined up
with the Sun Pirates.
[LUFFY]
You mean Arlong, right?
It's hard to believe.
I mean, Gold Roger was executed
22 years ago, wasn't he?
How did his Vice-Captain
avoid getting his head
chopped off, too?
The Marines captured the
entire crew, didn't they?
[CHOPPER gulps]
The Marines didn't catch Roger.
[LUFFY muffled grunt]
[SANJI gasps]
See, the Captain
turned himself in.
[ALL gasp]
[RAYLEIGH]
The government made it sound
like they'd caught him, though.
Likely just to look tough.
"Rattling their sabers",
if you will.
[NAMI] The "King of the Pirates"
turned himself in? Why?
[RAYLEIGH] Because he saw the
inevitable end to our journey.
See, about 4 years
before his execution,
Roger began to feel ill.
Turned out, he had
developed a fatal disease.
[ALL gasp]
No matter how strong he was, the
illness he had was incurable.
He knew that he would
submit to it eventually.
But, there was one man
with the skill and know-how
to help ease his suffering.
A lighthouse keeper and
well-respected doctor.
A man residing at the
Twin Capes named Crocus.
Huh?
[RAYLEIGH] We asked for
his help and brought him on
as the ship's doctor
for our final voyage.
Finally, three years later,
while managing to keep
the disease at bay, Roger
achieved what was said
to be impossible.
He conquered the Grand Line.
Did you say Crocus?
At the Twin Capes?
Oh, that takes me back!
Whoa! That's crazy!
I thought the old man
just lived at the
lighthouse for 50 years!
But he sailed with the
King of the Pirates.
[NAMI]
Come to think of it.
He did mention being a
ship's doctor for a while!
So he was a pirate on your
crew for those three years?
Oh, I have to assume
you've met him then.
It's good to know that
he's alive and well!
Crocus agreed to join with us
because there was a certain
group of pirates he wanted to
search for on the Grand Line.
Brook! I bet he was
talking about your crew!
Guess it's a small
world after all!
Crocus, you sweet man!
You went to such lengths!
Yes, he was only a
crewmember with us
for those three years.
But we definitely considered
him one of our own.
It's been such a long time,
it'd be great to see him again.
[SANJI] So, what happened
after Roger conquered the sea?
[RAYLEIGH]
That's when it all began.
The world starting calling Roger
the "King of the Pirates".
Before that, no one had ever
called him the king of anything.
[RAYLEIGH] Honestly, titles
don't hold much meaning
for a man about to die.
Still. Roger was
overjoyed to hear it.
[RAYLEIGH] Whatever he did,
he loved doing it
in a bold and flashy way.
Whether it was in
battle or celebration,
he enjoyed living
life to the fullest.
He seemed to take pleasure
in thinking out plans for the
future as well, even though
he wouldn't be a part of it.
Eventually, as per
Captain's orders,
the Roger Pirates were
secretly disbanded.
One by one, everyone
discretely left the crew
and went their own way.
As comrades, we risked
our lives together.
But I know next to nothing
about where they are
or what they're doing now.
[RAYLEIGH] Then, about a
year after we disbanded,
Roger turned himself in
and was incarcerated.
Shortly after, it was
announced that he would
be publicly executed in
Loguetown, the settlement
in the East Blue
where he was born.
[RAYLEIGH] I've heard that
many of the young faces
that bore witness in the
town square that fateful day
went on to make names for
themselves on the high seas.
There was a silence that
covered the entire world
the day of his execution.
I wasn't there in
attendance, myself.
But I hear that his final words
went a little
something like this:
While they may execute
me, I won't die.
[RAYLEIGH] The World
Government and the Marines
must've been shocked.
With one last remark from Roger,
the public execution that was
meant to serve as an example
and a warning to other
pirates, instead became
the opening ceremony
to what would become
the Great Pirate Era!
If anyone wants my treasure,
then it's yours for the taking!
Go find it!
I left everything I
gathered in one place.
[RAYLEIGH] In seconds,
he changed the dim flame
of his life into
a raging hellfire
that spread across the world!
[CITIZENS cheering]
[RAYLEIGH]
I've never laughed as much...
Nor have I cried as much...
Nor drank as much
as I did that night.
The Captain was
an amazing man,
and he sure lived
one hell of a life.
[NAMI, USOPP sigh]
I'd heard it before,
but it's still so amazing.
When one of Roger's
old friends tells it,
it's like it's a
whole new story.
Wait. It sounds like
you're trying to say
that Roger created the
Great Pirate Era on purpose!
That, I couldn't tell ya.
No way to know for sure.
Roger is no longer with us.
It's only the people
who are living now
who can create and
shape such an era.
I'm certain that there
are people who inherited
that spirit of adventure from
Roger that fateful day
in the town square.
Your good friend Shanks
is probably one of them.
[LUFFY muffled] Whoa! You
know Shanks, too, old man?
Perhaps you've heard of a pirate
named Buggy from the East Blue.
[NAMI, ZORO grunt]
[NAMI, ZORO]
Buggy?
He and Shanks
served us well.
They were both apprentices
onboard Roger's ship.
Whoa! You mean Shanks was on
the King of the Pirate's ship?
Hm? I take it he
never told you, then?
[RAYLEIGH]
I ran into him again.
Right here on this archipelago
about 10 years ago.
I noticed he lost his
trademark straw hat,
as well as losing his left arm.
[LUFFY gags]
[RAYLEIGH] When I asked
him what had happened,
he spoke about you with a smile.
[SHANKS] I was shocked,
Rayleigh. I couldn't believe it!
In the East Blue,
there's a kid who said
the same thing
Captain Roger said.
His spirit lives on in him.
And ever since, I've always
wanted to meet you, Luffy.
And see this spirited
boy for myself.
[LUFFY laughs]
Aw, Shanks!
[RAYLEIGH] But I can't in good
conscience talk about things
involving Shanks that he
hasn't mentioned yet himself.
In any case, you've done
well to make it this far.
I'm sure Shanks is eagerly
awaiting your arrival
in the New World.
Really? Do you think so?
Man, I can't wait to see him!
[RAYLEIGH chuckles]
Now then.
Getting down to business,
I believe you wanted
your ship coated, right?
Then it's high time for me
to return to my real work.
[HACHI] That reminds me: I
wasn't sure exactly how much
the coating would cost.
[RAYLEIGH] Ah, don't you
worry about it, Hachi.
I couldn't possibly take
money from friends of yours.
[HACHI] Oh, wow.
You're the best, Rayleigh.
[USOPP, NAMI cheering]
Not sure why, but he's
doing it for free! Thanks!
We certainly appreciate it.
That's very generous of you!
[NAMI]
We just saved a ton of money!
[ALL]
Huh?
[ROBIN]
Rayleigh. I have a question.
What exactly is the "Will of D"?
There was a Poneglyph
on Sky Island.
Roger's name was inscribed on it
in that ancient form of writing.
How does he know it?
How can he use that language?
[GOLD ROGER] I made it here,
and I will guide this passage
all the way to the
farthest ends of the earth.
Pirate Gol D. Roger...
Please tell me. Did you learn
what happened to the world
during the Blank Century?
The missing history
from 900 years ago?
Yes. We know.
[ROBIN gasps]
[RAYLEIGH]
We learned all of it.
The entirety of
the missing history.
[ROBIN shaky gasp]
[RAYLEIGH]
But, Miss...
You mustn't be so hasty.
Just keep moving forward.
See, this is your journey now.
We, and Ohara, might
have hurried too much
for our own good.
I'm sure that's not what
you wanted to hear...
Even if I told you everything
you wanted to know
about that history here
and now, just as you are,
you couldn't do
anything about it.
Once you've taken the time
to really see the world,
it might change your outlook.
And possibly lead you
to a different answer.
But if you still
insist on hearing it.
I can tell you everything.
It's up to you.
[ROBIN]
No. I'll pass.
And continue my journey.
It'll all make sense to
you one of these days.
I'm very sorry
for what happened
in your homeland of Ohara.
But, that doesn't change
the fact that Roger
didn't decipher that writing.
We were all pirates, remember?
Not geniuses or scholars.
No match for Clover or the
other great minds of Ohara.
See, Captain Roger
just heard the voice
of the universe, and
that's all that happened.
Are you sure about this, Robin?
Seems like you're passing
up a pretty big opportunity!
Hey! Old guy! I've got
a question of my own!
The treasure Roger talked about.
The legendary One Piece!
Tell me, is it really--?
That's enough!
[USOPP grunts]
[LUFFY panting]
I don't wanna know where
the One Piece is hidden.
I don't even wanna
know if it exists!
Every single one of us
put our life on the line
and set out to sea
without knowing anything!
I'd rather give up being
a pirate than know!
I won't go on a
boring adventure!
We need to sail and
find out for ourselves!
[USOPP gasps]
Uh, sorry! Sorry! I knew that!
It just slipped out of
my mouth, that's all!
I don't wanna know either!
Ah! I just remembered! I have
"I'll Die If I Learn Anything
About The One Piece" disease!
Don't say anything,
old guy! You'll kill me!
Keep it to yourself!
[SHAKKY laughing]
Well, in that case.
let me ask you:
Do you think you can do it?
The New World far surpasses
anything you can imagine.
Your foes will be powerful.
Knowing that, do you still think
you can rule this mighty sea?
[LUFFY grunts]
What? I don't wanna
"rule" anything.
Being King of the Pirates
is about being more
free than anyone!
Huh?
I see.
Monkey D. Luffy. I must
say, I like your style.
[RAYLEIGH]
Your ship is in Grove #1, right?
I guess I'll head over there
now and get started.
What do you plan to do anyway?
At any moment, an admiral
could be here looking for you.
[NAMI] That's right. We'll only
be a nuisance if we stay here.
So, maybe we go shopping?
What? Are you insane?
We're being chased by
the World Government!
We gotta hide!
He's got a point.
If we stick together,
that makes us an easy target
for those Marines.
And it'll be easier for the
old guy to finish his work
if we each find somewhere
to lay low in town for a while.
Right. Then I say we split up.
Keep track of the work and when
it's done, we meet back here.
Who is that guy
strategizing over there?
'Cause it's not Zoro!
Hey, Shakky. We have any cards?
[SHAKKY]
Yes. I believe there's one left.
[NAMI]
Whoa! This is a Vivre Card!
[RAYLEIGH] You know what it is?
That simplifies things.
Since I happen to be
a bit notorious myself.
I think I'll move your
ship from Grove #1
and work on it
somewhere more secluded.
I'll need three days to
complete the coating process.
[LUFFY, USOPP gasp]
Why does it take so long?
It needs time to seal,
so I can't go any faster.
Then it's three days of survival
in the woods for us. Scary!
[RAYLEIGH] Let's meet at
sundown, three days from now.
I don't know what
grove I'll be on then,
so use the Vivre Cards
to find me.
Wherever it leads you,
that will be the place
where I'll be finishing the
coating and waiting for you.
It's probably a good idea for
you to pick up some supplies
for your underwater voyage
to Fish-Man Island.
Luffy, all of you,
thank you for everything!
You guys are awesome.
And I'm sorry. Sorry I caused
you guys so much trouble.
I owe you my life!
We'll show you the way
to Fish-Man Island.
Don't worry about a thing.
So do you best to stay
clear of the Marines.
Hachi. Get plenty
of bed rest, okay?
See you again in three days.
We'll be there to send you off.
See you later, nice lady!
[LUFFY]
We're up against an Admiral.
We need to make sure
none of us gets killed.
Stop saying scary
stuff like that!
Three days, huh?
Let's all go...
[LUFFY]
...to the amusement park!
[ALL]
Ugh.
[PIRATE 400B] A Navy warship's
been spotted from the harbor!
[PIRATE 400A]
Oh, no! The Admiral's here!
[PIRATES screaming]
[PIRATES gasp]
[PIRATES scream]
[PIRATE 400D screams]
[KIZARU]
Ah, this is Kizaru.
Uh, I've arrived on site.
Please respond.
Over.
[CHOPPER]
They say an Admiral is coming!
[BROOK]
Can he not, please?
[CHOPPER]
The last one we met was Aokiji!
He had ice Devil Fruit
powers and was super-tough!
[BROOK] I do very
poorly with super-tough!
Perhaps someone
else can handle this!
[CHOPPER, BROOK]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"No Escape?
Admiral Kizaru's
Light Speed Kick!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!