Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy was sent flying
from the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring through
the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom
inhabited entirely by women,
Amazon Lily.
Condemned as a trespasser,
Luffy is thrown into an arena
and forced to
battle to the death
with the sisters
of the Snake Princess.
[AMAZONS cheering]
[AMAZON 413A]
I've never seen Marigold's
"Salamander" move before!
I can't wait!
[AMAZON 413B] Ooh!
Don't forget about Sandersonia's
"Eight-Headed Serpent!"
[LUFFY] There.
You're not cracked, are you?
Good. Just wait here, okay?
[LUFFY] Real sorry you got
turned into stone 'cause of me.
[LUFFY] All done.
Okay. Which one of you
wants your ass kicked first?
What a joke!
[MARIGOLD and
SANDERSONIA laughing]
Did he just say
what I think he said?
If he thinks he can win,
he's in for an ugly surprise!
Hilarious!
Let's find more men
to feed to the Gorgon Sisters,
because this is too funny!
Marigold! And Sandersonia!
Execute him, now.
For the crime of
sneaking onto our island,
and for personally offending me,
bestow on him the
ultimate punishment!
[MARIGOLD] Careful now!
Crap!
Poison, huh? That was close!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
[LUFFY coughing]
That hurt me.
But how? I'm made of rubber!
--[LUFFY] Gum-Gum Gatling!
--[SANDERSONIA] Snake Dance!
How is she doing that?
I can't get a punch in on her!
[MARIGOLD] Snake Stick!
Dammit!
[LUFFY]
What the hell are you doing?
You leave her alone!
Hey!
Stop! You're gonna
end up breaking her!
Good idea.
No! Stop!
I said stop! That's enough!
[AMAZON 413R] Ahh!
The warriors are fainting!
Unreal!
That was the Conqueror's Spirit.
You're kidding!
Only one out of a million people
can summon forth that Haki,
let alone control it!
[SANDERSONIA] I've never seen
anyone besides our big sister
do something like that!
[MARIGOLD] This boy has
the "Qualities of a Conqueror".
The ability to
stand above all others!
The same as me.
There's no doubt about it.
He wields such power.
But who the hell is this boy?
Is he toying with us?
All right. I get it now.
You two girls are really strong.
Back to the duel. Round two.
[LUFFY]
All-Out Special Power Battle!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake.
What are you hesitating for?
Men are unworthy
of our fear, sisters!
[AMAZON 414A]
Sonia! Mari! You can do it!
[AMAZON 414B] Yeah!
Teach that ape a lesson!
Hah! Rather silly
to be so startled. Right?
Indeed.
If he can't control
that Haki of his,
then we have nothing to fear.
Okay. Now...
If we're gonna go all out,
we better move
her outta the way.
I wouldn't want her to break.
Well look at you
making your little demands.
It seems you still
don't understand
the position you're in.
Perhaps smashing that
statue will shut you up!
No! Don't do it!
[SANDERSONIA] You should
be fighting for your life!
Why are protecting that statue?
[LUFFY coughs]
[LUFFY]
Because this was my fault.
And this is our fight.
She has nothing to do with it!
[HANCOCK] Very well.
Allow the man
to move the statue.
But why?
[HANCOCK]
I'd rather he stop his moaning
and show us what
he's truly capable of.
That way,
when we grind
him under our heels,
not only will he die
a miserable laughingstock,
he'll finally understand
how weak and useless men are.
--All right.
Not that you're going anywhere,
but hold on a little longer.
I'll figure something out
after I beat up
these big snake ladies.
'Kay. Now let's do this.
My! Where does that
confidence come from?
I don't know,
but I shall enjoy
beating it out of him.
You go ahead and try.
As long as you two stop
yakking, it'll be worth it.
[SANDERSONIA]
Insolent as ever, I see.
But you shall have your wish!
Owww! Damn it!
As long as I can dodge,
I don't care if you
spit that crap all day!
Now, Gum-Gum...
Bleh! What's up with this smoke?
Bleh!
[MARIGOLD] I don't
even have to hit you...
My poison can take many forms.
All deadly.
Marigold's poison gas attack
is my favorite!
Maybe now he'll stop
jumping around so much!
This stuff isn't so bad.
Oh man.
I'm feeling kinda woozy.
[MARIGOLD] You are my prey.
I'm done toying with you.
I'm killing you,
slowly but surely.
I'll weaken you with poison,
corner you, and then finally...
...finish you.
[LUFFY groaning]
You may have been speedy before,
but all it takes is
one whiff of my poison
to dull your senses.
[chuckling menacingly]
[AMAZONS cheering]
Damn it. That's enough!
Now Gum-Gum Pistol!
And another one! Pistol!
You're a mess!
Perhaps you'd like to lie down?
[SANDERSONIA]
I laugh, but at this point,
it's more of a tragedy.
[MARIGOLD] No matter
how strong they may be,
I can reduce any man
to a whimpering weakling.
It's time to die!
The fight's over!
Those blades'll
finish him for good!
I'm not dizzy now!
What d'you know?
The poison's all gone!
Eww! Is that his hand?
[LUFFY laughing, yelling]
Look, he's down there!
Persistent, isn't he?
Mari! Sonia!
He's still alive! Be careful!
That poison smoke's
a pain in the ass.
I gotta come up with a plan.
Hm?
All right, Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY]
...Balloon!
And fly away!
[AMAZONS screaming]
[LUFFY] Whew!
Yeah, that's much better.
All that poison
and smoke stuff
was really getting on my nerves.
Now I can beat you guys up
like I was supposed to.
[AMAZON 414F]
He turned into a balloon
and blew that poison
away like it was nothing!
[AMAZON 414G]
Can all men do that?
This is highly educational!
Is it, though?
So you're going to
beat us up now, you said?
With as badly as
you've been losing,
I admit, I have my doubts.
[LUFFY] Just watch.
[LUFFY] Okay.
I'll show you what
I can do when I go all-out.
Now Second Gear!
[AMAZON 414H]
What's he doing now?
[AMAZON 414I]
Is it me or is he steaming?
[AMAZON 414J] Men are
kind of scary, aren't they?
[AMAZON 414K] They're nothing
like us, that's for sure!
He's smoking!
This is incredible!
"All out"?
Do you mean to imply that
you've been going easy on us?
He's blowing smoke
figuratively and literally.
Think nothing of it, sister.
Perhaps we've beaten
the sense out of you
and you've forgotten,
but even if
you're hot and steamy,
we can still
read your every move.
[LUFFY] We'll see, won't we?
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
[SANDERSONIA] It's no use!
...Pistol!
You're not hurt, are you?
Whatever powers you possess,
I assure you that
ours are greater still.
In other words, boy,
all your little trick
has done is awaken our wrath.
[SANDERSONIA] Medusa Hair...
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
[AMAZON 414A] Go! Kill him!
[AMAZON 414B]
We love you, Sandersonia!
[AMAZON 414E]
She bit through the fence!
[AMAZON 414C]
Even though the snakes
are just made
out of her hair,
those fangs hit as hard as iron!
[SANDERSONIA]
Why can't I hit him?
I know what he's going to do,
but somehow I
still can't keep up!
[LUFFY yelling]
[MARIGOLD]
Sonia. Are you all right?
[LUFFY] Now, Gum-Gum...
Don't bother.
As you've clearly seen before,
your attacks simply
bounce off of me.
[MARIGOLD] As long as
I can match your speed,
you may strike
as hard as you like,
because my
defenses shall not fail.
[AMAZONS gasping]
Let's find out.
Jet... Bazooka!
[AMAZONS gasping]
[HANCOCK] Sonia! Mari!
[HANCOCK] If I recall, you
were supposed to kill the man,
not indulge in
his foolish games.
But... But sister...
[HANCOCK] His transgressions
are, in a word, unforgivable.
I refuse to
tolerate him any longer.
Yes. Of course,
we're very sorry, sister.
We'll finish him immediately.
Medusa Hair...
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
Whoa! She's on fire!
Medusa Hair...
...Salamander!
There's nowhere
left to run, man.
[AMAZON 414I]
If he doesn't get bitten,
he's going to
get burned for sure!
[AMAZON 414K] Ooh,
this is my favorite attack!
Now Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY]
...Jet...
...Gatling!
[AMAZONS screaming]
[yelling in pain]
No, Sonia! I didn't mean to!
Hurry, get away from me!
[yelling in pain]
Something is
dragging me closer! Ah!
Our tails! How did he...?
[SANDERSONIA]
I'm burning! I'm burning!
[MARIGOLD] Sonia, stop!
You're pulling me!
[SANDERSONIA yelling in pain]
Watch out, Sonia! Don't fall!
That's the pit of blades!
Hold on to the stands!
Whoa! That was close.
[AMAZON 414H]
Sandersonia... No...
This is absolutely pathetic.
Her back is exposed... Sonia!
You can't let
our people see that.
[LUFFY] Hot!
[HANCOCK] He can't be...
[AMAZON 414J] He's going to
knock her down and skewer her!
[AMAZON 414D] Isn't
winning enough, you animal?
Do you have to kick
her while she's down, too?
--Are you here to mock me?
--Don't move!
Even if you guys
want to kill me,
that doesn't mean
that I wanna kill you.
Why, of all
the insolent--Mari!
This is your chance
to finish him off!
Don't just stand there! Hurry!
I can't.
Don't you understand?
He isn't
mocking you, sister.
That man is... protecting us.
[AMAZON 414K] Oh no!
Sandersonia's clothing
burned off in the fire!
Her back is showing!
[AMAZON 414L]
If he gets off her,
her Gorgon Eyes will be exposed!
[AMAZON 414M] Hurry! Look away!
She's going to
turn us all to stone!
I didn't even realize...
It's like your sister
said before, right?
My secret is out.
He saw my back.
Then we mustn't let
him leave the castle alive.
Why not?
What's the big deal?
I just saw her back.
What you saw is a secret
we would die to protect.
Or rather, one that
we would kill to protect,
in this particular instance.
You'd rather die
than let people see this
thing on your back, right?
Like I said, don't move.
This match is hereby over!
Everyone, you must
leave the arena at once!
Do not gaze
upon the Gorgon Eyes!
[AMAZON 414B] Don't look at her!
You'll be turned to stone!
[AMAZON 414E]
Hurry! Get out of here!
[AMAZON 414A]
Run away! Run away!
[AMAZON 414F]
It's the Gorgon's curse!
[AMAZONS panicking]
You know that I
was trying to kill you
just a moment ago.
Why are you protecting me?
'Cause that mark on your back
has nothing to do
with our fight.
We can always
settle things later.
You owe your lives
to the man you tried to execute.
You must make a decision,
but what will it be?
You may be able
to fool this country.
But the time may come
when you can nyo longer
fool yourself, Princess.
If you truly want to
move forward in this world,
you must come to terms
with what you wear on your back.
[quiet sobbing]
[NARRATOR] After Luffy protects
the secret of the Snake Sisters,
they decide to spare his life.
Hancock reveals the story
behind the familiar mark
on their backs.
Her tale of her
childhood is one of tragedy
suffered at the hands
of a corrupt group
that Luffy knows all too well.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
Hancock's Confession!
The Sisters' Abhorrent Past!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!