Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Impel Down.
A living hell buried
beneath the waves where
the world's most notorious
prisoners are held.
Yet, despite being history's
most heavily fortified prison,
it has been breached
by an upstart pirate
named Straw Hat Luffy.
He hopes to free his
brother, "Fire Fist" Ace,
who is condemned to be executed.
However, he is not the
only one to make his way
through the prison's
iron defenses.
Another breach occurred
20 years before.
[PRISON GUARDS yelping]
[NARRATOR] The culprit
was the first and only man
to successfully break out
of the legendary prison
and see the light of day again.
[alarm blaring]
Unbelievable.
That damn lunatic cut off
his own legs to escape.
[NARRATOR] And with
this astonishing feat,
he wrote his name in
the pages of history.
[NARRATOR] Captain of
the dreaded Flying Pirates.
Shiki, The Golden Lion!
[NARRATOR] These events
transpired only a matter of days
before Luffy and the
Straw Hat Pirates.
Faced Shiki himself in battle.
[LUFFY] A Special Presentation
Related to the Movie.
A Golden Lion's
Ambition on the Move.
[slow beeping]
[AMIGO PIRATES laughing]
[AMIGO PIRATE laughs]
[AMIGO PIRATE 426A]
Captain! Senor Colt!
[COLT]
Si? What is it?
There's a call. I think it's
from Big Boss Shiki's people!
[AMIGO PIRATES]
Huh?
[COLT] About time.
Sure kept us waiting.
Bring me the Transponder Snail!
[AMIGO PIRATE 426A]
Yes, sir! Right away!
You hear that, big bro?
We might get to team up with
Shiki's crew. If this pans out,
we'll be in the Grande
leagues, just you wait!
[LARGO gasping]
Hey, Big Bro.
Uh. Are those happy tears?
Sad tears. The saddest,
hermano Colt.
I'm filled with a
beautiful sorrow. Ennui.
[COLT]
Eh?
If senor Shiki succeeds
in the implementation
of his odious machinations.
The world will be drowned in
a tidal wave of despair. Si.
When I imagine the
thousands of wailing voices,
crying out in agony.
I feel simply,
overwhelmingly sad.
[COLT grunts]
[AMIGO PIRATE 426A] Sir.
Here's the transponder snail!
Good. Put 'im through.
[GOLD LION PIRATE 426A]
Am I speaking with the captain
of the Amigo Pirates?
Captain Largo?
[COLT]
No, this is Vice Captain Colt.
But I'm speaking on behalf
of Captain Largo.
[GOLD LION PIRATE 426A]
Very well.
This call is to inform you
that Captain Shiki has decided
to accept Mr. Largo
into his assembly
as our 51st pirate captain.
Congratulations.
[AMIGO PIRATES gasp]
[COLT chuckles]
Well! Of course!
[GOLD LION PIRATE 426A]
However, there is one condition.
A mere formality that must
be completed before you join.
Oh?
Un condition?
Still no bites.
Where are you, fish?
[USOPP sighs]
Man, I'm hungry.
[stomach growls]
Ya don't say. 'Cuz you
look pretty full to me.
[CHOPPER]
Well we have been eating
giant banquets every night.
Our stomachs expanded.
And as a result, we need
to eat more to fill them up.
[BROOK]
Ugh. I know. It's ridiculous
how heavy my bones have
gotten these past few days.
That is not how it works.
[SANJI] How's it goin'?
Catch anything yet?
[USOPP]
Not yet. Not even a nibble.
[SANJI] We're completely
out of food, you know.
Either you catch something
or we don't eat.
[GROUP]
What?
Yeah, "what"?
I kept tellin' you guys
we didn't have enough food
to do banquets every damn night.
But ya had to party.
[GROUP]
♪ Banquet banquet ban-quet!
[LUFFY] Is that what we did?
[USOPP] Yeah.
[SANJI]
Buncha gluttons...
[BROOK]
Huh?
Oh, a bite! A bite!
A bite! I've got a bite!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Ah, reel it in!
[USOPP]
Nicely done, Brook!
[GROUP grunting]
It's a big sucker!
Awesome! We're havin'
a banquet tonight!
[SANJI] Catch that fish
even if it kills you!
[USOPP]
Banquet!
[CHOPPER]
Keep pulling! It's coming!
We might starve but at least
they're having fun.
[ROBIN chuckles]
[ALL grunting]
[FRANKY whistling]
[FRANKY] Hm?
[USOPP, BROOK, LUFFY grunting]
[FRANKY gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
Hm?
[GROUP]
And here it comes!
[FRANKY screaming]
[ZORO gasps]
What is that?
Huh?
That's not good.
[ALL yelping]
Wha--?
It's a huge beetle!
Our fish!
Banquet!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Awesome!
[YOKO]
Huh?
Don't tell me...
[YOKO]
It's a pirate ship?
Those evil bastards
aren't landing here!
[YOKO]
Boss! Take 'em down!
[BOSS groaning]
[NAMI]
It's coming back!
That thing is freakin' enormous!
[LUFFY laughs]
I wanna ride on it!
[CHOPPER]
What? That's just nuts, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Hey, Usopp! Let's catch it!
Ready!
Hold on, were you
waiting for this?
[FRANKY] I'm not lettin'
that bug destroy our ship!
Coup de...
Vent!
[FRANKY yelps]
Franky's attack
didn't even phase it!
[FRANKY]
But I'm so super!
[LUFFY]
I got this one, guys!
[LUFFY grunts]
Hey beetle! Bring it on!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY]
Bazooka!
He knocked Boss away!
That's crazy!
[BOSS groaning]
Not only is it gigantic,
but it breathes fire.
Damn. That thing's gonna
roast our ship to a crisp!
Luffy! Are you okay up there?
[LUFFY]
It's super big.
Super strong.
And it breathes fire.
It's the coolest thing ever!
[CHOPPER]
Uh...
Yeah, I get the
feeling he's okay.
[LUFFY]
I got a plan!
I'm gonna make him
join our crew!
[ALL]
Wait, what? Hang on, Luffy!
[LUFFY giggles] Alright,
big guy. You're gonna join--
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY giggles]
Yeah, I got ya now!
[YOKO]
This can't be happening.
[LUFFY laughing]
[USOPP] Looks like they're
headed back this way.
[BROOK]
Indeed.
[USOPP] In fact, it looks like
they're headed straight for us!
Make a run for it!
[USOPP slow motion]
Help! Help!
[USOPP]
Help me!
[SANJI]
Really, Usopp?
[ZORO]
Oh, c'mon, you damn idiot.
[SANJI, ZORO grunt]
[USOPP whimpering]
[NAMI]
Huh?
And now it's flying away.
[NAMI]
What's wrong with those morons?
[NAMI] Hey, there's an
island over there.
I'm guessing that's where
the beetle came from.
[YOKO]
Uh-oh!
Watch out, Boss! Pull up!
[USOPP screams]
We're gonna hit the wall!
[BOSS groaning]
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY laughing]
Good luck gettin' away now,
ya giant beetle!
So, you gonna join
my crew or what?
I'd say yes if I were you.
[LUFFY laughs]
[YOKO]
Boss is with me!
Huh?
[YOKO] And he'd rather
die than become a pirate!
[YOKO growling]
[LUFFY screaming]
[USOPP, SANJI, ZORO groan]
Okay, so now what?
I didn't even know there
was an island out here.
[USOPP pants]
Y'know what I wanna know?
[GROUP]
What the hell are they doing?
[VILLAGERS panting]
[YELLOW VEST GUY]
Yoko! What's wrong?
[YOKO] Be careful, stay back!
This guy's a pirate!
[VILLAGERS]
Wait, he's a pirate?
Have mercy on us!
[YOKO] Stop fighting back,
you pirate scum!
[FABRE]
Hm? If I'm not mistaken,
you folks are from the
Straw Hat Pirates, aren't you?
[ISLANDERS]
Huh?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, that's us.
Oh, man, you're right!
I thought I recognized them!
[BLUE SHIRT GUY] Yeah!
That guy's "Pirate Hunter" Zoro!
[PINK SHIRT GUY]
And him!
That's the infamous
"Black Leg" Sanji!
[GREEN SHIRT GUY]
And is that...
[ISLANDERS]
Wait, who is that guy?
Oh, c'mon!
[YOKO]
Lemme go!
That jerk tried to
take Boss away from me!
I'll bite him to death!
[YELLOW VEST GUY]
Yoko! Calm down!
[YOKO] You calm down!
Shut up and let me at him!
Who in the hell
are these people?
That really hurt!
C'mon! I didn't know you
were that beetle's owner!
What owner? He's my friend!
Nobody owns Boss!
Your friend? Really?
You're already on someone
else's team, then?
Don't you think he'd be
better off on a real crew?
[YOKO grunts]
No he wouldn't!
Because Boss and I
are inseparable!
Okay. Can't argue with that.
Huh?
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Here we goo.
Hey! What're you doing to him?
[LUFFY grunting, yelling]
[LUFFY yells]
He's free!
[BOSS groans]
[LUFFY]
Sorry if I hurt you, big guy.
You don't think you could
hurt Boss, do you?
[LUFFY] What? I didn't
mean it like that.
[BOSS roars]
[YOKO]
Hey, are you okay?
[LUFFY] Hey, is--
[YOKO] Stay back!
These wounds are nothin' more
than a few scratches to Boss!
They'll all heal up while he's
sleeping underground tonight!
Wow! That's pretty badass!
[YOKO]
Oh, yeah, you think that's cool?
Well, he's gonna
molt tomorrow, too!
He'll get even bigger and
stronger than he is now!
Huh? I didn't think
Beetles kept on molting
after they were fully grown.
[FABRE]
Boss isn't an ordinary beetle.
He sheds his skin once a month
no matter how large he gets.
So as big as he is,
he's only gonna get bigger.
He's gonna be even
stronger than he is now?
Sure is! What, do you
wanna fight about it?
Yeah! That's cool!
Listen, I'll come back
tomorrow and we'll try again!
Uh--
[LUFFY]
Then we'll know for sure
which one of us
is the strongest!
But that's just ridiculous.
[BOSS groaning]
Huh?
[LUFFY laughs]
Alright.
You better not
chicken out on me, then!
[BOSS roars]
[FABRE laughs]
If nothing else,
the boy sure is
spirited, isn't he?
Boss?
[FABRE]
Watch your step!
Wow! This cave is so cavernous!
[USOPP]
What's it used for?
[WHITE SHIRT GUY] Oh, this?
It's an escape route.
[USOPP]
From what?
[WHITE SHIRT GUY] This cave
is like a massive labyrinth
if you don't know
your way around.
So it's the perfect strategy for
outrunning marauding pirates.
[PONYTAIL GUY]
You'd be hard pressed to find
anyone more adept at
running away than we are.
And that's something
you're proud of?
[FABRE] That's the only
way we can survive
on the Grand Line.
We don't have a military.
And the island is so remote
that the Navy basically
treats us like we don't even
exist, so we're on our own.
Hey, speaking of the Navy.
I noticed that girl was
dressed up like a marine.
[SANJI]
What's all that about?
[FABRE]
She wears that hat and coat,
in memory of her father.
[FABRE] That man was
as good as they come.
He refused to look the other way
while we kept getting attacked.
So he left his battalion
and stayed on our island
in order to protect us.
[SANJI] And when you
said, "In memory of"?
[FABRE]
It happened five long years ago.
The poor, brave man took on a
group of pirates all by himself.
And he was killed.
And then, three years later.
Boss appeared out of nowhere
as if this was his home.
Yoko was the first to find him.
They bonded right away.
And he quickly became the
guardian angel of our island.
Truth be told, I get the
impression that Boss's strength
and bravery remind poor
little Yoko of her father.
Are you sure it's alright
for us to be here?
We are pirates.
A different class of pirate.
Now. Here we are.
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
Wow! A windmill! It's huge!
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
We're so high up!
[USOPP]
Whoa.
I thought we were just
gonna get more rocks
but it's actually
beautiful back here.
Well, then again...
[USOPP] Not to be rude,
but there's not much
of an architectural
uniformity here.
It's interesting though.
[FABRE laughs]
You don't recognize the theme?
It was a deserted island
when we came here,
so we worked hard to
make all the buildings
look just like they do.
The strange thing is that
everyone who's landed here
since has come from
the same ocean.
So our town is like
a microcosm, in a way.
So we'd like to
welcome you, Straw Hats.
To Kansorn Island.
Home away from home for
expatriates of the East Blue!
[FABRE] We like to
call it Little East Blue!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
Wow! I never dreamed
we'd have the East Blue's
most famous rookies
show up on our shore!
[RANDOM VILLAGER 426D]
Hey, Zoro!
You're from
Frost Moon Village, right?
We've got a dojo just like
the one you trained in!
You should come
and check it out!
[ZORO]
Really?
[RANDOM VILLAGER 426E]
And you grew up on the Baratie,
right, Sanji?
We'd love to hear what you think
of the food at our Baratie.
It's pretty good!
There's a Baratie here?
[USOPP]
Anyone here from Syrup Village?
[YELLOW SHIRT GUY]
Let's see.
I think Luigia might
be from there, actually.
Luigia?
[YELLOW SHIRT GUY]
Yeah, that's right.
She lives in the
biggest mansion in town.
A mansion? But the only
mansion in Syrup Village
is the one Kaya lives in.
Ugh. Everybody thinks
they're so great.
But no shifty pirate's
gonna trick me!
I swear it.
It's been a while.
Do you think they're okay?
[NAMI]
Don't get so worked up, Chopper.
I'm sure they'll call us soon.
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, I hope so.
You might wanna think about
building an insect cage
for when they return, Franky.
Hey, good idea.
I guess we're gonna need one if
that thing's our new shipmate.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
Ca-lick.
[NAMI]
You see?
[USOPP] It's me, Usopp,
I need to talk to Nami!
Hey, Usopp. It's Nami.
What's going on?
Did you guys catch it okay?
[USOPP]
No no no, forget about that.
Will you shut up, calm down!
I can't hear her!
Look, how quickly do you think
you could get over
to where we are?
Huh?
[USOPP] There's a town right on
the other side of the island.
[VILLAGERS clamoring]
[USOPP]
Take it easy, guys.
I said I'd ask her, didn't I?
I'm so confused.
[USOPP] Please, just get
over here! I'm begging you!
[NAMI] Wait, why, Usopp?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL] Cah-lick.
[NAMI]
He hung up on me!
Why do they just
want you to come?
[NAMI]
I dunno.
Well, I guess I might as
well see what they want.
[NAMI]
You guys take care of the ship!
[FRANKY]
Yeah! You got it!
[CHOPPER]
And there she goes.
[COLT]
Is this it?
[AMIGO PIRATE 426A] It matches
the description they gave,
rock bound and
surrounded by reefs.
A natural barricade
against approaching ships.
Well. That's easy.
No reefs are going to
slow down this ship.
[slow beeping]
Alright, it's time
to go hunting, boys!
[COLT]
Let's grab the giant beetle
that escaped from
Shiki's hideout!
Now are you men
ready to catch a bug?
[AMIGO PIRATES]
Si!
[NARRATOR] The Straw Hats
have landed on an island
Where settlers from
the East Blue live.
Surrounded by familiar sights,
they're suddently
reminded of home,
even in far away waters.
However, the peaceful
settlement is soon disrupted
from an attack by
the Amigo Pirates.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
A Special Presentation
Related to the Movie:
Little East Blue in Danger.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!