Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[HOGBACK] Although most people
associate zombies with fear,
what if you think
of them in terms
of "someone who has
come back from the dead"?
Then it's a miracle!
The dream of all doctors!
Everyone in this world
has a loved one they'd like
to see come back to life!
Why, that's human nature!
And yet the medical
community condemns it.
Madness, they call it!
I'm trying to
play God, they say!
That's why I disappeared
from society,
so I could continue
my research in seclusion
on this island
without interruption!
Oh wow.
So I finally
found out the truth!
But just think-- If your
research here is a success,
then you're going to bring
happiness to thousands
of people all over the world!
As a doctor, myself, sir,
I'm behind you all the way!
How open minded!
Why, thank you, Doctor Chopper.
[CHOPPER] Even if you
acknowledge me as a doctor,
you won't get on my
good side, you big dummy!
[CHOPPER] C-Could I
have your autograph?
Oh, of course!
"To my dear, Doctor Chopper."
So, do you think
you could give me
a little tour of your lab later?
No one, and I mean no one,
can look inside my lab!
[LUFFY]
"Nami's in a Major Pinch!
The Zombie Mansion
and the Invisible Man!"
[USOPP] You're a big girl, Nami.
Can't you do this kind
of thing by yourself?
Usopp is right.
I could be picking Dr. Hogback's
super brilliant brain right now.
Yeah, yeah--just shut
up and keep walking.
I know I shouldn't,
but I wanna take a peek.
What? You do?
Chopper, I'm shocked!
I'm not talking about
Nami's butt, you silly human.
The thing I wanna take a peek at
is Dr. Hogback's
awesome laboratory.
Speak for yourself.
It's probably haunted.
Why do we have to sit out here?
Y'know, Nami, if you're
that afraid to take a shower
by your lonesome, maybe you
should skip it altogether!
Maybe some of us
don't wanna smell
like zombies any
longer than we have to!
Stinky-butts.
[USOPP] Oh yeah?
How would you know
what our butts smell like?
[CHOPPER] Yeah!
As soon as night
time hits, we're outta here.
[CHOPPER and USOPP] What?
At night? But it's scary
enough during the day!
We finally found a place where
nobody's trying to eat us!
But as soon as we step outside,
we're the main course
in a Straw Hat buffet!
That sounds painful,
so for the time being
I'm staying right where I am.
All we gotta do is wait
for Luffy to show up.
He'll save us.
[CHOPPER]
I think he's right, Nami.
This island's way
too creepy for us!
I'm not going through
that graveyard again!
We're not any
safer inside than out.
You did take a look at
this mansion, didn't you?
No. Whaddya mean?
[NAMI] If my hunch about
this place is correct,
we're right in the
middle of spook central.
There're more zombies
in this mansion
than you can shake a stick at.
Get me outta
here--I need my brains!
[NAMI] The one I'm worried
about is Dr. Hogback himself.
He's lying to us.
There's no doubt about it.
If he really has nothing to do
with the zombies on this island,
then you tell me why
they leave his place alone
and terrorize everything else.
Hey. Whaddya think
we should do, Chopper?
If what she's saying is true--
[CHOPPER thinking]
No way!
Is she saying that Dr. Hogback
is working with the zombies?
That's why we're
gonna make our escape
while we still have the chance.
When I'm finished here,
we make a break for the coast.
[MALE VOICE] You are
a very observant woman.
[NAMI] What? Usopp,
Chopper--what did you say?
[CHOPPER] Huh?
[USOPP] We didn't say anything.
[fart]
[USOPP] Hahaha!
But my butt just did!
[CHOPPER] Ew! Stinky!
[USOPP] Maybe you
should call me poo-sopp!
Huh?!
Huh?
Augh!
[NAMI] What the
hell is going on?
There isn't anybody
in here, is there?
[growls]
[NAMI] No way!
[MALE VOICE]
You're even prettier
than the lass on the ship.
Fear looks so good on you.
[NAMI] Who said that?
Usopp, Chopper, I--!
[MALE VOICE] Hush, my darling!
Or should I say, my bride!
Did you just now call for us?
I betcha you can smell
his fart in here, too, huh!
Auuuughhhh!!
[USOPP] Thank you very much!
Why are you thanking her?
[MALE VOICE] Damn them.
[NAMI] Help me, you idiots!
[MALE VOCIE]
Urk!!
What are you waiting for?
Save me already!
Something's in here!
[sniff, sniff]
Yeah-- I can smell it!
Sorry! Geez!
I'm not talking
about your fart!
It's a person!
Do something!
He's escaping out the window!
Great! Now I have to
shoot at an invisible target?
Special Attack, Gunpowder Star!
That fool. Is he doing it again?
[USOPP] Uh, what now?
Should I keep shooting?
[CHOPPER] Nah.
I don't smell anything.
Whatever it was, it's gone.
[NAMI] Then he must've escaped.
Oh, Nami!
You're not hurt, are you?
[NAMI] Well, whoever
it was, they heard it all.
Wait, who heard what?
I still don't
understand all this!
You sure it wasn't my fart?
He was in here the entire time.
An invisible man.
[FRANKY] Well this is no good.
Thanks to this gigantic spider
web we're dead in the water.
Uh, no pun intended.
[ZORO] Something's
not right about this.
[SANJI] It's not like
we'd be leaving, anyway.
We have to find Nami--and
the others too, I guess.
Let's head out.
[LUFFY] Hey! Zoro! Get your
butt down here already!
Even if meeting that
skeleton was a fluke,
the fact that the Thousand
Sunny and the Mini Merry
both got tangled up in this web
in the exact same spot
is pretty damn fishy.
Somebody went to a helluva lot
of trouble to make sure that
when we enter this place,
it's through the front gate,
and nowhere else.
[ZORO] Geez.
If they were gonna
make it that obvious,
they might as well have
laid out a welcome mat for us.
[LUFFY] Zoro, what are you
mumbling about up there?
You're gonna miss all the fun!
Are you seriously
about to walk into a trap
that's so damn obvious,
one even a headless zombie
would have the sense
to run away from?
Pretty much, yeah!
It's not like we have anything
better to do right now!
It'll be fun!
If you don't go, then
I'm taking your lunchbox!
Son of a-- Fine.
If I leave you alone, I'll
just have to rescue you later,
so I might as well just
save myself the trouble
and help you now.
[LUFFY] All right! Onward!
[SANJI] Sure took ya
long enough, moss head.
[ZORO] Aw, shut up.
[SANJI] Why's there suddenly
a staircase leading down?
[LUFFY] It's the only way in.
Let's just go with the flow.
[LUFFY] Hey, I wonder if
these skeletons can poop, too.
Ruff!
Roof!
Rawr!
Yum!
Check it out,
everyone--it's Cerberus.
We are literally on the
path to hell right now.
Aw, I think it's kind of cute.
Are they a threat?
'Cause I'm feeling super.
Three heads are overkill.
Wonder what they taste like!
Hahahahaha!
Raff! Raff! Raff! Raff!
[ZORO] More like a
three-headed chicken.
Ruff!
Roof!
Rawr!
[ZORO] Weird how they got
all riled up outta nowhere.
[SANJI] Maybe one of
the heads remembered
that they're supposed
to be brave?
[ROBIN] That's possible.
Anyway--
[LUFFY] Nuh-uh! Dibs!
I'm gonna tame this bad boy!
[ZORO] Huh? You idiot!
You can't just tame it!
You do know it's not
a regular dog, yeah?
[LUFFY] How different can it be?
C'mon, who's a good boys? Shake!
[FRANKY] I assume we all
saw this moment coming?
[ROBIN chuckles]
[LUFFY] What big
strong teeth you have.
Now leggo of Uncle Luffy's head.
That's a good boys.
Easy does it.
Just like I said. Now sit!
[LUFFY] Roll over.
[SANJI] That just happened.
The poor thing's body
looks pretty beat up.
I'm surprised it can
still walk around like that.
I wonder what wise-ass
put this thing together,
cause whoever it was,
they can't tell the difference
between a dog head
and a fox head.
[chuckles]
If this is the first
creature we met on the island,
I can't wait to see what
other stuff we run into!
Cerberus seems pretty
down in the mouths.
C'mon Robin,
don't pity 'em.
It just makes
'em feel worse.
Leave 'em alone already.
Can you hear
me, Nami sweet?
Hello? Where are you,
my feisty truffle?
I'm all turned around.
It's like a maze full
o' creepy! Hey, wait up!
[SANJI] Okay, Nami!
When I say "sweetie,"
you say "here!" Sweetie?
I got a good
sense of direction,
but I can barely
tell my Strong Right
from my Coup de Boo around here.
With so much fog everywhere,
for all that we know we
might be going in circles.
Hey, Nami!
We would've had better luck
if ol' moss-head had
just stayed on the boat.
How is this my fault?
[FRANKY] Whoa.
A tree with
some geezer's face
is totally getting drunk
with a beat-up unicorn.
Just leave me alone
already, you crazy kid!
I'm making
a wish on you,
whether ya' like it or not!
[LUFFY] Gum Gum Bug Catcher!
[FRANKY] Strong Right!
Look at what I caught!
Please just
lemme go!
Oh, no! No! Stop shaking me!
I-- oh geez.
[ZORO] Hey, Luffy!
Whaddya wanna do
with these guys?
[SANJI] Don't tell me.
They're so cool!
How 'bout you
join my pirate crew?
Overruled, dumbass!
[MALE VOICE]
That was too close.
You're there, right, Absalom?
I can never tell.
What was all that ruckus?
Were you peeking in on
a bathing beauty again?
[ABSALOM] I'm on the
hunt for a bride, Hogback.
[ABSALOM] The redhead.
I quite fancy her.
I'll make her mine soon enough.
[HOGBACK] I hate to
burst your bubble,
but you shouldn't go
marrying the golden goose.
[ABSALOM] What's that
supposed to mean?
We have six guests
with bounties
on their heads this time,
including that girl you like.
Her captain's worth
300 million berries!
[ABSALOM] Three hundred million?
You don't seem
very worried, Perona.
If his bounty is that high,
we can only assume
he's one tough customer.
If you understand that,
then you'll know
you have to go all-out
on this one--and that
means no chasing skirts.
Looks like we'll have
ourselves a busy night tonight.
[USOPP] Invisible
men don't exist, Nami!
End of discussion!
[NAMI] Then who
accosted me back there?
Listen to me!
You just imagined it, okay?
I betcha clammy invisible hands
are a really common delusion!
I didn't imagine it, you ninny!
When you came in there,
you saw how it was holding
me off the ground, didn't you?
Yeah, I saw--I mean,
uh--Sorry, Nami!
Didn't see a thing!
Don't lie to me!
Ah! Trick question!
That's no fair!
As soon as I confess to
seeing you naked, I'm done for!
You're gonna slap me
into next week!
Ugh! I'm not trying to
play mind-games here!
The slapping can wait!
[USOPP] See? I knew it!
You wanna
know what I think?
Nothing I've seen on
this island has been real,
including you being naked!
The invisible man
was just a draft!
The ghosts were weird birds!
And the zombies were just
some, underground tribe!
[NAMI] Are you nuts?
[USOPP] Sure, we ran into
a fiddle-playing skeleton
with an afro who was brought
back to life by a devil fruit!
--But he was the exception!
No two devil fruits in
the world work the same!
If his fruit brought him back
to life, then he's the only one!
So, zombies and ghosts
and all the other horrible stuff
around here is impossible!
Right, Chopper?
Huh?
Come on, back me up!
The creatures we saw,
there's no natural explanation
for 'em, so they can't be real!
If you're looking at this
from a medical point of view,
then you're correct, Usopp.
There should be an
explanation for all this stuff.
Then again, if Dr. Hogback
thought his work on the island
was important enough to
leave his whole life behind,
maybe the natural
order of things
is turned upside
down on this island.
That is not what
I wanted to hear!
Maybe Hogback's not the
hero you think he is.
[CHOPPER] Doctor Hogback
is an amazing man,
and a medical titan!
I think he's incredible!
How come you think
the worst of him?
We don't know if he's
friends with those zombies!
You can't prove anything!
[NAMI] Prove?
Who needs proof,
when it's as plain as
the nose on Usopp's face?
Your idol is the Zombie King!
[USOPP] This is the
worst argument ever!
Just agree to disagree!
[CHOPPER] All right, let's go
ask Dr. Hogback what he thinks.
How's that sound?
That sounds horrible!
I wish Luffy would
hurry up and save us!
I know I don't have
anything to base it on yet,
but I don't trust that Hogback.
He gives me the creeps.
[NAMI] Pretty sure I know,
but I have to ask.
[USOPP] Huh?
[CHOPPER] What is it, Nami?
[NAMI] Isn't this the room
we just ate dinner in?
[USOPP] Yeah, so how come
it's pitch black in here?
[CHOPPER] What the--?
[USOPP] Uh. Cindry. You around?
[CHOPPER] Dr. Hogback,
can you hear me?
[NAMI] Yeah. We're done
with the bathroom. Thanks.
Anybody home?
Hello! Calling Dr. Hogback!
[HILDON] I'm afraid the doctor
and Cindry have called it a day!
[USOPP] Wait, Hildon?
Why, you little!
What's the big idea,
ditching our carriage in the
middle of a scary graveyard?
[HILDON] I feel bad about that.
Out of nowhere, I really
had to go to the bathroom.
You know how it is.
[NAMI] You're such a liar!
Admit it, weirdo--you're in
cahoots with those zombies!
How could you say such
awful things about poor Hildon?
But enough of
that unpleasantness.
If you'll follow me
to the guest rooms?
So if you don't turn us
into zombie chow at first,
try try again?
I don't trust
you any farther
than I can throw you, pudgy!
FYI, we're leaving
here right now,
and there's nothing
you can do about it!
[CHOPPER] Huh? Wait a minute!
Just let me straighten
things out with Dr. Hogback!
[FEMALE VOICE] Heh heh. Looks
like you bungled it, Hildon.
[CHOPPER] Who--
who said that? Hello?
You don't have
to be so mean to me.
I'll take them up
to their rooms, okay?
I think it's a
little late for that.
These three have noticed
far too much around here.
We can't risk them
telling anyone about us.
I-I don't believe it!
The painting!
It's holding a conversation
with us like it's people!
You're shaking like
leaves on a tree.
How adorable!
Wanna know a secret?
You're so cute I could
swallow you whole right now!
Let go of him!
That painting's
trying to eat Chopper!
I don't wanna be a still-life!
Chopper! I'm coming!
Attagirl, Nami! Keep pulling!
[NAMI] Get your butt
over here and help!
[USOPP] I'm moral support!
Heheheh!
It is not the painting
that you have to
worry about, but I,
the great Oinkchuck!
You fools will never
leave this room alive again,
so just get that
outta your head!
That mounted pig-head on
the wall is talking, too!
And it threw a sword!
I know you're busy, Nami,
but there's some pretty
threatening taxidermy back here!
[BEARSKIN RUG ZOMBIE]
Wait up, is that a sword?
Okay, who's the wise-guy
who stabbed the bearskin?
Auuugh!!
Nami was right! This mansion
is wall-to-wall zombies!
Even the decorations!
What're you doing?
Here it comes!
Eat this, you freaky undead rug!
Huh?
I can't believe you
threw a candle at me!
Seriously--who does
that? Hot, hot, hot!
We've got a fire
in the dining room!
The rug-manity!
That guy on the
chandelier did it!
Throw lit candles at him!
See how much he likes it!
Oh no ya don't!
Because I know your weakness,
foul minions of the underworld!
The power of Usopp
compels you!
[USOPP]
Take it!
Nami! Chopper!
Open the door!
We need to get outta here!
I don't care about Dr. Hogback!
I wanna leave!
Open it! My heart can't
take much more of this!
What are you doing, Nami?
You're kidding, right?
No, I'm not! We're really
trapped in here, Usopp!
Auugh!!
How dare you set me on fire?
You dumb little pyro!
You're not getting
away that easy!
No!
[USOPP] Chopper, I hate to ask,
but what's that on
the operating table?
[CHOPPER]
You really want to know?
[USOPP] Of course not!
But I mean,
is it what it looks like?
[CHOPPER] I'll tell you,
if you're ready.
[USOPP] No! Maybe just
give me a little hint.
[CHOPPER] It's a--
[USOPP] Ah! I'm scared!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"The Zombie's Secret!
Hogback's
Nightmarish Laboratory!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!