[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[SPANDAM laughs]
Watch carefully, men!
Because you're about
to witness the first step
of a hero that is destined
to go down in history!
[yells]
[quavered exhale]
What's he doing up there?
It's so far away!
How the hell's he hitting us?
[USOPP] Shing!
[MARINE U] Is he
using a slingshot?
[MARINE V]
This guy's a monster!
The wind's blowing like crazy
and he's all the way over there,
but he's still hitting
his mark every time!
Thank you, Long Nose.
[ROBIN panting]
[MARINE Y] Nico Robin
is getting away!
Then stop her!
Shoot her down!
[MARINES] Sir!
Shoot her just dead enough
to keep her alive!
[SPANDAM] Fire!
Aaah...
[FRANKY breathing heavy]
[yells]
[MARINE AA]
Who the hell is that?
Franky.
Bullet's are no problem
when you're made of iron.
But that landmine wasn't
very nice, Spanda.
[yells]
[FRANKY laughs intensely]
We got it!
[quavered breathing]
Okay, we got it!
Hey! You hear me?
[FRANKY] We got the
handcuffs off Robin,
no problem!
[USOPP and SANJI] Yes!
[ROBIN] Thank you, Long Nose.
That was wonderful.
[USOPP] It was the
least I could do.
The true heroes
are those who fought
to retrieve those keys
from the enemy.
[USOPP] The Straw Hats
will be proud
to have you back.
Hold your head up
high and meet them
with a smile when
all of this has ended!
Right.
[USOPP laughs]
Everything went
according to my plan.
[distant shrieking]
[USOPP] Eh? What's that?
[shrieking continues]
[USOPP] I swear
I heard something.
[screeching]
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
♪
[USOPP] Huh?
What the hell was that?
[MARINES whisper]
Already?
[MARINE A] The battleships
are firing on us?
[MARINE B]
It took out the stockade.
[MARINE A] Vice Admiral!
Our canon fire
landed a direct hit
on the stockade at
4 o'clock in front
of the main island.
[DOBERMAN]
So, what's your point?
[MARINE A] Um.
[DOBERMAN] Is there
any reason why
that should matter to me?
[MARINE A] Oh.
I guess not, sir.
This is a thorough,
indiscriminate attack.
I only care if we
don't hit something.
Right.
[DOBERMAN] Our mission
is to bomb everything
on this island into the sea.
We'll start by targeting
the Tower of Law.
And once we're in firing range,
we'll unload a full-scale
blitz on Enies Lobby.
Yes, sir.
[DOBERMAN] If you
so clearly understand
the orders you've been given,
stop wasting my time
and start reloading the cannons!
Sir! Yes, sir!
[ZORO] They blew
a hole in the fence
around the island.
That was a pretty
massive explosion.
[SANJI] They've got
enough room to steer
a whole fleet through there
and rain fire all over us.
And take a look at that.
[SANJI] The whirlpools
that usually
surround the island
have completely vanished.
If they aren't around
to keep ships out
and the Gates of
Justice are wide open,
there's nothing
to stop the attacks.
I guess those
whirlpools were only there
'cause the gates
were blocking the flow
of the current
to the waterfall.
[ZORO] So now that
the gates are open,
the current has a
straight shot to the falls
and it's smooth sailing
for all those battleships.
Things are about
to get ugly.
Yeah, we'd better get
moving while we still can.
[SANJI] Hey, Sniper King!
[ZORO] Things have
gotten serious.
Hurry up and jump
down from there.
[USOPP] Is that
supposed to be a joke?
First off, I don't
have the same kind of
freakish super-human strength
that you guys have, alright?
And while perfectly ample,
my bravery is not
the life-risking kind!
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm a normal super hero,
not a super, super hero! Eh.
[BOTH] No, Usopp!
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINE C] They bombed
the Tower of Law!
Long Nose was--
You think they hit him?
[FAMILY A] Look! They took
out the Tower of Law!
It's falling over!
Let's just hope
those guys are okay.
That wasn't just some
accidental explosion up there!
[MARINE B] You're right!
I think we're under attack!
We gotta get off
this damn island!
[rumbling]
[glass breaking]
Uh.
[ZORO] He--He can't be.
Where are you, Usopp?
[USOPP screams]
Someone say my name?
[SANJI and ZORO] Why'd you
make us think you were dead?
You guys couldn't
even be bothered
to catch a hero
who's plunged off
an exploding, falling building?
Some friends you are!
[SANJI] Hey, Franky! Robin!
We're all okay over here
and we're headin' your way now!
Thank goodness.
Well, we better
get things in order.
How're you
feelin' right now?
You think you're
up for a fight?
Of course.
[SPANDAM] What the
hell are you waiting for?
Wipe them out before
their backup arrives!
[MARINE D] Yes, sir!
You noticed the ship
on the other side
of the bridge, right?
[FRANKY] I'm thinkin'
it's our best chance
to get out of this mess.
Well, we're already
wanted criminals;
we might as well steal a ship.
Take them down!
Dieciseis Fleurs
should stop you!
Fire!
[MARINES gasp]
What the hell?
Time for some Strong--
[FRANKY] Face Slap!
[grunts] Ha-ha!
[FRANKY] Yeah!
[wails]
Second formation, go!
[MARINES yell]
Next is Treinta Fleurs!
[MARINES grunt]
[FRANKY] Master Nails!
[MARINES groan]
Alright, third group, attack!
Fourth, fifth,
sixth, all of you!
Just get in there! Stop them!
[MARINES yell]
Damn, they're like a parade
of lemmings that
goes on forever.
Hey, take a step
back for a second.
Alright, Weapons Left!
[MARINES scream]
[FRANKY] Fresh Fire!
[FRANKY] Franky Boxing!
[FRANKY] Yow!
[chuckles]
That is some
serious fire-power.
There's no way
we can fight this guy!
[MARINES whimper]
What, you're still
not impressed?
Okay. Franky--
[MARINES gasp]
Transform!
[MARINES groan]
Now gaze upon
Franky Centaur!
He's a horse?
No, wait, that doesn't
make any sense.
His torso should be in
the front, not the legs.
Monster!
[MARINES yell]
[FRANKY] Hey, get back here!
[FRANKY] Quit running, dammit!
Hey, what the hell
are you morons running for?
Turn around and fight him!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Please,
somebody help me!
[MARINES yell]
Ugh!
Aah!
Escort ship!
Come in, escort ship!
We need reinforcements A.S.A.P.!
[MARINE H] Yes, sir! How
many men should we send in?
Did you really just ask me
how many men, you idiot?
We've got a couple of
extremely dangerous criminals
going on a rampage,
leaving a trail
of battered marines
in their wake!
[SPANDAM] Ship's
captain, navigator,
signalmen, corpsmen,
I want you to send
every single man you've
got on that damn ship!
Yes, sir!
We'll all work together
to bring the
criminals to just--
[SPANDAM] Get down
here and save me!
[BOTH] Ahhh!
[BOTH]
That's all you care about?
♪
Come on, you two.
Let's pick up the pace!
Wow! You're fast, Granny!
The power of booze
is amazing, huh?
Nnyah, nnyah!
Oh, no. To be honest,
it's not the booze
that's doin' it for me.
No?
I'm havin' fun!
[chuckles]
Come to think of it,
I haven't had this
kinda excitement
since the good 'ole days,
back when Tom was with us.
[laughs]
[FRANKY (BOY)]
What're ya laughin' at
ya big yellow weirdo?
[ICEBERG (BOY)] You're crazy!
Stop attacking him,
ya stupid kid!
♪
And how're you two
feelin' right now?
Great!
I'm havin' a blast!
So much fun, so much fun,
the life of a pirate
is nothin' but fun!
Nnyah! Nnyah!
[NAMI] Kokoro! Chimney! Gonbe!
[ALL] Huh?
Thanks for leavin'
the guide marks!
[CHIMNEY] Yay,
it's the pirate lady!
Nnyah, nnyah!
Did you guys feel
that giant tremor?
Sounds like the party's
starting up there, for sure.
Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
Nnyah! Nnyah!
[LUFFY panting]
[grunts]
Now Shave!
Bring it on!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY] Jet Pistol!
[LUCCI] Huh?
Now Jet Whip!
[panting]
And Shave!
[LUCCI] Finger Pistol!
[LUCCI] Yellow Lotus!
Uh?
[LUFFY] Jet Stamp!
[LUFFY panting]
♪
[gasps]
[LUCCI] His physical
prowess is comparable
to that of a
Six Powers Master.
He's completely different than
when I fought him at
the Galley-La Mansion.
[LUCCI] That steam
he's giving off.
And that strange
red tint to his skin.
Just what the hell is going
on inside this guy's body?
[LUCCI] Of course!
[BOTH grunt]
Now Razor!
Jet Pistol!
[growls]
[LUFFY panting]
I figured as much.
It's like you're
doping yourself
with your own blood.
You use your legs as pumps
to accelerate your blood flow.
Good thing you're
not an ordinary human.
That kind of blood pressure
would make your heart burst.
[LUCCI] But since
your internal organs
are made of rubber,
you can handle it.
A technique only someone
like you could use.
But that doesn't
mean you should.
It's obvious that you're
pushing your body too far.
And I doubt that
you can take much more.
Not very clever. Are you?
You're shortening
your own lifespan.
Just for a few
minutes of strength.
It's better than
letting you take away
everything I care about!
[LUFFY] I'll do anything
to keep that from happening.
[LUCCI] But you've still lost,
even if you do defeat me!
You must've felt
that explosion earlier.
It's a pretty safe bet that was
a battleship launching
a warm-up shot.
Shouldn't be too much
longer before they start
a full-scale bombardment.
[LUCCI] And for all we know,
your friends at the Tower
of Law could be dead already.
Maybe they got out.
Maybe they're already
running through
the underground passageways,
trying to get here
in time to help you. Heh.
[LUCCI] Tempest Kick!
What did you do?
You might defeat me, but you
can't stop this seawater
from flooding the tunnel
and drowning anyone
who happens to be in there.
[ALL panting]
[BOTH panting]
You bastard.
[LUCCI]
Face the facts, Straw Hat.
Nothing's going your way.
But don't let me
stop you from trying--
I'm interested to
see how far you'll go
in your misguided attempts
to save your little friends.
This isn't a game
we're playing, damn it!
[gunfire]
[MARINES yelling]
[commotion]
[yelling]
If nothing else, they sure
are persistent, huh?
Based on the
head count so far,
we're taking on
a full unit.
Speed it up, you goons!
I want Nico Robin captured
on that ship post haste!
We don't have long!
The battleships are coming!
Actually.
We're out of time, sir.
What did you say? Aah!
[gasps]
[MARINE E screams]
Look behind the fog!
[MARINE F] The ships are here!
[SPANDAM] Hey!
Why're you running?
Get back here!
[ROBIN] Oh, no.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
You asked for it,
Nico Robin!
The Buster Call is here!
♪
[BOTH yelling]
[FAMILY B] They're here!
[FAMILY A] They've
started the attack!
[FAMILY B]
Hurry up! Run faster!
[FAMILY C] Get us outta here!
Whad'dya think
we're trying to do?
[MARINE G] The Buster Call
has commenced!
Our primary targets
are Straw Hat Luffy
and his crew of
approximately sixty pirates.
However, due to an
agreement with Admiral Aokiji,
the criminal Nico Robin,
currently located on
the Bridge of Hesitation,
is not to be targeted.
Assessment of the current
situation is unnecessary.
Our objective is to
launch a full scale attack
on the judicial island
and Enies Lobby.
[ALL quavered exhales]
[SPANDAM laughs]
♪
[explosions]
[SPANDAM laughs]
The invocation of
merciless death.
The Buster Call
has finally begun!
[USOPP] Boss, there's
trouble! Big trouble!
[LUFFY] What's wrong?
You sound sick!
Do you have hay fever
or something?
[USOPP] Seems like it.
Itchy nose, watery eyes,
hard time breathing--wait!
That's not the problem!
The famous millennium
sakura tree is missing!
[LUFFY] What? That really
is trouble! Let's go!
On the next One Piece:
"Boss Luffy is the Culprit?
Track down the
Missing Great
I'm gonna be a policeman!