[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
You know what? That place was
pretty awesome, wasn't it?
Uh, I think I've had enough
of that ship graveyard.
[LUFFY] Well, it's not
like I want to live there,
but it would be nice to visit.
[CHOPPER] I can't believe
you actually enjoyed that.
[ZORO]
Hmm? Is that rain?
No way. This ain't rain.
[SANJI]
That's interesting.
It looks like a‐‐ Oh.
[CREW screams]
[LUFFY]
"Caught Log!
The King of Salvagers, Masira!"
Grab a holda something!
Whatever you do, don't let go!
Why are there ships
falling out of the sky?
[CHOPPER screams]
[USOPP]
Oh!!
I know. This is
just an awful dream!
Great, I love dreams!
Heads up! I don't think
the party's over yet!
It won't stop falling!
[NAMI]
The rudder! Turn the rudder!
That'll never work
in these waves!
[SANJI] Luffy, you
gotta protect the ship!
She's taking a beating!
Right! Huh?
Usopp?
I cast aside my worries
and reach deep within
to find my happy place.
And when I open my eyes,
this serene landscape is
all that will lay before me.
[shrieks]
A skeleton‐dead guy!
[NAMI] Don't throw the nasty
thing at me, you idiot!
[SANJI]
They're falling everywhere!
[USOPP]
I'm surrounded by death!
[NAMI] When is this stuff
gonna stop falling?!
All right.
Why did a ship just
fall out of the sky?
Captain error?
[ZORO]
The sky's clear.
Who knows?
I knew coming to the
Grand Line was a mistake.
It freaks me out.
First we travel over
a ship graveyard
and now they're falling out of
the sky complete with skeletons.
[NAMI]
Huh?
What's wrong, Nami?
Problem?
Oh no!
The Log Pose is broken.
It's pointing into the sky.
It's not broken.
The Log Pose registers an island
with a strong magnetic pull,
and its needle
is reflecting that.
Huh?
If the needle is
pointing toward the sky,
then it must be
pointing toward sky island.
Sky island?
[NAMI]
Are you serious?
There's a floating
island up there?
If there is one,
then it's full of skeletons
and rickety old ships.
That's ridiculous.
I don't see anything but sky.
[ROBIN] Hmmm...
That's not exactly how it works.
It's not an island above us
but an entire ocean.
[NAMI]
No way.
I'm still confused.
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
Raise the sails and set
our course for sky island!
Men, are we ready?
Put the rudder down, and point
the bow high into the sky!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Skyward, ho!
Did it just hit you?
The fact that, you know,
we can't fly and all that?
To tell you the truth,
all I know about sky island
is word of mouth; rumor.
I've never actually seen it.
Of course not!
Because it's a lie!
Islands don't float in the sky.
Our Log Pose is broken.
That's all it is.
Not quite, Miss Navigator.
You're trying to fix something
that's not even broken.
We should be trying to find
a way to get to sky island.
You really need to learn
to trust your instruments.
No matter how crazy things get,
or how weird the situation
is we find ourselves in,
never doubt the Log Pose.
Out here, on the water,
this is one of
the most steadfast
and unbreakable rules.
What we should be doubting
is the common sense
we all have that tells us
an island cannot exist in
the sky on an ocean of nothing.
That needle is pointing
toward an island.
I'd bet my life on it.
That's disgusting,
digging through
a dead man's clothes.
[NAMI growls]
That's really gonna
tell you something?
Dunno.
You're into some pretty
weird stuff, Robin.
Any lady with a fascination
for dead things is
interesting in my book.
[ZORO]
Hmm?
Where'd Luffy go?
[USOPP]
Okay, jump!
What kind of trouble
are those two getting
themselves into now?
Probably the bad kind.
[SANJI]
Hey! Looks good as new.
Except for the
holes on the crown.
Those came from
an external source.
Oh yeah.
Looks like it could have been
arrows or a spear, or something.
[ROBIN]
Not quite but good guess.
These are from a medical
procedure called craterization.
Right, doctor?
[CHOPPER]
Mm. An ancient one.
They cut out a
small hole in the skull
to remove a foreign
mass, like a tumor.
And since it leaves
a crater behind,
that's how you get the name.
Knowing how old of
a technique this is,
I'd say this man has been
dead at least 200 years.
[ROBIN] I can also say
with confidence this man was
in his early thirties
when he died.
It must have been
during his voyage
that he finally succumbed to
the illness, whatever it was.
Much more than
the rest of his bones,
his teeth have remained
in surprisingly good condition.
Because he rubbed tar on them.
It was a common
practice in the South Blue
to keep out
bacterial infections.
And considering
the history of that region,
I'd suspect that he was
with an exploratory party.
Here it is.
The Briss Kingdom
of the South Blue.
They launched the St. Briss
as a scout ship, 208 years ago.
[NAMI]
That's it!
That's the ship that fell on us.
[ZORO] Yeah, I recognize
that figurehead out front.
[ROBIN] It's probably sailed
the seas above us unmanned
since the captain and crew died.
It's amazing what you can tell
from looking at old bones!
I'm sure you've heard
that dead men
tell no tales, right?
But everything aroud them does.
If this was a scouting party,
we should find evidence
of that on the St. Briss.
Yeah. Except it's
sinking like a stone.
What are you doing, you idiot?
You can't swim!
[LUFFY]
Help! Help me!
Heh. You won't believe it!
I did it!
[pants]
I found the most
incredible thing!
[CREW]
A map of the sky island?
It's called Skypiea?
That's right.
Then it's true.
There really is
an island up there.
[cheering]
The island's real!
It's a dream!
Time to journey up
to sky island!
Hold on, guys.
We don't know how to get there
or if it's even possible.
Not to mention there are
a lot of fake treasure
maps in circulation.
[NAMI]
No, I mean. Sure, it's real.
It's gotta be because...
Well, just 'cause.
But the fact is that map doesn't
tell us how to find the place!
You're the navigator!
Navigate something!
I can't just make things up!
[SANJI]
That Nami is a vision
even when she's chewing
someone's head off.
[punch]
[NAMI]
This isn't about me.
It's about reality.
And the reality is that
we know next to nothing.
What we do know is that we can't
defy gravity and sail upwards.
That's impossible.
What we need is
more information.
If a big ship like
that made it up there,
then the odds are we
can do the same thing.
We just have to find all
the records left on that ship.
I think the ship's at the
bottom of the ocean by now.
If it sunk, we'll salvage it!
Salvage!
We can't do that!
Salvage? Really?
Yeah, but we couldn't pull
a ship up from the bottom.
I think they'll have to come up
with a more refined plan.
Ha ha ha! This is adventure!
I know I've done
more dangerous things,
but I can't remember what.
[SANJI] Nami, I swear to find
you the answers you seek,
or I will refuse to return!
I'll hold you to that.
You'll be safe.
Those barrels
are my special design.
They've never been busted.
Good luck! Be careful!
We'll be pulling for ya.
[LUFFY]
Hey, look at that!
This is Chopper here.
Can you guys call off?
[LUFFY]
This is Luffy,
and there's a ton of
monsters down here.
[ZORO] We're on a nest
of giant sea snakes.
[SANJI] This is Sanji,
and they're staring at me.
Keep going.
They could die!
[NAMI]
They'll be fine, Usopp.
Don't worry.
And Chopper.
Hold that brake tightly.
Right.
I'm so glad they
didn't make me go.
[PIRATES]
Salvage!
Salvage the sea!
What's all that noise?
[PIRATES]
Salvage the sea! Salvage!
[MASIRA]
Company, halt!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, sir!
[MASIRA] Are we on top of
the place where the ship sank?
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, Captain, sir!
[MASIRA]
When they say captain and sir,
they're talking about me!
Prepare to raise the ship!
What lies on the
bottom now belongs
to the King of All Salvagers!
Captain of the
Masira Pirates, Masira!
[cheering]
[NAMI] Great. A boat of unstable
men led by an unstable monkey.
Hey! What are
you guys doing here?
In case you didn't know,
all these waters belong to me.
They do?
Yeah, that's right!
Every vessel that sinks
in these parts
automatically becomes mine.
You're not trying
to take something
that belongs to me, are you?
[ROBIN] So he's going
to bring it to the surface.
Easier for us.
[USOPP] But not for the
three guys already in the water.
We should just keep our mouths
shut and let him do it.
Stop mumbling and answer me!
Are you people trying to yank
one of my salvages
out from under me?
[NAMI]
Excuse me!
Can I ask you a question first?
You've got questions for me?
Fine. Sure. Whatever.
Ask me anything.
[NAMI] Are all of you
tough, good‐looking men
gonna salvage that ship?
[MASIRA]
What?
[whistles]
Thank you.
I see you know what
a real man looks like.
[NAMI]
What are you talking about?
You called us all
tough and good‐looking.
That includes me.
[NAMI]
Well, of course!
Stop! You're making me blush!
[giggles]
[USOPP]
This is disturbing.
So, are you gonna
salvage that thing or what?
[MASIRA]
Of course!
I'm not the King of All
Salvagers for nothing!
If there's a sunken ship
before me, then I'll salvage it!
If it's not sunken, then I'll
sink it and salvage it later.
Now, I know how impressed you
are, but we have to save it.
There's salvaging at hand!
Loser.
Do you mind if we watch
you big strong men work?
[MASIRA]
Huh?
Don't tell me you've never seen
a professional salvage before.
Haha!
You just watch us till
your heart's content!
That's that.
Now we just have to wait
and see what happens.
Below.
In the water, there's a‐‐
Captain, we have a problem!
What is it?
Something happened to the guys
who went into the water
to set the cradle.
Was it one of those
Sea Kings again?
[PIRATE B]
I don't think so.
It looks like someone went to
town on them with their fists.
What?
You mean someone else besides
our guys are down there?
I'm gonna kill 'em.
You may not get the chance.
Listen up, you!
There's someone else
down there, so be careful!
Oh, sure.
[NAMI, USOPP]
What a moron.
I want all hands
setting the cradle!
The ship comes up in 20 minutes!
We've got salvaging to do!
Aye aye, Captain!
[NAMI]
Okay, he's waving at us.
Smile and wave back, I guess.
Just act normal.
[USOPP]
Doing my best.
Don't get stage‐fright, fellas.
They're observers.
They want to see something new.
So show them how it's done.
If you're still nervous,
try picturing them
in their underwear.
Aye aye, Captain!
[MASIRA]
Drop the cradle!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye!
[MASIRA] Keep your eyes
peeled for those intruders!
[DIVER A]
Aye aye, sir!
These guys really take
their salvaging
seriously don't they?
I think they're showing off
because their captain
has a crush on me.
[MASIRA]
Move it, men!
I want this done fast!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, sir!
Ohhh...
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
[SANJI]
[LUFFY]
Zoro.
Look.
[DIVER A]
Cradle set is locked in place.
[LUFFY]
What was that?
Huh?
Uh, so why such a big monkey?
There on the bow of the ship.
[MASIRA]
Oh, that.
Hehehe. You like?
It's a special prow I designed.
It aids in our salvage.
Just watch.
[sighing]
You're gonna love this!
Lower the Barco‐hunter!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, sir!
Monkey, monkey, monkey!
Wow! Awesome!
Completely amazing!
Are you kidding?
[DIVER D]
Forty meters to the target.
Thirty meters.
Twenty.
[DIVER D]
Ten.
Barco‐hunter joint locked!
[MASIRA]
Excellent!
Now it's time for me to blow!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, sir!
Wait. There's no way.
He's actually going to use his
breath to bring up that ship?
[NAMI]
That's ridiculous!
[LUFFY]
Is that a bubble?
[DIVER A] The body of
the ship is off the floor.
All right! Haul her up!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, sir!
Let's hustle, men!
Send more air!
Aye aye, sir!
[DIVERS scream]
[PIRATE B]
Captain!
There's a problem with
the underwater crew!
[MASIRA]
What?
Talk to me!
What's happening down there?!
Is it the intruders?
[DIVER B]
Yes, sir!
They're in the ship!
[screams]
[roars]
How dare you lay a hand
on my hard‐working men!
Intruders!
[NAMI] Uh, you know, we're
not gonna take your picture
or anything.
[MASIRA]
You're not?
[USOPP]
He was giving us a photo op?
[DIVER C]
Help us!
Someone please, help us!
I'll be right down.
Continue with the
salvaging operation men!
[PIRATES]
Aye aye, sir!
[MASIRA]
Monkey punch!
The salvage looks good.
[LUFFY]
Check it out.
We don't even need
the barrels now.
Well, I don't know how
they pumped this much air
into a downed ship.
But what I really want
to know is who they are
and why they're trying
to salvage this thing.
I wonder if something
bad happened to Nami
and Robin up on the surface.
I've tried calling them,
but they won't respond.
Who do you guys think you are?
Trying to muscle in on my turf?
Nice makeup.
Thanks! I feel it adds a
refined quality to my face.
Oh, yeah.
It certainly adds something.
What the hell are
you talking about?
What do you mean?
[SANJI] What he means
to say is, who are you?
[MASIRA]
You're right.
How rude of me.
Sometimes I get caught up
in the details of life.
It's one of my shortcomings.
[ZORO] Come on!
Just tell us who you already!
There's something
else down there.
It's huge!
Anybody just wanna run?
Yeah, all you guys
from the East Blue have the
best sense of humor!
Well, I don't really
know about all that.
Nothing compares to a
one ton gorilla in makeup.
Oh, shut your mouth.
You know I look good.
[NAMI]
Does anyone else see
the monster the size of
an island in front of us?
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[USOPP]
Ah! It's a monster turtle!
[NAMI] What did you
think we'd find out here?
[USOPP]
Luffy, Zoro, and Sanji!
[NAMI]
Calm down and shut up, would ya?
[USOPP] How can you be so
calm when a galleon falls on us
from the sky, we're bombarded
by a giant weird monkey guy?
[NAMI] Why has it gotten dark
in the water all of a sudden?
[USOPP]
Oh, no more. Please!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Monsters Appear! Don't Mess
with the White Beard Pirates!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!