[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
Give back Pops' gold!
Every bit of it! Right now!
What gold?
[laughs]
You mean the junk we got
from old man Cricket?
So long, Straw Hat!
[yells]
[SARQUISS]
No! I'll show you a real punch!
Where are you going?
[ALL gasp]
[LUFFY]
Where am I going?
Up there.
[LUFFY] "Take to the Sky!
Ride the Knockup Stream!"
Where the heck is that
rubbery, bug‐eyed idiot?
This is just like him!
Didn't we all agree to be
here over 45 minutes ago?
We're gonna miss the current!
Ugh. I'm sure the genius
didn't even stop to consider
how the gold would
weigh him down.
Why does he always insist
on making everything
ten times harder?
[USOPP] The only schedule
Luffy's concerned with
is his own.
Yeah. He's got a point there.
You don't think someone in
town beat him up, do you?
What, you mean that guy Bellamy?
Well, if Bellamy
didn't beat him up,
you better believe I will!
Oh, is that right, tough girl?
[LUFFY]
Hey!
Huh?
Look there! He's back.
I knew he'd make it.
I did it, you guys!
[SANJI] Luffy, hurry!
We're already behind schedule!
[laughing]
[LUFFY]
Look, it's a Hercules!
It took me forever to find it!
You're kidding me!
Are you crazy?!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Whoa! That's awesome!
Introducing the Going
Merry flying edition.
It can fly?!
I know! They built
it just for us!
[MASIRA CREW]
Yahoo!
[LUFFY laughs]
[MASIRA CREW laughs]
Morons.
Something about it makes
me feel kinda uneasy.
Well, for once I agree with you.
Chickens don't even
know how to fly.
They should've made it a pigeon.
What's that got to do
with anything, ya dope?!
It's time to set sail!
C'mon, if you're with me,
let me hear it!
[MASIRA CREW]
Yeah!
What are you waitin' for?
Get on board.
Unless you plan on missin'
your chance at the sky.
Like a fool.
Heh. Thanks for the ship.
Thank them. They built it.
Yeah. Thanks for
the ship, you guys!
You can have my Hercules!
[SHOJO] Ooh! Really?
You mean it? Are you sure?
[ALL]
That's so kind of you!
All right, enough of
this foolishness!
We don't have much time!
[SHOJO]
Follow us! We'll lead the way!
[USOPP]
Come on, Luffy! Let's go!
[LUFFY]
Coming!
[BELLAMY] This "City of Gold"
is just a fairytale!
That liar, Noland,
dreamt it all up!
Your dreams will never
come true! Ever!
[BELLAMY, SARQUISS laughing]
[laughing]
Saruyama!
[MASIRA CREW]
Aye!
[CRICKET]
I'm counting on you, men.
I don't care what happens,
you give our friends here
everything you've got!
[MASIRA CREW]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
Time to set sail!
You heard him. Shove off!
All right!
Yes, Nami!
[CRICKET] Well, kid, looks like
this is where we part ways.
Yep.
[CRICKET] There's only one thing
you gotta remember,
above everything else.
[LUFFY]
What?
Not one person in history
has ever disproved
the existence of sky island.
People may say I'm crazy
and even laugh at me,
but I don't care.
I'm a romantic. Like you.
Romantic.
So long!
Oh, yeah. Thanks for the gold.
And hey, don't be fallin'
from the sky, ya hear?
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
See ya around, Pops!
[NAMI]
Thanks for everything, Cricket!
[USOPP]
Think of us when you find
the City of Gold, old‐timer!
[LUFFY]
Try and take it easy, okay?!
[CRICKET]
Mind your own business!
[BLACKBEARD]
It's morning already?
Burgess. See anything out there?
[BURGESS] Can't even see an
outline of the shore yet.
You really think they're
going to that sky island?
Yeah, so they say.
They'll be pretty tough
to follow up there,
so we gotta take care
of 'em before that.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Who'd have thought that twerp
would be worth a
hundred million Berries?
[MASIRA] Okay, listen up!
It's currently 7:00 am.
We need to arrive at our final
destination no later than 11:00.
It's like Cricket
already told us.
The spot where the
Knockup Stream erupts
is different every single time.
We need to get there
as early as possible
in order to pin point
it's exact location.
[LUFFY]
Check it out.
[MASIRA] It looks like
we're already running
a little behind schedule.
Hey! Are you knuckleheads
payin' attention?!
[LUFFY] Did you see that?
It has to face forward!
Strange. I've never seen
a bird quite like him.
[LUFFY laughing]
He only faces south,
isn't that funny?
The goofy bird acts
just like a compass!
[LUFFY laughing]
Did you hear what it said?
He said he's going to face a
different direction on purpose
and laugh at us once we're lost.
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
Go ahead and try!
[grunting]
Whoa. He's really facing north.
[LUFFY]
Told ya he couldn't do it!
[LUFFY, CHOPPER laughing]
[SHOJO CREWMAN A]
Hey!
Show the boss some respect
and pipe down over there!
No. They're fine.
Why, it reminds me
of the old days
when I was young and irreverent.
Uh‐oh. What'd they'd say?
Hey! There's no point
gettin' so worked up, fella.
Ha‐ha! Try to relax!
And who put us
behind schedule again?
You know what, he's right.
Being tense won't
get us anywhere.
We may as well enjoy ourselves.
I see your point.
Full speed ahead, men.
Anyone not relaxing
answers to me.
[SHOJO CREW sighs]
[LUFFY]
Ahh. That's better.
[MASIRA CREW sighs]
[ZORO]
This is ridiculous.
Wait. What's over there?
The sky! It's dark!
[MASIRA CREWMAN A]
Boss! Look!
What's wrong?
I see the cumuloregalis cloud!
To the southwest!
[MASIRA]
It can't be! What time is it?
[MASIRA CREWMAN A]
Ten o'clock!
They're a full hour early!
[MASIRA] Shojo! Do you
think we can make it?
[SHOJO]
Dispatch the Utan Divers!
Find me those currents!
[NAMI]
They're incredible!
What's going on now?
The cumuloregalis
clouds appeared
a lot sooner than expected,
so now everyone's scrambling
to find a current!
[screams]
Sonar waves detected!
There's a large current
at 12 o'clock!
[SHOJO CREWMAN B] Large creature
detected at nine o'clock!
It could be a Sea King!
There's wave activity
detected at ten o'clock
going against the current!
I believe it's a giant
whirlpool, sir!
That's it! Full speed ahead
directly for ten o'clock!
That's where the Knockup
Stream's gonna erupt,
I'm sure of it!
Now go!
Hold on!
[NAMI]
The waves are getting higher!
[USOPP]
We're gonna sink!
[MASIRA] Steady, men.
It's a pre‐eruption tremor!
[CHOPPER]
Eruption?!
Hey, Navigator! What
does the Log Pose say?
It's pointing straight
at those clouds!
[USOPP] You mean the sky
island's above that?
The wind direction's perfect.
The clouds are lining
up exactly over
the center of the whirlpool.
[LUFFY] What whirlpool?
I haven't seen anything.
Nice work, brother!
I think we hit the
jackpot this time.
Yes! And it seems we're in
for a nice‐sized explosion!
[LUFFY]
Do you think we'll make it?
[MASIRA]
Of course!
What's that?
We'll lead you
to the inner edge.
All right. But what
should we do?
Position yourself on the flow
and head towards the center.
Then you'll be fine.
[NAMI]
He wants us to go to the center?
[CRICKET] I've never met a group
of characters like them before.
You mean there's no sky island?
Are you for sure?
Cricket's gold! It's all gone!
I'll be back by morning, guys.
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
See ya around, Pops!
[CRICKET]
Always yappin' about dreams.
[USOPP]
But I don't wanna get sucked in!
I don't remember
signing up for all this!
[SANJI]
Don't worry!
I'll make sure nothing
happens to you!
[ROBIN] I've never seen one
quite this big before.
[chuckles]
This is bad! I change my
mind! I wanna go back!
[ZORO]
Sorry, Usopp, too late for that.
"You know who"
is already excited.
Let's go! To the sky!
[laughs]
[CHOPPER, USOPP wheezing]
[MASIRA]
It's time for us to go!
The rest is up to
you now! Good luck!
Bye, guys! And thanks
a lot for everything!
Don't go!
Don't go! I don't want to die!
Please, take me with you!
Gimme a break, I'm scared!
Please don't make me!
[NAMI] No one said anything
about diving head first
into a giant whirlpool!
[USOPP]
Why's it getting dark?!
[CHOPPER]
Oh, no! We're being sucked in!
Don't be so unreasonable, Luffy!
Let's go back while
we still have time!
Don't you understand
this sky island stuff
is just a bunch of make‐believe?
It's not worth
getting us killed!
It's all make believe?
Is that what you think?
Usopp's right! I think
this is a really bad idea!
[LUFFY] It may be a stupid
dream, but I have to try.
It could be our
greatest adventure!
[USOPP, NAMI]
No. It's too late.
Instead of wasting
your time bickering,
you all might wanna take a look.
What do you mean?
[ZORO]
It's sucking us in.
[STRAW HATS yelling]
[SANJI] Hurry, Nami!
Let my arms protect you!
[STRAW HATS screaming]
[screaming]
[SANJI]
What happened? It disappeared.
[LUFFY]
What's goin' on?
[USOPP]
Wait. I‐I don't get it.
Where'd it go?
I feel it.
It's starting.
[NAMI] The whirlpool sunk
under the surface.
[USOPP]
You don't mean...
[BLACKBEARD]
Hold it right there!
Hey, uh, Zoro?
Look.
[BLACKBEARD laughing]
[BLACKBEARD]
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Straw Hat Luffy.
It's him. It's that
Mock Town guy!
What guy?
I've come all this
way to collect
on your hundred‐
million‐Berry bounty!
So don't be shy!
[BLACKBEARD laughing]
[SHOJO] Were those youngsters
expecting some company?
[MASIRA]
I don't know, brother.
Hm? Why's it getting
dark out here?
Hundred million?
What're you talkin' about?
Don't play dumb with me, kid.
It says right here.
Monkey D. Luffy wanted
for a hundred million.
And for Pirate Hunter Zoro:
60 million Berries!
It's true. He's got a different
poster for each of you.
Hey, Zoro. Congratulations
on your new bounty! Ha!
[SANJI]
Wait a minute, Usopp!
Come on. Do you see one for me?
[USOPP]
Uh, no.
Look closer.
Nothin'.
It looks like your bounties
must've gone way up
after the Alabasta incident.
But a hundred million?
[LUFFY]
This is great!
Hear that? My bounty
went up big time!
[ZORO chuckles]
Sixty million's not
too bad either.
It's not a good thing!
[SHOJO] Make sure to keep your
eyes open, Going Merry crew!
It's here. I hope
they're ready for it.
[SHOJO]
Brace yourselves!
[BLACKBEARD]
Huh?
[SANJI]
Everyone hold on or get inside!
[USOPP screaming]
[USOPP] Oh, no! The ship!
It's being lifted up!
[USOPP crying]
[ALL screaming]
[MASIRA CREWMAN B]
Help! We're gonna capsize!
Hold steady!
Don't let go, men!
[MASIRA, SHOJO]
Go sky island!
[STRAW HATS yelling]
[USOPP]
What's happening?!
[SANJI] We're sailing up
a huge pillar of water!
[LUFFY]
This is awesome!
[USOPP]
How are we doing this?!
Wind.
[LUFFY] All right! I can't
believe it's finally happening.
Let's go to Skypeia!
Hold on. It's not gonna
be that easy. Look!
Oh, what now?!
What's wrong? Did we
forget about something?
[SANJI]
The hull's starting to float!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[SANJI] If we don't stop it,
we're gonna fall into the ocean!
[USOPP] What do ya expect
us to do about it?
We're having a hard enough
time holding on as it is,
or haven't you noticed?
Oh, no! What is that?!
[ZORO]
The Sea King!
[CHOPPER]
Is that the one from before?!
See, it's only a matter of time
before the same thing
happens to the Merry!
I know! But what can we do?
We don't have a
whole lot of options
when it comes to mother nature.
We're at her mercy.
[SANJI] I guess we hold on
and hope for the best!
[screams]
Ships are falling from the sky!
We're gonna end up
driftwood, just like them!
[USOPP] We're gonna take a nose
dive to the bottom of the ocean
all because Luffy had to
follow some stupid dream!
[NAMI]
Spread the sails! Right now!
Sure it's a pillar of water,
but it's still part of the sea.
It's a rising current!
The wind from below is
a rising air current
produced by geothermal heat,
causing a steam explosion!
It may be packaged differently,
but it's still wind and water!
Trust me. I'm a
navigator, aren't I?
[SANJI]
Thank you, Nami!
All right, gang!
Nami's leading the way!
[STRAW HATS]
Yeah!
[NAMI] All right, guys,
catch the starboard wind
and align the ship
with the current!
[STRAW HATS]
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, we're rising up off
the water! Is that okay?
[LUFFY] Nami, do something!
We're gonna fall!
Come on. Do it!
[LUFFY]
We're flying!
Yeah! We're headed to the sky!
We made it.
[screams]
I did it!
Yes!
Nami! Good job!
I think I love you!
[CRICKET]
Go for it, kid!
Always remember
to keep dreaming!
[MASIRA, SHOJO]
Yeah!
[NAMI]
If the wind keeps this up,
we can sail as high as we want!
Hey, Nami! Are we
almost to Skypeia?
If it exists, it's
past those clouds!
[LUFFY]
Past the clouds!
I can't wait to find out
what's up in the sky!
Let's bust through
'em and find out!
[LUFFY yells]
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
[LUFFY]
Hey, guys, take a look around!
[SANJI]
What is this place?
[LUFFY]
It's solid white!
[NAMI]
It's like an ocean in the sky!
[USOPP]
What is that?!
[SANJI]
What a strange creature...
Is it a fish?
[USOPP]
What is that?!
[ZORO]
What now?
[SANJI]
Look! Someone's coming!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Sail the White Sea!
The Sky Knight and
the Gate in the Clouds!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!