Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy discovered
that his brother Ace
was captured by the Navy
and now faces execution.
With the help
of the Snake Princess,
Luffy snuck aboard a Navy
ship bound for the prison
known as Impel Down.
[LUFFY]
The Friends' Whereabouts!
The Science of Weather
and the Mechanical Island.
[KUMA]
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
Zoro!
Brook, no!
Usopp!
[LUFFY]
Sanji! Franky!
Nami!
[LUFFY]
Chopper!
Robin!
[HANCOCK] Luffy?
It was a dream.
You were screaming.
It sounded like it was awful.
I lost all my friends.
A second time.
[HANCOCK] I see.
[HANCOCK] Surely there's
something I can say
to raise his spirits.
Hey, Luffy?
You don't need to worry.
Right now, you have
to put all of your focus
into saving your brother.
Have faith that your friends
can look after themselves.
You trust them, right?
Yeah, of course.
Now remember.
Even though you were
separated from your crew,
you have never been alone.
I'm right here to
comfort you if you need me.
You mean that, don't you?
Hancock.
I've been so foolish.
All this time...
I was with an angel.
And had no idea.
Luffy.
[LUFFY] Hancock.
[HANCOCK] Clearly, that's
exactly what he would say.
[giddy squealing]
[HANCOCK] No, we can't!
--Of course I want to,
--Uh, hey, Hammock?
--but no! We can't!
--What're you doing?
[NARRATOR]
Not long ago,
only a few days
before, in fact...
--[loud crash]
--[screaming]
Goodness!
What was that noise?
[HAREDAS] Be careful, now.
Well, this is new.
Are you finally awake?
[screaming]
What is this?
Who the heck are you?
And where am I?
Calm down, you're in my house.
I dragged you in here while--
[NAMI] You did what to me?
Uhh... I'm scared.
Your body's still healing,
so you shouldn't
move around too much.
And you won't get far
in this weather--
Just stay back!
I don't care what
shape my body's in,
I'm gettin' out
of your creepy shack!
My crewmates need me.
I've gotta get back to them.
Aww...
[NAMI] Back off!
[HAREDAS] Please forgive me.
I can't help
wanting to help you.
[NAMI]
I said back off, you freak!
[HAREDAS] Hey.
Hey hey hey, hey hey hey.
Hey hey hey, hey hey
hey there, young lady.
Young lady who came
plummeting out of the sky?
[NAMI] Yeah, I heard you. What?
[HAREDAS] Do you think you've
calmed down a little now?
No more inclinations
toward violence?
[NAMI] Yeah.
This is good!
Oh, it's nothing
special, really.
You slept for two days
after you crashed,
so I'm sure anything would
taste amazing right now.
Wait, I was out for two days?
Mmm. You really
must've been through
quite the ordeal, haven't you?
[HAREDAS] Ta-dah!
This may look
like ordinary rope,
but they are in fact
tightly wound Wind Knots!
If I untie one,
it creates a gentle breeze.
But if I untie two,
a strong gust will blow.
And if I untie three,
it becomes a gale!
[NAMI screaming]
What'd you do that for?
I'm sorry,
I just thought it might
cheer you up, that's all!
[NAMI] Oh, yeah,
I'm real cheery now!
I'm outta here!
[HAREDAS]
Don't be crazy, young lady!
You'll get yourself
killed out there!
This isn't so bad.
I can handle this.
[NAMI yelling]
[thunder crashing]
I know those clouds.
We're in the path
of a huge cyclone.
[HAREDAS]
Oh, no. Just look at you.
You've got mud all over.
Why don't you come in
and take a shower?
[HAREDAS] You get yourself clean
and I'll wash and dry
your clothes for you.
Listen up, old man.
[HAREDAS] Yes, young lady?
That isn't any
ordinary rain storm.
There's a cyclone coming--
A huge one that'll
barrel right through us!
Did you say something?
I'm trying to tell
you we're in trouble!
We are right in the
path of a gigantic storm!
Oh, yes, it's coming this way.
Hopefully with some
more pleasant company.
[NAMI] Geez. Dumb old coot.
Well I've already
warned him once.
What? Rain clouds?
[HAREDAS] Just turn the wheel
and hot water will come out.
Turn the wheel?
They're raining hot water?
How's this possible?
Is the water temperature okay?
If you push the wheel,
it'll blow hot air.
I made tea while you bathed.
Oh. Thanks.
--Ahh, that's nice.
Wait! Why are we so calm?
That giant storm is
going to wreck this place!
Unlike you,
I'm too young to die!
Oh, please don't start
throwing objects at me!
There's really
nothing we can do?
Oh, yes. It's time.
I'll be back
before you know it.
You just stay inside and
wait here, okay, young lady?
[NAMI] What? Hey! No!
Wait!
[NAMI] How is he able to
walk so easily in this weather?
[NAMI] There it is!
Now Cool Ball!
[NAMI]
Heat Ball!
Here we go!
Cyclone Burst!
[NAMI screams]
Well, damn.
[HAREDAS]
Hey hey hey, hey hey hey!
Hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey hey!
Hey there, I'm talking
to you, young lady.
You don't say.
Okay, what's up?
Well, now.
I only showed it
to you the one time
and you're using
the Wind Knot like a pro.
You're quite impressive.
[NAMI laughs]
[NAMI] Nothing to it.
Anyway, looks like
it's time for me to go.
Wow. This is a surprise.
Are those...
Where are we?
[HAREDAS] This is a small
Sky Island, called Weatheria.
We conduct studies
of the weather here.
[NAMI]
What? This is a Sky Island?
That cyclone looked
like it had the possibility
to be a rather
intriguing specimen.
But it just suddenly
up and disappeared on us.
Now I wonder how
that could've happened?
[NARRATOR]
And so Nami found herself
on a small
island in the sky.
Will she ever be able to find
her way back to her friends?
The storm is only getting worse.
Why don't we take a
break somewhere, Kitton?
Okay.
[growling]
Is something wrong, Taroimo?
Ahh!
It's... huge!
Get behind me, Kitton!
[growling]
[FRANKY yelling]
Hold on, wait!
What are you doing?
[FRANKY] Augh! Come on!
No! Stop!
[KITTON] What? He's a human?
This is terrible,
what are we gonna do?
Um... Excuse me,
are you all right, sir?
My dog. He thought you were
something we're hunting.
Yeah, no biggie.
Ahh! It's like this
guy doesn't even care!
Hm... No harm done, then.
I bet you're relieved, Taroimo.
There is one problem, though.
Where the heck am I
and how did I get here?
It's cold. Damn!
Don't you have the sun here?
Ah... ah... ah-ch-Franky!
Oh, no!
He's only wearing
underwear in all this snow!
Did bandits steal your pants?
Why don't you
put on this fur pelt?
Whoa, a fur pelt?
No thanks, I'm trying
to maintain a style here!
That'd cramp my reputation...
...as a freak!
Oh! I gotta move, man!
Like this! Wow!
C'mon! Follow my lead!
[FRANKY]
Shake your hips to the right!
Right hand to the waist.
And then stick out
your left hand!
Now slide and reverse!
[FRANKY] Right, left, right,
left, right, left, right, left!
Now repeat after me, guys.
One, two, one, two! One, two!
Right, left, right, left,
right, left, right, left
right, left!
One, two,
one, two, one, two!
Right, left, right, left,
right, left, right, left!
Wow!
One, two, one, two!
Haha!
[FRANKY] Super!
That's how it's done!
Crap! I'm still freezing!
Where the hell is this place?
[KITTON] What?
You don't know where you are?
[FRANKY] Why would I
know something like that?
This is the
Future Land Baldimore,
which is located
on Mechanical Island.
It's known as the
birthplace of the genius.
The what now?
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
The genius.
[FRANKY] The... The who?
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
The genius.
[KITTON]
Mister!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER]
Oh, my!
He really should've
taken the pelt.
We better get him
to the hospital, Kitton.
[KITTON] Yeah.
[SURGEON 418A]
Well, he's definitely a cyborg.
[SURGEON 418B]
I can't believe he runs on cola.
[SURGEON 418C]
What should we do?
We don't have any
sodas to refuel him.
[SURGEON 418B]
There's no time to lose.
We need to begin.
[SURGEON 418A] Right.
Hey, mister!
You seem different.
Hello. You're the young
lad from earlier, correct?
I do hope that I haven't
kept you waiting for too long.
Yeah, you're
definitely different.
What did they do to you?
[FRANKY] Well it seems that
cola is hard to come by here,
so they brewed up
some fine hot tea instead.
Darjeeling, to be precise.
Hot tea?
The aroma and
flavor are truly super.
Lovely. There's really
nothing quite so relaxing.
Okay. If you say so.
I'm sorry,
where are my manners?
[FRANKY]
Enjoy. Careful, it's hot.
No, no, this is weird!
It's all wrong!
Hey, Mister!
You're not funny now.
I liked you more
the way you were!
Oh? Is that so?
What was I like before,
pray tell?
You were like this!
Super!
You know, lad...
That's just a tad embarrassing.
We need to get you
some cola right away!
[NARRATOR] And so Franky
became a gentleman
on Mechanical Island.
Will he ever be
a super freak again?
And what does fate have in store
for the rest of the Straw Hats
scattered around the globe?
[NARRATOR] Chopper awakens
on a faraway island,
only to be attacked by
giant birds and natives
hungry for a reindeer dinner.
Meanwhile, Sanji finds himself
in a peach-colored paradise.
The inhabitants seem
harmless enough,
but is Sanji
walking into a trap?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
The Friends' Whereabouts!
An Island of Giant Birds
and a Pink Paradise!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!