Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[ZORO] It shouldn't be
night yet, right?
So why is it so dark?
And what's with this fog?
It's strange, huh?
[FRANKY]
That's right. Be careful.
You've heard of the
Florian Triangle, right?
Y'know, it's also called
The Devil's Triangle!
[chuckles] Bring on the
ghosts! I can't wait!
[VOICE]
♪ Yo ho ho ho.
[USOPP] No. No!
It's a ghost ship!
♪ Gather up all
of the crew. ♪
♪ It's time to ship
out Binks's Brew. ♪
[slurps]
Yeah, well, maybe
he's the one guarding
all the awesome treasure.
Anyway, I'm going!
[gasps]
There he is.
[NAMI screams]
I really was quite surprised!
It's been so many
years, you see--
wandering these
waters all alone!
I got one for ya.
Ya ready?
Will you join our crew?
Huh?!
Yes. Certainly.
[LUFFY]
"The Joy of Seeing People!
The Gentleman Skeleton's
True Identity"
[BROOK]
Yohohohohohoooo!
It's such a pleasure
to meet you!
Hello and good day to you all!
As of today,
I will be joining you
on this ship as your
newest crew member!
Once dead and all bones,
my name is Brook and
I do hope we can get along!
Are you kidding me?
What the heck is this thing?
Yohohohoho!! Oh my,
what a tough crowd you are!
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Please don't haunt me!
My goodness, and what
a lovely young woman--
perhaps you would like
to show me your panties?
That's enough
sexual harassment!
[CHOPPER] It's a full
set of anti-ghost gear!
You've got him now!
[USOPP] Remove yourself
from this ship, you fiend!
Submit to the holy
power that I wield!
Evil begone! Evil begone!
[BROOK] How frightening!
It's working!
Keep it up!
You're awesome, Usopp!
Heh! Of course I'm awesome!
I mean, I paid a lot of
money for all this stuff,
so it darn well better work!
Where is this evil creature?
I can't see it!
It's you, stupid!
[shrieks]
Hahahaha!
Damn it!
There's no way a walking,
talking afro-sporting
skeleton could exist!
This must be a dream!
We just need to wake up!
Oh, it's a dream?
What a relief! That's nice.
[BROOK] Ah, excuse me?
Hello, hello? Good morning!
That's enough!
What is this thing and
why is it on our ship?
That's our new crew
member! Isn't he funny?
Who cares?
He's not joining our crew!
This is exactly why
I wanted you to go with him.
What the hell happened?
Were you just picking your noses
while he brought a
skeleton back to the ship?
I know. We messed up.
[BROOK]
Yohohohoho!
Now, now, let's be
civil, everyone.
Why don't we go inside?
You can treat me to dinner!
You don't get to decide that!
Hahahaha!
I love this guy!
[BROOK]
Yohohohoho!
What a spacious
dining room you've got!
And such a splendid kitchen!
A magnificent ship,
if I've ever seen one!
Yohohohoho!
[LUFFY] Yep!
Of course it is--
it's the most super ship
I've ever made!
Those sockets look empty,
but you've got a
good eye for quality!
Franky, don't get friendly
with the skeleton.
Speaking of quality,
I can't wait to try
out your cooking.
Since I was stuck on
that dreary ghost ship,
it's been decades since
I've eaten a proper meal.
I felt my stomach
shrink and shrink
until I couldn't even
tell the back of my belly
from the front of
my back anymore.
That was the sort
of miserable life I led.
And let me tell you,
that's saying a lot,
seeing as skeletons don't even
have a proper back or stomach!
Yohohohoho!
[chuckles]
It's a skull joke!
I get it!
Let me say. I am
quite the gentleman,
so I am well-versed in the art
of patiently waiting
for my food,
no matter how long it takes.
--Food! Food! Food! Food!
--Dinner, yeah! Dinner, now!
My dear boy, can
I have a glass of milk?
It's good for the
bones, they say.
Shut up or I'm gonna
smash your skull!
Oh, by the way skeleton.
Sorry, but my name is "Brook."
Ah, but that reminds me.
I know this is rude, but I don't
believe I ever caught your name.
Oh, me?
My name is Luffy.
So anyway, what are you?
You invited him to join the crew
and you just now ask him that?
Okay, food's ready!
[SANJI] We can finish
interrogating
the skeleton later.
For now, let's put all those
octopi you caught to good use!
Magical!
Go ahead and eat all
of this you want, Brook.
Sanji's cooking is the
best in the whole world!
Although, my stomach is empty.
I think my heart has
already been filled.
Don't cry.
I couldn't help but notice
that your portion
is a bit large--
would you be interested
in switching with me?
You can have seconds,
just leave her alone!
We pulled the
octopus from a fish tank
we have on the ship.
It's really big,
you've gotta see it!
You have a fish tank with
octopus on your ship?
Truly the wonders never cease
with you people! How splendid!
And that's just the start!
Did you know the ship
can transform, too?
It can fly in the air and stuff!
I've never heard
of anything like it!
How fortunate that I met
with such a fascinating ship!
If you're that interested,
I could show you.
Oh, yes, by all means,
right after dinner!
He can understand
that nonsense?
[BROOK] Gonna see the ship yeah,
gonna see the ship, uh-huh!
Would you
shut up and eat?
[NAMI] The Revive-Revive Fruit?
[FRANKY] So it was a
Devil Fruit after all.
It's a complicated tale.
The truth of the matter is,
I actually did die already,
many years ago.
[SANJI] Could you clean
off your damn face?
I've never seen
such a messy eater.
The Revive-Revive Fruit...
[slurping]
...allows a person to be
reanimated after they have died.
[slurping]
Even among
devil fruit powers,
the ability to live two lives
is indeed quite strange.
So you're a "revive man"!
Then you're not immortal.
It's more like you died once
and it gave you a
second chance at life.
[BROOK] In short, yes.
Ah, excuse me.
[burps]
[BROOK] As I said, it's
complicated, but during my
"first life" if you will,
I was a pirate, just like you.
[LUFFY] That explains the ship!
[BROOK] That it does.
Excuse me again.
[farts]
I'm gonna beat
some manners into you
if I have to break every
single one of your bones.
[BROOK] A long time ago,
I was sailing
with the rest of my crew
through these accursed waters.
Now, for the record,
I had flesh and blood like
anyone else back then.
At any rate,
we had the misfortune
of running afoul of a
very powerful adversary.
[BROOK] Soon, the entire
crew met its demise.
Of course, that
included me as well.
When I was alive,
the Revive-Revive Fruit
did precious little,
other than rob me
of my ability to swim.
But on that fateful day,
its true power awakened
as I lay dead.
[BROOK] My spirit returned
from the netherworld
and came to unite with this
body of mine once again!
[BROOK] Now, if it had actually
found my body as intended,
that would all be well and
good, but as you can see,
the fog around
here is quite thick,
so the matter became
a bit complicated.
In short, poor little Soul Brook
couldn't find his way back home.
All in all, my spirit
wandered through
the foggy waters, searching
for my body for an entire year.
Then at the end of
its tragic journey,
the two were
reunited once again.
Much to my soul's dismay,
by the time it found my
body there was nothing left
but a miserable pile of bones!
I was so shocked,
my eyes were as
wide as dinner plates.
Not that I have eyes to
begin with! Yohohoho!
You got lost, huh?
So you're stupid, just
like Zoro! Hahahaha!
Hey now...
And so a walking,
talking skeleton was born.
Man, those Devil Fruit powers
can be pretty scary sometimes.
Even though you're just bones,
it still brought
you back to life.
Yeah, but it only does
it once, despite the fact
that he still can't swim
and he's stuck like this.
It seems kind of like a
crappy deal if you ask me.
Skeletons aren't supposed
to have hair, are they?
Especially not
so much of it.
Is that afro a wig
or somethin'?
No, my roots are
just very strong.
I'll take your
word for it.
Then that means you're not
actually a ghost after all?
You're just a normal
human like us?
Well, normal is a stretch,
I suppose, but--
The important thing
is that you're definitely
not a ghost?
Ohhh! Oh, heavens no,
I hate ghosts!
If I saw one, I'd scream
my lungs out if I had any!
You're a skeleton and
you're afraid of ghosts?
Have you tried looking
in the mirror lately?
Aaaah!! No mirrors! Stop!
[USOPP] Hm? What's wrong?
Hey. Hold up.
What's going on here?
No, why?
Why can't we see you?
Why don't you show
up in the mirror?
Aaaaah!!
[NAMI, CHOPPER, and USOPP]
A vampire!
Are you for real?
That's awesome!
Look at his feet!
He doesn't even have a shadow!
[CHOPPER] Aaaah! You're right!
What kind of creature are you?
[slurps]
Don't take a tea break!
You better explain
yourself right away, mister!
I suppose that I should
tell you the rest of the story.
About what happened while
I was drifting in this evil sea,
and the second tragedy
I was forced to face.
What I told you about
becoming a skeleton is true,
but the reason
I don't have a shadow
is a different matter entirely.
To be continued.
How 'bout you tell us now?
[BROOK] My shadow was stolen.
Someone took it from me,
several years ago.
[USOPP] Stolen?
But how?
[ZORO] I guess that's
not any more ridiculous
than a talking skeleton,
but it's still hard to swallow.
Can something like
that really happen?
[BROOK] Yes. I'm afraid it can.
And in addition to
losing my reflection,
having my shadow stolen means
I can no longer exist
in the world of light.
[LUFFY]
But you're still alive, right?
[BROOK] Yes, for now at
least, but only because
I'm able to stay in this
place with no sunlight.
Although, you can
scarcely call it "living."
I am saved by the
grace of the thick fog
surrounding these seas.
[ROBIN] Then what would happen
if you were exposed to sunlight?
If even a ray of
sunlight touched this body,
every inch that it fell upon
would be reduced
to naught but ash.
[BROOK] A single step
into the sun,
and in a matter of moments,
every trace of me would
be wiped from this world.
[STRAW HAT CREW]
You'd be killed?
Yes.
[panting]
[MAN]
Auuuuugh!!
Heh... Hahahaha!
[grunts]
[screams]
Aaaah!!
[BROOK] I saw someone
with the same curse
as me lose his mind and
run into the sunlight.
When at last his
screams went silent,
nothing was left
but a pile of dust.
It was so frightful,
I swear my soul practically
left my body a second time!
And just as the sunlight
does not cast my shadow,
my image cannot be
reflected in a mirror
or captured in a photograph.
You must forgive me
for startling you,
but I hope you can understand my
reluctance to share this story.
For as you see,
not only have all of
my comrades been slain,
I also live in a
world without light.
Well, I hate to say it,
but your life sure does suck.
Even still, right now,
I'm so happy to have it!
A fluffy afro, a big smile--
the cheery gentlemen
skeleton, Brook!
Always a pleasure!
Where does all this
optimism come from?
Yohohohoho!!
Uh, hey. What's wrong?
He's flipping out!
What a wonderful
day this has been!
I met other people!
[BROOK] Buried in a heavy fog,
even though I knew
decades had passed,
I couldn't tell when one
day ended and another began.
[cheering]
[BROOK] Unable to
navigate or steer the ship,
my companions long since dead,
I could only drift aimlessly.
And so I waited and waited
as the waves rocked me
back and forth.
You can't even imagine
how lonely I was
all those years.
Not just lonely, but scared,
wanting to die every single day!
Even still, a long life
is a blessing, not a curse.
You've made me so happy.
Meeting such wonderful people
gives my life meaning!
Yohohohoho!!
If I had but the
eyes to shed them,
I would be crying tears
of happiness right now!
I was happy beyond measure
when you asked me
to join your crew
and I sincerely want to thank
you from the bottom of my heart!
[chuckles]
However, I fear that
I must decline your offer.
What?
Why would you do that?
As I mentioned to
all of you just now,
my shadow has been
stolen from me,
and I am unable to come
in contact with any sunlight.
Lonely though I may be,
for now I am able
to survive thanks
to the thick fog
covering these seas.
However, if I were to go
on a journey with you,
it would only be
a matter of time
before I met my
unfortunate demise.
[BROOK] Therefore,
however unlikely it may be,
I'll wait for the day when
my shadow can be restored--
make no bones about it.
I don't want to hear you
make excuses like that!
If you need your
shadow back so bad,
then we'll get it back for you!
You said someone
stole it from you, right?
Who was it?
Where can we find them?
Thank you.
You truly are a kind
person, aren't you?
But for that reason, I'm
afraid that I cannot tell you.
We've only just met, you see,
and I cannot ask you
to throw your life away
attempting something
that's nearly impossible.
[FRANKY] I'm sure
the guy's tough and all,
but gimme a break.
You got nothing to lose.
Least you can do
is tell us his name.
No, it's best that I don't.
Besides, I doubt
I could find him anyway.
Yohohoho...
But I have decided that
when and if I do ever reach him,
I will fight him to the
death for my shadow.
I don't know when
my second life will end,
but I am willing to wait for
him for the rest of my days.
[BROOK] But never mind that.
Why don't I play a song for you?
[CREW]
Hmm?
I am skilled
with a great many
instruments, you know.
When I sailed the seas with my
old crew, I was their musician.
What? Are you serious?
Our crew needs a musician!
Hurry up and join us
already, I'm begging you!
Yohohoho.
I haven't played
music for anyone in years,
but here goes!
[shudderin breaths]
Auuuugghh!!
Hey, what's wrong?
You're freaking out!
A g-g-ghost!
[CHOPPER] Ah! He's right!
Get out! Go away!
[LUFFY] This is too cool!
[ZORO] It's leaving.
[rumbling]
Wha-- Something's
happening to the ship!
[BROOK] No, it can't be.
What terrible fortune!
He must have
been watching them.
That's the only thing
that makes sense.
[BROOK]
Everyone look to the front!
That noise we heard was
this gate slamming shut.
Our passage has
already been blocked off.
That thing is a gate?
It looks like teeth.
Like a giant sea monster
is gonna eat us all!
What's going on here?
It seems this is the
backside of the gate.
That bad?
This is very bad.
[BROOK] Come to the
rear of the ship, hurry!
What in the world is that?
Did you, by any chance,
pick up a barrel
from the waters
on your way here?
[ZORO] Hey! There's something
floating in the ocean!
[LUFFY] Hey, you're right!
Maybe it fell off
a treasure ship!
Okay, let me see.
Fireworks?
Yeah, we did.
It was a trap.
You're all in great danger!
Simply put, your
ship's been targeted
ever since you came here.
You mean there's someone
out there hunting us down?
And by the way,
how'd we run into that gate
when our ship's not moving?
[LUFFY] Where the heck did
that creepy island come from?
[BROOK] This is the ghost island
that wanders
throughout these seas.
They call it "Thriller Bark."
Thriller Bark. I see.
[USOPP] Where did
that skeleton run off to?
And hey, let me steer
the paddleboat, Nami!
[NAMI] Not a chance!
You can try it out next time!
This is too much fun!
[USOPP] Wait a second,
is it just me or is that
island trying to swallow us?
[NAMI] Oh, you're just trying
to scare me--ah! It is!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"One Unnatural
Phenomenon After the Next!
Disembarking on Thriller Bark!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!