Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR]
To reach Fishman Island,
Luffy and the Crew
began searching
for a coating craftsman
on the Sabaody Archipelago.
Unfortunately, the area is also
home to the Celestial Dragons,
world nobles powerful enough
to hold influence
over Navy Headquarters.
A number of other formidable
pirates headed for the New World
were also lurking nearby.
You do have me a little afraid
for the old coating
mechanic pirate guy.
This town sounds pretty rough.
[SHAKKY] Oh, you've
got nothing to worry about.
Trust me,
Rayleigh's all right.
He's a hundred times
stronger than you.
[LUFFY]
The Target is Camie!
The Looming Clutches of a
Professional Kidnapper!
[LUFFY]
You ready, Chopper?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
[SHAKKY]
Just so you know,
I'm sure the Navy is aware
that all you up-and-coming
heavy-hitting pirates
have made landfall here.
I'd keep an eye out for anything
suspicious, if I were you.
[BROOK]
Well that's not good.
So you're saying they
could strike at any time
from out of nowhere?
Yes, but you
might be in luck.
In addition to the
usual troublemakers
around these parts,
with all the other pirates
landing here at the same time.
Navy Headquarters probably
has its hands full right now.
Unless something
especially problematic happens,
the Navy won't waste
major military resources
on checking it out.
In other words:
keep your heads down,
try not to cause any trouble,
and you should be fine, okay?
Sure! I understand.
Thanks a lot!
You were a real big help.
Maybe we'll see you again after
we find the boat-coating guy!
If you can find him.
[LUFFY]
We're here! Sabaody Park!
[CHOPPER, HACHI, CAMIE, BROOK]
Yay!
[PARK-GOERS screaming]
Aw, man!
This place looks fun!
Focus!
Remember why we're here!
[LUFFY]
I remember!
That lady said this is where
we should look for him, right?
[PAPPAGU] Only if we couldn't
find him in the lawless area!
It's the Ferris Wheel!
I've never seen it
from this close before!
[LUFFY]
All right!
Listen up!
It's fun time!
[PAPPAGU] You're not
even trying to find him!
Yay!
Camie! You are forbidden
to step inside that place!
Absolutely forbidden!
[BROOK] My, what a lovely
and leisurely ride this is!
Yohoho! Oh, and
look at this view!
How relaxing!
[screaming]
Awesome!
Let's do it again!
That was your first time.
Were you scared, Camie?
Yeah! I was
scared out of my mind!
But it was so fun! I loved it!
I've never had so much
fun in my whole life!
Come on!
You had it easy!
I was in the very front!
[zooming noise]
[PAPPAGU]
We were going so fast
my face was about
to fly right off!
My heart nearly
beat out of my chest.
Not that I have
a heart, of course.
[laughing]
[BROOK]
Yoho! Yes.
Gentle rides like this
one are more my style.
This way, I can still enjoy the
lovely view without having to--
[screaming]
[CHOPPER]
Look!
[LUFFY]
Faster, faster, faster!
Spin! Spin!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Spin!
Faster! Faster!
[screaming]
[RIDE GUY] What the heck
is wrong with you people?
Who in their right minds
would spin that hard?
Are you crazy?
Who's gonna pay
for all this damage?
Oh, wow! We're so high up!
[CAMIE]
Look, Luffy!
They're selling ice cream!
[LUFFY]
For real?
[CAMIE] From up here,
everyone looks so tiny!
[CAMIE]
Look! Over here!
The ocean!
[LUFFY]
Cool!
It's all so beautiful!
It's the most amazing
thing I've ever seen.
Hey, what's the
crying all about?
It's just...
I've dreamed of this moment
ever since I was a little girl.
I've never been so
high up in the air before!
I'll always remember this day.
Thank you so much!
I couldn't have
come here without you.
Hatchin and Pappagu only
let me come to this place
because they knew
you'd keep me safe.
Nyuu!
I gotta admit,
I'm probably every bit as
happy as Camie is right now.
Every mer-child and fish-kid
dreams of coming to this place,
though not many of us
get to really do it.
So high!
So very high!
Let's ride this one!
Gondola!
Yeah!
[cheering]
[screaming]
[laughing]
[BROOK screaming]
[CAMIE] Come on!
Let's go inside!
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
Yohohoho!
[CHILD screaming]
[BOUNTY HUNTER 391A]
I'm telling you.
They were crazy strong!
[PETERMAN] Sounds like
you had a rough time.
So what is this
"proposition" of yours?
Right. I'm sorry, sir.
You see, Master Peterman,
I think the girl
with Straw Hat Luffy
might be a mermaid.
I noticed something
when I saw her before.
[HACHI]
Leave them alone!
Camie! Pappagu!
[BOUNTY HUNTER 391A]
After she fell to the ground,
her shoe came off.
When it did, I saw
a fin instead of a foot.
[PETERMAN] But these strong
companions you mentioned
sound like they could
be a lot of trouble.
Nonetheless.
A mermaid spotted on dry land
is certainly a
golden opportunity.
They're impossible
to catch in open water.
I appreciate all the info.
You came to the right man.
And for that info,
you can have 10 percent
of her selling price.
Well...
We were really hoping for 20.
[BOUNTY HUNTERS] I mean,
uh, 10 percent is plenty!
[PAPPAGU] Wait here
a minute, okay, Camie?
Yeah, okay!
But get something yummy
for me, too, all right?
[FALLEN MONK PIRATE 393A]
High Priest Urouge.
Look over there.
My, my. What a sight.
[UROUGE]
A Celestial Dragon, huh?
To think they'd wander
around the lawless area
without a care in the world.
I don't like this,
but our only choice is to
kneel and let him pass on by.
Shalria and Father left me.
And in this cesspool.
Where did they wander
off to this time?
Well, we do know
their final destination,
so rest easy.
We'll meet up
with them soon enough.
This is all your fault!
You're slow as a turtle!
You can't even crawl gracefully!
What a horrible ride you are!
You irritate me to no end,
you pathetic worm!
Hey! You!
What are you doing there?
Why are you moving?
You should be still and bowing!
I'm so very sorry!
Please overlook this, sir!
This man needs urgent care!
We're racing against time.
The hospital is just up ahead!
[CHARLOSS]
Yes, I see.
This is very bad, indeed.
Well, in that case.
You must be swift.
[CHARLOSS] And put
him out of his misery!
[DOCTOR 393A]
I beg you, stop!
[MARIE]
Oh, no!
Look at that.
Now that is one selfish Noble.
[CHARLOSS] Tell me.
What's more important?
Showing me courtesy or
a mere commoner's life?
Every commoner
owes their very existence
to the Celestial Dragons.
It's settled.
I'm making you my new wife.
Very good, sir.
I shall make arrangements
to send her to the Holy Land
as your 13th wife.
By the by...
I've grown quite weary
of wives 1 through 5 lately.
Have them sent back to
live with the commoners.
Of course, sir. As you wish.
Please, don't do this!
I beg you!
[PUB GUY]
What are you doing?
She's my fiancée!
You can't just come here and--
[gunshot]
How dare you speak to me
when you should be kneeling!
[PUB GUY]
Marie...
[screaming]
[MARIE]
You murderer!
How could you?
Somebody help him!
Help him, please!
He's going to die!
Someone! Please!
These Celestial Dragons
are as wicked as the rumors say.
What was that?
You would have these
people act out against me?
[MARIE] Please,
let go of me! Stop it!
Take her ahead
to the harbor for me.
[RANDOM ATTENDANT 393A]
Yes, sir!
[PIRATE 393A]
Who's that?
I recognize him, Captain!
That guy is Pirate Hunter
Zoro from the East Blue!
Why is he walking
right down the middle
of the street?
Don't he know you don't
do that around here?
He's gonna cause
a lot of trouble!
Hey, what's the matter?
Do you need some
directions or something?
What in the hell does
he think he's doing?
[ZORO]
A kid?
[BONNEY crying]
[BONNEY]
Big brother!
Why'd you have to die?
Why'd you leave me?
No!
[BONNEY]
Just stay still, tough guy.
[crying]
[BONNEY]
Big brother!
Why'd you stand up
to a Celestial Dragon?
You know that can
only end in death!
[crying]
I guess I actually
shot him, huh?
Thought for sure he dodged at
the last second, but ah well.
Must be imagining things.
[CHARLOSS]
Well, whatever.
As long as he's dead.
Why in the hell
did you get in my way?
[BONNEY]
What?
I just saved your
life back there! Moron!
What the heck were you thinking,
attacking a
Celestial Dragon like that?
You'll bring admirals here!
What's with
all this tomato juice?
It's to make you look dead!
And unless you want
to be that way for real,
Mister Troublemaker, you better
obey the unwritten pirate rules!
What are you talking about?
Hey, wait a minute.
There was a kid here.
Where'd she go?
[BONNEY] Don't get the rest
of us caught up in your trouble!
Are you messed up in the head?
[ZORO]
No, I'm fine.
I didn't hit my head.
[BONNEY]
You numbskull!
I'm talking about the inside!
Geez, what a dumbass.
How have you survived this long?
Well thanks to
Jewelry Bonney over there,
we managed to avoid
the worst-case scenario.
That man is Pirate Hunter Zoro,
a member of the
Straw Hat Pirates.
I heard their crew
was kinda wild,
but attacking a Dragon?
And in a public street
in broad daylight?
That's plain bonkers.
It's only natural
that he was saved.
I didn't see the shadow of
death upon him at this time.
I felt his bloodlust.
That guy'll cut you down
without a second thought.
He's a real monster.
A bounty of a hundred
and twenty million berries.
Doesn't seem like a lackey,
but he's number two
on the Straw Hats.
I guess that goes to show
the caliber of his Captain.
Right.
So... Where's
the nearest hospital?
[BONNEY]
Hospital?
This man needs a doctor.
He took a bullet.
[BONNEY]
What? Forget him!
He's a total stranger!
You've gotta be kidding me.
A pirate helping
out some random guy?
Never seen that before.
[laughing]
I saw something
when I went into town.
These bubble bicycle
things were flying around.
Yeah! I saw those, too!
Pretty cool, huh?
We should buy a couple!
I betcha those bikes
have a really smooth ride!
The snail.
It's probably Nami.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
Hello, my beautiful Nami!
[CHOPPER]
Sanji! Sanji, it's Chopper!
Listen to me!
[CHOPPER]
Basically...
They had so many
kinds of ice cream.
We got caught up
and made a mistake!
Slow down.
You're not making any sense.
[CHOPPER]
Sanji!
It's terrible! Terrible!
What are we gonna do?
I dunno what you're saying.
Calm down. Just start over.
[CHOPPER]
It's Camie!
What's going on, Sanji?
[CHOPPER]
Camie's been kidnapped!
Wait, what did you say?
[CHOPPER] I think it was a group
of kidnappers working together!
People here capture and
sell merfolk and fishmen,
whoever they can profit off of!
Camie's gonna get sold!
She'll be a slave forever
and it's all our fault!
There are lots of Human
Shoppes on these islands,
so there's no telling
which one she'll be at
or when she'll be sold!
We don't even have
a clue who kidnapped her!
This place is gigantic.
We need to split up and start--
Don't move.
Tell me exactly where you are.
We'll come and meet you there.
[CHOPPER]
But... But we...
We know some experts
when it comes to this
sort of thing, remember?
I'm calling in the
Flying Fish Riders.
[FRANKY and USOPP]
What?
[DISCO]
A young mermaid came in?
It's been a while since we've
had such quality merchandise!
[CAMIE]
Let go of me!
[DISCO] She's a nice
and lively one, too!
All right, then!
Welcome the bidders
into the auction house!
Get ready for some
hot bidding wars, people!
[CAMIE]
Hatchin, please! Save me!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Rescue Camie!
The Archipelago's
Lingering Dark History!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!