Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the next
King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After his crew was
scattered around the world,
Luffy set off to rescue
his brother, Ace,
who had been
captured by the Navy
and sent to a massive prison
known as Impel Down.
On his way down to Level 5,
a closely guarded floor
where the most infamous
criminals were held,
Luffy encountered
an old acquaintance.
Time for my specialty.
[LUFFY grunts]
[BLUGORI grunting]
Causing chaos!
Works for me!
[BUGGY grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
[BLUGORIS groan]
[LUFFY]
Break Through the Crimson Hell!
Buggy's Chaos-Inducing Plan!
[BLUGORIS panting]
[LUFFY]
Now, Gum-Gum...
Whip!
[BLUGORIS groan]
[BUGGY]
Uh! Stay back! Go away! No!
[BUGGY screams]
I'm just screwin' with ya.
I call this my Chop-Chop
Emergency Escape!
[BUGGY]
Heh...
[BUGGY yells]
[BLUGORI groaning]
[BUGGY cackles]
[BUGGY] A drop like that should
break your skull just fine!
And this one here is my
Aerial Tailspin Big Top!
[BUGGY laughs]
You picked the wrong clown
to mess with, monkey.
[BLUGORI groans]
No. Don't get up!
Hey! Hey! No punching! Stop!
[LUFFY grunts]
[BLUGORI groans]
[BUGGY gasps]
[LUFFY sighs]
Damn, you got a lot
stronger, didn't ya, kid?
[LUFFY] I don't know,
these guys are pretty tough.
What are they?
[BUGGY] Sea Monkeys.
Blue Gorillas, they're called.
Or Blugori, for short.
But stay sharp,
should be four more of them
left to take the place of--
Well, never mind,
guess you got them already!
[LUFFY] Either way, I hope
that's the last of 'em.
I don't have time to
mess around right now.
That guy's a monster!
How did he do that?
You came here to
let us out, didn't ya?
We'll be your best
friend, pal! I promise!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
Ca-lick.
[SKINNY GUARD]
Something wrong?
[SURVEILLANCE 424A]
You bet there is!
I thought you said only
one prisoner escaped.
Yeah, it was just the clown guy.
[SURVEILLANCE 424A]
Pretty sure I saw two guys,
but maybe I'm crazy.
And speaking of crazy,
5 Blugori got taken down
in front of
Community Cell Number 10.
[SKINNY GUARD]
On Level 1? There's no way.
The prisoners down there
aren't strong enough
to take on even one Blugori!
What? You broke in
here to rescue Ace?
[LUFFY]
Yep.
[BUGGY gasps]
Shh! We gotta stay quiet!
Not really followin'
your own advice there.
We could really use
the keys to our cell
--if you're not too busy--
--Would you shut the hell up?
Nobody gives a damn!
[LUFFY]
Wait, do you know Ace?
Yeah. And though I can
see the resemblance,
he made a much better
impression than you did.
[BUGGY PIRATES laughing]
[BUGGY laughing]
You really think this is
the time to throw a party?
How can you plan on beating
Luffy and the rest of his crew
when you don't have
any idea where they are?
Oh, come on, don't be such
a party pooper, Alvida.
We'll find Luffy when we
find him, so just calm down.
[ACE]
If you're looking for Luffy,
I can tell you where he is.
There you go, problem solved.
This fellow here can lead us
straight to Straw Hat, any time!
Hold on, who in
the hell are you?
[ACE] Oh, hello.
Sorry for crashing your party.
Anyway, the name's Ace
and as you might guess,
I was drawn here by the
delicious aroma of your feast.
Thanks for feeding me.
No need to be polite,
we're all friends here.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, friend.
Just 'cause you
introduce yourself,
doesn't mean you get
to eat my food!
My ship, my banquet, my rules!
So you take that meat
out of your mouth!
Captain! Be careful!
That guy is Fire Fist Ace!
Just let the man eat.
He's from Whitebeard's Crew.
The Second Division Commander.
[BUGGY PIRATES]
Did you say "Whitebeard?"
What?
Oh! You guys know
the old man, huh?
That's nice, he's a real--
He's sleeping?
After he woke up,
we had a few drinks,
chatted it up and
became pretty good pals.
So yeah, I think it sucks your
brother got thrown in here, too.
Kind of stupid of
the Navy to do that.
I'm sure Whitebeard'll
give 'em hell.
I heard they're
keeping Ace on Level 5.
Could you show me
the way to get there?
Not a chance in hell--
Go by yourself!
What, do you think
I'm your friend now?
In fact, you can die
down there for all I care.
So long.
If you don't want
to break out of here,
I'll just do it on my own.
[LUFFY] Okay, but there's
ten battleships out there.
I hope you've got a good plan.
That's not good.
All right. I get it.
They must be expecting
an attack from Whitebeard.
Guess I picked a bad time.
Huh. Maybe I can just lay low.
I'll find someone else then.
So are we getting
the key, or not?
No, no, I must be
imagining things.
What would he be doing
with something like that?
[BUGGY]
Then again...
Well, good luck
with your escape.
I gotta get moving.
[BUGGY]
No, that's gotta be it.
Wait, Straw Hat, don't go!
[LUFFY]
What's your problem?
[GUARD]
Up there!
[BUGGY] They found us!
[LUFFY screams]
No kidding! 'Cause you
won't stop yelling so much!
By the way, that's a lovely
armlet you've got there,
Straw Hat, do you think you can
give it to me, pretty please?
[LUFFY] No, it was a gift from
Nami. What do you want with it?
[BUGGY]
If you let me have the armlet,
I'll tell you how to get to Ace!
That a promise?
Sure. Just fork it over, kiddo.
Okay. Then you got a deal.
Alright! First off,
let's shake those guards.
Grab onto my feet, okay?
Your feet?
[BUGGY]
Good, now start running!
[BUGGY cackles]
Be careful with those!
Can't have you drop them!
[NARRATOR]
Let's review how Buggy's
Chop-Chop power works, shall we?
When he chop-chops
his body to pieces,
he can control each
part however he likes,
but only within a limited area.
And if his feet aren't
close to the ground,
he becomes unable to levitate
the rest of his body.
[BUGGY]
Damn, I am one lucky clown!
[BUGGY] I got the treasure
of a lifetime and a ticket
out of this crap
hole in one shot!
[MOHJI]
Captain. Captain.
[BUGGY]
What?
[MOHJI] I'm just starting
to have second thoughts
about this place, that's all.
You sure this is the cave where
Captain John kept
his hidden treasure?
And the crew he left behind
never found it this whole time?
It seems a bit too easy.
[BUGGY] Just hold the
lantern and keep walking.
[MOHJI]
Yes sir.
[BUGGY] Now look alive boys,
the treasure is near
but so is unspeakable danger.
If you let your guard down
even for a second,
then death will creep up on you.
There's no telling what
kind of monsters will appear
or what kind of vicious booby
traps await to kill us all.
Hm?
[MINER BOSS 424A]
Come on men!
Another fine day carving
out tunnels awaits us!
[MINERS]
Right-O, boss!
Oh! You three must
be the new guys!
[BUGGY] Nothing like working
up a sweat, right Boss?
All a man really
needs is a pick axe
in his hand and
a tunnel to dig!
[MINER BOSS 424A]
That's right!
And because of our good old
fashioned elbow grease everyone
who comes to this
tunnel will smile!
[BUGGY]
It's liberating!
You know, after all this hard
labor we ought to head over
to the Old Bilge Barge for a--
[BUGGY screams]
How dare you make me work
like one of your lackies!
[BUGGY] Unfortunately that
wasn't the first dead end
we hit and it
wouldn't be the last.
We ran all over the Grand Line
looking for that treasure.
As if that wasn't crappy enough,
my ill-fated treasure hunts
brought me straight to
a Navy Post one day and the
bastards threw me in this dump
when they captured me.
[BUGGY] But maybe it was
destiny all along guiding me
to Captain John's treasure.
[BUGGY] Step on it,
Straw Hat, time's a wasting!
[LUFFY grunts]
[BUGGY] Follow me and we'll
be at Level 2 in no time!
[LUFFY] Level 2?
Were you listening to me?
I said I wanted
to go to Level 5!
[BUGGY]
Don't you know how numbers work?
You gotta go through
2 to get to 5!
Let me explain.
Think of this as an
upside down tower.
The place we're at right
now is called Level 1,
which is the
first basement floor.
After that you go to
Level 2 and 3 and so on.
The deeper you get, the more
infamous the criminals are.
They tortured me in the
fires of Level 4 a few times
but that's as far as
I've gone, myself.
Everything else is just things
I've heard from other people.
[BUGGY] Level 5 is where they
take all the big shots, though.
So with a bounty as high as your
brother's, he's gotta be there.
[BLUGORI D panting]
[LUFFY panting]
As for what's
below Level 5, well,
I've heard some rumors,
but the details are scarce.
The theory is, the criminals
they send down there
are so dangerous that
they've been completely
wiped from history.
Now that I think about it,
there's a good chance
that's where they
took your brother.
But the furthest I can
take you is Level 4,
so you're on your
own after that.
Thanks, Buggy!
I thought you were a real jerk,
but I guess I was wrong!
[BUGGY cackling]
A deal's a deal!
And if that armlet leads me
to Captain John's treasure,
I'm getting a real bargain, kid!
[BUGGY] I shouldn't have
opened my big mouth.
Hey, you know what?
[BUGGY]
Uh, what?
If you got caught,
you're a pretty crappy pirate.
What the hell, man,
gimme a break!
[BUGGY]
The idiot didn't even hear me.
I'm lucky he's so stupid.
[LUFFY]
That's awesome.
This is a treasure map?
I didn't have a clue.
Bet that'll be really fun, huh?
[BUGGY gasps]
Sorry kid, but if
you know the truth,
I'll have to kill ya!
[LUFFY] You better take this
now in case I forget later.
[BUGGY gasping]
[BUGGY] You... You know
that's a treasure map
and you're still gonna
give it to me?
[LUFFY]
Yeah, of course.
Treasure's cool and all,
but Ace is more important.
But if you give it to me now,
what's to stop me
from running off with it
and leaving you
down here to die?
Nothing, I guess.
But you gave your
word you'd help out,
and that's good enough for me!
[BUGGY] Those trusting eyes,
boring into my soul!
I'm a scoundrel,
Straw Hat, can't you see?
Don't do it!
You deserve better than this!
I'm no good for you!
[BUGGY] After all this time,
I finally have the key
to Captain John's secret
and I owe it all to you!
Thanks, buddy,
you're a real champ.
[BUGGY] Now how do I ditch you
and get the hell out of here?
[BUGGY groans]
Oh, if we break through
the walls here,
is it like a shortcut?
I can do that!
[BUGGY]
What's wrong with you?
[LUFFY yells]
[BUGGY groans]
[HANCOCK]
I do hope Luffy is safe.
I warned him to
stay out of trouble
but that may have been in vain.
Breaking your brother out
will be challenging enough,
but if you get captured as well,
who knows what
horrors you might face.
One wrong step and you may never
see the light of day again.
I know you want to save Ace,
but this is dangerous.
Please, take care
of yourself, too.
[HANCOCK gasps]
I won't let you down,
you have my word.
Thanks for everything, Hancock--
you're the best.
[LUFFY]
Hancock...
Hancock... Hancock...
[HANCOCK sighs]
Oh, my love.
I can hear your angelic voice,
echoing through the
chambers of my heart!
[HANNYABAL]
Okey dokey, almost there.
[PRISONER screams]
[HANNYABAL] Whew, that was
a good one, wasn't it?
[DOMINO] Our jailers
are certainly skilled
at what they do.
[HANNYABAL]
Did you hear that, empress?
No? Well worry not, milady,
there are plenty more
blood-curdling screams
where those came from.
If you don't have a
taste for sadism yet,
we'll do our darndest
to change your mind before this
little visit has come to an end.
[HANCOCK]
Silence, you accursed fool!
You interrupted my
romantic reverie!
I thought I was being polite,
but she's stepping on me.
This might require
a new approach.
[DOMINO]
Please, empress, he means well!
Actually, this is kinda hot.
[DOMINO]
Huh?
Oops! I said that
out loud, didn't I?
[LUFFY yells]
[BUGGY groans]
[LUFFY grunts]
What the hell is going on here?
That clown is Buggy,
the escaped prisoner.
But who is the other guy?
[BUGGY]
Oh no, this is the guard room!
If we keep going this way,
I'm in trouble.
For crap's sake, please stop!
[BUGGY screams]
This place is crazy!
I mean there's a
forest in the prison?
And why's everything all red?
[LUFFY]
Who are those guys down there?
They're prisoners, stupid!
This so-called "forest"
is a torture chamber!
[BUGGY] Every leaf is
as sharp as a razor.
That's why they call
them "Blade Trees."
And the grass is made of spikes
that prick you like needles!
It's called "Spike Needle
Grass." Original, I know.
The jailers release
venomous spiders
and chase the prisoners up and
down the forest all day long.
Deadly pitchforks behind them,
piercing needles beneath them
and cutting razors
everywhere else.
They run until they're
drenched in their own blood,
suffering agonies they
never thought possible.
This is Level 1,
otherwise known as
the Crimson Hell!
The true face of Impel Down!
[RANDOM PRISONER 424B]
Haven't I suffered enough?
[RANDOM PRISONER 424C]
You're gonna kill me!
Wow, this place
really is like hell!
Are they doing this
kind of stuff to Ace, too?
Don't think about it!
Just keep falling!
That's dumb!
We're gonna get cut!
[BUGGY]
Oh yeah? Ha! Watch this!
Listen up, kid.
Now take my feet
and throw 'em down
on the ground right below us!
Are you sure?
Okay.
Holy crap. You don't
see that every day.
Whoa! Careful!
[BUGGY laughs]
Are you kiddin' me?
This is a cinch!
[BUGGY] And the good news is,
we don't need to go down
any stairs to get
to the next level.
No stairs, no gate, no key--
just free falling.
The normal prisoners
wouldn't want to take it,
but there is one way to get
out of the Crimson Hell
that'll be perfect
for our little plan!
Okay, I'll take
your word for it.
[BUGGY]
See? We're already here.
[LUFFY]
A hole?
Whoa! I can't see a thing!
[BUGGY laughs]
Like I said, there's a way out,
but nobody wants to take it.
Can you guess why?
It's not 'cause it's
dark and scary.
It's because this hole
is a one way trip
down to Level 2. And if you
think things are bad here, well,
you ain't seen
nothing yet, kiddo.
When people get sent to hell,
you better believe they'll
try to claw their way out.
But no one in their right
mind would ever dream
of diving further into
the abyss.
Yeah, I get it. Then it's
good thing we're crazy!
Just jump down, huh?
[BUGGY] Yeah, but be
careful, there's a--
[LUFFY grunts]
[BUGGY screams]
[BUGGY]
Are you kidding me?
Wow, it's deep!
What do you think's down there?
Jeez! Would you
give it a minute, kid?
You got huge balls
or just a tiny brain?
Well, this works out for me.
Now I can blow this joint
and he can't say a damn thing.
[BUGGY cackling]
I got the key to the treasure,
I got that chump off my back
and soon, I'll be free!
I'd say "see you
in hell," buddy,
but I've been there
and done that!
I robbed you, got my revenge,
and you thanked me for it!
[BUGGY cackles]
Stupid! You can't chop me!
What do you think the
Chop-Chop Fruit is for?
[BUGGY]
Crap. Those are my feet.
No! No!
[BUGGY screams]
[GUARD 424A]
Surveillance Room, come in!
We sighted another escapee!
He and Buggy both
fell to Level 2.
Can you find 'em?
[SURVEILLANCE GUY]
I'm on it.
[MONSTER 424A growls]
[MONSTER 424B growls]
[RANDOM PRISONER 424D]
Hey.
Is it just me, or do the beasts
seem kind of restless today?
[RANDOM PRISONER 424E]
As long as they're not hungry!
Anything but that!
I'm too tired to be
afraid anymore,
I don't even care.
I'm going to be their
dinner sooner or later--
it might as well
be today, I suppose.
[PRISONERS screaming]
[BUGGY screams]
[NARRATOR] Luffy and Buggy
make their way to Level 2
where the wild beasts
of Hell dwell.
And they soon find that
the strange creatures
live up to their reputation.
Meanwhile, Hancock reaches
the heart of the prison,
and is greeted by none other
than the warden, Magellan.
[LUFFY}
On the next One Piece:
"The Strongest Man
in the Prison!
Poison Man Magellan appears!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!