[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope, and
others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era in
the country's history
that will forever be
overshadowed by sadness.
Vivi and her friends
continue their struggle
to save Alabasta
from its crisis.
Sanji found himself at the
mercy of Mr. 2, Bon Clay,
the master of Ballet Kenpo,
and fought a difficult battle.
Fortunately, during
the conflict,
he was able to figure out the
Clone Clone power's weakness
and finally emerged victorious.
Meanwhile, Princess Vivi decided
to destroy the royal palace
in order to save the
lives of the citizens.
However, as the countdown
to the explosion began,
Crocodile appeared.
[LUFFY] "Nami's Cyclone
Advisory! Clima Takt Burst!"
Luffy dead? Impossible!
I don't believe you!
[CROCODILE]
Nonetheless, it's true.
Poor Straw Hat, buried in
the sands of Rainbase,
dear Miss Wednesday.
If only he hadn't gotten
involved with you;
he might've lived
a long and happy life.
You're a liar!
He couldn't be killed
by the likes of you!
You know, it's only
because of his sacrifice
that you're still alive to rave
and rant at this moment.
You owe him your deepest thanks.
That way, maybe he'll
at least be able to...
Tell me where he is!
Did you come here
just to torture me?
[chuckles]
...be able to rest in peace.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[NAMI]
I guess her plan must've failed.
She wasn't able to stop the
rebel army at the entrance.
I wonder if Vivi and
the others are all right.
They're all fighting, putting
their lives on the line...
...and here I am
running and hiding.
[NAMI]
You heard me! I need help!
I want you to build me a weapon!
Build you a weapon?
And what are you gonna do
with it, hide behind it?
[NAMI]
Touché.
Okay, so I'm not a warrior.
I'm just really cute
with a great figure.
[USOPP]
Say what?
[NAMI]
But even so...
I at least wanna
be strong enough
not to endanger the others.
Especially this time. For Vivi.
[LUFFY chuckles]
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY, CHOPPER yell]
Usopp, I know you
understand how I feel.
We're not like the others.
They're all as
strong as monsters.
In a fight, they can
rely on their own power
to defeat almost any enemy.
But us, we're just a couple
of ordinary humans
with no special abilities.
When a battle starts,
you and I are just in the way.
We're a burden to the others;
we can't even protect ourselves.
If we're gonna fight beside
them, we need weapons.
Really powerful ones.
Or else...
[NAMI] Isn't that the
reason you're always
inventing new weapons?
So you'll be able to hold
your own in a battle
with them without shame?
Am I right?
It's the same for me!
To help Vivi, I wanna fight
with my own two hands!
Will you help me or not?
[USOPP sighs]
[USOPP] We don't have much time
left till we reach Alabasta.
You're right.
I guess you can't turn me
into a warrior overnight.
Sorry for being so unreasonable.
Unreasonable, maybe,
but it's not impossible.
Hey, were you suggesting
there's something
the mighty Usopp can't do?
[gasps]
Yeah?
[chuckles]
[NAMI] Does that mean
you're really gonna do it?
I love you! Thank you, Usopp!
Now, as to the matter of
the cost, this won't be‐‐
I really, really
mean it, thank you!
Yeah, we covered
the gratitude part.
But top‐of‐the‐line
weapons aren't free.
I'm counting on you, 'kay?
[USOPP]
Hold on a minute!
[NAMI] Relax, boys,
you're off the hook.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[USOPP]
But, Nami...
[gasps]
[NAMI]
What am I doing?
I'm jumping at noises now.
[NAMI]
And after I shot my mouth off
in front of Usopp like that.
I'm ready, aren't I?
To fight for Vivi?
[NAMI] After all,
Usopp kept his promise.
Okay, I'll fight!
If it's just that one woman,
I should be able to‐‐
Give it up, girl. It's useless.
[NAMI]
Miss Doublefinger!
But what was that spear‐like
weapon she used?
Does she have Devil
Fruit powers too?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
I know what you're thinking.
You're right. I ate
the Spike Spike Fruit.
It granted me the power
to release spikes
from anywhere on my body.
[NAMI]
Spikes that can pierce
right through a
solid stone wall!
If I slip up just once, she'll
make a pincushion out of me,
and that'll be the
end of the story!
What?
Don't tell me you're actually
going to try and fight me!
Yes!
It can call upon clouds.
It can summon forth the rain.
It can create the wind itself!
My marvelous invention
can cause disaster
with its elemental power!
Stay away, or feel the
force of my Clima Takt!
Clima? What now?
[NAMI]
First, sunny weather!
Fine Tempo!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Uhh...
Wow, look at that!
It made doves appear!
[NAMI laughs]
Dumb thing!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Are you all right?
[NAMI] Okay, that was
just the first try!
Besides, now we've gotten
her to lower her guard.
Very clever, Usopp!
This time you've had it!
Cloudy Tempo!
And now we've got
some pretty flowers!
[NAMI laughs]
Piece of junk!
What's going on around here?!
Don't play dumb with me, bird!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] I don't know
her story, but what a poor kid!
[gasps]
Try again! Save the princess!
[SOLDIER B]
Cannons! Bring cannons in!
Destroy the gate!
[SOLDIER C]
Hurry!
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Dieciseis Fleurs!
[yells]
[SOLDIER E]
What the‐‐?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[gasps]
Maybe now we can have
a little peace and quiet.
[yelps]
[gasps]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
What a stubborn girl.
You're just wasting your
time dodging my attacks.
You know you haven't
got a chance.
I do too!
These instructions say there
are tons more attacks to try!
[screams]
[NAMI]
My Clima Takt!
But how? When'd you
take it from me?
I didn't. You dropped
it all on your own.
[NAMI]
Give that back!
Sure, glad to.
Though, I don't care
much for magic tricks.
See, I have enough power
to fight on my own
without needing a
hunk of junk like that.
Now be a good girl and
stay right where you are.
That way I'll be
able to kill you
without causing you
too much pain.
Aw, does this show of
yours have a second act?
Forecast: Thunder!
Thunder Tempo!
Thunder Tempo...
Thunder Tempo. Thunder...
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Finger... Stinger!
[NAMI screams]
[NAMI screaming]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Eh.
[NAMI]
My cheek is bleeding.
Am I gonna die like this?
I am, aren't I? I'm gonna die.
And I'll haunt him!
Long‐nosed fool!
Long‐nosed‐‐ Why didn't
he make a real weapon?!
What's this?
So, I'll kill you now, okay?
How is she doing that? And why?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Hedgehog Stinger!
Too close!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait!
Hold on!
I said hold on! Just a minute!
Can't you give a girl a minute?
I'm not ready yet!
Come on! Cease fire!
No fair! Time out! Stop!
[NAMI] I can't stay out
in the open like this!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
This is it!
Time for you to get skewered!
No...
...thank you!
Well...
It looks like she's got a
little more battle experience
than I thought.
Not that it'll help.
[NAMI]
Where was it?
I saw it.
There was something
that looked useful
somewhere in these
Clima Takt instructions.
Dammit, where?
[USOPP]
That's it!
Next time you're at a party
and things are slow,
just use these little
tricks I've written up
and things'll really
start to jump!
People will love 'em!
I'll kill you!
[USOPP]
Oh, by the way,
I've jotted down a few battle
configurations on the back.
[NAMI]
On the back?
Hm?
[gasps]
Let's see, where could you
be hiding yourself this
time, little kitty?
[NAMI laughing]
[NAMI]
I'm through running and hiding!
I may not look it, but during
my eight years as a thief,
I survived all kinds of
crises all by myself!
You can't treat me like
some ordinary girl.
Now bring it on, hussy!
My, my. Kitty found her claws.
Well, then. Show me
what you've got.
You got it! Taste my real power!
[USOPP]
The battle configurations
of the Clima Takt!
First, understand the
characteristics of each section!
Each one can shoot
off air bubbles,
either by shaking or blowing!
The first shoots hot air.
[USOPP]
Heat Ball!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
What's this? It's warm.
[USOPP]
Next shoots cool air.
Cool Ball!
Ah, how pleasant.
[USOPP]
The last shoots electricity.
Thunder Ball!
Oh, my, that tingled!
[USOPP]
Of course, these techniques
aren't quite finished yet,
so if you use 'em at parties,
you need to be careful.
Then why write 'em down?!
Look, are we done here?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Sewing Stinger!
Please, please, something
I can use for battle.
Not for parties,
some real techniques,
something I can fight with!
I'm sorry, girl, but I've
had enough of these games.
Stinger Step!
I see! The Heat Ball and
Cool Ball join together!
When they stop spinning,
the bubbles hit each other,
creating an air flow,
generating a powerful wind!
Brilliant, Usopp!
[USOPP] The Cyclone Tempo is
like an ordinary boomerang,
so if you take it outside
after the party to play with,
you have to watch out.
He really doesn't get it.
But let's see here...
Maybe I...
What kind of weapon is that?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] Don't you
dare turn your back on me!
To turn your back to your enemy
in the middle of a battle...
You didn't value your
life too highly.
[gasps]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER gasps]
I changed the air density
by using a Cool Ball.
The temperature difference
caused a refraction of light
known as...
A mirage!
No way. At this distance?
[USOPP]
We can't win with power.
If we're gonna survive,
we gotta use our brains!
Heh. That's how we fight, right?
Used properly, this
can make miracles.
I'd say this is the
perfect weapon for me.
[growls]
Okay, Spiky. I'm ready.
Now why don't you give up?
No, Father!
[CHAKA] Let the king go,
Crocodile! At once!
Now, now.
After all the trouble
I went through
to immobilize him like this,
you really think I'm just gonna
turn around and let him go?
Use your head.
It's not gonna happen.
[COBRA]
Vivi, I'm sorry.
I failed you and the nation.
I didn't use the chance
you risked your life for.
Oh, Father.
Come on, is this the best you
can do after years apart?
Anyway, Miss Wednesday.
Don't call me that!
[CROCODILE] Let me tell
you a little something.
I have no intention of keeping
you or your father alive.
When a kingdom dies out,
it only seems natural its royal
family should die out as well.
Don't you agree?
But first, before
I take the throne,
there's something I need
to ask the current king.
If you have a moment, that is.
In fact, this has been my goal
from the very beginning.
Cobra, tell me,
where's the Pluton?
[gasps]
How can... you know that name?
[chuckles]
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[USOPP]
Tornado Tempo!
It's the centerpiece
of this weapon!
But if you miss,
you're done for.
[NAMI] I'll make this last
technique work for sure!
[VIVI]
What is Pluton?
[CROCODILE] It must be sleeping
somewhere in this country.
It's been my goal
from the start.
[VIVI] Such a thing
exists in our country?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Secret Passed Down
in The Royal Family!
The Ancient Weapon Pluton!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!