Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[panting heavily]
I saw you fight those zombies.
All of you have such
unbelievable strength!
There's an evil man
who must be brought down!
If you'd help me get my shadow
back, I'd be ever so grateful!
Your shadow?
Hold on.
Did we just find another guy
who had his shadow taken away?
He's just like Brook!
Well damn. That sucks.
So who did that to you?
Is he here?
Somewhere on this island?
His name is Moria.
And he's terrifying.
Moria? You don't mean--
[ROBIN] Gecko Moria,
by any chance?
[SPOIL] That's right.
Yes. That's him.
[LUFFY] Robin,
do you know this guy?
[ROBIN ] Yes.
Gecko Moria is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Gaaah!
You fools!
He found us!
[HOGBACK] What did you see?
Didn't I tell you never to
peek into my research room?
We didn't see anything!
Right! Nothing! We swear!
I didn't see anything at all!
Really?
Really!
It's the honest truth!
We certainly didn't see that,
uh, that zombie you were making!
Dumbass!
Alright, fine then.
Huh?
[HOGBACK] I'm sure
you've figured out some of
my secrets by now,
but you're too late.
Woe unto those foolish enough
to wander this
island after dark.
No intruder shall
survive the Night Hunt!
[growls]
Now! Zombie Soldiers!
The Zombie Generals
will lead the attack.
Let's finish off those pirates!
[cheering]
[PERONA] Are the preparations
complete, my zombies?
[cheering]
[MORIA] In this dark realm,
one of ghosts and ghouls.
This place we
call Thriller Bark.
They are going to
see nothing short of
the nightmare
to end all nightmares!
Well, here we go.
To the Ghost Mansion!
[LUFFY] "Feast of
the Zombie Song!
The Night Hunt's Bell
is the Sound of Darkness!"
[groaning]
What was that nonsense about
studying zombies, Hogback?
There's no hiding it now.
We know you're the one
making all the creatures
on this island, so out
with the truth already!
Whoa, easy there,
Nami! Don't piss him off!
Fasfasfasfasfasf!
Your accusations
are meaningless,
whether they're true or not.
But out of curiosity,
what's your proof?
[NAMI] We read your
assistant's obituary!
Victoria Cindry,
you died ten years ago!
You cretins! How the
hell did you know that?
Answer me!
So not only did you
sneak into my secret lab,
but that room as well.
My dear Cindry.
Samurai Ryuma.
Throw them into the world
of darkness, never to return!
Wait! Let's talk this over!
Sorry Doctor, but I'm afraid
it's too late for that now.
The Night Hunt has
already begun, you see!
[clacking footsteps]
[RYUMA] Done with your
little tour of the lab?
Do you need me to show you out?
[RYUMA]
Nyohohohoho!
Oh my. Upon
closer inspection,
you're quite the lovely
young lady, aren't you?
Beautiful!
Oh no. Not at all.
You know, I only have
eyes for girls like you.
Or I would, if I had any
eyes in the first place.
Nyohohohoho!
That said, perhaps you
would like to show
me your panties?
Yeah right!
Eh? I know that line.
I'm all eyes
for ladies like you.
Or I would be if
skeletons had any eyes.
Yohohoho!
Could you, perhaps,
show me your panties?
[NAMI] Yeah, right!
[NAMI thinking] This can't
just be a coincidence!
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfasfas!
This fellow is of
a much better stock
than the zombies you've
encountered thus far.
He is one of my
"Zombie Generals."
His body is quite special.
It hearkens from the country
of Wano in the New World.
[HOGBACK] They call his
sort a "samurai" and this one,
supposedly slayed
a flying dragon.
At least, according
to the legend.
Stay back! Stay back!
Please, don't hurt me!
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfas!
There's nowhere to run!
[RYUMA] Cindry,
if you would, my dear,
please open that door for me.
And if you have a moment,
I'd like a sandwich as well.
Wait. What happened?
I thought he was
going to cut us.
Yeah, so did I.
He looked really
scary just then.
Whatever, you guys! Come on!
Let's get out of here
while we still can!
Look, the door is wide open!
Good point.
[CHOPPER] Uh, right!
Run!
Splendid!
Fasfasfasfasfas!
They say when a
true master cuts you,
you can just walk away,
humming and smiling.
It's not until later that you
realize you've been struck down.
[RYUMA] Three-Verse Humming:
Arrow Notch Slash!
Fasfasfasfasfas!
[LUFFY] Hello?
Nobody's there. I'm going in.
[SANJI] Hey! Give 'em a minute!
[LUFFY] Oh. It's locked. Huh.
Hey, now it opens.
Yeah, since you
smashed the lock off.
[LUFFY] Gecko Moria!
I'm here to kick your ass!
[FRANKY] Pretty creepy
looking entryway.
[ZORO] Doesn't seem
like anyone's here.
Hey! Any monsters
in here? Gecko Moria!
Shouldn't there be a
servant around here?
They gotta have tons of
them in a mansion this size.
[SANJI] And what's
with the mess?
They have a fight
in here or what?
They better not have hurt Nami.
[sinister chuckling]
[OINKCHUCK] You're quite
audacious, aren't you?
Those who know our master
usually know to fear him!
Huh? Why is there a pig
sticking out of the wall?
Oh, we've many
surprises yet to come!
What do you say we welcome
our guests, gentlemen?
Well, that's great.
Are these paintings
zombies, too?
That's certainly
what it looks like.
After all we've
seen on this island,
we should expect this
sort of thing by now.
Ohhhhh!!
I'll only ask this once:
Where did you hide Nami?
Screaming like that
isn't very ladylike.
A shame, since you're so pretty.
You think so?
Though you're
better off just staying
in your frame and smiling.
Now twist!
The same goes for you.
He broke my spear in half!
What is this guy's
body made of? Metal?
[PAINTING ZOMBIE 342F]
Oh! Okay, stop stop stop!
Who are you guys?
[PAINTING ZOMBIE 341A]
You're really on the same crew
as those cowards from before?
Yep!
Two Sword Style. Nigiri.
Nigiri?
What is that, sushi? Gimme some!
Open wide.
I should stick to ramen. Uuuugh!
[chuckles]
Wow, this island's like
a party everywhere you go!
You little twerp!
Hahahahaha!
Too bad! If you hadn't
tried to smash me,
I would've asked
you to join my crew!
[LUFFY] Now Gum-Gum Bazooka!
No! Not Bear Rug!
[LUFFY] Well, that
takes care of that.
Hold on. Not yet.
[CREW] Hm?
[FRANKY] Still got
this little piggy up there.
Fasfasfasfasfasfas!
All right. Now take
the intruders away.
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfasfas!
[groaning]
Eh? Uh... Oh, those
three friends of yours?
We fed them, bathed them,
and gave them a
warm bed to sleep in!
Good news, right?
We're all friends!
Like we're gonna fall for that.
No, I swear,
I'm not lying to you!
Why don't you go
see for yourself?
Right up those stairs! Go ahead!
Hold on.
Something's wrong here.
Hm?
[FRANKY] Didn't you notice?
Our chef is missing.
Huh?
He was just here a second ago.
Any of you zombie
guys see where he went?
[snickering]
[OINKCHUCK] Hey, stop
laughing! They can hear you!
Hm.
[snickers]
They must've nabbed him
and taken him away
while we weren't looking.
Goodbye Sanji.
Rest in peace.
That ain't cool.
Eh. No biggie. It's Sanji.
I'm sure he's gonna be fine.
Maybe.
But I'm worried
about the other three.
If the zombies were able
to kidnap Sanji so easily,
I'm sure they're in a
lot of trouble right now.
Heh heh heh heh.
You're not so strong.
The truth of the matter is,
you hardly even put
a dent in our numbers!
[FRANKY]
Oh?
You, on the other hand,
just lost one of
your key fighters!
I wonder who's next!
At any rate,
let's be careful and try to
stick together from now on.
Admit it, you're scared.
You don't stand a chance in...
I suppose that we
could threaten him,
but even if we did, I doubt he
would tell us where they are.
Fine.
We'll just drag him with us
and use him as a guide.
What?
[snickering]
Hahahaha! Yes, guide them!
Hey now, come on!
Go ahead.
If you want to die so badly,
then challenge our master.
It's your funeral.
He's so frightening,
I can't speak his name.
But here, let me try.
Gecko Mori--ah!
Just as I thought.
It's too scary.
That's right.
He's one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea, you know!
Those missing friends
of yours are probably dead,
or even worse!
Consider yourself lucky
that you've lost so few.
I'd save my own skin,
if I were you.
If you face
Gecko Mori--I mean,
if you face our master,
none of you will survive.
You'd do well to leave
before you incur his wrath!
[LUFFY] Sorry, but I don't
take advice from paintings.
You wanna help, give a message
to that stupid master of yours.
Tell him if he
lays a single finger
on any of my friends,
I'll kick his ass so hard, this
whole island will split in half.
Sanji's fine.
Even if he's alone,
it's not like he's gonna
just roll over and die.
C'mon guys.
Hold on!
You're not really taking
me along, are you?
Say something, you guys!
[OINKCHUCK] Dear Master.
It would appear that some
rather terrifying guests
have made their
way to your abode.
It is with no irony that I say
that they've managed to surprise
even the surprise zombies.
[rock music]
♪ Rise from your grave
and raise your arms. ♪
♪ It's Fiesta Time!
♪ Bring those pirates
to the ground. ♪
♪ Bite them and drag
them through the grime! ♪
♪ Everyone, it's Zombie
Night! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Round and round until
you die! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Everyone, it's Zombie Night!
(woop woop) ♪
♪ Round and round
until you die! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Zombie Night!
♪ Everyone, it's Zombie
Night! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Round and round until
you die! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Everyone, it's Zombie
Night! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Round and round until
you die! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Everyone, it's Zombie
Night! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Round and round until
you die! (woop woop) ♪
♪ Zombie Night!
[cheering]
[ABSALOM] Listen well!
The intruders have all
wandered into our territory.
They are our prey now.
Let your hunger run wild!
This will be a feast of terror!
Now awaken,
Zombie Generals!
[ABSALOM] The fallen warriors
shall pick up their swords anew!
[ABSALOM] The
Straw Hats are arrogant.
They number only eight.
They'll fall quickly.
Tear them down and offer
their bodies to our Master!
Zombie Generals!
March forth and teach
them the meaning of fear!
[NAMI] Hey Chopper, this
might seem kind of random,
but how do you feel about
putting animals in zoos?
[CHOPPER] Are you kidding?
I'm a reindeer!
I think animals should run free!
[NAMI] Oh, me too.
But what if those
animals were zombies
and they were
trying to kill you?
[CHOPPER] Oh yeah. Lock 'em up.
[BOTH] Would anybody like
to start an Animal Zombie Zoo?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"A Bunch of Animals?
Perona's Wonder Garden!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!