[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
The land is in the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other.
After many adventures,
Luffy's band reached Crocodile's
headquarters in Rainbase.
Unfortunately, here they
encountered the Marines,
led by Captain Smoker
of Marine Headquarters.
[NARRATOR] Forced to defend
themselves against
both the Marines and
Baroque Works' Millions,
Luffy's party storms
the Raindinners Casino,
attempting to
confront Crocodile.
[LUFFY]
"The Trap of Certain Defeat!
Storming Raindinners!"
[LUFFY]
I know you're in there!
I'm comin', Crocodile!
[yelling]
[MILLIONS A]
Not so fast, you!
Don't talk, just shoot them!
Damn, these guys are annoying!
Heh. I think that
oughta shut 'em up.
[PEOPLE chattering]
Hey, Crocodile! Show yourself!
Listen!
I crossed an ocean and a desert
so I could kick your ass!
Crocodi‐‐!
That's not gonna make him come
out here, you loud‐mouthed dope!
[USOPP]
Don't forget we're dealing
with this country's hero!
You wanna turn all these
customers against us?
Okay, fine. So what do we do?
[USOPP]
Whoa! Hold on!
Without Vivi, we don't even know
what Crocodile looks like!
[NAMI] Now that you
mention it, where is Vivi?
[ALL]
Vivi!
Crocodile! Come out!
[ZORO grumbles]
Your pardon, sir,
but some undesirables
have entered the casino.
Oh, for Heaven's sake.
Have security throw them
out, and relax, will you?
Hey! You know what?
I'm thinking they might not
come just 'cause we called.
[SMOKER] I've got you
this time, Straw Hat!
[NAMI]
Smoker!
You think you can stroll
in anywhere you like
and I won't find you?
[LUFFY]
Not Old Smokey!
[USOPP]
Run!
Oh, great.
What's that refugee
from an ashtray
doing in a casino in Rainbase?
If you ask me,
I'd say he's developed
a special affection
for Luffy here!
This building's surrounded by
a lake‐‐there's nowhere to run!
Now hold on! That's far enough!
[EMPLOYEE C] Government
officials aren't allowed inside!
You must leave at once!
Move it!
[LUFFY]
Man, he's stubborn!
[SMOKER]
Hold it!
Ugh. I'm in no mood to try
to deal with this right now!
[SECURITY GUARD A]
Excuse me, sir.
I'm gonna have to ask
you and your frie‐‐
[LUFFY yells]
Hold on a second,
did I just hit something?
Manager, this is terrible!
Some strange people
have forced their way in.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Send them to the V. I. P. room.
Mr. Crocodile's been
expecting them.
[SMOKER]
Give it up!
[PEOPLE scream]
Hey, look! Ahead! It's‐‐!
[EMPLOYEE A]
Thank you...
[EMPLOYEE B]
...for coming!
Please step this way!
The V. I. P. lounge welcomes you!
Did he say the V. I. P. lounge?
Hold on, do you think it
could be a trap maybe?
Hey, don't these lounge deals
usually have free drinks
for their guests?
It's not like we have
a choice. Run for it!
The V. I. P. Lounge?
Don't tell me these jokers
are friends of Crocodile's!
But if it's true,
all of them could end up
on the gallows together!
[LUFFY]
What is a V. I. P. anyway?
Hey! The hall splits!
[USOPP]
It says V. I. P. s go left!
[NAMI]
And pirates go right!
[LUFFY]
Which way do we go?
[ZORO]
Decide quick!
V.I.P.s! Choose V. I. P. s!
That's gotta be the way to go!
That's crazy talk!
We're pirates, and pirates
are supposed to go this way!
Come on!
[USOPP] Well, yeah,
you got a point there!
Hey, wait!
[SMOKER]
Straw Hat!
[ALL]
Huh?
This is certainly unexpected!
[NAMI screams]
[ZORO] Can't believe
we fell for this old trick.
[USOPP]
It's an outbreak of my old
"I end up swimming when I
fall into a dark pit" disease!
[LUFFY]
I hate trapdoors!
[CHOPPED] That's strange.
What happened to everybody?
[TASHIGI]
Captain Smoker?
[yelping]
I wonder where Captain
Smoker could've gotten to.
He must be chasing
after Straw Hat, but...
[CHOPPER] She's with the
Marines. She's after the others!
[CHOPPER]
Stop! You can't.
[TASHIGI]
Oh. Oh, no.
My glasses! Where are they?
This is just great.
I'm helpless without them!
[TASHIGI gasps]
Oh, no. Are you all right?
'Scuse me, sir, you haven't
passed out, have you?
Come on, you, say something!
[MARINE A]
Sergeant‐Major Tashigi!
We've been looking
for you, ma'am!
I'll be right there!
[CHOPPER]
Uh, umm...
Are these...?
[chuckles] Oh, how nice.
You found my glasses!
You're such a kind person.
Thank you so much for
your help! Be seeing ya!
[MARINE A]
This way!
Not the sharpest tool
in the shed, is she?
Did you hear that?
She said I was a kind person,
but of course I don't
care what a big moron...
[SANJI]
Speaking of which...
Pretty clever trap, wasn't it?
Oh, yeah, no way to
see that one coming.
What are you talking about?!
I told you it was a trap
in the first place.
I can't believe what a
couple of idiots you are!
Something's wrong here.
I feel weak all of a sudden.
Really? What's the matter?
Are ya hungry or something?
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[screams]
Luffy!
I‐I‐I‐I'll take you on if you
want, you smoke‐filled freak.
I didn't do so bad against
the bomb guy, you know.
So I'll just wait over
here in the corner
and you let me know
when you're ready, okay?
What's wrong?
I feel so helpless. It's like
when I fall into the sea.
All right, just what have
you done to Luffy?
The tip of this staff is
made from a substance
called Sea Prism Stone,
a rare mineral.
It supposedly exists
in one certain sea
in the distant corner
of the world.
Not much is known about it,
but it's believed to
give off mystical energy
on the same wavelength
as the ocean itself.
Basically, you can think of it
as a solid form of the sea.
So it affects Luffy the same
as if he fell in the ocean?
Prison cells at
Marine headquarters
are made of this same substance
to prevent criminals who
possess any Devil Fruit powers
from successfully escaping.
Well, then I'm betting this
cell is built the same way.
If it wasn't, you can be sure
I'd be long gone by now.
And you four'd be
on your way to prison
waiting for your date
with the hangman.
[USOPP screams]
Are you crazy?!
There's no point in fighting
in a situation like this!
Stop!
And besides,
what good is a sword
against a guy who's
made outta smoke?
[CROCODILE]
She's right. Give it up.
[CROCODILE] You're all
going to die together,
so why not make an
effort to get along first?
Huh. It's Crocodile.
All right!
[growls]
[chuckles]
[USOPP, NAMI whimpering]
So he's one of the
Seven Warlords, is he?
Huh. You're every bit the
low‐life sea scum I imagined.
My, my.
You're every bit the wild dog
I heard you were, Smoker.
Unlike your superiors,
you've never really believed
I was on your side, have you?
And of course, you were right.
You know, Smoker,
I have a feeling you'll die
bravely in the line of duty.
I'll be more than happy
to inform the government
that you put up a valiant fight
against the vicious
Straw Hat Pirate here.
I haven't the vaguest idea
what really brought you
to this country,
but I'm betting
you're on your own.
We both know the government
would never order you
to come to this land.
They have every confidence
in me, a Warlord of the Sea.
You big old bag of wind,
you're Crocodile?
[CROCODILE]
Hm?
Come on and fight me like
a man, ya big dumb...
Pay attention, stupid!
You gotta remember
not to touch the bars!
Straw Hat Luffy,
I congratulate you
on getting this far,
and I promise to dispose
of you neatly and efficiently,
once our special guest of honor
has made her appearance.
A guest?
Why, even as we speak,
my partner is on
the way to fetch her.
[VIVI]
I can't afford to waste time
with these second‐rate thugs!
[VIVI]
Who's next?
Ya got some pretty impressive
moves there, Princess.
I gotta tell ya.
[MILLIONS A ] Of course,
I'd expect no less
from a former Frontier Agent.
But don't you think it's time
you accepted your fate?
[MILLIONS A laughing]
[VIVI] I have to get away
and reach the others!
Fun time's over! The boss
is waiting for you!
Don't you dare touch me!
[MILLIONS yell]
What is that thing?
Some kinda bird?
[MILLIONS yelling]
[MILLIONS G]
It's a falcon!
A falcon with a machine gun?!
Are you out of your mind?!
It's huge!
Hurry up and shoot it down!
[MILLIONS K]
Crap! The princess!
Oh, Pell! I can't
believe it's you!
It's very good to see
you, Princess Vivi.
How is my father?
He's doing well.
Your father and I both
read your letter,
and he sent me on ahead to
scout out the situation.
You mean, Karoo made
it safely to Alubarna?
He's all right?
That's right. You've got
quite a duck, you know.
Thank goodness!
Alabasta owes you a
great debt, Princess.
Thanks both to you and Igaram,
we know who we're fighting.
Now, if you'll please excuse me.
[MILLIONS L]
Pell!
[MILLIONS M]
You don't mean Pell the Falcon!
Oh, no way!
He's the strongest warrior
in the entire country!
The Bird Bird Fruit.
Model: The Falcon!
Just five types in the world
have the power of flight.
The power to which you
will now bear witness!
Shoot, you fools,
and don't stop!
[MILLIONS L]
He's gone!
[PELL]
Flying Talons!
Thank you, Pell!
I have to find everyone!
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Really?
Don't you think you're getting
a bit ahead of yourself?
You've certainly been
a thorn in our side.
Miss All Sunday.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
I'm just in time.
It looks like our
precious employees
are no longer of much use.
Sorry, Miss Vice President.
And who are you?
That was marvelous.
I've never seen anyone who
had the power of flight before.
Even so, do you think that
you're stronger than me?
Princess Vivi,
this arrogant girl,
is she one of those
threatening our homeland?
I'm simply here as a messenger
to invite the princess
to a little gathering
at our mansion.
If you have no objections.
Sorry, I'm afraid the princess
has a prior engagement.
I see.
[VIVI]
Stop screwing with us!
Now, really.
Do you think it's
proper for a princess
to use such coarse language,
dear Miss Wednesday?
Igaram. You killed him.
Igaram?
Ah, yes. Mr. 8, of course.
What's this? The one
who killed him was you?
Oh, come now, why are you
getting so worked up about it?
It's really no different
from what you did
to our employees just now.
Don't be childish.
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[PELL]
Damn you!
[MISS ALL SUNDAY chuckles]
Your bones will be
the sand of Alabasta!
Really? Tres fleurs!
[gasps]
[PELL groans]
Princess Vivi! You're alive!
[chuckles]
Oh, dear, did it look to you
as if I'd killed the girl?
[PELL]
Damn you, what did you do?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] You ought
to lighten up a little.
I was only teasing you.
You have Devil Fruit powers,
it's the only explanation!
That's right. I ate the
Flower Flower Fruit.
The power to make body
parts bloom like flowers.
That is my ability.
Even with the power of flight,
you cannot escape my reach,
for my limbs can bloom anywhere.
Who's escaping?
I'm staying right here.
And taking vengeance
for the life of Igaram!
I wish I could stay.
I'd love to play a few
more hands with you.
But time doesn't wait.
[PELL] Oh, don't worry,
this won't take long!
I'm afraid you don't understand.
Seis Fleur!
[groaning]
It isn't possible.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Power, speed,
these things mean nothing to me.
My reach is limitless.
And Clutch.
No! Pell!
Was he really Alabasta's
greatest warrior?
How sad.
No. Oh, no.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Well, time to go.
It can't be.
Our boss is waiting to see us,
and so are all your friends.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] Inside a
prison cell at Raindinners.
Hey, look, I'm Sanji.
Okay, which one of
you ate the meat?
[USOPP laughs]
Oh, really.
[USOPP]
I'm Zoro! Oni.
Get serious!
How can you two screw around
when we're in this
desperate situation?
[LUFFY]
Well, we can't get out,
so what else is there
for us to do?
The fact that we can't get out
is the reason it's so desperate!
If we don't do something soon,
we're gonna wind up dead!
And why are you sleeping?
Oh, is it morning?
It's afternoon, you moron!
You're certainly a
high‐spirited young lady.
Whatever!
You'd better go ahead
and enjoy yourself
while you've still got
the time, mister!
Because when these
fellows get outta here,
they're gonna kick
your smug butt
up and down the Grand Line
like a flabby beachball!
Right, Luffy?
Yeah! You better
believe we will, buddy!
[USOPP whimpering]
Your crewmembers seem to place
a lot of trust in your talents,
Straw Hat Luffy.
How foolish.
[chuckles]
I think trust is
completely unnecessary.
Who does he think he is,
sneering at us like that?
Knock it off, Nami.
You're just gonna end
up making him angry!
[VIVI]
Crocodile!
[ALL]
Vivi!
My humble greetings, Vivi,
Royal Princess of Alabasta.
I mean, Miss Wednesday.
I compliment you on having
evaded our assassins
in order to get this far.
You've no idea what I'd do,
or how far I would go,
to see you dead, Mr. 0.
I wish that you'd died in
your cradle, you monster!
Vivi! Wait, first get
us outta this thing!
This country would still be
peaceful if it weren't for you!
Peacock String Slasher!
[ALL gasping]
Not gonna work.
[CROCODILE]
Feel better?
As a native of this country,
you must surely know
that I have the power
of the Sand Sand Fruit.
Want to become a mummy?
He's made of sand.
You leave her alone!
I'm warning you!
Right now, or I'll
kick your ass!
[CROCODILE]
Have a seat, Princess.
I trust you'll be
comfortable there.
I must say, your
timing is perfect,
the party is about to begin.
Isn't that right,
Miss All Sunday?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Yes.
Party?
It's exactly noon right now.
Time for Operation Utopia.
Huh? Utopia?
What's an Operation Utopia?
[chuckling]
[LUFFY]
Hey!
[CROCODILE laughing]
It will mean the demise
of the Kingdom of Alabasta,
Miss Wednesday.
I'm going to wipe it off
the face of the map,
as if it never was.
[gasps]
[CROCODILE]
All people, great and small,
will be sucked into
eternal darkness
as they writhe in agony!
[CROCODILE]
Let Operation Utopia... begin!
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[NAMI]
Alabasta's going to die?
[VIVI]
What is he planning to do?
[CROCODILE]
The operation has begun.
This country will fall at the
hands of the rebel army,
the royal army, and the people!
Love for the kingdom will be
what destroys the kingdom!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Operation Utopia Commences!
The Swell of Rebellion Stirs!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!