[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[LUFFY] And thank you, Merry.
We never would've made it
if you weren't there.
[LUFFY] I was pretty surprised
when you showed up,
but when I think about it,
you've always been
there to protect us.
We've always counted on you.
Anyway, I'm just happy
you've been part
of the team, Merry.
You're a good friend to have.
[FRANKY] I don't mean
to spoil the mood,
but damn, you guys did
some crazy stuff back there.
[FRANKY] I don't
think the government's
gonna let you off that easy
after you burned
down their flag.
[LUFFY] Eh, whatever.
It doesn't feel
like a big deal to me.
[LUFFY] The only reason
I did any of that
was 'cause they took our
friend and I wanted her back.
[LUFFY] Thank you, Merry!
Snow Falls over the Parting Sea!
[LUFFY] Hey! Usopp!
Are you there?
[CHOPPER]
Where did you run off to?
Come back!
[LUFFY] Hey! Usopp!
[LUFFY] Thought he'd
be up here for sure.
Where are you hiding?
Are you in there?
Usopp?
[LUFFY]
Seriously, I just saw him!
[SANJI]
Hey, they're calling you.
[USOPP] No, I can't.
It's too soon.
[LUFFY]
Stop playing hide and seek!
[giggles]
Get out here
or I'll kick your ass!
Kick your ass!
Hey, do you know where
Usopp's at, Sniper King?
You're his friend, right?
[USOPP]
Oh, ah, no need to fear.
He took a different boat
and went on ahead by himself.
But why?
That doesn't make sense!
The Merry's his ship, right?
You gotta be kidding me.
If they haven't
figured it out yet,
then what's it gonna take?
Not here, either.
What the heck is going on?
[NAMI] I checked everywhere.
Looks like we're
the only ones on the ship.
[SANJI] That's pretty strange.
[NAMI] The Merry didn't
sail itself here, did it?
[ZORO] Of course not.
Someone was calling us.
The whole crew heard it.
[KOKORO] And you
don't know who it was?
[ROBIN] No.
Just a voice
beckoning us to the sea.
Come on, you guys,
the answer here is obvious!
I'm telling you, that was
Merry's voice we heard!
Huh? You think so?
Merry! Come on!
Say something else!
[ZORO] I think we'd know
by now if the ship could talk.
Y'know, as ridiculous
as it may sound,
I was thinking the same thing.
[NAMI]
But there's no way, right?
That's impossible.
[FRANKY] Hm?
[USOPP] The whole
situation remained a mystery.
For some reason, these words
lingered in my heart.
[USOPP] I don't know
if it's something
I actually heard someone say,
or maybe just
something I imagined.
[VOICE] Don't worry.
[VOICE]
I'll carry everyone
for a little bit longer.
I know it sounds
ridiculous, but I--
I think it was--
An incarnation of the Merry.
And she spoke to me.
You think I'm completely
out of my mind, don't you?
I don't care.
You don't have to believe me.
[FRANKY]
Whether I believe it or not,
you said that
whoever it was you saw
looked like someone holding
a wooden mallet, right?
That's right.
Does it mean something?
[FRANKY] Yeah, it sure does.
It means that you
saw a Klabautermann.
Kla--Klabau-what?
A Klabautermann.
It's an old legend that's passed
down from sailor to sailor.
[FRANKY] The more
care a ship receives,
the more they grow
to appreciate the sailors.
[FRANKY] This ship
must've been determined
to make sure you made it to
the next shore, no matter what.
Just think about it.
This ship had a caring crew
that was so special to her.
She even appeared in human form
to reassure them that everything
was going to be all right.
I betcha she's been very happy.
I see.
So it was you.
You were the one
who made those repairs
and spoke to me
back then, weren't you?
Merry.
Hey, look!
There's a ship coming!
[USOPP] What? Who is it?
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312A]
I can see the Straw Hats!
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312B]
They're alive!
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312C]
I knew they'd make it!
I just knew it!
[SANJI] It's a
Galley-La Company ship!
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312D]
I thought they were done for
when they went out
during Aqua Laguna!
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312A]
Forget Aqua Laguna!
They survived Enies Lobby!
Ahoy!
What's up, Ice Pops?
Ice for brains, huh?
Nico Robin survived.
They pulled it off after all.
They took on the
World Government and won.
[cheering]
[ICEBERG] They lost it all, and
then they brought it all back.
[wood cracking]
[USOPP] Merry!
Their ship! It's breaking!
[ZORO] Hey, why's it falling
apart all of a sudden?
[SANJI] There's
nothing sudden about it.
We all knew this was inevitable.
They told us, right?
Before we left, they said
Merry was unfit to sail.
[LUFFY] Yeah, but--
What happened to you, Merry?
[LUFFY] Ice Pops, help!
Merry's in trouble!
Can't you do something?
[LUFFY] You got
here just in time!
You're all shipwrights,
aren't you?
I'm begging you!
Don't let her die now!
Merry's more than just a ship!
She's a member of our crew!
If it wasn't for her,
we all would've died back there!
So come on, do something!
She's fought hard for you.
But it's time to let her rest.
Besides, I've already
done everything that I can.
[hammering noise]
[ICEBERG] What's that noise?
[ICEBERG]
Is someone on Scrap Island?
[ICEBERG] Wait a second--
This is the Straw Hats' ship!
[ICEBERG] Aqua Laguna
did quite a number on it.
It's a wreck.
No, this is
from long before that.
[MERRY]
I want to sail.
What was that voice?
[MERRY]
I want to sail.
One last time.
[ICEBERG] What am I doing?
There's no hope for this ship.
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312A]
Mr. Iceberg!
You gotta get outta there!
Another tidal wave's
about to hit!
[MERRY]
Thank you.
Huh? Ready a ship?
The weather's still
too rough out there!
[ICEBERG] Then I'll go alone.
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312B]
Are you kidding?
[RANDOM SHIPWRIGHT 312C] No, no.
We'll go with you!
This is a miracle.
There's no other word for it.
The miracle of a ship
that's gone beyond its limits
to see you one last time.
As you know, I've been
a shipwright for many years.
But I've never seen a ship
as incredible as this one.
[ICEBERG] It's lived
a wonderful life.
[MERRY]
Let's go back, everyone!
[MERRY] Back to
the seas of adventure!
Merry!
[MERRY]
I came to get you!
[LUFFY] I understand.
Well? Guys, you ready?
Yeah.
[LUFFY] Merry.
I know the floor of the sea
is a dark and lonely place,
but don't worry.
We're here to see you off.
[LUFFY] And I'm sure
you wish he was here,
but it's probably best
that Usopp isn't around.
I don't know if
he could take this.
Well, is that true?
[USOPP] Of course it isn't.
We all must say
our farewells someday.
Every man knows that.
We must hold back our tears.
[USOPP] Luffy knows
what has to be done.
[LUFFY] Thank you for
carrying us for so long,
and for so far, Merry.
Snow?
A real caravel!
Yeah!
[LUFFY] Now the
Going Merry has everything
she could possibly need!
[LUFFY] Cheers to a
new ship and a new crewmate!
[NAMI] Look at all the damage
you did to poor Merry!
A crew has to
take care of its ship!
And don't you forget it!
Right. We're sorry.
Hey, Luffy,
what's so loud down there?
Cannon firing practice!
But it's not going very well.
[USOPP] Let the expert
aim the thing.
[LUFFY] Awesome!
You hit that on the first try!
Whatcha think?
So are you impressed yet?
[LUFFY] Zoro!
That's the Captain's seat!
[NAMI]
Hey! Look! A light!
I'm going to the Grand Line
to find the All Blue!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
The world's best swordsman!
I'm going so I can draw
a map of the whole world.
I'm going to be a
brave warrior of the sea!
[LUFFY]
And now to the Grand Line!
The entrance to the
Grand Line is a mountain.
A wha--?
[ALL] We made it!
I can see it!
This is the greatest sea
in the whole world!
The Grand Line!
Let's go!
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY] We're flying!
Don't bother looking back!
'Cause we're
going straight ahead!
I'm afraid there's
nowhere left for me to go.
And for that matter,
there's no place for me
to return to, either.
So I've decided
to stay here with you.
I see your problem.
Guess there's no other choice.
Welcome.
Luffy!
Trust me.
I'm a navigator, aren't I?
[LUFFY] We're flying!
Yeah!
We're headed to the sky!
[LUFFY]
There it is! Sky Island!
[MERRY]
I'm sorry.
I wanted to carry everyone
just a little bit further.
[MERRY]
I had so much fun.
I wish our adventures
would never end.
Merry!
[SHIPWRIGHT 312C]
Who is that?
[MERRY]
But I'm sorry, I can't--
[LUFFY] No, Merry!
If anyone should apologize,
it's us, not you!
[LUFFY] I'm no good at steering.
I ran you into icebergs
and all kinds of stuff.
I took bad care of you
and ripped your sails.
Zoro and Sanji are idiots, too.
They were breaking
your stuff all the time!
[LUFFY] Usopp tried to fix you,
but he wasn't any good at it.
We all know that.
If anyone's sorry, it's--
It's us!
[LUFFY crying]
[MERRY]
I don't mind.
I was happy.
[MERRY] I know you
always treated me with love.
Thank you.
[MERRY] Even if the time
we spent together was short,
I'm glad that I could
spend it with you.
[LUFFY] Merry!
[KOKORO] It was a lotta work,
but we're finally back!
[CHIMNEY] Yeah!
[GONBE] Meow!
[KOKORO] Now it's time
to get Water 7 back to normal.
Looks like there's some kinda
hubbub going on, though.
[CHIMNEY] No kidding!
The Marines are here!
[GONBE] Meow!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Peace Interrupted!
A Navy Vice-Admiral
with the Fist of Love!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!