[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy struggled in vain
to rescue his brother Ace
from execution at
the hands of the Navy.
Marineford was then thrown
into chaos by Blackbeard,
who stole Whitebeard's
Devil Fruit power.
Traumatized by the
death of his brother,
Luffy is carried away by Jimbei,
who fights to escape the island
alongside Whitebeard's
surviving crew.
How about I give Marineford
a burial at sea?
[BLACKBEARD groaning]
[BLACKBEARD]
Shock Wave!
You can tear down our buildings,
but in time,
we will rebuild them.
But this island is different,
it's more than
a symbol of our strength.
It stands in the
center of the world,
and that means if we want
to protect innocent people
from criminals such as yourself,
it must be our stronghold,
so its light can
reach every corner.
It doesn't perish,
and it will certainly
not sink by your hand.
Time to learn your place.
Well? C'mon!
Let's see what you're made of!
[MARINE Q]
Destroy them!
[MARINE Q, MARINE R]
[MARINE Q, MARINE R, MARINE S]
Destroy them!
[MARINES]
What are these
voices in my head?
I dare not face him on dry land,
but the sea will aid me!
[AKAINU growls]
[JIMBEI grunts]
The water, it's frozen solid!
Sables!
[JIMBEI groans]
I say if you're gonna protect
someone, then do it right!
I don't like either of you,
but if you screw this up,
then you let the Navy win.
What is that?
It was underwater... A ship?
[PIRATE FF]
It's a submarine!
[PIRATE GG]
That's a Jolly Roger.
[LAW]
Quick! Hand over Straw Hat!
Huh? I don't take
orders from you, pal!
And besides, what do you want
with him anyway, ya weirdo?
Actually, who the hell are you?
Hand him over and we can escape.
He'll die without my help.
What?
Trust me. I'm a doctor.
Oh, "Doctor," my ass!
What kind of doctor
carries a giant sword?
And the whole submarine
thing is fishy, too.
What's your deal?
Who is it?
Another pirate crew?
It's Trafalgar Law, sir!
He's a rookie from
the North Blue.
[MARINE A] Then he must
be Straw Hat's accomplice.
The two started trouble with the
Celestial Dragons on Sabaody
a while back, but we weren't
able to capture either of them.
He's quite dangerous.
[MARINE B] They must be
planning to escape by submarine!
[LAW]
Stop screwin' around!
Hand him over!
[BUGGY] What's in it for me?
What's in it for you?
Uhh...
[BUGGY yelping]
[HEART PIRATE A]
Captain Law!
Navy battleships are
approaching from the stern!
Damn it! There's no time!
We gotta escape now!
Even if he does survive today,
what makes you think Straw Hat
will do you any favors?
He's the son of the most
heinous criminal in the world.
He could be your undoing just as
easily as he could be your ally.
If you're so determined to
stand in the path of justice,
I will grind you
beneath it's wheels.
Let's finish this.
Hound Blaze!
Don't let him gain another inch!
That's enough!
You're not laying another finger
on Straw Hat or anyone else!
[MARINE AA]
Prepare for combat!
Team A will pursue
the Whitebeard Pirates
and Team B will stop Blackbeard
and his crew at any cost!
[MARINES yelling]
[PIRATE A] Reinforcements
are coming from underground!
[PIRATE B]
Do they ever stop?
Finally...
Now let's rush 'em down!
[BLACKBEARD groaning]
[COBY gasping]
Hey, pal?
You're acting kinda
weird. Snap out of it!
C'mon! Let's go!
[panting]
[MARINE F groans]
[MARINE G grunts]
[panting, gasps]
[PIRATE D grunts]
[MARINES yelling]
[PIRATES yelling]
[BLACKBEARD panting]
[BLACKBEARD]
So, the leader of the Navy
can still slow me down a bit.
Nobody's perfect,
even with my power.
Still, that's not enough.
I'm sinkin' this dump. Watch me!
You'll do no such thing.
I'll strike you from this
island and from this world!
[BLACKBEARD yells]
[SENGOKU grunting]
[laughs]
[MARINE BB]
He stopped the shock wave.
[MARINE CC] Even the
Fleet Admiral can't phase him!
[BURGESS]
Hey, Cap! Save some for me!
[BURGESS laughs]
[BURGESS yelps]
What... hit me?
Garp!
[GARP]
I'm a Marine, same as you,
and I've spent enough time
feeling sorry for myself!
Hah! Sorry, gramps.
You're finished.
This is the face of a new era!
[GARP]
Huh?
[MARINES, PIRATES]
[SENGOKU growls]
[HEART PIRATE B]
Captain, we're almost within
their firing range!
[JEAN BART]
Curses, Bepo, do something!
C'mon, you just joined the crew
and you're already
ordering me around?
[HEART PIRATE B]
They've got us surrounded!
All cannons fire
at once! Sink them!
[BLACKBEARD laughing]
[MARINE I]
Fire!
[MARINES yelling]
[BEPO]
Oh, great, now what?
Not again.
Must be Blackbeard doing this.
I thought we were done
with these earthquakes!
This power is a real pain!
Is it just me, or is this way
stronger than the last time?
Watch out, men! This is bad!
[cackles]
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINE DD]
This is all wrong!
Look at the clouds!
Look at the sea!
He's tearing everything apart!
[MARINES, PIRATES yelling]
[MARINES screaming]
[cackles]
Ya gotta admit, it's
pretty fun to watch!
You didn't forget
about me, did you, clown?
[shrieks]
[CURIEL]
You forget about us?
[AKAINU grunts]
[HELMEPPO whimpers]
One was enough!
[PIRATE BB]
Block the Marines!
Even if we die,
our friends can escape!
--[gunshots]
--[gasps]
[MARINE EE]
Don't make me laugh!
We're hunting down
every last one of you!
[DEVON laughs]
Another fabulous show,
though a bit close
for comfort this time.
[BLACKBEARD]
Yeah, power's not an issue,
but control is tricky.
Hah! You're not kidding!
If you're gonna sink this place
at least wait till we're
not standing on it!
Stop this. It's madness!
[GARP] Not enough that you
killed Whitebeard in cold blood.
Now you're abusing his power and
putting his own crew members
at risk with this nonsense!
[BLACKBEARD] What, are you
tryin' to nag me to death?
If you got a problem,
then do something about it!
I don't play nice.
Those days are as dead
and gone as Whitebeard!
[cackling]
[MAN AA] No one should
have that much power!
They can't stop him!
[WOMAN AA]
It's a nightmare!
[MAN BB]
No one's safe!
[P.A. SYSTEM] This is a warning
from the Sabaody Archipelago
emergency broadcast system.
Following an Earthquake
at Marineford,
a tsunami is expected
to hit our southern shores.
[P.A. SYSTEM]
Everyone please remain calm
and listen carefully for the
following safety instructions.
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN A]
Run for it!
[CROWD]
Huh?
[P.A. SYSTEM]
Those in groves 1 through 39
should relocate to the elevated
northern groves
of 40 through 50.
[MAN CC]
Move it! What are you doing?
[MAN B]
I'm a nobleman!
I'll pay good money
if you let me go ahead!
[P.A. SYSTEM] Please
proceed in an orderly fashion.
[PIRATE CC]
Those weird robots are crawling
over the crack in the plaza!
[MARINE M]
C'mon!
Move! Follow the
Pacifistas and open fire!
[PIRATE E panting, yelps]
--[PIRATE F] Aw, crap!
--[PIRATE G] Hey, you okay?
I got this, guys, you two
go on ahead without me.
[PIRATE G]
Are you nuts?
Look, we have our orders--
this makes sense!
Better you escape than all
four of us get killed here!
Okay, I guess you're right.
[PIRATE G]
Good luck.
C'mon, stay with me.
What a joke!
You're all just marching
to your damn graves!
Pops, I'm sorry,
but for the first time,
I can't follow your orders.
I'm gonna fight
these guys to the death!
I'm with you!
Looks like we'll be joining
Pops in heaven soon enough.
[HELMEPPO]
Finally, it stopped shaking!
[crying]
[HELMEPPO] What the
heck is going on with you?
[COBY]
I don't know!
There's too much sadness.
[HELMEPPO]
What does that mean?
[crying]
[COBY] There are all
these voices in my head,
but I can feel them
disappearing one by one.
--Huh? Voices?
--[gunshot]
[MARINE FF] We'll show
you the meaning of justice!
[PIRATE DD]
Justice? This is murder!
[PIRATE I] Hold them off!
Let the others escape!
[MARINE O]
They're criminals!
Shoot the bastards in
their backs if ya have to!
[MARINES, PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE J yelps]
[MARINE P] There! That's for
my friend, you damn murderer!
[MARINE Q] You're gonna pay for
your crimes in blood, scumbag!
[MARINE GG] We're sending
a message, you hear me?
We rule this world!
Order rules this world!
--[gunshot]
--[MARINE HH] Got one!
Okay, I know we're all
stressed out right now,
but you're losing
your mind here.
Pull it together!
Please, somebody help.
[PIRATE K]
I can make it!
I can-- [groans]
[COBY gasps, groans]
[HELMEPPO]
Coby! Hey, wait!
Don't run from me!
We're not losing anymore, okay?
Now stay back!
We'll save you.
You'll be fine! Hear me?
[MARINE T]
Please, I'm scared.
Leave him!
We're not done fighting, dammit!
[MARINE S]
But, sir...
The pirates are escaping.
Our job is to enforce justice.
We don't have time to
tend to the wounded. Go!
[MARINE S]
Y-Yes, sir!
Kill every last one of them!
Show the world what
happens when you defy us!
[MARINE T groans]
We've got a man down! Medic!
[PIRATE M groans]
They're all running away!
Just shoot one and move on!
[TASHIGI]
It's not about winning anymore.
They're bloodthirsty.
They want revenge.
It went straight through him!
[PIRATES]
Run!
--[MARINE II] Chase them down!
--[MARINE JJ] Open fire!
[SMOKER] Even if our enemies are
criminals, this isn't justice.
Their wrongs don't
make us right.
[panting]
[MARINES, PIRATES yell]
[CURIEL]
Crap!
If you're a Marine,
then follow my lead,
and strike them
down with no mercy!
[BOTH]
Curiel!
[MARINES]
Yeah! Sakazuki!
[MARINES cheering]
[COBY panting]
[grunting]
[COBY] Hey, are you all
right? Damn it, get up!
[COBY gasps]
[COBY crying]
[cackles]
Funny, I don't see
anyone stopping me!
Or even trying!
Are you Navy boys scared?
Yikes! He's nuts!
He's fighting Sengoku now,
but I have a feeling if he
gets bored, we'll be next!
'Scuse me, friend,
but why don't you
come on down here?
No, not you!
Kizaru!
Drop them now, you idiot!
[BUGGY]
You know what, fine!
I don't need this right now!
I've done enough! They're
prob'ly gonna die anyway!
[BEPO]
Jean Bart! Here they come!
--[JEAN BART grunts]
--[BEPO] Ooh! Nice catch!
All right, now submerge!
Don't think I forgot about
what happened on Sabaody.
Time to pay.
Whoa. These wounds
are pretty bad!
Hang in there!
Damn!
[AKAINU]
Time to die.
You've done enough!
Huh?
A Marine?
[LAW gasps]
[AKAINU]
Hmm?
[crying]
[MARINE V groans]
Coby!
[COBY] There's no point
in fighting anymore!
There's no point in killing!
It's over! We won!
We can end this!
[PIRATE EE]
What is he doing?
[MARINE W]
I can't move...
Please, someone help.
These are human lives!
This is wrong!
They have families, children!
They're our friends and
we're watching them die!
[COBY] We killed Ace!
Whitebeard is dead!
The pirates don't have
the will to fight anymore!
What are we trying to prove?
What's the point?
[COBY]
There are wounded men out there!
We could save them if
we stopped fighting!
[COBY] But no! We're
just making more victims!
More casualties! Those Marines
have nothing to be proud of.
That's Coby...
Why are they dying?
What are they even fighting for?
Boy, you better run.
[COBY gasping]
You're wasting my time.
If you would impede justice,
I have no use for you.
[COBY]
This is it.
Not exactly what I'd hoped for,
but at least I said
what I had to say.
[AKAINU growling]
[COBY]
I have no regrets!
Coby!
[MARINES gasp]
[AKAINU]
Huh?
A splendid speech,
touched my heart.
And though they were few, those
precious moments of courage
you showed will
change this world.
Though only the future will tell
if it's for the better
or for the worse.
Inside! I'll be
right behind you!
[BEPO]
Roger!
I don't think so.
Put your hands up, now.
Oooh, I'll be! Ben Beckman!
[MARINE KK]
Hey, wait a second.
I know that ship!
[LAW]
Let's move!
What's he doing here?
One of the Four
Emperors and his crew!
[MARINES] It's "Red-Haired"
Shanks. Oh, no!
[SHANKS] It's been
a long time, old friend.
Let's end this war.
[NARRATOR] Suddenly, the
Red Hair Pirates appear!
As the Navy stares on in shock,
Law tries to escape
while suffering heavy
fire from the admirals.
Narrowly missing
a reunion with Luffy,
Shanks utters a speech
on the battlefield
that brings the
fighting to a halt.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Here Comes Shanks! The War
of the Best is Finally Over!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!