We're almost to the exit now.
Full speed ahead until
we fly outta here!
What?
No way!
You're kidding, right?!
All right!
There it is!
Time to move out, men!
Let's charge ahead, join them,
and get Franky back!
Yeah!!!
Sodom! Gomorrah! Jump!
Straw Hat!
The entire Franky Family
thanks you for helping us!
We'll never forget it!
Cool!
Hey, nice job!
Pretty high-grade bulls
you've got there!
But no matter what I said
or did, I couldn't stop you.
And the enemy that you'd
go through all of this
to rescue your friend
from is the exact same one
that tried to kill Iceberg.
I've got a word or two of my own
I wanna say to those bastards!
Right.
So even though we got in
a few fights back in town
with both the Franky Family
and with the
Galley-La shipwrights,
the enemy we're all going
after here is one and the same.
Oh, no!
Rocketman can't be controlled.
My job ended as soon as
I got us up on the railway.
There's nothing anybody
can do to stop it.
This train's gonna--!
Everybody on this train
has the exact same goal.
There's no point in
fighting separately.
From this point forward,
we fight as one!
Listen up!
We're not gonna let
that big wave beat us!
We will achieve our goal!
Let's go!
Yeah!
All right boys,
why don't you show me what
you can do about that wave!
You got it!
Fire all cannons!
Blow it to bits!
Cannons are my specialty!
It's just water!
Don't be afraid, bros!
Prepare the cannons!
Roger!
Get a move on!
Puru-puru. Puru-puru.
Ah! The Transponder
snail's ringing!
Hey guys, it's from Sanji!
Wh-What's going on here?
Oh, no!
Not him, too!
It was the same
thing in the last car!
Hey, you there.
Yes, Captain T-Bone!
How did you get that
injury on your arm?
Huh?
This?
I got bitten by a bug earlier
and it bled when I scratched it.
How awful!
We must staunch the bleeding!
We'll have to make do with this.
Sir! You don't have to tear
your cape just for me!
It may be your
arm that's bleeding,
but when one of
my men is injured,
it's my heart that
hurts the most.
Captain!
Thank you!
Let us fill today and every
day forth with good deeds,
so that peace and
kindness shall reign.
His face is still really scary.
Captain!
I'll help!
Oh good, but let me
explain the problem first.
If there's anything I can do.
Even if it kills me
I will protect you!
Uh, thanks.
But the problem is with the
officials in car 6 and 7.
They were completely wiped out!
Not only that, the two criminals
detained in car 6 are missing.
That's awful!
We can't tell if the prisoners
escaped on their own,
of if they were helped
by an unknown intruder.
For heaven's sake, man,
start a rescue operation!
Help the injured and spread
the word to the other cars!
Yes, sir!
Nami!
Nami, can you hear me?
Yeah!
What's going on, Sanji?
I've got some bad news.
Things have gotten complicated.
What do you mean?
Hey, wait a sec
what was that noise?
Is someone there
with you or something?
It's nothing just some dumb ass.
Huh? Say what?
Sanji!
What's that noise?!
It sounds like a bunch
of screaming-are you
okay over there?
What d'you mean by "dumb ass"?
Sorry, dumb asses, actually.
Demi Cannon!
Leave it to us!
Not even making a dent.
I shoulda figured.
You think those puny
things are gonna work?
Everybody, step back!
Let the Franky Family's
Special Cannon do its stuff!
Target Aqua Laguna!
Go!
Super Scrap Cannon, fire!
Fire again!
Don't let up!
Bring more cannonballs!
Got it!
Aim at the center!
Focus on one spot!
Focus pocus,
give it all you got!
Yeah, good luck with that.
By the way, the
tracks do rise up a bit
but not enough to
get us over that wave.
Rocket Man has done
pretty well out here so far.
But if we get hit,
we're finished.
Does that mean
we're all gonna die?!
No guarantees!
I warned you, now didn't I?
What?!
I don't wanna die!
I see.
They still have Robin.
It sounds like things are
pretty lively on your end, too.
Hey listen, Sanji.
I need to tell you why
Robin's doing all this.
And also why everyone's
screaming, for that matter.
Shut up!
So, like I was just saying.
We found out why
Robin's with CP9.
We're out here
trying to follow her,
but things are kind
of crazy right now.
It's a long story.
We're all gonna die!
But I don't wanna die!
Me either!
If you have time
to cry, keep firing!
We'll find a way out!
Hey, Luffy.
Yeah.
I know what you're thinking.
That wave's asking for it, huh?
C'mon!
Keep those cannon's firing!
What're you guys
planning on doing?
Same thing as you.
Watch.
Hey, how much is a
hundred and eight times two?
Two hundred and sixteen.
Two hundred sixteen, huh?
That's too long.
Can't we round up or something?
Fine make it 300, then.
I don't get it. What do they
think they're doing?
If cannons don't work, what
good are swords are gonna do?
Well, they did say we
should keep fighting, though.
Stop yapping and back them up!
Roger!
Okay!
Ready?
Uh-huh.
Now Gum-Gum--
Three Hundred Caliber--
We're gonna crash!
Cannon!
Roger!
Okay!
Ready?
Uh-huh.
Now Gum-Gum--
Three Hundred Caliber--
We're gonna crash!
Cannon!
Sanji--
It's all or nothing!
We... We made it!
Take that, Aqua Laguna!
I thought we were gonna die!
Hey! Hey, Nami are you okay?
Yeah, I-I think so.
We survived after all, huh?
You pirates know how to party!
Keep up the good work!
They're even stronger
than Aqua Laguna!
If we were enemies,
I'd be scared right now,
but since we're
friends, I'm happy!
Go Straw Hat!
We'd all be dead right
now if not for them.
Lucky that little trick worked.
Let's not get ahead of
ourselves, everybody!
We're not through the storm yet!
Yes, ma'am!
I'm not afraid of
anything, anymore!
Wow, that was really fun!
I knew you were strong,
but that was something else!
Are you an alien or something,
'cause that was totally
out of this world!
Oops.
Sorry 'bout that.
Luffy, c'mere a sec.
Huh?
Sanji wants to talk.
That you, Luffy?
Yep, it's me!
What's up?
You save Robin?
No, sorry.
Afraid I'm still
working on that one.
Nami just told me
why Robin surrendered
and all of that stuff.
So yeah I know what's going on.
I see.
That's good.
Well anyway,
you know what's next.
Go ahead. Give 'em hell, Sanji.
Huh?
Hold on!
He'll die if he fights them now!
If wants to stand a chance,
he's gotta wait on us!
Hey, Cook, can you hear me?
Some of the guys on that train
are really tough,
you shouldn't--
Zoro!
It's fine.
If it was you, would you wait?
If you were on that train
right now instead of him and
I told you that Robin sacrificed
herself to protect us.
Would you just sit
there and do nothing?
No use trying to stop him.
Read me like a book.
But thanks, Moss Head.
I never knew that you
cared about me so much.
I hope they kill you!
Anyway, that settles it.
I was willing to fight for Robin
even before I knew the truth.
But now that you told
me how she really feels.
I wouldn't stop,
even if you begged me.
Why'd you break
it, you bastard?!
I wanted to talk to
Straw Hat, too, damn it!
Huh?
Deal with it.
No point in griping at me now.
What, was I supposed
to interrupt you
while you were talking?
That's just rude!
You're rude anyway.
I hope he's okay on his own.
Granny, hurry!
Make the train go faster!
Faster?
Yeah!
More like zoom, y'know?
Oh, don't you worry!
This baby is already
going way faster
than it was ever supposed to!
In fact, we're going so fast,
we can't even stop anymore!
So much stuff has
happened since I left.
It almost doesn't seem real.
In a way, Robin's in
the same boat you are.
Never found out
about what happened
with the Merry or
your fight with Luffy.
It makes me ashamed to think it
but while we were busy
fighting amongst ourselves.
Robin surrendered to the
government
so the six of us could be safe.
That includes you.
Oh, man!
That's such a sad story!
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying, you are!
Damn it!
Now I'm all torn up!
I always thought Robin
was some evil monster,
but it turns out
she's got a soft side!
What if I'm confused
about other stuff, too?!
How am I supposed to go on?
I'm not gonna stand here in
the rain when Robin's so close.
I gotta save her
before it's too late.
Sweet.
Once again, I'm Franky,
leader of the Franky Family.
You 'n me'll make a
good team, Eyebrows Bro.
I won't go into the details,
but I've got a pretty good
reason to keep Robin away
from those
government chumps, too!
Besides, you really
touched my heart
with that story of yours.
Hey, Long-Nose,
let's do this thing!
No, I'm... I'm not coming.
This doesn't have anything
to do with me anymore.
You're about to make
yourselves personal enemies
of the World Government.
I don't want to
be any part of that.
Besides, Luffy and the
rest of the crew are coming.
After I humiliated
myself in front of them.
I just can't pretend like
nothing ever happened
and laugh it off.
I still feel bad for
Robin but I'm sorry.
It's not my job to save her now.
I am not a part of Luffy's crew!
See ya.
"See ya?" There's
no place to go!
Come on!
You guys can
talk this over, bro!
Forget it.
Just leave him.
You are both stubborn as hell.
Check every corner!
They gotta be here somewhere!
What?!
This is just terrible!
We'll have to make do with this.
The train's in a lot
of trouble right now!
Wanze!
We need your help!
Shut up, stupid!
Your face is in trouble!
Nero! The criminals
made an escape!
Hm?
How's it going over there?
Have you noticed
anything strange?
No. Nothing yet at least.
Keep looking!
Sir!
They're right here!
Dammit, they found us!
Metallic Star!
Who the hell are you?!
Your friend told me everything.
I understand that you are here
to rescue a certain
mademoiselle.
That alone is reason enough
for me to join your cause.
My weapons are at your disposal.
My name is Sniper King.
We'll now begin
Operation Rescue Robin!
Wait Sanji, don't you want
to learn more about me first?
Before anything else, we gotta
clear out the enemy forces.
Like my origin story
or super moves?
We'll start with the weak
guys, then work our way up.
Sniper King,
I'll-Do-My-Best Star!
Hey, would you shut up
and listen to me?
Yes, sir. Sorry.
On the next One Piece:
"A Mysterious Man Appears?!
His Name Is Sniper King!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!