[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[LUFFY]
"How's Tricks?
The Designs of
Zenny the Moneylender!"
[GOATS bleating]
Come on, can't you
work harder than that?
This isn't a
tea party, you know!
Try putting your backs
into it, why don't you!
Look, Old‐Timer,
just take it easy!
We can handle this
without your help!
That's right, Gramps,
you just settle down
and take a load off!
[ZENNY]
Ah!
How about a nice
shoulder rub to relax you?
Ah! Wait!
Where'd they come from?
So, I was wondering
why are you building
this ship of yours way up
in the mountains, Old‐Timer?
Ah, it's not a ship.
Uh, it's not a ship?
Come on!
If this isn't a ship,
then what is it supposed to be?
Well, son, it'll be...
...my coffin.
[GROUP]
Your coffin?!
Yeah, it's my
final resting place.
I see.
We're standing on your grave.
You'll jinx him! Stop that!
Now hold on, slow down!
Yeah, you shouldn't
over‐prepare!
[NAMI] Could Gramps here
have a premonition
that his life is almost over?
What are you all so jumpy about?
I live all alone on an island!
I have to plan for everything,
even the possibility
of my own death.
After all, I'm gonna
die someday, aren't I?
[USOPP]
Someday?
More like any moment now.
It's not so unusual for a
grave to be in the mountains.
Yeah, but why would you want
your grave to be a pirate ship?
[GROUP]
Old‐timer!
[yelling]
[SANJI]
Wait, old man!
Coffin or grave or
whatever you wanna call it,
it's almost finished!
You don't wanna go
jumping the gun, do ya?
Don't die yet!
Shh!
He's just sleeping, that's all.
I see. So you've located
the Straw Hat pirates?
Yes! We've confirmed that
they've taken refuge
on a deserted island, just as
I reported to you earlier!
Good, then get ready
to attack at once!
We're gonna storm
that island with every man
we've got and take those
miserable Straw Hats down!
Every last one of 'em!
If you please, sir, hold on!
[CAPTAIN]
Hm?
Not only do some
of the Straw Hats
have Devil Fruit powers,
but we'll be up against
the master swordsman,
Roronoa Zoro!
What does that matter?
Are you losing your nerve,
Sergeant Minchy?
Not at all, sir!
No, I'm just trying to avoid
any unnecessary casualties.
And your plan would be?
If you will only follow
my directions, Captain,
I am confident that we
will be able to take down
the Straw Hats while sustaining
only minimal casualties
to our side.
[NAMI]
Ha!
A‐ha, very nice.
Oh, wow!
How did you make this?
It's delicious!
It's from the milk
of the island goats.
Eat, it'll give you
lots of energy.
Though at this point it'll
just be a drop in the bucket.
Well, Gramps, it's your move.
Let's see, ah, here we go.
Check and mate.
[NAMI gasps]
Now wait a sec!
Sorry, all moves are final,
that's too bad!
Fine, you win.
How about just one more
game huh, please?
Sure thing!
There's nothing better
than playing chess against
a good‐looking girl
like you while getting
your shoulders rubbed
in the bargain!
[laughing]
[LUFFY, USOPP laugh]
Some catch, huh?
Sanji!
Make the old goat man
something yummy again,
will ya?
Sure, I'm all over it!
Hey, old man, if there's
anything else at all
you'd like to eat or have us do,
don't be afraid to
speak up, okay?
Because we'll be
more than happy to do
anything you want!
Nah. I think I can
die happy now.
Heaven. I'm in heaven.
Don't even think that way!
Sure, time's short.
But stay positive!
No matter how long you've got!
[crying]
Hey guys, can we have a word?
What's that?
About the old guy, he's only
got three days to live, right?
That's right, only three.
He's only got
three days left to live!
That's really only the briefest
moment of time, isn't it?
[crying]
Yeah, very brief,
and in that brief moment
three days have already gone by!
[GROUP]
Huh?
Say what, now?
[USOPP]
You're right,
so how is it that he's
still alive and kicking?
[SANJI] What's more,
he looks even healthier
than he did before, doesn't he?
How 'bout some more cheese?
Hey, Gramps,
here's today's medicine.
Make sure you
take it right away!
No way. I'm done!
It makes the food taste bad!
A‐ha! Checkmate!
Gah! Not again!
Chopper, I thought
you said that old guy
wasn't supposed to live
for more than three days!
From the way he looks,
he might be good
for another 30 years
at the very least.
Did you misdiagnose him?
No, impossible.
Though if I did,
it wouldn't really be
a bad thing in this
case, would it?
That's not the issue here!
If he's not dying, then no
matter what anyone says,
I'm leaving this
island right now!
Yeah!
I'm not gonna hang
around here kissing up
to that crazy old geezer
for the rest of my life!
I want to get back
to having adventures!
That settles it then!
Nami, we're setting sail!
Uh, can we hold
off a little while?
What, are we supposed
to hang around here
cooling our heels while you
play another game of chess?
I can't quit playing now, okay?
I lost so many games to Gramps
that I ended up pawning
the ship to him!
You what?!
What are pirates who lost their
ship supposed to do, huh?
Don't worry, guys,
I'm sure that I can get it back!
[ZENNY]
Checkmate!
[NAMI yells]
[GROUP yells]
[USOPP]
Stop playing!
[CHOPPER]
Earthquake!
[USOPP] If you don't stop
playing this stupid game now,
who knows what else
we're gonna end up losing!
[ZENNY] If you want
to get your ship back,
then you're just going to
have to work on this island
until you've paid me back
as much as it's worth.
By my reckoning,
you're gonna be working for me
for the next ten years.
So how's tricks with you?
[laughing]
‐‐[LUFFY] Nami!
‐‐[SANJI] Nami, sweetheart!
[NAMI]
I'm sorry!
I thought if I got lucky
I could get the old guy
to tell us where his
treasure's stashed away!
[USOPP] Are you still
going on about that?
Our only option now
is to leave the old man
and run away. Who's with me?
[LUFFY]
Uh‐uh, not me.
Come on, what are you
talking about, Luffy?
We're all just lucky that
Zoro was paying attention,
'cause if he hadn't been, we
might've spent the rest of
our lives on this island
waiting on that old man
hand and foot!
You just gotta accept it!
You're not gonna have any
adventures around here, Luffy.
It's time we were moving on.
‐‐No way.
‐‐Luffy!
A gambling wager is just
like a promise, isn't it?
I'm not going to do
anything to break a promise.
This is no time to
get hung up on details!
Zoro, what do you
think we should do?
Hey, the captain is
the one who decides this.
Luffy!
I said no and that's
what I meant!
That's checkmate.
[GROUP]
Hm?
Well I'll be.
Looks like we can
get the ship back.
[chuckles]
[GROUP chuckles]
Well, old man, give up?
You win.
[GROUP]
Hooray!
Looks like we can
always count on you,
right, Big Sister?
So how's tricks with you?
Don't rub it in.
[ZENNY laughing]
[ZENNY]
I've lived many years,
but I've never met pirates
as interesting as you!
I love you kids.
Let's have a party
tonight and celebrate!
[LUFFY]
Ah, yeah, let's celebrate!
Getting our ship back!
[GROUP laughing]
Gramps, you really
are just like a pirate.
You sure drink like one!
[ZENNY laughs]
Nami, do you think
that I'm a pirate?
Well, it would explain
why you can afford
to have such exquisite
glassware, right?
It does look like it's
from a treasure trove.
I see, you're trying
to get the old man drunk
so you can make him tell you
where he keeps the treasure,
is that it?
Well, don't spell
it out for him!
So goat man, do you have
a hidden treasure, huh?
Didn't I just ask you guys
to keep your mouths shut?
At least you could have a little
respect for the process!
You really wanna know?
[NAMI]
Mm‐hmm.
My treasure is what I've shared
all my joys and sorrows with.
My beloved goats.
[GOATS bleat]
What a beautiful story.
Ha! Gotcha!
Ha ha!
Oh, come on, Gramps.
Please tell me.
Okay, you asked for it.
Of all the great pirates who
have sailed the Grand Line,
I was known as...
I knew it!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Hm?
The only moneylender who
would do business with them!
Moneylender?
I'm Zenny the Moneylender,
not Zenny the Pirate.
You are?
Well that's too bad, huh, Nami?
He may not be an actual pirate,
but it must've
taken a lot of brass
to lend money to them,
right, old man?
Why's that?
Hey, use your head!
Do you think most pirates
are gonna take out a loan
and then pay it back
with a smile?
Not to mention all the interest!
Your friend is right.
Every one of those seafaring
serpents tried to bilk me
out of my money.
They all broke their words,
went back on their contracts,
and did their best
to betray me when it
finally came time to collect.
Wow, Gramps, I guess it's true
that you really do
hate pirates, huh?
If I'd just sat back
and taken it from them,
my business would've been
wiped out in no time at all.
Every time I went out
to collect a debt.
I had to fight against pirates
at the risk of my own life.
So in order to stay in business,
you'd have to be stronger
than any of them,
wouldn't you?
Were you that strong,
old goat man?
Hell no, I was
weaker than a kitten,
but back in those days,
I had a dream.
[LUFFY]
A dream?
[NAMI]
You did?
[PIRATE CAPTAIN]
What?
Pay back the money?
Right, 'cause I'm
Zenny the Moneylender,
not Zenny the Money Giver!
I'd sooner see you and
your crew frying in hell
than let you skip out
on your debt!
Now what's it gonna be?
N‐Now hold on, Zenny! Here!
Well, how's tricks
with you? Heh.
Not so fast!
You think we'll just give up?
Nah, of course not!
[PIRATES yelling]
Zenny! You're dead! Y'hear?
[ZENNY] Hee hee!
Nice doing business with you!
I may have been weak,
but I had a dream to fight for.
Fight for it I did,
no matter what the risk!
What was your dream, exactly?
Ever since I was
just a little kid,
I wanted to be a pirate!
A real pirate!
The king of pirates!
That's why I first got started
in the moneylending business.
[GROUP]
Hm?
But instead of
realizing my dream,
I end up getting ambushed
by a bunch of pirates
out for revenge and marooned
on this deserted island,
fighting for my survival.
That was 20 years ago.
Are you telling me that you've
been making your grave
that whole 20 years?
At first, I planned to
build the ship near the sea,
but I realized rather quickly
that hauling the lumber
down from the mountain
was too much.
But I wasn't going to give up
over a little thing like that.
Instead I built it
in the mountains.
It was going to be
a great adventure.
But somewhere along
the way I wised up.
Before I knew it,
I was too old to set sail
for the Grand Line.
It's funny the way time can
sneak up on you like that.
So much for my dreams
of being a pirate.
Well. Dreams are just dreams.
[laughing]
I don't understand
why you gave up, goat man.
Age doesn't have
anything to do with it.
If you wanna be a pirate,
you should just do it.
Now hold on,
what are we gonna do
if he starts taking
you seriously?
Remember a pirate needs a ship,
and this guy's ship is a coffin
that's sitting halfway up
the side of a mountain!
Then all we have to
do is haul it down, right?
Don't say that like
it's gonna be easy!
[ZENNY]
That's true, there's still time!
I warned you,
he's taking it seriously!
Nonsense!
He's just a little bit drunk,
aren't you?
That's right, yeah,
I'm drunk, honey!
[laughing]
Really?
[ZENNY] This straw‐hatted kid's
got me absolutely intoxicated,
and not just with wine!
So here's looking
forward to the day
when the Zenny pirates
finally set sail!
[GROUP cheering]
[CORPORAL]
Can we really do this?
Lure the Straw Hat pirates off
the island all by ourselves?
[MINCHY]
They're just a bunch of kids.
As long as we don't
lose our heads,
we have nothing
to fear from them.
It's not like I'm gonna
fight them myself.
Now calm down.
But is the captain
really going to be able
to take the Straw Hat Pirates?
I don't really much
care one way or another.
While the big boys are
off fighting for justice,
we're just gonna be walking
off with a bunch of treasure.
And you needn't worry, Corporal,
I won't forget about you.
You'll be taken care of.
Uh, thanks.
[MINCHY chuckles]
[ZENNY] Age doesn't have
anything to do with it, huh?
He had to go and
say something to start
an old man dreaming
again, didn't he?
That straw‐hatted kid
sure is a sneaky son of a gun.
[laughs]
I agree.
Oh, hi.
[ROBIN] Our captain also
rescues people who want to die
without asking them,
and then lets them live.
And are you sorry
he let you live?
Don't know, it may be
too soon for me to tell.
No, you're not sorry.
You may not know it yet,
but I can tell by looking
at you that your life
is just getting started.
But in my case,
my dream's going to lie
buried here, forever.
[GOATS bleat]
[ZENNY]
What do you see?
[CHOPPER]
Emergency! Wake up!
I slept good. What's to eat?
The Marines!
The Marines are here, guys!
What's that?
[USOPP]
Just one ship?
[NAMI] They don't look like
they're about to attack, either.
Then what is it doing here?
[MINCHY]
Straw Hat Pirates, greetings!
I'm Sergeant Minchy
of the Marine Corps,
it's a pleasure!
[NAMI]
I bet it is.
[MINCHY] Hey, I'm really sorry
about the other day, okay?
Forgive us. If we'd had a
better idea of who you were,
we wouldn't have spent
all day chasing after you!
Please accept our apology.
Maybe I'm just paranoid,
but I always thought
the Marines were supposed
to chase pirates.
It's like he's campaigning for
the Miss Congeniality Award.
Stay sharp.
[MINCHY]
Now hold on! Let's not be hasty!
We know all about how
you guys defeated Crocodile
back in Alabasta, okay?
The last thing we want
to do is go up against
pirates as great as you guys
are without any back‐up!
Think about it!
I'd have to be dumb
as a bag of hammers
to come with just
one ship if I was planning
to take you on!
Well, what do you think of that?
Huh. This Marine's
actually afraid of us!
[laughing]
Assuming we were foolish enough
to risk our lives fighting you,
we wouldn't be earning
any money on the deal!
So then what are you doing here?
[MINCHY]
Oh, well, you know how it is,
this is a newly discovered,
uncharted island.
We're just here to,
uh, investigate it.
[NAMI]
What's to investigate?
There's just an old man
and his goats.
Hey, guys, where did
the old man get to?
A‐ha!
So Zenny is being taken good
care of here then, is he?
[NAMI]
Zenny?
[MINCHY]
Once our survey is done,
we're planning on
returning to our base.
I don't want to be pushy,
but I suggest you set sail
out of here as soon as possible.
No one would blame you,
considering what a frenzy
Marine headquarters
is in to eliminate you all.
He's got a point.
We should get away
now while we still can.
I'll go grab the supplies.
Gotta call Robin too.
Look there!
[ZENNY] It's a trap!
A dirty Marine trick!
[SANJI]
So what should we do, set sail?
[MINCHY] The weather's really
good when you get past the fog.
Gentle waves, a steady breeze,
and we won't lay so much as
a finger on you, I swear it.
I'll go when I'm good and ready!
You're not the boss of me!
Y'know, if I were a Marine,
I'd be fighting against
us no matter what
the odds were against me!
And there's another
thing that's strange!
How did you happen to
know his name was Zenny?
We didn't say a word about it,
but you came right out with it
like you knew he was here!
[MINCHY]
I was just...
And I'm getting just a tad bit
suspicious of this "survey"
you're planning to conduct!
You're not after Gramps's
treasure, now, are you?
That's it, right?
Don't trust this guy. He lies!
[MINCHY] Well, so much
for the innocent routine!
She sounds like she knows all
about the mountain of treasure
Zenny the Moneylender
received in order to settle
the pirates' debts!
[GROUP gasps]
[NAMI]
I just knew it!
See! There is a treasure!
I smell gunpowder!
Are his ship's cannons loaded?
Maybe. It's from
more than one ship.
It's from more ships
than I can count!
[NAMI]
What's that? Look!
[SANJI] If we'd set sail like
our friend here advised,
we'd have been caught in
a sneak attack by that fleet!
[ZORO]
That does it!
Just come and get me!
Wait! Please wait!
[USOPP whines]
Luffy!
Usopp, no!
Help me!
No one move,
not even one little twitch,
or the big‐nosed one gets it!
So they already had
a landing party in place
waiting for us, did they?
Excellent work,
Corporal, nice timing!
[ZENNY] Hurry up and take
a warning to them, guys!
[ROBIN] It's too late, they'll
never make it down in time!
But what other
alternatives do we have?
At this rate your fellow
crewmembers are done for.
This whole thing
stinks like dead fish.
What'll we do?
You're a pirate, old man,
think of something.
Come on!
Yeah, great,
maybe I am a pirate,
but this ship is my coffin.
It's stuck in the mountains.
And me... I wouldn't know
which way to sail.
[LUFFY] Then all we have
to do is haul it down, right?
The wind blows
down from the hills!
Prepare to set sail!
[GOATS bleat]
[ROBIN]
Huh?
[ZENNY] What are you
all standing around for?
Remove those support beams!
Ready? One! Two!
Let's go!
[GOATS bleat]
[CORPORAL]
Drop your weapons now! Or else!
[USOPP whimpers]
‐‐[NAMI] Usopp!
‐‐[ZORO] Damn it.
Forget me and
make a break for it!
These guys are planning to kill
us no matter what happens,
so run!
Keep your mouth shut, big nose!
You rotten coward!
Now that we've
captured all of you,
we don't even have to wait
for the captain to land!
Men, take aim!
[USOPP whimpering]
It figures.
You rotten creep!
Big deal, I can handle bullets!
That's great,
but we can't handle them!
[MINCHY laughs]
I get the treasure
of Zenny the Moneylender,
the heads of the
Straw Hat Pirates,
and all the credit after
I send you to hell!
‐‐[GOATS bleat]
‐‐[ZENNY laughing]
[ZENNY]
Drop sail!
[USOPP]
Huh?
No! Impossible!
A pirate ship sailing
down a mountain?
Zenny Pirates, attack!
Hit 'em hard!
Goat man!
[GOATS bleating]
[laughing]
[ZENNY]
How's tricks with you?
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories
go racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[ZORO] Oh, yeah!
I gotta give him more credit!
[CHOPPER]
Admire him later, okay?
[NAMI]
No kidding!
[USOPP] Wouldn't it be
a good idea to hide
since they're after us?
[NAMI] Old man, you better let
me take care of the treasure
for you till things calm down!
[ROBIN]
Naughty girl.
[LUFFY]
If it's something dear to you,
fight to protect it, old man!
On the next One Piece!
"Whereabouts of the
Island Treasure!
Attack of the Zenny Pirates!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!