Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Ha! I don't care what
happens along the way.
Nothing will stop us from
returning to Laboon!
[YORKI] This'll be the
last time we say goodbye!
We're comin' back!
We're your friends.
Nothin'll ever change that!
[LABOON vocalizes]
[YORKI] Hey, Laboon!
Don't go swimmin' off now!
Once we travel the world,
we're comin' right back here!
Just wait for us!
[LUFFY]
"Bink's Brew!
The Song that Connects
the Past with the Present!"
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380A]
Hey, Brook.
You're really amazing
with that sword.
What d'you say?
Think you can teach
me a few tricks?
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380C]
A tornado?
How? It was sunny a second ago!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380B]
Quit yappin' and run away!
This place is cursed! I've
been trying to tell you guys!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380C]
This is a disaster!
These seas are a
complete nightmare!
I just can't keep up!
[YORKI] Well, you know
what I always say:
Bitter seas make for sweet
booze at the end of the day.
Brook! You wanna
play a number for us?
Can't beat good tunes and beer!
You know the song.
I was starting to
think you'd never ask!
All right, here I go!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380D]
Yeah! Make it a good one!
[screams]
Of course. It's a mirror.
I keep forgetting I'm
a skeleton now. Ow, ow.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380B]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Captain, stop it! Lemme down!
Why are you punishing me, too?
[YORKI]
'Cause I don't want you two
fighting over
every little thing!
It's not
"some little thing!"
This lunatic almost
hit me with a stray bullet!
I coulda died!
Yeah, well, you didn't, okay?
And he said he was sorry.
What's done is done.
No point in going
on about it now.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380B]
That hurt!
[YORKI] Good!
That proves you're alive!
[ALL laugh]
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380B]
All right, fair enough!
[BROOK]
Look at the stars.
A sea of lights,
spreading out forever.
I wonder if Laboon is
looking up at the same stars.
What do you think, Captain?
[YORKI]
Hey guys! Come look!
Brook's getting
emotional out here!
I was being sincere!
Don't make fun of me!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380D]
It's the Marines!
What do we do?
[YORKI]
Same thing we always do!
Give 'em hell!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380E]
Damn! Look at that!
Captain Yorki's bounty
went up again!
He's on a roll!
[YORKI]
Eat that!
[BROOK]
Let's celebrate with a song!
♪ [BROOK (SINGING)] Yorki,
Yorki, a bounty on his head, ♪
♪ out of Twin Cape flies the
news the Navy wants his head! ♪
[BROOK humming]
Bad news, men!
There's something wrong
with the captain!
He ain't lookin' so good!
I'm serious!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380E]
A virus?
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380G]
'Fraid so. Everyone stay out.
We've got a dozen men
infected already.
I figure they
must've contracted it
when we passed
through that jungle.
I've never seen anything like
it. None of my treatments work.
We've all gotta
be careful now.
If this plague keeps spreading,
we won't have enough men
to sail this ship.
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380F]
Please hang in there, Captain!
[YORKI] Come on,
don't sound so depressed.
[YORKI coughs]
[YORKI] We're the Rumbar
Pirates, remember?
We bring smiles
to children's faces!
Though I admit,
I've seen better days,
and that goes for the
rest of the ship, too.
[YORKI]
I'm sorry I won't be able
to travel the
Grand Line with you.
We'll have to part ways here.
I'll take this ship,
but I want all of you to
move forward with a new one.
Captain, no.
[YORKI]
We can't risk the infection
spreading any more
than it already has.
We'll drop you off, try
passing through the Calm Belt
and look for help
for the sick crew members.
[YORKI] It'll all
work out somehow, I hope.
I'm sorry, guys.
Give Laboon my regards.
Wipe those tears away.
Stand up straight.
Yes, sir.
[YORKI]
If you stay any longer,
you're gonna end up
as sick as me.
Hurry up and get outta here.
Take care, okay?
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380G]
All right men,
you heard the
Captain's orders.
C'mon.
There's no use crying now.
[YORKI]
Brook?
[BROOK]
Yes.
Give them hope.
I will, my Captain.
I swear! As long as I live,
I will never forget those words!
Hey. Hear that?
I've engraved them in my heart!
Captain. We'll meet
again, so take care!
We may be parting ways now,
but this isn't the end!
So please don't die.
Take off that mask.
Let me see your face.
We'll all sing together
again someday!
[YORKI]
Hey, Brook.
While you're here,
why don't you send me off
with my favorite song?
♪ [BROOK (SONG)]
Gather up all of the crew, ♪
♪ it's time to ship
out Binks' Brew. ♪
♪ Sea wind blows,
to where, who knows? ♪
♪ The waves will be our guide.
♪ O'er across
the ocean's tide. ♪
♪ Rays of sunshine
far and wide... ♪
[BROOK] Yoho!
I took off my pants!
I hope no one saw me!
Yohohohoho!
It's scary outside,
but I'm still having fun!
All alone but I'm
still having fun!
[yells]
Hello!
45 Degrees! Quick,
somebody look!
Oh wait, I'm the
only one here. Yohohoho!
C'mon, Brook, wake up!
Get with the program already!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380I]
Yeah, pal!
Look! We sighted an island!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380J]
It's a summer island!
Check out the beach!
Uh, wait, are you--?
I mean, is this--
is this real? You're alive!
Hurry up, Brook,
what's wrong?
Yeah, we can't get this
thing started without you!
Everyone's here!
How? I'm happy, but how?
You mean you didn't
die after all?
What happened?
You were having a
bad dream, that's all!
Now get over here
and play a song!
I can't believe it!
That really hurt!
That means this isn't
a dream! This is reality!
It was just a
nightmare after all!
Thank goodness--
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380K]
I hope Captain Yorki made it
through the Calm Belt.
You think he'll be okay?
[BROOK] That's a
question for the waves.
All we can do is carry
out his final orders.
We'll sail around the world
until we see Laboon again!
♪ Rise and shine!
Time to wake up! ♪
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380L] Do
you have to do this every day?
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380M]
The winds are too strong!
The sail's gonna tear!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380N]
This is nothing!
We'll sing our way through it!
[RANDOM RUMBAR PIRATE 380O]
Wow, look at this, Brook!
You got yourself a bounty!
Nice job!
[lively piano music]
Hey! What's the problem, Brook?
Why'd you stop the jammin?
Keep going!
I put chopsticks
in my nose for this!
Yohohoho!
Give me a moment, please.
Let's see.
[USOPP and SANJI] I didn't
know you could do that!
[BROOK]
This is a Tone Dial.
I purchased it from a
merchant ship many years ago.
I hear there are many
different kinds of dials,
but this one in
particular has the ability
to record and reproduce sounds.
Ohh, we saw those in Skypeia.
[BROOK] Then you
know how they work.
You see, when
I meet Laboon again,
I want to play this for him,
so it's something
I always keep in my heart.
Though, all things considered,
you might say it's
in my head, as well!
So do you have something
special recorded on it?
[BROOK]
Yes. A song.
It's the last song
performed by my former crew.
Although they're all gone now,
we wanted to leave
a message to Laboon
tho let him know that we were
merry until the bitter end.
May I play it for you now?
Oooh! Yeah, do it!
If Laboon'll like it,
I bet I will, too!
All right.
[BROOK]
Are there any survivors?
Surely a few of us
can still stand.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380M]
We got a couple men left.
But I don't think there's much
hope left for us at this point.
Well, at least we're all
dying together, right?
I guess their weapons
were all poison-tipped.
And our doctor is dead now, too.
When I became a pirate,
I knew I might die on the seas
and I was ready for that.
But I still have
just one regret.
Laboon.
Hey, Brook.
How does that Devil Fruit
of yours work?
[BROOK]
Who knows?
This is my first time dying.
But wait. I have an idea.
If we're going to die anyway,
why don't we sing a song?
[BROOK] I don't know
what will happen
any more than you do,
but if the Revive-Revive Fruit
really does bring me back
to life after I die here,
I will deliver this to him,
without fail.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380P]
The Tone Dial.
[BROOK] I'll take Laboon the
song he and our Captain love.
The song we've all shared
so many times.
And when we meet
at that cape,
he'll know this crew
died without regrets,
and that we kept our promise
to our dear friend.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380S]
That's a great idea!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380Q]
All right, men,
don't you dare die until
we finish this song!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 380M] This is it!
The Rumbar Pirate's
once-in-a-lifetime
performance
for our friend
across the seas!
[lively piano music]
Eh? If this is the
song you're playing,
we can all sing along!
Yeah!
♪ [ALL (SINGING)]
Yohohoho, yohohoho. ♪
♪ Yohohoho, yohohoho.
♪ Gather up all of the crew,
♪ it's time to ship out
Binks' Brew ♪
♪ Sea wind blows,
to where, who knows? ♪
♪ The waves will be our guide
♪ O'er across
the ocean's tide. ♪
♪ Rays of sunshine
far and wide ♪
♪ Birds they sing,
of cheerful things, ♪
♪ in circles passing by
♪ Bid farewell
to weaver's town. ♪
♪ Say so long to port renown
♪ Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off ♪
♪ Cross the gold
and silver seas, ♪
♪ a salty spray
puts us at ease ♪
♪ Day and night,
to our delight, ♪
♪ the voyage never ends
♪ [piano continues]
♪ Gather up all of the crew,
♪ it's time to ship out
Binks' Brew ♪
♪ Pirates we, eternally,
are challenging the sea! ♪
♪ With the waves
to rest our heads, ♪
♪ ship beneath us
as our beds. ♪
♪ Hoisted high upon the mast,
our Jolly Roger flies! ♪
♪ [RUMBAR PIRATES (SONG)]
Somewhere in the endless sky ♪
♪ stormy winds are blowing by
♪ Waves are dancing,
evening comes, ♪
♪ it's time to sound the drums
♪ But steady men
and never fear, ♪
♪ tomorrow's skies
are always clear ♪
♪ So pound your feet
♪ and clap your hands
'til sunny days return ♪
♪ Yohohoho, yohohoho.
♪ [BROOK (SONG)]
Gather up all of the crew, ♪
♪ it's time to ship out
Binks' Brew ♪
♪ Wave goodbye, but don't you
cry, our memories remain ♪
♪ Our days are but
a passing dream, ♪
♪ everlasting though they seem
♪ 'neath the moon, we'll meet
again, the winds our lullaby ♪
♪ [ALL (SONG)]
Gather up all of the crew, ♪
♪ it's time to ship out
Binks' Brew ♪
♪ Sing a song and play along,
for all the oceans wide ♪
♪ After all is
said and done, ♪
♪ you'll end up a skeleton
♪ So spread your tale
♪ from dawn til dusk
upon these foamy seas ♪
♪ [BROOK (SONG)]
Yohohoho, yohohoho. ♪
♪ Yohohoho, yohohoho.
♪ [BROOK (SONG)]
Yohohoho, yohohoho. ♪
♪ Yohohoho, yohohoho.
Well, it would seem
we're down to a quartet.
[BROOK]
A trio.
And a duet.
[BROOK]
A solo.
It isn't right.
Leaving just the accompaniment.
[YORKI] If you want
to join my crew,
all I ask is
that you love music!
[YORKI] Let's hear it
for the Rumbar Pirates!
The crew that brings
a smile to every child!
[ALL cheering]
[YORKI]
Laboon!
Once we travel the world,
we're comin' right back here!
[YORKI]
You just wait for us!
[BROOK] Laboon, thank you
for waiting for us.
I know that 50 years
is a long time.
But please, do you think
you could be patient
for one or two more?
I have my pride as a pirate.
I promised you
I would see you again
after circling the globe.
I intend to keep my word
and return from the
right direction.
My name is Brook.
I have died and then
skeletonized yet still I live.
I am a wanted man.
I have a bounty
of 33 million berries.
And as of today, my life belongs
to you, Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A New Crewmate: The Musician,
Humming Brook!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!