[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
It was somewhere around here.
[NAMI]
Found it!
Good. If things are
going as planned,
Luffy and the others
have recovered the gold
and are heading back
to the ship right now.
Yeah, and we need
to do the same.
I wonder how we're going
to sneak this thing
back across the bay
to the Merry?
Wait! Where's my head?
The waver works just
as well on the Blue Sea, too!
Come on, let's move!
Now grab on, Sanji,
and hold on tight!
Onto you?
I've been truly blessed!
Thank you!
Ah. You've smiled upon me,
fate. Hallelujah!
[NAMI] Yeah, yeah.
Whatever. Just get on already!
With pleasure, Nami! [laughs]
Moron!
I didn't mean it like that! Guh!
[SANJI]
Nami, that love tap was dynamic!
It knocked me off my feet!
Hang on tight, Romeo!
[SANJI yells]
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[USOPP whimpers]
[ZORO] Looks like they
pulled one over on us, guys.
Ya have to hand it to them.
I wish I could eat a fish
that big right now.
How can you think about
food at a time like this?
We almost got killed
opening this thing up!
[OFFICER B] Commander Jonathan
knew you'd show up here
once he realized
you'd stolen the map.
Perceptive.
There's nowhere to run. Give up!
[USOPP] Even with Luffy and
Zoro, we don't stand a chance.
So, do we just wait here
for Nami and Sanji
to come save our bacon?
[ROBIN]
No.
I'm sure that the whole base
knows where we are now.
Reinforcements are
no doubt on their way
and it's only a matter
of time until they arrive.
We need to get out of here.
Yeah! If our gold's not here,
then we just need to go
look for it someplace else!
That's easier said than done!
In case you haven't noticed
those doors are the only way
outta here, and we gotta fight
our way through those
guys to get to 'em!
So, what's the problem?
Come on, you guys!
We're getting out of here!
Not if the men of Navarone
have anything to say about it!
This isn't good!
I think we're done for!
[rumbling]
End of the line, pirate scum!
What the...?
Condoriano?
You came to the vault,
just as I predicted you would.
And just who the hell are you?
And who gave you permission
to open those doors?
[SHEPHERD]
Who am I?
I'm a Special Inspector from HQ!
The name's Major Shepherd!
Your commander gave
me and my mobile unit
permission to open those doors!
We'll take it from here.
You and your men
aren't needed anymore!
[OFFICER B grunts]
Hey, wait... Don't I know you?
Oh! You were the guy locked up
in jail with Usopp and Zoro!
What are you doin'
bossin' these guys around?
--[SHEPHERD growls]
--[USOPP] Yo, Condoriano!
How'd you manage to escape?
[SHEPHERD growls]
You're looking well.
I can't tell you how much I've
been looking forward to this.
Thanks to you,
I've dealt with humiliation,
incarceration,
and being called Condoriano!
You'll rue the day
you crossed me!
You're all going to pay!
[OFFICER B]
Major Shepherd!
What? Can't you see
I'm talking here?
You're gonna need some more men.
Trust me, I say this
from experience.
Just don't
underestimate them, Major.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
We're elite forces,
not G8 nincompoops like you
who let pirates run
circles around them!
[SHEPHERD] I'm going to
take down the Straw Hats!
So, unless you want
a court-martial, stand down!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
[SHEPHERD]
Hm.
Are you done yet?
[SHEPHERD] Yes, just like your
pathetic lives are about to be!
You! Bring my new toy!
Sir!
[SHEPHERD cackles]
Say hello to the latest,
state-of-the-art bazooka:
the Eagle Launcher!
It's as deadly as its
namesake, I assure you!
Plus, it packs as much punch
as a warship's main cannon!
[MARINES yelping]
[USOPP]
What?
Is that supposed to
impress me or something?
[LUFFY]
I'm not scared! Bring it!
You asked for it, Straw Hat!
Die!
Nice shot, Condoriano!
[MEMBER A]
Major...
...you have it backwards!
Oh, yes, I see.
[MARINES]
Ass!
Shut up! I'll get
them this time!
[ZORO, LUFFY, USOPP grunting]
[SHEPHERD grunts]
[MARINES shouting]
No!
[MARINES continue shouting]
No! Don't pull that trigger!
[SHEPHERD screams]
[USOPP]
Condoriano is such a blast.
[ZORO]
Why did he come here again?
He and his special mobile unit
weren't very impressive.
[ROBIN]
Well, then? Shall we go?
Yeah, and find our gold!
[LUFFY laughing]
[USOPP]
Hey! Wait up, you guys!
[SHEPHERD] Curse you,
Straw Hats! I'll get you!
[USOPP]
Oops! My bad, Condoriano!
After them, men! Come on!
So. where do you
think our gold's at?
How should I know?
[NAMI] Security's tighter
than I thought.
[SANJI] I'm all alone with Nami
on a romantic night.
This is so darn great,
isn't it, Nami?
Sanji...
So darn wonderful!
Sanji!
So darn fantastic!
And so darn incredible!
[thud]
[NAMI]
And you're so darn loud! Quiet!
This can only mean
that those Marines
think we're still inside
the base somewhere, but...
Why aren't those ships moving?
It just doesn't make sense.
[ROBIN] We need to find
someplace safe to hole up
and rethink our plan.
[USOPP] Is there even such
a thing as a safe place here?
[LUFFY] Yeah! That kitchen
where me and Sanji were at!
[ZORO] The one where all
the Marines eat? Get real!
[USOPP]
Yeah! We'd be crazy to go there!
Then again, the enemy might
think the same thing
and not bother to
look for us there.
Right! It's decided.
We're getting some food.
[USOPP, ZORO]
No, we're not!
[CHOPPER]
There's nothing to worry about!
I'm a full-fledged pirate!
And pirates don't get scared,
even when they're left in
a spooky, abandoned dock
all by themselves.
--[engine rumbles]
--[NAMI] Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
Nami! Sanji! Thank goodness!
Um, I mean, I didn't get scared
guarding the ship all by myself!
Luffy and the others
aren't back?
[CHOPPER] No!
I've been alone all this time!
I wonder where they are?
Something must have
happened to 'em.
And the gold, too?
I'm gonna go look! 'Kay?
Date with Nami part two!
[CHOPPER]
Alone again...
[NAMI]
Sanji, stay here.
I need you on the ship.
[engine rumbles]
[NAMI] As I recall, that vault
was somewhere down this slope.
[NAMI]
Huh?
Oh, no.
The Straw Hats fled
into the mountains!
I want these hills scoured!
Pick up the pace, men!
Double-time it!
[MEMBER A]
Are you all right, sir?
Darn it, I almost
had those pirates!
Stupid instruction manual.
Still, finding an empty vault
doesn't necessarily mean
they've given up!
In fact, I'm sure they won't!
And that means we still
have a decent chance! Heh.
[NAMI gasps]
Empty?
I knew it was possible they
might spring the first trap,
but I've already
got another one set.
I always have
a back-up plan! [laughs]
[NAMI]
Wait! The vault was a trap?
If the gold wasn't in there,
where could it be?
[LUFFY] Hmm. Coulda sworn
it was around here somewhere.
[USOPP] Wait. You mean
this isn't the right place?
I dunno. I can't tell.
You can't? But weren't you and
Sanji here just a few hours ago?
According to this map,
we're in the medical ward.
Shh! I think hear
someone up ahead!
[USOPP hums]
[KOBATO] Dad, please listen
to me! You have to take it!
[MECHAO] I don't care if you are
my daughter! That stuff's nasty!
[KOBATO]
It's medicine, Dad!
Those voices...
It's that doctor
who acted as our hostage.
And the old man!
So, the gold wasn't
on your ship?
[ROBIN]
Or in the vault.
[USOPP] It's wild that you two
are father and daughter.
Say, are you sick or
something, old man?
Let's just say there's
nothin' wrong with me
that a nip from
the bottle won't cure!
The stuff in this bottle's
all the medicine I need!
Ugh! Dad!
You know there's no smoking
or drinking in the medical ward!
[MECHAO]
Come on! Just one drink!
--[KOBATO] No!
--Why do you have
to be so stubborn?
Come on, old man. You really
need to listen to your daughter.
I-I mean your doctor.
[MECHAO]
You're lecturing me?
The same guys
whose hides I saved,
but instead of escaping, they
come waltzing right back here?
Oh, that's rich!
Is that dad-blasted gold really
that important to you guys?
Of course it is, old repair guy!
We are pirates after all!
[KOBATO]
Think about it, Dad.
Would you walk away from that
much gold if it was yours?
I'm sure they must have
worked really hard for it.
You just stay out
of this, Kobato!
We were saving that gold.
Saving?
[USOPP] Yeah. We were gonna
use it to hire a shipwright
to make major repairs
to The Going Merry,
like you said we should.
[MECHAO] Hah! Like I'd believe
a bunch of pirates!
Fine! You don't
have to believe us!
But we are going
to fix the Merry up!
I don't care what
you believe, you old coot!
Coot?!
[KOBATO]
Dad, I believe him.
[MECHAO, USOPP]
Huh?
It isn't just their ship.
[inaudible]
[KOBATO]
It's also their home.
Home? Yeah.
Well, there it is!
It's not the quickest
way to get around,
but there usually aren't
any guards up that way.
That path'll take you
right up into the mountains.
It looks more like a sheer cliff
than it does a path!
[LUFFY]
All right then!
Let's go get our gold!
Thanks, old repair guy!
Good luck!
Well, off we go.
Thanks again for the help!
See ya!
Hold up!
Uh, huh?
Our commander's hobby
is fishin', ya see.
Yeah. That figures.
Who else would have
a big fish painting
like the one we
saw in the vault?
He's found the perfect bait
to reel you guys
in with: your gold!
Like a good fisherman,
he's probably got it dangling
where you can see it
in plain sight.
[USOPP]
In plain sight... Think so, huh?
[LUFFY]
You coming?!
Uh, yeah!
Now! Get outta here! Go!
'Kay! See ya!
Hey, wait up, guys!
[MECHAO] Even if they somehow
manage to get their gold back
and escape,
Navarone'll be in trouble.
Yep, I bet the brass'll
finally shut us down.
I must be crazy.
[ROBIN]
Too bad we didn't have time
to come up with
a plan back there.
[USOPP] So, what are
we supposed to do now?
Just wander around aimlessly
until we find the gold?
[grunts]
Hey, what is it?
Quiet. I thought
I heard something.
Then again, maybe not.
[ROBIN]
No. I hear it, too.
[rumbling]
[USOPP panting]
Something's coming!
[USOPP]
Uh...
The waver!
And Nami! Uh...
[NAMI] I see. And then
you ran into Dr. Kobato.
Mm. Unfortunately,
we still don't have any clue
about where the gold is.
[yawns]
I'm gettin' sleepy.
Dawn's gonna be here
before we know it
and it'll be a lot harder
to sneak around. We need a plan.
Are there any other
storage vaults here?
Even if there are more,
they could just be bait
to lead us into another trap.
Hey, wait, that reminds me of
something the old man told me.
He said something about "bait."
[NAMI] Huh? What do
ya mean "something?"
"Hiding bait in plain sight,"
I think that was it. Hmm.
[NAMI]
Usopp, that's it!
Huh? What's it?
[NAMI] Well, the bait's
obviously the gold.
If it isn't locked away, then
it's somewhere we can see it.
[LUFFY yawns]
"In plain sight."
[NAMI] And what if
"in plain sight" meant
"in plain sight" of
a crafty fisherman?
[ROBIN]
Oh! Nice thinking!
[ZORO]
What do ya mean?
[ROBIN]
It's simple.
Really, who's the person
dangling our gold as bait
to catch us right now?
You mean the commander
of this place?
[NAMI] Right!
The commander is the fisherman!
And if the bait really is in
plain sight of the fisherman,
then that means
there's only one place
where our gold could be kept.
You don't mean--
[NAMI]
Yep! That's right!
[thud]
Hey, what gives?
You did say that you knew
where the commander's
office was, right?
So, take me there!
Uh, okay.
[NAMI]
All right, Luffy and I will go.
Robin, you and the others
get back to the old dock.
Chopper and Sanji
will be waiting for you.
[ROBIN]
Want any back-up?
[NAMI] No. The waver
can only hold two people.
We're gonna get spotted anyway,
so stealth isn't
an issue anymore.
[NAMI] I'm gonna run
this baby at full throttle!
You ready, Luffy?
Yeah! Anytime you are!
[NAMI grunts]
Then hold on!
[MARINE F]
Huh? The pirates!
[NAMI]
Where is it?
[LUFFY]
It's, uh...
Hurry up and find it!
U-Up there!
[NAMI]
Where exactly?!
[MARINE G]
Stop 'em!
[LUFFY]
That's it!
Hold on!
[gasps]
[JONATHAN] I've got to
hand it to you, Straw Hat!
You really know how
to make an entrance! Bravo!
That guy, he's the commander?
Yep! That's the old
fortress guy!
[JONATHAN] That contraption
of yours is incredible!
Just where in the
world did you get it?
[LUFFY] It's called a waver,
and it's not from this world!
It's from the sky
and Nami's the only person
who knows how to drive it!
Don't tell him!
Oh, right. Sorry.
[JONATHAN]
You're one of the few members
of the crew I haven't met,
Miss, so, welcome.
You Straw Hats have
really impressed me.
You're brave, perceptive, and
bold, which I greatly admire,
but you're pirates
and outlaws nonetheless.
What a shame.
I'm sorry we couldn't have met
under happier circumstances.
I'm afraid there won't
be any hungry soldiers
coming to save you
this time, Luffy.
Hang on a minute!
Shouldn't a fisherman let
his prey see the bait at least?
[JONATHAN]
Hm?
[NAMI]
Where's the gold?
Can't we see it one last time
before you haul us away?
It's somewhere
in this room, right?
[JONATHAN]
Yes, it's right there.
It's out in plain sight?!
Whoa! There it is! Our gold!
Nami, we finally found it!
Hey! It's not fake, is it?
Oh, no.
It's the genuine article.
You can check for
yourself if you'd like.
I will! Thank you!
Wait!
[LUFFY]
It's real!
This is our gold, all right!
There's no doubt about it!
I guess we can be going now!
Hey, sorry about the doors,
old fortress guy!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat.
I can't let you just
take the bait and run.
[JONATHAN]
Arrest them, and please
try not to harm the young lady.
Oh, thank you.
[JONATHAN]
Take Straw Hat first.
Okay, fine! Wanna fight?
I'll kick all your butts!
Not another one
of those stupid nets.
The ones that make me weak...
Sea Prism Stone!
[MARINE H]
We got 'em, sir!
Excellent work, men.
Now then...
[NAMI]
Not good! What do I do?
Come on, think!
Wait, that might work.
--[clink]
--[JONATHAN] Hmm?
Rain Tempo Sprinkler!
[MARINES grunting]
[NAMI]
Cool Ball!
Uh... It's cold.
[NAMI]
Heat Ball!
It's warm.
I did it!
[MARINE I]
What the--?
[MARINE J]
A cloud?
[NAMI] Today's forecast
calls for clear skies
and a zero percent
chance of rain,
but cumulonimbus clouds may
suddenly develop in some areas!
Watch out for lightning strikes!
I've had quite enough
of your parlor tricks, Miss.
Thunderbolt Tempo!
[lightning cracks]
[MARINES screaming]
Luffy!
[JONATHAN groans]
[NAMI]
Luffy!
[LUFFY groans]
[NAMI]
Snap out of it!
Hey, thanks, Nami.
Get the gold and get on! Hurry!
[JONATHAN] Even if the bait
gets stolen from the hook,
there's more than
one way to catch a fish.
[JONATHAN] All a fisherman
needs to do is be patient.
Luffy! Do you see the Merry
out there anywhere?
It's so dark.
I can't see anything!
Nami, be careful!
They're gonna spot us!
[NAMI laughs] You know, it
sorta does look like a warship!
Hmm, hm. It's them!
Hey! Luffy! Nami! Over here!
[SANJI] Nami! You're back!
Are you all right?
[SHEPHERD] So, somehow
you allow the Straw Hats
to escape from
your very own office,
and with their gold, too.
What a setback.
I'd hate for that to be
on my record. [chuckles]
[JONATHAN] Hmph. The Straw Hats
haven't escaped yet,
nor will they
on my watch, Major.
I assure you.
After losing them
umpteen times already?
Heh, don't make me laugh!
Since you can't
catch them yourself,
why don't you sit back
and let me? What do you say?
Are there any bazookas
involved this time?
What happened earlier
was just a minor complication!
My special pirate subjugation
squad wasn't with me
because they were
setting another trap!
Really! In that case,
I think I will sit back
and watch your men in action.
[SHEPHERD]
Shepherd to Pinepeak!
You should almost be in position
at the Sea Gate, so listen up!
Those pirates should
be arriving shortly!
The minute you see them,
blow them out of the water!
Got it?
Aye-aye, major sir!
Captain! We're about
to reach the ambush point, sir!
Good! We can't let the
pirate ship slip past us!
All cannons are to
open fire once it's spotted!
Catching them will be as easy
as shooting fish in a barrel.
A fisherman like you should
appreciate that analogy.
Place a pole in--
Could you please not
touch that pole, Major?
[SHEPHERD]
Ow!
I would like to ask you
something about your plan.
Sure, I'd be more than
happy to answer any questions
about how to catch pirates.
This special pirate
subjugation squad of yours
was on the Pinepeak,
is that correct?
Who's that on the
other ship following 'em?
[SHEPHERD]
Other ship? What are you--? Ugh!
That vessel isn't one
of Navarone's warships.
In fact, the more I look at it,
I don't think it's
a warship at all.
Then... what is it?
[MARINE L] Captain! A warship
is closing in on us, sir!
Well, it appears
to be a warship.
A Navarone warship? And what
do you mean by "looks like one"?
Well, I'm not quite sure
how to explain it.
[MARINE M]
It's gonna smash into us!
[MARINE N]
Stop! Look out!
Full speed ahead, Merry! Yeah!
Wh-What the--?
Thank you for showing us
where the currents are!
We couldn't have made it
this far without you!
We owe ya one!
Thanks, you guys!
Quick! We can't let them escape!
We've got bigger problems!
[CAPTAIN]
Huh?
[SHEPHERD]
No!
I can't believe they used the
Pinepeak to help their escape!
Curse those Straw Hats!
Don't worry,
they haven't escaped yet.
In fact, they're about to
get caught in a very big net.
A net?
Every day at 9AM,
the waters of Navarone
bare their fangs.
It's a trap that
Mother Nature provides,
one in which
escape is impossible.
[LUFFY]
Woo-hoo, we're finally free!
And we finally got our gold!
Yay, we did it!
Yeah! Let's get to
the Sea Gate and get out!
--Sure thing!
-- [SANJI] Yeah!
A future lies
before us waiting
to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running,
and running,
traveling along
an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[JONATHAN] Attention,
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew!
This is Commander Jonathan!
You've fought valiantly
against some of the
toughest Marines in the service,
not to mention one of the
toughest fortresses!
You've done admirably,
but this is the end!
It's time to give it up
and surrender, Straw Hats!
[USOPP]
We still have a chance!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Farewell, Marine Fortress!
The Last Battle for Escape!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!