[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] At God's Shrine,
Luffy and Nami found themselves
unable to reach Eneru's ark.
[NAMI] He's too far from
the top of the beanstalk.
What can we do?
How can we get to him?
There must be a way!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile,
Eneru had finally
located the Golden Bell.
So this is it.
Splendid!
At last!
The grand belfry that
was once the pride
of the legendary
city of Shandora!
[NARRATOR] Devising a plan,
Nami sent a message
down to Usopp and
the rest of the crew.
[AISA]
Hey, look!
There's something written on it!
"Cut down this beanstalk
and make sure it falls
towards the West."
[NARRATOR] But, Eneru's final
attack was already bearing down
upon them!
[ENERU] I've accomplished
all of my objectives but one.
So now...
...it's time I destroyed
this pathetic land
and the Cumuloregalis
Clouds it rests on,
and set off for
the Endless Vearth.
[ZORO yells]
[WYPER]
Reject!
Now fall, Giant Jack! Fall!
This is it! Get on, Luffy!
Gun it! Go! Now!
[NAMI]
Okay!
[NAMI yells]
[ENERU laughs]
That you should even
try to reach me now
is insolent far beyond
the point of stupidity!
Now pay for your folly!
Mamaragan!
[LUFFY]
"Miracle on Skypiea!
The Love Song
Heard in the Clouds!"
[CITIZEN A]
Upper Yard is crumbling.
Luffy! Nami!
[NAMI]
You know...
I think he's trying to make sure
you don't get near him again!
Too bad! He's mine!
He's destroying the cloud
cover over the ruins!
He plans to destroy
the ground itself!
[AISA] But Wyper's lying
on the ground down there!
[USOPP]
So is Zoro! That bastard!
The ruins...
[WYPER]
It won't work, Eneru.
This city will
never fall to you.
[AISA gasps]
Wyper!
[WYPER]
This land of Shandora
was home to a proud
race of warriors.
This ancient city preserves
and protects their memory.
What's more, their memory
protects this city.
That mighty power
will never fall to you.
No matter how
much forest you burn.
[USOPP, AISA gasp]
This land won't fall!
[AISA yells]
No! Wyper!
--[ROBIN] It's too dangerous!
--Ah! Let me go! Wyper!
[yells]
Eh?
I can still hear the little
fools whining down below.
[laughs]
[USOPP whimpering]
[yells]
[NAMI yells]
[GROUP gasps]
[GAN FALL]
The Vearth. Of course!
[SHANDORAN A]
It didn't fall!
Upper Yard is still standing!
Its power is unbelievable!
[GAN FALL]
It must be.
The Vearth is so powerful.
What fools we've been!
It was never something
to be fought over!
We've spilled so much blood.
And lost so many
countless lives.
How could we be so
blind for 400 years?
[AISA]
Wyper!
[USOPP gasps] Get outta there!
The beanstalk's coming down!
Come on, this way,
let's move it! Move it!
Now go!
[LUFFY grunting]
[WYPER grunts]
Go! Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
Here I come, Eneru!
Those fools never learn.
[LUFFY]
Give back the Golden Bell!
Right now!
[ENERU]
That's enough!
It's ready!
Now disappear along
with this land!
[LUFFY growling]
Raigo!
[engine running]
Thanks for your help.
It won't be for nothing!
[LUFFY, NAMI yell]
[NAMI]
Luffy! Wait!
The ark's over there!
[NAMI yells]
No! Don't do it, please!
[NAMI] The air currents and
lightning discharges in there
could kill even you!
[ENERU] What do you think
you can do against
this kind of power?
Man of rubber!
[laughing]
[LUFFY yelling]
[NAMI gasps]
[ENERU laughing]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[yelling]
...Fireworks!
Golden Peony!
[yelling]
[LUFFY] You with your
thunder and lightning!
We made it all the
way to sky island,
and you had to come along
and ruin the weather!
You electrical freak!
Uh, what's with all the
crazy lightning bolts?
[ENERU]
I forgot!
That gold ball stuck on his
arm is a natural conductor!
Well then.
I'll just drop it before you
can discharge the electricity!
[ENERU]
Let everything be destroyed!
[WHITE BERET A]
Captain McKinley!
Please stop it!
This is God's land!
It is pointless!
[MCKINLEY]
I don't care if it's pointless.
It's the only thing people
can do when they're caught
between life and death.
Don't you see?
We've abandoned our home
and chosen to live.
We can't go back.
Nor can we go forward.
Praying.
Is all that we can do.
[GAN FALL]
The song of the island.
When our ears hear that again,
the war will have ended.
[CONIS]
I wonder...
Are we all doomed?
Maybe, if I'd had the courage
to stand up to Eneru...
...our friends would have
been spared all this.
Oh, Suu...
[SUU]
Suu?
Does God exist?
If He does...
...why doesn't he save us?
[SUU]
Suu.
[CONIS crying]
Please. If You do exist...
...You must protect those
brave people and keep them safe!
Please! Give us a miracle!
Protect this land, Lord God!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
Clear the sky!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
Clear the sky!
[NAMI gasps]
That mass of thunderclouds
has vanished!
[CITIZEN B]
What could've happened?
[MCKINLEY gasps]
[LUFFY yelling]
[USOPP gasps]
Yeah! It's him, Luffy!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah!
Now ring it, Straw Hat!
Light the fire of Shandora!
Go, Luffy! Go, Luffy!
[GAN FALL]
Let me hear it, Straw Hat!
The song of the island!
[LUFFY yelling]
You destroyed my Raigo!
Insolent Blue Sea ape!
You're next!
I'll ring you along
with the bell!
[ENERU]
Impudent fool!
Two hundred million volt...
[grunting]
...Amaru!
What the hell is that?
[ENERU]
Ring the bell?
Is that what you said?
You must be one of
those fools who believes
in the old legend
that when the bell rings,
it will mean the end of the war
between Skypiea and Shandora!
I am God!
[LUFFY growls]
[NAMI gasps]
I don't care how strong you are.
You're still just
a Paramecia type!
You could never match
the might of my Logia power
no matter how hard you try!
No matter what you might do!
That won't work on me!
And quit calling yourself God!
What kind of god destroys
everything and saves nothing?
Fake!
[LUFFY grunts, yells]
Well done, rubber man,
that was very agile of you.
You grabbed it before
you could be impaled.
Luffy!
[ENERU laughs]
But what will you do now?
You have nowhere to run!
The pull of the
golden ball on your arm
will draw you deeper and
deeper onto my trident!
And if you should let go,
you'll fall to your death below!
[LUFFY yelling]
I admit I'm impressed
you made it this far.
But this is the end
for you, boy.
And this land. Everything!
I can easily create
another Raigo!
[LUFFY grunting]
[CONIS] It's the duty of every
citizen here on the Island.
I'm so very sorry!
[LUFFY grunting]
[AISA] Will the sky islands
really be destroyed?
[LUFFY grunting]
So you prefer to fall, do you?
[laughing]
[NAMI gasps]
Luffy, no!
Nami. Get out of the way, hurry!
[LUFFY yelling]
What's this?
You should never mess
with me, earlobes!
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Are you going to try
that same old trick again?
I'll keep trying
till the bell rings!
This time I'll skewer you, fool!
[LUFFY]
...Golden Rifle!
[yells]
[ENERU]
Too fast!
[ENERU yelling]
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY yelling]
[KALGARA] When you finally
return, what will you think
when you see we're gone?
Hold on a little longer!
I'll let you know
that we're still here!
[KALGARA]
Noland!
Light the Fire of Shandora!
[CHIEFTAIN]
The war in the sky
began 400 years ago.
I didn't think I'd
live to see this moment.
[GAN FALL]
Yes. The Holy Land...
...will sing once more.
Someday, it will.
[NOLAND]
Six years ago,
on the island of Jaya
in the Grand Line,
I saw the City of Gold!
The City of Gold does exist!
Not one person in history
has ever disproven, heh,
the existence of sky island.
I'm a romantic! Just like you!
[LUFFY]
Let it ring!
Hey, Pops!
Can you hear it?
The City of Gold is here!
For 400 years,
the City of Gold...
[bell rings]
...has been in the sky!
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[CRICKET]
I can hear the bell.
Now this is romance!
I'd thought the story
was just a fairy tale
and I'd almost forgotten it.
But there's only one
bell in the world
that sounds like that!
The City of Gold was in the sky!
My ancestor, Noland,
wasn't a liar!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Battle Ends!
Proud Fantasia Echoes Far!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!