[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[WARRIOR A]
Another warrior has died.
[WARRIOR B] And there was
that terrible earthquake.
[WARRIOR C]
You are the evil spirits!
Now we will punish you!
[SAILOR Z]
This wasn't the agreement!
--[SAILOR AA] Look out!
--[SAILOR Z, SAILER BB] Stop!
[WARRIOR C]
Seto! Move aside!
[WARRIOR D]
What's the meaning of this?
[SETO]
This is pathetic.
The Shandoran warriors
I know and look up to...
They show a lot more
pride than you do.
Kid...
[LUFFY] "Free from the Spell!
The Great Warrior Sheds Tears!"
[KALGARA]
It won't be long now.
You should prepare yourself
for when the sun sets.
That's when the
lives of your men...
...will be an offering...
...unto the gods.
[grunting]
Dammit!
[KALGARA chuckles]
My...
The earth certainly did
swallow you up skillfully.
It was truly an act of god!
The fact that you're still alive
is what's hardest to believe!
[NOLAND yelling]
[KALGARA]
Hm?
The ground!
[NOLAND grunts]
[NOLAND yelling]
[CLERIC]
Prepare for the ceremony!
Bring every sacrifice
to the altar!
[SAILOR CC]
Please, wait a little longer!
[SAILOR DD] The commodore'll
be back in a few more hours!
Give us more time! Please!
[SAILOR EE]
Why are they doing this to us?
[KALGARA]
The sun is setting.
The ceremony must
be starting soon.
[NOLAND panting]
[KALGARA]
How disgusting.
Is this the wreck of a man
who defied the gods?
[NOLAND] What exactly
are you so afraid of?
Afraid?
[NOLAND]
You fear what you do not know!
And you trade innocent people's
lives for false consolations!
[KALGARA]
What are you saying?
Sacrifices...
...are pointless deaths!
[KALGARA growling]
[NOLAND grunts]
[KALGARA] We have lived
this way for centuries!
[NOLAND]
That doesn't make it right!
[KALGARA]
Silence!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
[NOLAND] The lives of your
citizens are more precious
than gods.
[grunts]
They're real people!
[tribal drums]
[CLERIC] Take the
sacrifices to the altar!
Burn them at the stake and
send them to the Heavens!
[SAILORS yelling]
[SAILOR AA] Commodore!
Don't let them burn us!
[SAILORS yelling]
[NOLAND] You can send an
innocent girl to her death.
And have no remorse, so I doubt
you'd understand, but try.
What you're doing
is less than human!
Don't you see that?
[KALGARA]
No remorse, you say.
The innocent girl you speak of.
She was my daughter!
What?
You would tell your own
daughter to give up her life?
You're very wrong.
And you don't understand.
There is so much power
in the words of our gods.
And the people must obey.
The gods will not
hear our pleas!
Even if we ask them
to spare our children.
[SOUTHBIRDS call]
[KALGARA]
It's smaller than the last one.
It must be one of
Kashi's children!
The gods' blood has come
to pass judgment on you!
[NOLAND]
Judgment my ass!
[SNAKE hissing]
[NOLAND]
Let me explain.
Tree Fever is a plague.
A plague that wiped out
hundreds of thousands of lives
in my own village years ago
and now it is ravaging yours.
But it's gone.
No one's died in decades
as a result of this
awful disease. No one!
And do you know why?
Because we discovered
a cure for it!
I'm holding in my hand
bark from the Cona tree.
This is the cure!
I only need to extract
the Conine from it!
If I can bring this
back to your people,
I can save all of their lives!
But you insist on
keeping countless masses
from their cure.
Do you realize how
many innocent victims
have already perished
because of you?
So I stand by what I said.
Your ceremonies are
an insult to my people.
You're too busy
blindly trampling over
great advancements to see how
much it could benefit you!
[SNAKE hisses]
I may die in judgment,
or I may die in an accident.
At least I'll stay
true to my people.
How will your village die,
by ignorance?
Is the pain you cause
your people worth it
to be true to your Gods?
[SNAKE hisses]
This is a man who
speaks earnest words.
I recognize that.
[KALGARA]
Answer this.
What is this thing?
What have I killed?
--[NOLAND] A snake.
--[KALGARA] No!
You're wrong!
I just broke one
of our commandments!
I just killed a precious god!
A god! Do you understand me?
But all you can see is a snake!
And you see our deadly curse
as some curable disease!
Tell me!
Can you save our village?
[NOLAND]
I can.
[SAILORS laughing, chattering]
[BABY SNAKE hisses]
[SAILOR FF]
A snake!
Wait just a minute.
Hey! Kalgara! Look at this!
[BABY SNAKE hisses]
What a shock.
I didn't realize that
snake had a grandchild.
"That snake," huh?
[laughs]
A snake!
[laughing]
[SAILORS]
Huh?
[SAILOR II]
Would you look at that?
It doesn't make any sense.
[SAILOR JJ] Those two were
trying' to kill each other
not too long ago.
Now they're laughing
together like good friends.
[WARRIOR E] Usually Kalgara
isn't very friendly
with the villagers either.
[laughing continues]
[WARRIOR E] I've never seen
him smile like that before.
[KALGARA]
All right, follow me.
We climb down here.
[NOLAND]
Climb down?
[bell rings]
[KALGARA chuckles]
That... ringing.
Kalgara.
Where is that beautiful
ringing coming from?
[KALGARA]
Follow me and I will show you.
[bell rings]
[SOUTHBIRDS call]
[ringing continues]
Ah...!
[SAILORS]
[ringing continues]
They're here!
[KALGARA] You're speechless.
I'm not surprised.
This is Shandora.
And we're the survivors
of this golden city.
[NOLAND]
A city of gold.
It's like I'm dreaming!
It's a city... full of treasure!
There's gold everywhere!
[cheering]
[NOLAND]
Hey!
Wait! Everyone stop!
[KALGARA]
It's all right.
Load up your ship with
all the treasure you can.
Just leave the golden bell.
[SAILORS]
Huh?
Seto!
Show these sailors where
they can find the treasure.
Right!
Kalgara, are you sure?
All the villagers here
agree that this is right.
It is a gift.
We want to thank you
for saving our tribe
from that terrible disease.
--This is nothing at all.
--[SAILORS yell]
[SAILOR LL] You're so
generous, Great Warrior!
[NOLAND]
But... I don't understand.
Haven't your people been working
hard to protect this city?
That's true.
We have worked
hard to protect it.
Although...
It's not necessarily
the treasure we guard.
Come!
Let me show you.
[SAILORS]
Ah...!
[cheering]
[KALGARA] The only thing
we guard is this stone.
[NOLAND]
Ah.
Look at that writing.
What's it mean?
[KALGARA]
We don't know.
It is a Poneglyph: writings
left over from ancient history.
[NOLAND] You mean this isn't
something that was written
by your ancestors?
There is only one
thing we know for sure.
That the city of Shandora
fought and fell trying
to protect this stone,
and we will, too.
As descendants, we feel
it is our duty to continue
to protect it with
the same resolve.
This stone now represents
proof that our ancestors
not only fought a
vicious fight, but survived.
And we revere our ancestors
as we would our gods.
Still, when I heard
the bell ringing before,
I had no idea it
would be this huge.
[KALGARA] The bell's rings
have words to them.
[NOLAND]
Words?
[KALGARA]
Yes.
It speaks so that the
spirits of our ancestors
who have passed can
still return to this land
at any time
without getting lost.
We continue to ring the bell
as if to shout to them,
"We are here!" "Come home!"
"We are waiting for you!"
And the sound.
The sound itself proclaims
the glory of Shandora.
Making its existence known
to the ends of the sea!
It shouts:
"We will never run or hide!"
Because of this, we have
given the grand bell a name.
We call it the
"Fire of Shandora."
Makes sense.
That explains
the majestic sound!
You think so?
Yeah!
It was this fire
that reached out to us
and helped us arrive here.
I heard the ringing
during a terrible storm.
I heard it clearly when it
shouldn't have been audible
at all.
[BABY SNAKE hisses]
You like the bell's ringing too?
Yeah, I bet you do.
I bet someday,
you'll grow up just like
that other giant snake.
[BABY SNAKE hisses]
[KALGARA laughs]
But probably not for
another hundred years!
[ALL laughing]
[KALGARA] Noland,
I invite you to stay here.
Please.
It's been 400 years
since Shandora fell.
And you're the first
guests we've had,
so I want to welcome you.
Won't you accept my offer?
[NOLAND]
Thank you, Kalgara.
And with your permission I
would also love the opportunity
to collect some
plants from the forest
and see this plague
all the way through.
[SAILOR OO]
Commodore!
[NOLAND]
Hold on, now.
What's with the clothes?
[SAILOR LL]
We found an Eternal Compass!
[SAILOR OO]
And look at this map, Commodore!
Just look!
[KALGARA] We took these items
from those who intruded upon us.
[SAILOR OO]
Is that a map of this island?
[KALGARA]
Yes.
That skull shape is
definitely our island.
The name "Shandora" means
"the skull's right eye."
The name refers to
the city's location.
Right here.
[door opens]
[DOCTOR]
Well, take care!
And make sure she
gets plenty of rest, okay?
I will, thanks! G'bye doctor!
[VILLAGER A]
Hey, look, everyone!
Noland brought us
some exotic crops!
[NOLAND] I have a greenhouse
on our ship with all kinds
of plant samples.
I'll leave some seeds and
sprouts here that are suited
for your soil.
Does it taste good?
[NOLAND]
Very!
And it's full of nutrients!
[laughing, chattering]
[KALGARA laughing]
[NOLAND laughing]
[KALGARA, NOLAND laughing]
[SAILOR JJ]
All right!
Time to begin another
day of hard work!
[SAILOR II]
Hard work doing what?
Having a campfire party?
[SAILORS laughing]
But why?
Why would the doctor
and the others do this?
[crying]
[WARRIOR A]
Chief!
Noland and the
others are coming!
[ELDER] You are not to say
anything about last night!
Is that clear?
They said they are going
to set sail in a few days.
So until then,
don't do anything rash.
Do you hear me?
Fine, then. Our people will
never understand each other.
They've only done harm.
[WARRIOR G] I don't care
how good his medicine is.
He's still a god killer!
Do these people think
they can just show up here
and stomp all over our history?
They'll pay!
Silence!
We must endure it, and we must
wait quietly for them to leave.
[WARRIOR I]
They're here!
Hello, everyone.
I'm looking for Kalgara.
[doors closing]
[NOLAND] Why is everyone
acting so cold all of a sudden?
And where's Kalgara?
Turn around and leave now.
You're not welcome.
You're outsiders.
Kalgara doesn't want
to see you anymore.
Seto, stop!
When are you going
to leave, anyway?
Answer me!
[SAILOR II]
What's going on?
It seems like they
suddenly hate us.
Now, hold on!
You can't just start
acting like this!
It's not fair!
Let it go.
[NOLAND]
Let's continue our work.
We still have some
forest to inspect.
[WARRIOR F]
There you are, Kalgara!
Noland has been looking for you!
[KALGARA]
I know he has.
I have no desire
to speak to him.
If I see him right now,
I'm afraid I might kill him.
[KALGARA growls]
[SAILOR GG]
That's strange.
The bell didn't ring today.
[SAILOR HH]
Yeah.
It's the first time that's
happened in the month
that we've been here.
[DOCTOR]
Commodore?
[NOLAND] I'll be done exploring
the forest in two days.
Uh... Right.
[NOLAND] Let everyone know
we set sail in three days.
Tell them that this is their
last chance to enjoy dry land
for awhile.
Commodore,
to tell you the truth,
I can't wait to get
off this insane island.
Only after we've
finished our duties.
Goodnight.
[KALGARA]
You should stay here, Noland!
I have an idea!
Why don't you make
Mousse your wife?
[KALGARA, NOLAND laugh]
[NOLAND]
Don't be silly!
I have a family at home
and kids who are her age!
You're outsiders.
Kalgara doesn't want
to see you anymore.
When are you going
to leave, anyway?
Answer me!
[NOLAND]
I know you're here, Kalgara!
Come out, now!
I won't understand
what's going on
unless you talk to me!
This is ridiculous!
Not to mention unfair!
Hey!
Come on!
We set sail in a few days!
I don't want us
to part like this!
[NOLAND grunts]
[KALGARA] How dare you
show your face here!
Do you want your wife
to live her life as a widow?
[KALGARA grunts]
Kalgara!
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[KALGARA] The bell has
lost all its meaning!
[NOLAND]
I don't understand.
I only did what I had to!
[KALGARA] If these were
sacrifices for your
advancements, we should
have never accepted you!
[NOLAND] They have
every right to be angry
and we have no
reason to be forgiven.
We're returning to
the Lvneel Kingdom!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Eternal Friends!
The Vowed Bell Echoes
Across the Mighty Seas!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!