Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[VIGARO] Because I know
he truly is a phoenix.
That he'll rise again and again,
no matter what he faces,
and each time, he'll be
even stronger than the last.
[PUZZLE] I--
[yelling]
[PUZZLE] I'm sorry, everyone.
I've been a fool.
A sorry excuse for a captain
who couldn't even bring
his best friend's
dying wish to fruition.
But now, you've all
brought me back to my senses.
Show these bounty hunters
what we're made of.
We'll reclaim our flag
in Vigaro's name
and fly it proudly in
the winds of the New World!
[LUFFY] Gimme back my flag!
I think the bigger issue
is that Luffy's arrived,
and he doesn't seem very happy.
Robin's got a point!
We're too late!
It's over! We're doomed!
No, there's still
something left we can do.
That's true.
I'm not even sure
how he discovered
the flag was missing
in the first place.
It's a mystery.
But the fact is: he didn't
actually see it being stolen.
Right!
That's why we still have
a chance to pull this off.
I know exactly
where our flag is.
Leave it to me.
I'll get it back!
That's awesome!
Robin, you're the best!
It was stupid to
think we could rely
on that idiotic Moss Head.
If you promise to remain
my big sister forever,
then I promise to
save you from those plants.
You tore the
Accino family apart!
Nobody does that to us!
You're the bastard
who trapped our ship
and stole our flag!
Naked balloon guy!
[ACCINO] Yeah, so what?
What are you going to do
about it, ya little brat?
Pshoo!
I'm gonna beat
the crap out of you!
And then I'm gonna
get our flag back!
[LUFFY]
The Red Hot Decisive Battle!
Luffy vs. The Scorching Don!
Awesome!
So you have
Devil Fruit powers, too, huh?
It's been a long time
since I've hunted down
a pirate bounty.
My children
can usually handle it.
You should be proud
of yourself, Straw Hat.
"Don" Accino.
I see.
So this must be
the big boss man
to all these
bounty hunters, huh?
It seems like he has
some sort of heat power.
[NAMI] That means these strange
fluctuations in temperature
are probably his doing.
So you're going to beat
the crap out of me, huh?
You've got guts,
but you should know
you're not the first pirate
to make such a ridiculous boast,
and you won't be the last.
Do you wanna know what
happened to the others?
--They were no match for--
--Gum-Gum...
How rude!
I was in the middle
of telling you something!
[LUFFY] ...Pistol!
[yelling in pain]
All I have to do
is touch something,
and it melts into nothing.
[gasping in awe]
Still think you can beat me?
Gum-Gum...
...Axe!
It burns!
Luffy can't land
a hit on this guy.
Hit him?
He can't even touch him!
That hurt!
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
[ACCINO] You still
don't get it, do you?
--[LUFFY] Ow ow ow ow ow ow!
--Luffy!
It's gonna be hard to beat me
when the only thing you're
doing is hurting yourself.
Every time I try to
punch him, it burns!
[ACCINO]
Heh heh heh!
I'm pretty slippery, huh?
Get it?
He's... skating?
Just another perk
of my Devil Fruit power.
By applying heat to
the bottoms of my feet
and melting
the ice beneath them,
I can slide around
wherever I like!
Nice, huh?
Awesome! Lemme try!
[LUFFY laughing]
What's he doing?
--[LUFFY yelling]
--[ACCINO laughing]
[LUFFY and ACCINO laughing]
[ACCINO] Slide and spin!
[LUFFY laughing]
I gotta admit...
I really like your power.
[chuckling]
I like yours, too,
Mr. Big Bounty.
[LUFFY, ACCINO]
You're a pretty cool guy!
[NAMI, SANJI]
Morons.
But...
...the real fight begins now!
[LUFFY] Wait. It does?
[ACCINO] Heat Whirlwind!
[LUFFY screaming]
Dammit! I can't see
anything! What'd you do?
[ACCINO] Heat Rise!
[LUFFY screaming]
[LUFFY]
Hey! Let me go!
[JIRO] Our flags are somewhere
inside that big mansion.
C'mon. Let's get moving.
Huh? But what about--
He'll be fine.
Let's get the flags.
All right!
[ACCINO] Hold it!
I really do love children.
Well, my own children, that is!
[CHOPPER and JIRO yelling]
--Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
So windy!
Put me down,
you naked balloon!
Take it easy, kid.
You'll be down soon enough.
I'm gonna smash you flat, kiddo.
Steam Iron!
Wahhh! No! Luffy!
[CAMPACINO] I can't
let Papa get any angrier.
But there's no stopping him now
that he's fighting Straw Hat.
[CAMPACINO] All right,
Mr. 100 million Berry bounty!
It's time to bring you to Papa!
Not gonna happen.
A two-bit bounty hunter like
you could never take me down!
[CAMPACINO] Arrogant chump.
You're not even in
the same league as me!
Soon, the tide will change.
Ohohohohoho!
[PENGUINS squawking]
So cold! I'm freezing!
[LAGO, RACE]
They're trapping us with ice!
Man up!
A little ice is no match
for a Phoenix Pirate!
I'm trying,
but it's just that--
[muffled speech]
[ACCINO] That's more like it.
I can almost taste
your bounty already.
You hurt my head,
naked bastard!
Wha--?
That should have
finished you off!
[LUFFY] At first
I was squished and hot,
but then the ice
started melting and I sank!
Felt good!
Is that so?
Then this time
I'll make it so hot
you won't live
to tell me about it.
No amount of ice will
cool you off after this!
Temperature up!
3000 degrees!
How are you making
all that cool smoke?
[ACCINO] It's not smoke!
Either way, as long
as I don't touch you,
you can't burn me.
[LUFFY straining]
All right, Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
[ACCINO]
Augh!
All right!
You sure showed him!
Nice shot!
Luffy!
Come on! We don't
have time to celebrate!
The faster he
finishes this guy off,
the faster he'll be able to
get back the flag on his own!
Oh crap, oh crap, oh crap!
This is bad!
If he does that,
he'll know for sure
that we lost it to begin with!
Hey, wait, what's he doing now?
That's it.
You've made me mad now!
That's what you get for relying
on such a primitive weapon.
I'm afraid this is the end!
[PENGUINS squawking]
Dammit!
We'll be completely frozen over!
If this keeps up, we won't
be able to move an inch!
Crap!
Bastards!
Listen, guys!
We need to huddle up and share
our body heat to keep warm!
It's stinky!
It's way stinkier down here!
Oh, shut up!
You think any of us
like the smell?
Get over it!
It's not like there's
a rescue team coming.
It's up to us!
[STANSEN] Oh, yeah!
It's better to fight on our own!
[ALL]
Damn straight, Captain Stansen!
All right. Let's go!
--[ALL cheering]
--[PENGUINS squawking]
[CAMPACINO] Prepare yourself!
Right back at you, jerk!
Tell me where the flags are!
Let's move!
Yes, sir!
You're the first opponent
I've ever gone up against
that's worn me out
like this, Straw Hat.
Heh! Too tired
to fight me then?
Not to mention,
you're the first opponent
to piss me off this much.
Get ready for Five Thousand
Five Hundred Degrees!
Red Hot Fried Egg!
It's Don Accino!
And Straw Hat!
Since we haven't heard
anything back from Robin yet,
we have no choice but to
take that flag back ourselves.
You're right!
We have to get it
back before Luffy!
I'll monitor things out here.
[SANJI]
Good plan. Meeting adjourned!
[PUZZLE]
Jiro! Are you all right?
[JIRO] Captain!
I'm sorry I made you
worry about me all this time.
It's no big deal.
I was never really
that worried, Captain.
Now it's time
to get our flag back.
Right.
Then let's do it,
and we'll take back the
pride of the Phoenix Pirates
along with it!
[PUZZLE] 'Atta boy.
Captain Puzzle!
Big trouble!
It's our ship, sir!
It's drifting away on its own!
What?
[STANSEN]
Leave the ship to us, sir!
You and Jiro go on ahead!
We're counting on you, Stansen!
Come on. Let's go.
[JIRO] Right.
You're good at
dodging my attacks,
but you can't dodge forever.
Check this out!
Let's see how you
like Heat-Heat Gatling!
No way! That's my move!
What?!
[LUFFY] Man, he's fast!
But what good is that supposed
to do when the eggs are so slow?
Hey! Move!
Dodge them, you idiot!
Luffy!
That was close!
I don't care about collecting
your bounty anymore.
This is personal!
I hope you're
ready to sweat, boy!
If five thousand still isn't
hot enough for you, fine!
I'll just have
to turn up the steam!
Quit treating me like
a sauna, naked balloon!
I will erase you from
this world, Straw Hat!
Hot! Hot!
You brought this upon yourself.
You hurt my handsome sons
and my cute daughter.
Unforgivable! Prepare to die!
[NAMI] The temperature's
rising bit by bit.
Are his Heat-Heat Powers
really that strong?
Or is there something
else going on here?
[loud banging noise]
Hey, Sanji.
Where did Franky run off to?
I don't think I've seen
him around for a while.
Don't worry!
Knowing him, he's
probably got something else
to worry about right now.
Huh?
Those damn Domo Penguins!
This is all their fault!
[RACE] And look!
They wanted to make sure we
couldn't chase after them!
What're we gonna do?
[GUYLE]
I bet this is payback
for what we did
to their friends.
Little bastards!
We're not gonna let a bunch
of birds make fools of us!
I know, without a doubt,
Captain Puzzle
will get our flag back.
But if he comes back
with it and finds
there's no ship to hoist it on,
all his efforts
will have been in vain!
--Captain Stansen!
[LIL] Please, Robin. Give up.
[LIL]
Please say you'll stay with me
and be my
big sister forever.
Promise you won't leave
and I won't have to hurt you.
I can't do that, Lil. Sorry.
But why not?
There you are!
Robin!
[LIL]
Your friends can't beat Papa.
This is the only way!
Is that girl
controlling these plants?
I guess I'm just gonna have
to teach that brat a lesson!
Lay one finger on that girl
and I'll make you regret it.
[USOPP] It never ends, does it?
[SANJI] Let go of my Robin,
you stupid plants!
[USOPP] Yeah! Let's show
this shrub who's boss!
Are your friends really
that important to you?
Yes. They're here
for me and our pride.
You mean the
Straw Hat Pirate flag?
It's strange.
Papa always seems so happy with
his collection of pirate flags,
but... not me.
I never really cared
that much about them.
Right.
To most people, a simple flag
wouldn't be that important.
But for pirates, like us, it is.
Even more important
than our lives.
There's no way
we'd ever let it go.
If it means so much
to you, then I--
[loud banging noise]
Oh, no! This is bad!
Papa is really angry!
[USOPP] Help! Save me!
I wouldn't do that
if I were you!
Eating him will
give you indigestion!
[LIL screaming]
Lil!
[USOPP] Gunpowder Star!
[ROBIN] Lil!
It's okay now. You're safe.
You... You saved me.
If anything happened to you,
Big Sister Robin would be sad.
Gotta keep my precious
little sister safe.
Don't you see, Lil?
You're not alone.
You've never been.
Treasure your family.
[NAMI] Wait...
Is that what I think it is?
[LUFFY] Second Gear!
You'll never win.
Just give up.
Never!
I'm here to take back our flag!
I won't let you.
And if you can't beat me, you'll
never make it in the New World!
I'm going.
It's already been decided.
It's only a matter of time.
Nobody's gonna to stop me.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
--There it is!
--[yelling in pain]
--[JIRO] It hurts!
Hot!
[CHOPPER] Zoro! You rule!
I'll die before I let go!
This is our flag!
This is our pirate pride!
Jiro!
Look, Captain.
I found it. Our flag.
Good work, Jiro.
Well done.
High Heat Nose Jet Surprise!
Pshoo!
[USOPP, SANJI] Chopper!
Hey guys!
[laughing]
Look! I got our flag
back before Luffy!
Just in time!
All right! We did it!
Now there's nothing
Luffy can say--Huh?!
No! You gotta be kidding me!
[screaming]
It was right in front of me!
How could this have happened?
Now we're right back
where we started, huh?
Were Robin and Sanji able
to find our flag in time?
Don't tell me it's one of those!
[ACCINO] You hurt my family.
Destroyed Lovely Land.
And decimated my
precious flag collection!
I'll rip you apart
with my bare hands!
Time to feel
my full heat power!
Maximum Temperature!
10,000 degrees!
So he can get even hotter!
[FRANKY]
Well! This battle's heating up!
They're going to melt
all the ice at this rate!
[ROBIN]
They'd better get back soon.
I'm starting to get
concerned about our Log Pose.
[FRANKY] No worries!
If they take too long out there,
I'll just zip over and pick 'em
up in my super sharkmarine!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
Waiting in the New World!
Farewell to the
Courageous Pirates!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!