[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
After losing his brother Ace
in the War of the Best
against the Navy,
Luffy comes face-to-face
with Dark King Rayleigh.
Well, then, that's it.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the rest of the Straw Hats
are in a hurry to reunite
to keep the promise they made
to each other and their captain.
[LUFFY]
Okay.
I've made up my mind.
If you think I should,
I'll go back... to Marineford!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[MARINE A]
This is Navy Ship Number 2-0-4,
requesting permission
to enter, urgently.
[MARINE B]
You're right on time,
I just need your code number
and I'll get you through.
[MARINE A]
Yes, that would be 5-9-6-3.
All right,
code number confirmed.
Open the Gate of Justice.
[MARINES]
Sir!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[JIMBEI]
Well done, young man.
[MARINE A grunts]
Luffy, are you starting
to feel better now?
Yep! Doesn't hurt at all
anymore. Good as new!
Man, the Warlord Jimbei.
The one they call
the "First Son of the Sea"
with the former first mate
of the King of the Pirates...
[MARINE A]
...Dark King, Silvers Rayleigh.
And Straw Hat Luffy, too!
What could they be after?
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, in Birdie Kingdom,
where the birds and the humans
have finally reached
an agreement.
[NATIVE A]
We not long ago make friends.
Raccoon really leave now?
[BIRDS squawk]
[CHOPPER]
Yeah.
As soon as I read that newspaper
and found out what
my friend's been going through,
I realized I couldn't
stick around any longer.
[CHOPPER] I had just met
Luffy's brother in Alabasta.
I can't believe
what happened to him!
I'm worried about Luffy.
What if he needs
medical attention?
He always pushes
himself way too hard.
Good friend.
Anyway, It's good
to see you and the birds
are getting along better now.
Understanding only happen
because brave Raccoon friend
risking life to do talking!
[CHOPPER]
Aww.
You guys remember not to pick
fights with the humans, okay?
[BIRDS squawk]
[CHOPPER]
They're not gonna hurt you!
They just want you to
let them pick the plants
that grow on that tree!
[NATIVE B]
Raccoon speaking truth!
We no fight you or taking eggs.
We not same as bad humans
that stealing your treasure and
chase you away! We your friends!
[BIRDS squawk]
Oh, by the way,
I was really impressed
with that medicine
you guys gave me when
I got injured before.
It's great stuff!
See, I'm better already!
Right! We using
special medicine recipe
we passing down
over many generation!
[CHOPPER]
To tell you the truth,
I wish I could
stay here with you guys
and study those
plants for a while.
I'm sure there's still
a lot I could learn,
but the timing's
kinda bad right now.
Come back soon, okay?
[NATIVE A] That right! You
always welcome here, Raccoon!
--[BIRDS squawking]
--[NATIVES cheering]
Really? That makes me so happy!
After my friends
and I find each other,
I'll tell them all about
this amazing place I found!
And I promise, when I can,
I'll come back and visit, okay?
Take. Journey long.
Maybe get hungry.
Oh, wow. Thanks!
See Raccoon soon!
[BABY BIRDIE chirps]
Hey, I love cotton candy!
[CHOPPER]
So long, everybody!
Be nice to each other!
[NATIVES] Goodbye,
Raccoon, you travel safe!
Now that I've got a yummy lunch
and all the cotton candy
I can eat, I'm ready to head
for the meeting spot
so I can help Luffy!
[gasps]
[CHOPPER] Wait, I just realized
I don't have a pirate ship!
And even if I did,
I don't have a navigator!
How am I suppposed
to make it to Sabaody
if I don't even know the way?
It's okay, I'll just get
on any ship I can find.
No, then they might
take me someplace weird!
Also, what ships? Where?
What was I thinking?
He... big dummy.
[CHOPPER] Some pirate I am!
I can't even make it to sea!
Sorry, Luffy!
[BABY BIRDIE screeches]
[chirping]
Huh? What did you say?
Your papa can fly me there?
Hey, that's an awesome idea!
[BABY BIRDIE chirps]
--[BIRD squawks]
--[CHOPPER] Woo-hoo, lucky me!
Why didn't I think of
this in the first place?
I'll be there in no time flat!
You're so fast, Mr. Bird!
[BIRD squawks]
What? You can go faster? But--
[CHOPPER laughs]
Cool!
It's just like a roller coaster!
--[BIRD squawks]
--[CHOPPER screams]
[CHOPPER screaming]
That was too fast.
I think I might barf.
[NEWS COO squawks]
[CHOPPER] Hey, News Coo!
I'll take one of those!
[squawks]
[CHOPPER] I can read this
while I have my lunch.
They should have some new
info about the war by now.
[screams]
What?! That's crazy!
[BIRD squawks]
No way! I don't believe it!
Luffy! What's going on?
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, in the East Blue,
now that Robin has been freed
by the Revolutionary Army.
Thank you!
Thank goodness.
We won't forget this!
--[WOMAN B] You're okay!
--[WOMAN C] I'm so happy!
[SORAN]
Robin!
Oh!
We're all safe!
This means everybody will
be free from now on, right?
Yes.
[ROBIN]
At the very least,
you won't be forced to work
on that awful bridge any more.
[SORAN]
Hey.
[ROBIN gasps]
Um, I hope you like this.
Soran, thanks.
You're leaving now, huh?
Yes.
[SORAN]
Robin!
Will you be back?
[BUNNY JOE]
One question.
You're headed for
Sabaody now, aren't you?
[ROBIN]
I am.
[BUNNY JOE]
"The light of revolution."
[ROBIN gasps]
For ten years,
we have been searching,
and that's what
we've called you.
It's quite suitable, I think.
You're the only
survivor from Ohara,
the brave country that
fought against the whole world.
And now that we've
finally found you,
we will shield you from
the Government at all costs!
Those are our boss's orders.
Boss?
The leader of our army, Dragon.
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
Luffy's father.
[chuckles]
Fate is strange sometimes.
Huh?
[BUNNY JOE]
Once again, I implore you--
Would you please let us
introduce you to our boss?
I'll take you to him myself.
[ROBIN]
I can't.
There's somewhere I have
to return to immediately.
Besides, I don't need
you to look out for me.
After all, I have my friends.
[BUNNY JOE]
I assume you're talking about
the Straw Hat Pirates.
[ROBIN]
Yes.
[BUNNY JOE] Then at least let
us carry you part of the way.
The bridge we're on,
it's incredibly long.
You can walk for days
and not see the end.
I insist, wherever you're
going, let us help you.
[REVOLUTIONARY E]
Sorry to interrupt, sir,
but I have good news!
It looks like we'll be able
to unlock the third and fourth
prisons before much longer!
[BUNNY JOE]
Roger that.
In the meantime, make
sure we have a team ready
in case they're
injured or confused.
[REVOLUTIONARY E]
Sir!
Please, tell me something.
Absolutely.
It's about your army.
You seem to need me and
I would like to know why.
[BUNNY JOE]
All right then.
[BUNNY JOE] Between here
and the end of the bridge,
you'll notice a lot
of ghost towns.
[BUNNY JOE] That's because
the whole country relocated
while the construction
was going on.
For example, that one there
is from 300 years ago.
Then why would
they keep building?
As always, because
the World Nobles ordered it.
[ROBIN]
I see.
But honestly,
the reasons don't matter.
That doesn't justify the deaths
of those who've been enslaved
here. It's all the same.
[REVOLUTIONARY A] Hey,
Dragon's kid, Straw Hat Luffy,
was in the newspaper today.
Did you see it?
[REVOLUTIONARY B]
Yeah, he's nuts.
Goes missing after the war,
then pops up again to do
something crazy like this.
Either way, we should
show this article
to Nico Robin as soon as we can.
She's been worried
sick about Straw Hat.
[REVOLUTIONARY A]
Sure, but I don't think
they've made it to
the end of the bridge yet.
Oh, thanks for the newspaper.
--[BUNNY JOE] This is for you.
--[ROBIN gasps]
Luffy!
Oh, good. He's safe.
[gasps]
What? Is everything all right?
Hard to tell whether you're
shocked or amused over there.
Both.
[NARRATOR] Now we take
you to Kamabakka Kingdom,
a pastel-colored paradise
on Peachy Island
where the New Kamas reside.
Come on! Really?
I told you to give me a ship!
I have a promise
I'm supposed to keep, dammit!
There's no time
for me to goof around
with you guys
anymore, all right?
Try a bit harder, Candy Boy!
That's obviously an excuse
to escape this island!
We're not letting you go!
[SANJI]
So, what if it is an excuse?
I'll come right out and say it!
If I don't see
some pretty girls,
I'm gonna shrivel up and die!
In case you haven't noticed,
this isn't my scene.
Could that be who I think it is?
[QUEENS]
Huh?
[QUEEN D]
Oh my god, it is!
Queen Iva is on that boat!
[QUEENS screaming]
Huh? Why do we care?
[CAROLINE whimpering]
Jeez, control yourself. Whoever
he is can't be that special.
[CAROLINE] She is the
ruler of our kingdom...
Queen Emporio Ivankov!
Ivankov? Hold up.
[SANJI] That's the queen
I read about in the paper.
Talk about good timing.
She was traveling with Luffy,
so she's gotta know
something useful about him.
[gasps]
[IVANKOV]
Ah, home sweet home.
Whoa, it's my lucky day!
Wh-What a body!
No. I can't.
She's totally a dude
under all that hotness,
otherwise she wouldn't
be on this island.
I'm not gonna fall for it!
Huh?
Hey there, you got a name?
Uh, I, uh...
[gasps]
[SANJI]
Her boobs are a perfect ten,
and her butt's nice
and tight, too!
No! You're not
gonna win me over.
[IVANKOV] Is there
anything I can do for you,
Candy Boy?
Yeah! I've got a lot
of questions for you, buddy,
and the first one is
are you single?
Uh, I mean, it's about Luffy.
What? Luffy?
You mean the cutie
with the straw hat?
Bingo!
Listen, I just read in the paper
that you were busting heads
with him at Marineford.
Ahh, Luffy, you lucky bastard!
Anyway, you might
know how he's doing.
So, I was hoping you would
fill me in on that, baby.
[IVANKOV]
Huh?
[IVANKOV giggles]
[gasps]
How about no?
Aw, man! And I saw it coming
from a mile away, too!
Screw you!
Too bad! Now tell me,
how do you know Straw Boy?
We're shipmates.
Huh? You're a part of his crew?
[IVANKOV] So, Straw Boy
here is your captain?
[SANJI]
Yeah, so?
[IVANKOV] Then you're friends
with Pirate Hunter Zoro?
No!
[IVANKOV]
And what about Cat Burglar Nami?
[SANJI gasping]
[IVANKOV]
Are you familiar with
the King of Snipers
pictured here?
Yup.
And this one... is you?
Hell, no!
[IVANKOV] You're not on
any of these wanted posters,
so you must be a fraud!
Sorry, but I have yet to see
proof of your relationship
with Straw Boy!
What do I have to do
to convince you?
Tell me what you
know about Luffy,
you fishnet-wearing
freak show! Now!
It says right here
in this newspaper
that you were there with him!
[IVANKOV]
So, you admit this is you.
[SANJI]
No, it's not!
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
I mean, kind of, but...
I'm Sanji, but I...
[coughs]
Gosh, this is a problem
area for you, isn't it?
[SANJI panting]
[SANJI coughs]
All right.
Fine! It's me!
That hideous thing on
the wanted poster is me!
You win!
Now--
[SANJI groans]
Nope. No match!
But you still made me say it?!
I was coughing up
blood, you jerk!
Too bad for you,
because if there's even
an infinitesimal
fraction of a chance
that you're a puppet for
the Navy or the Government,
I won't be divulging
one iota of the information
I have about Straw Boy.
Certainly, you can
understand why.
[SANJI] Yeah, I get it.
At least let me borrow a ship.
I've gotta get to the meeting
spot as soon as I can.
No ship for you!
[SANJI] All right, then.
I'll start swimming!
[gasps] Such awesome dedication!
You were telling the truth
when you said that you
were a member of his crew!
Well, in that case,
I have no choice.
You moved me,
so out of respect for your
undying devotion to Straw Boy,
I'll tell you everything.
[gasps]
Or maybe not!
Hee-haw!
[QUEEN E]
You had me going!
[QUEEN F]
What a trickster!
[QUEEN G]
You're so smart!
Nobody asked you morons!
[SANJI groaning]
[SANJI]
Damn it.
Ooh, looks like
his guard's down.
Nice! Maybe we can get him into
that darling dress from before!
Not even if you
paid me! Now back off!
Listen! I'm a manly man
who likes ladies! Sexy ones!
Hear me? And none of
you creeps make the cut!
[QUEENS]
Boo! Boo!
Hey, Iva, I think it was?
I decided since I'm a pirate,
I'm gonna take your ship.
I challenge you to a duel.
All right.
[QUEEN H]
And now, Queen Iva,
the grand master
of New Kama Kenpo,
will face Black Leg Sanji
in a three minute,
winner take all match!
[IVANKOV giggles]
[SANJI] Judging by how
strong his stand-in was,
he's probably gonna be tough.
I gotta warn you,
I won't hold back.
[QUEEN H]
Fight!
[SANJI]
Diable Jambe!
[yelling]
[SANJI]
Premier Hachis!
[IVANKOV groans]
[IVANKOV groaning]
My! You're powerful!
I don't think I can resist!
I'm beginning to falter.
I do believe this
is the end. Here I go.
Not!
[SANJI grunts]
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
[QUEENS] Aw, you got us again!
You're such a kidder!
[SANJI grunts]
[IVANKOV] You appear
to be a sturdy fellow,
but I dare say you could benefit
from some serious discipline.
--What?
--New Kama Kenpo,
44th Aesthetic Technique!
I call it my Hair Removal Fist!
--[SANJI gasps]
--[IVANKOV yelling]
[IVANKOV]
Death Wink!
[SANJI groans]
[IVANKOV]
Hell Wink!
[SANJI groans]
[IVANKOV]
Galaxy Wink!
[SANJI groans]
[IVANKOV chuckles]
[SANJI groaning]
[IVANKOV]
Very well, Mister Curly-Brows,
I'll give you an
update on Straw Boy.
So, what made you change
your tune all of a sudden?
[IVANKOV]
Oh, please.
There's no need to hide what
the whole world knows anyway.
What's going through that
little guy's head, I wonder?
[SANJI]
It's in today's paper?
[gasps] Whoa!
You've got a call from Baltigo.
Oh?
The boss is waiting.
Please come with me.
[IVANKOV] Goodness, everyone
seems to have learned
a great deal about you since
the war haven't they, Dragon?
That must have been very
upsetting for your men.
[DRAGON] Hah. Actually,
they were happy to find out
their mysterious boss didn't
have a heart of stone after all.
Well, it doesn't make any
difference now, does it?
Luffy's not a kid anymore.
Regardless, I was surprised to
hear you were there with him.
[IVANKOV] Destiny sure works in
interesting ways, huh? [giggles]
As for myself, it's been
one twist after another.
What with the prison break
and meeting your
little bundle of joy.
Needless to say, I have
several questions to ask you.
I'm sure you do.
The time has come for us to
call our commanders from
every corner of the world
as quickly as possible.
Now that Whitebeard is dead,
the Government regime
and the world's situation
are going to change.
Not only that,
but it occurs to me
I haven't gotten to tell
you what happened to Kuma.
[IVANKOV] Yes, that certainly
was a nasty surprise.
Working for the
Government is bad enough,
but now robot clones?
I still can't believe
he tried to do me in!
I suppose the Kuma
we once knew is no more.
[IVANKOV] By the way, Dragon,
have you seen today's news?
Straw Boy's thrown me
for a loop yet again!
He's just as wild as his father.
He seems to be relaying
some kind of message,
and in Marineford, no less.
[NARRATOR] Although Navy
Headquarters was left in ruins
after the War of the Best,
marines and reporters
still stalk its grounds.
Luffy, Rayleigh,
and Jimbei return
to where Ace lost his life
to carry out a mysterious plan.
The world is shocked,
but will Luffy's crew
understand his actions?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Unexpected Relanding!
Luffy, to Marineford!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!