[LUFFY]
Alright, let's go, let's go!
There's nothing at all!
[neighing]
Chopper. That's not a giraffe.
That's a horse
with a long neck.
A long horse.
Gum-gum whip!
[loud crash]
[CHOPPER]
What's going on?!
Well, uh, I think that
bamboo tree was possessed.
This can't be good.
[FOXY CREW A] We are
the notorious Foxy Pirates!
We want more than
just a fight from you.
We want a showdown!
[TONJIT]
I'm in your debt!
Come to my house and let me
show you some hospitality!
[LUFFY]
Awesome! I'm starving!
[CHOPPER]
Me too!
[TONJIT] Finally home,
after all these years!
It's a custom in this
village to treat visitors
to extra-delicious milk from
our extra-long farm animals.
Village? I didn't see
any village out there.
Or a farmhouse.
Now that you mention it.
[shocked gasp]
[TONJIT] The village is
gone! All our animals, too!
You're nuts, old man.
I know it's been ten years,
but whole villages
don't just disappear.
[TONJIT]
Yes, but this is a special case.
I'll save the explanation until
after we've had
a nice cool drink.
I believe I had some milk
tucked away somewhere.
Hmm...
Did you say "milk"?
You realize you were
stuck on those stilts
for ten years, right?
[shocked gasp]
I... uh... hope this
cheese is to your liking.
You think we're stupid?!
You can't pass off your
disgusting old milk as cheese!
[TONIT] If you don't want
to eat it, I won't force you.
But far be it from me to
let cheese go to waste.
Wait so you're saying it's okay
to eat this stuff after all?
Are you out of your mind?!
What's the big deal?
Some cheese tastes better
once it's finely aged!
Your high-stress lifestyles
have made your stomachs weak,
whereas laid back
fellows, such as myself,
can eat whatever we like!
You kids go on your
fancy adventures,
but you're shy when
it comes to new food!
Someone, call a doctor.
What did you think
was gonna happen? Moron!
Doctor, someone
get a doctor, hurry!
Wait, that's me!
It's food poisoning.
Yeah, you think?
Ha ha ha ha!
You're funny old man!
You okay?
Yes, excluding the fact that
the entire camp packed up
and moved on without me.
I see now.
The village didn't
disappear, it moved.
That must mean the
people here are nomads!
Indeed, and Long Ring
Long Land Island is our home.
You are welcome here.
Oh, uh, thanks.
The island got its name
from its ring-like shape.
Although it's
technically one big circle,
the tides divide it
into 10 smaller islands.
You probably wouldn't
guess that all of the islands
were actually connected.
But once a year,
when the tides
are at their lowest,
you can see Long
Ring's true form,
if only for a few hours.
We use this time to migrate
from one island to the next,
every three years, circling
the ring again and again.
So everyone moved to
the next island while
you were stuck up in the
trees. What rotten luck.
That's a good one!
You're a real rebel, old man!
If they stay on each
island for three years
then subtracting the
10 years you spent living
on those stupid
bamboo stilts.
It would still take a
good twenty years for them
to come back around and
meet up with you again,
assuming you don't eat
that "cheese" of yours
and die of food
poisoning, of course.
Well, it's sad, but true.
I just wish I had my
hooo-oorse to ride again.
Then I could cross an
island every time the tides
were low and catch up
to the other villagers
in only five years.
Hoooo-orse?
That's right.
They're the most graceful
and beautiful animals
on the whole island.
Once tamed, they
can be used to cross
the grassy plains with
the greatest of ease.
Without them, it
would be impossible
for our people
to migrate.
After all, our belongings
are far too heavy
to carry on our own.
And even if we
were strong enough
to move all our luggage,
the tide would still rise
and drown us before
we could make it across.
Wouldn't it be easier
to take a boat instead?
Yes, of course
but unfortunately,
we don't know how to sail.
And besides even
if we were able
to charge a Log Pose
here, that doesn't mean
it would point
to the next island.
The land may be
split into ten pieces,
but it's all part
of the same place.
Suppose I'll just
have to wait 20 years.
You'll be lonely.
That's a long time.
Oh! Wait a second.
Is a hoooo-ooorse
like a horse?
Hey, I almost forgot about that!
We saw a horse on the way here!
Oh, my sweet little Shelly,
you waited for me
all these years!
You're such a pretty
girl! Look at you!
So cute! I missed
you so much!
You've sure grown
long since I've been away!
Awe, you make
me so proud!
Good girl!
That's a good girl!
I'm so sorry if you were
lonely while I was gone!
It's all my fault!
I promise I'll never
leave you again!
Don't leave her waiting!
She wants to
go out for a ride!
[USOPP]
What a pal, huh?
Even though everyone else left,
she still hung
around all these years.
[LUFFY]
That's my kind of horse!
[CHOPPER] I don't know which one
of them is happier right now!
[TONJIT laughs happily]
Man that horse
sure is fast, huh?
I wanna ride it too!
I see why that old man
likes horses so much!
[thinking] Now that I'm back,
let's cross the sea together
as soon as the tide
is low again, okay?
You've waited
through rainy days.
And you've waited
through snowy days as well.
But from now on, we'll
have nothing but sunshine!
[NOMAD MAN A] Shelly,
are you sure you want
to wait here for
Tonjit all alone?
We're taking all
your friends with us.
[NOMAD MAN B]
Littonto, wait, come back!
[NOMAD MAN A]
Please, come with us, Shelly.
We won't return to
this island for 27 years.
You're going to be lonely
if you have to
stay here by yourself.
[NOMAD MAN A] We don't
know where Tonjit ran off to.
It's not worth waiting here.
He might be gone for good.
[LITTONTO]
I'm gonna stay here, too!
Grandpa's coming back,
I just know it!
Put me down!
I'm not gonna leave
Shelly and Grandpa all alone!
Stop! Let me go!
Grandpa's coming back!
I know it! We have
to wait for him!!
[NOMAD MAN A]
Good luck, old girl.
Live well.
[LITTONTO]
Shelly!
[sad neighing]
[patter of rain]
[happy neighing]
Whoa, hold on there, Shelly!
You know this old man's
afraid of heights, don't you?
Hahahaha!
[ALL laugh]
[loud gunshot]
Oh no!
Are you okay?!
[pained grunting]
[frantic neighing]
Huh?
[USOPP]
Shelly! What happened?!
[CHOPPER]
We heard a gunshot!
[USOPP]
What's with this net?!
Here! I'll get it!
[FOXY]
Feh-feh-feh-feh!!
Sorry suckers, but
that horse is mine!
[PORCHE]
Yeah! You tell them, Boss!
Put those losers in their place!
Whoever you are, you'll pay!
[FOXY] "Whoever you
are?" You don't know?
[PORCHE]
My goodness! How rude!
[HAMBURG]
Puh-puh-puh-puh...
Don't tell me you've never
seen this face before!
The only thing
I know about your face
is that I'm gonna break it!
[FOXY]
He really doesn't know me.
[PORCHE] Oh no,
don't get depressed, Boss!
He's just saying
that! It's a joke!
Everybody knows who you are!
[HAMBURG] Like he'd have
any reason to know him!
[PORCHE] You're gonna
make him cry, Hamburg!
My name is Foxy!
What's mine is mine and
what's yours is mine, too!
Feh-feh! You should see
the looks on your dumb faces!
What kind of pansy
gets so worked up
over some stupid horse?
If I didn't steal
that thing myself,
then somebody
else would do it!
[LUFFY]
That's enough! Gum-gum...
Hold it, Luffy, not yet!
Huh? How'd you know
my name was Luffy?
[FOXY] Because unlike some
people, we did our homework!
[PORCHE] Monkey D. Luffy,
with a 100 million Berry bounty.
Roronoa Zoro, with
a 60 million bounty.
A lump of cash like that
is nothing to scoff at,
especially considering
that you only have
seven crew members.
Now, with introductions
out of the way,
as Captain of the Foxy Pirates,
I challenge you Straw Hats
to a "Davy Back Fight!"
I don't know
what that means,
but if you want a
fight, bring it on!
I'm sick of hearing you talk!
Huh? Wait! Now it
all makes sense!
I bet that messed up crew
we saw on the way here
got challenged to a
Davy Back Fight, too!
Which way do we turn?!
Who knows?!
Where's the navigator?!
Give orders!
--What navigator?!
Captain!
--What captain?!
This's bad I got to
stop him! Luffy, no!
We're gonna end
up losing our crew!
What're you
talking about Usopp?
I know this guy is a jerk,
but you can't
agree to fight him!
[FOXY]
Hoi-hoi-hoi! Feh-feh-feh...
Aw, too bad kid,
but no take-backs!
You already agreed, remember?
"Bring it on,"
I believe you said.
Ain't that right, Porche?
Oh, that was definitely
a "bring it on" I heard!
And once you
say, "bring it on,"
there's no turning
back, that's the rule.
Should have kept
your mouth shut.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you aren't
man enough to keep your word?
Am too!
You're falling into his trap!
But what about
the horse?! Come on!
Shelly.
You landed on your
back pretty hard!
Don't push yourself too much!
[TONJIT]
Both of you step aside!
Are you crazy?!
[TONJIT] Shelly waited 10
years for me to come back!
I won't let you take her!
I know that you're angry,
but those are pirates, old man!
You said the fight's
already started?
[FOXY CREW A]
That's right!
A Davy Back Fight
begins as soon as
one captain
accepts the challenge
from the other captain.
No take-backs!
[FOXY CREW B]
In other words,
your captain is
fighting our captain,
whether you like it or not!
All you can do is sit
back and deal with it!
I don't get this.
If it's a fight, why do
I have to sit and wait?
Let's do this right
here, right now.
[SANJI sighs]
You don't know anything, do you?
It's not a real fight.
It's more like a sports match
between different pirate crews.
[ZORO]
Hmm?
[ROBIN] Exactly.
Supposedly, the game originated
in a faraway place
called "Pirate Island."
As the name implies,
it's a sort of secret
paradise for pirates.
At any rate, the main
purpose of a Davy Back Fight
is to plunder
desirable members
from another pirate's crew.
[NAMI] Pirates
plundering other pirates?
Yes.
[FOXY CREW A] No wonder
your puny little crew
only has seven members!
A Davy Back Fight
is the best way
to pull in some new recruits!
[FOXY CREW B]
Since you're so clueless,
I'll tell you how it works.
After each match,
the winner can take
any crew member they
want from the losing team.
And once that
person is chosen,
they got to pledge
their undying loyalty
to their new captain,
on the spot.
Both crews take their oath
in the name of Davy Jones,
the Pirate of the Deep.
So if you lose, you
lose a crew member?
[FOXY CREW A]
Now you're getting it!
[FOXY CREW B]
Also, if the losing team
doesn't have any
members worth plundering,
the winning captain
can add insult to injury
by robbing the ship
of its Jolly Roger!
[SANJI] So you're not
just betting your crewmates,
but the pride
of your ship, too.
Winning might
make you stronger
but losing can leave
you with nothing at all.
Might as well be
betting your life.
I see, that explains it.
That ship without a captain
or a navigator or sail,
they must've lost everything
in a Davy Back Fight.
Oh? So you saw the
Fang-Frog Pirates
or what's left
of them at least.
How about we
give you a chance
to admire our
handiwork in person?
Here! Let's have a
round of applause
for our brand new recruits!
[FORMER CAPTAIN]
Long live the Foxy Pirates!
Before I came here,
I was the Captain of
the Fang-Frog Pirates!
I was the doctor.
I was the navigator.
And I was the shipwright!
We played five three-coin
games, and lost them all!
The captain,
thirteen crew members
and our Jolly
Roger, taken away!
[FORMER CREW B] With so
many people jumping ship,
I guess it was more like
a merger than anything!
[FORMER CREW MEMBERS laugh]
What about your crew,
huh? You don't care?
Just join a new ship
and leave them out to dry?
Yeah, no kidding.
Those poor saps got a one-way
ticket to a watery grave.
Watery grave?
That's their problem.
Don't look at me!
You're nothing but scum.
We're not playing
your stupid game, got it?
There's no way we'd
ever sink to your level!
[FOXY CREW A] You can
say that all you want,
but it ain't the
crew's decision to make!
The Davy Back Fight begins
the second one captain
agrees to another
captain's challenge.
[FOXY CREW B]
What's the matter?
Don't you have
faith in your captain?
If you don't agree with
the decisions he makes,
maybe you're better off
joining us after all!
[SANJI]
Sorry Nami, but they're right.
Huh?
All pirates take
an unwritten oath
to follow their captain
to the bitter end.
If we turned our back
on this fight now,
we'd be sailing
away in disgrace.
So? Who cares?
That's better than losing!
Maybe for you,
but I'd rather die
than live in disgrace.
The same goes for me.
[NAMI] Are you kidding?!
Get over yourself!
You know how men can be.
There's no point in
arguing with them.
UGH! I'll stop Luffy
by force if I have to!
Don't bother.
It's too late.
All that's left
now is to sit back
and wait for the
captains to fire a shot
to signal the
beginning of the match!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
Ah, no way.
Hhh... Guess that settles it.
Well, I'm
not complaining.
Should be interesting at least.
[FOXY CREW E]
He's agreed to the game!
[FOXY CREW chears]
Yay!!
Feh-feh-feh-feh!!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Why did you agree?!
You could end up
losing your crew!
You could lose me!
[LUFFY] Nuh-uh! I'm
gonna win this thing!
[FOXY] Now the Davy Back
Fight is officially underway!
[LUFFY] Good! The sooner I can
pound your face in, the better!
[FOXY] Feh-feh-feh...
I'd like to see you try!
All right! Bring
it on, Split-Head!
[FOXY]
He doesn't like my haircut.
[PORCHE] That's not true!
Hey! Apologize to him!
Our boss is sensitive
about his looks!
[HAMBURG] He's sensitive
about everything.
He's got a heart of glass.
Puh-puh-puh...
[PORCHE] How many times do
I have to tell you, don't laugh!
Luffy, now listen, I'm as angry
about the old guy's
horse as you are,
but this is madness.
Good! Use that
anger to thrash 'em!
What're you doing up?!
I thought you hurt your back!
Leave it to me!
You don't know what
you're getting into.
[fireworks booms]
[FOXY CREW F]
Sausage on a stick!
Get your sausage on
a stick! We got rum!
We got cheese burgers!
Turkey legs,
yakisoba we got it all!
[ITOMIMIZU] It's time
for the opening ceremonies!
Everybody simmer
down, simmer down,
simmer down, simmer
simmer down, simmer down!
[FOXY CREW I]
C'mon, let's hear the odds!
[FOXY CREW B]
All competitors get ready!
Split-head
may be a jerk,
but he sure
knows how to party!
And check out all
the people he invited!
Is that his crew?
Wow! There's so many!
[TONJIT]
Five jumbo yakisobas, please.
Whose side are you on, huh?
Now, let's calm down, boys!
We're about to start!
[FOXY CREW G]
I love you Porche!
[FOXY CREW H]
Marry me!
Since our challengers
have never played
this game before,
let's go over the rules, 'kay?
First of all, whatever you
lose in one of the matches,
whether it's your
crew, your Jolly Roger,
or anything else the
only way you can take it
back is with another
Davy Back Fight.
Second, any crew member taken
by the winner must
swear undying loyalty
to their new captain on
the spot, no exceptions.
Third, if your
Jolly Roger is taken,
you can't ever fly
it again! Never ever!
Nami! I got you
some cotton candy!
I don't know how
everyone can be so calm
at a time like this!
It's already settled,
so you might as
well stop complaining.
Finally, if you happen to
break any of these rules,
you'll be labeled a
disgrace to all pirates,
and banished to
Davy Jones' Locker!
So do you swear to uphold them?
I swear.
I swear!
[CROWD cheers]
All right then, Straw Hat.
I'll let you
choose your fate.
One coin? Two coins?
Three coins?
It's all up to you, kid!
That's our boss for you!
Always a good sport!
Feh-feh-feh-feh!!
What do the coins do?
Decide the number of games.
The boss is letting
you choose how many
matches you want to have.
You can quit after
one, or you can do
as many as three if
you're feeling lucky.
Well, the more games we do
the more fun we'll
have, right? So let's...
[USOPP and NAMI]
Luffy!
Huh?
Got it!
'Kay! Then I'll take three!
[USOPP and NAMI] You idiot!
Why did you add them?!
And why'd you
count an enemy, too?!
That was easy!
Puh-puh-puh...
Then it's settled!
Three coins, three
games, orthodox rules!
Let Davy Jones be our witness!
Huh? So who's
this Davy Jones guy?
[ROBIN] A pirate who
was cursed by the devil
and forced to
spend all of eternity
at the bottom of the sea.
I've never heard of
people living underwater!
Well, that's what
the legend says.
And all the ships
and treasures that sink
beneath the waves
go to his "locker,"
never to be seen
by anyone again.
I knew the ocean was scary,
but that's crazy! Yummy!
Davy Jones has
been taking his picks
from all sorts of
pirates for as long as
anyone can remember.
That's why we call
it a "Davy Back Fight"
in honor of the
pirate that may someday
claim your crew as his own.
[FOXY] The stage of
battle is set, Straw Hat!
Are you ready?!
[CROWD cheers]
You bet!! Let's go!!
♪ ending song ♪
[FOXY]
Hoi-hoi-hoi-hoi!
At long last, the Davy
Back Fight has begun!
Just so you know,
I've never lost
using orthodox rules!
Ah, but who should
I take? Your chef?
Your doctor? Your
archeologist? No, no!
I've already made
my choice! Let's fight!
[LUFFY]
All right Split Head!
Calm down already!
[FOXY]
You're hurting my feelings!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Round 1! One Lap
of the Donut Race!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!