[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy launched a desperate
attack on Navy Headquarters,
in hopes of saving his
brother from execution.
However, his struggle ended in
vain, with his enemies claiming
an overwhelming victory,
along with Ace's life.
My brother Ace is
really dead, isn't he?
[JIMBEI]
Yes, I'm afraid that he is.
[LUFFY sobs]
[screams]
[LUFFY]
Ace!
"Luffy and Ace!
The Story of How
the Brothers Met!"
[NARRATOR] No one could
have guessed it at the time,
but the path that led Luffy
to Marineford began long ago.
Ten years ago, in fact,
in the East Blue.
There lies a small town,
known as Windmill Village,
where people lived
quiet, peaceful lives.
But it was the
nearby Mount Corvo,
where few would
dare to set foot.
For only the strong could
survive in its dark woods,
faced with beasts that would
make quick work of trespassers.
[LUFFY] What's wrong with being
king of the pirates, Grandpa?
Pirates are cool!
And what makes you think I care?
[LUFFY]
I'm gonna slap you!
[GARP] Eating that Devil Fruit
wasn't enough trouble for you?
Now this nonsense?
You, and your big brother Ace,
are both going to become fine
Marines, you understand me?
Ow, ow, ow you suck!
I thought I was supposed to
be made outta rubber now--
why does this
still hurt so much?
[GARP] I thought leaving
you in a nice village
would keep you safe,
but pirates won't be satisfied
until they get their grubby
hands on everything!
And I forbid you to associate
with that "Red-Haired" Shanks.
He's a terrible influence!
[LUFFY]
Nuh-uh, he's awesome.
And I'm gonna be just like him!
Oh yeah?!
What's this dump?
Hey, shut the hell up!
Whatever it is you're sellin',
I don't want none!
[GARP]
Dadan.
Huh?!
[shrieks]
Garp! What are you doin' here?!
[GARP]
Charming as ever.
Sorry for the cold welcome,
but I hope
you don't have another
ridiculous favor to ask us!
You realize Ace
is already ten, right?
[GARP]
Oh, is he now?
And how's the
little scamp doing?
Good?
Well, he's a handful, of course!
And we've been watching
over the brat for long enough!
So just take him away!
[GARP]
Never mind.
Yeah, that's the
problem--we do mind!
And speaking of brats,
would you shut that one up?
He's yours now.
[DADAN]
Huh?
Hey, Luffy, tell 'em hello.
Yo!
Wait a sec, who is he?
He's my... grandson.
[DADAN, MAGRA, DOGRA]
Huh?! What?!
[DOGRA]
I never heard about this!
[DADAN] And you want us to
take care of the little monster,
uh, little darling, I mean.
Well, no way!
Fine.
Then I'll give you two choices:
You can either raise my grandson
or spend your life in prison.
Pretty generous, considering
all the crimes you've committed.
[laughs]
No fair!
The thing is,
I'd rather stay
outta the slammer.
Frankly, if you asked me
that on one of Ace's bad days,
I might have to go for
the prison option after all.
And two brats?
Yeah, I don't think so.
This kid looks like
a real charmer, too.
[LUFFY]
Like your face?
You wanna fight,
you little punk?
So rude!
[DOGRA, MAGRA]
Dadan!
[DOGRA]
Don't let him get to you!
What the heck?
Ew!
Spit!
That's gross!
Who did that?
Hey!
You jerk!
You better apologize for that!
Hey!
There he is!
Oh, hello, Ace, welcome back!
I'm waiting!
[GARP]
Luffy, This here is Ace.
He's three years older than you.
Anyway, you're gonna be living
with him and Dadan from now on.
What? Not so fast!
You play nice.
We said, "No"!
You'll do it.
Sir, as you wish, sir!
[GARP]
Well, time to hit the road.
I'll stop by again
when I have time.
[DOGRA]
What about some child support?
[GARP]
Put it on my tab.
[DADAN]
This isn't a bar.
[GARP]
Huh?
[DADAN]
Nothing! Come back soon!
[MAGRA]
Boss, we're bandits!
We can't take in another kid!
[DADAN]
Shut up and fix dinner.
We'll figure it out.
[MAGRA]
Yes, ma'am!
Say you're sorry!
Hey, come back!
[SHANKS]
I'll leave this hat to you.
[LUFFY]
Where did he go?
[BANDIT A]
Hold it!
Let me go!
Give me all of your money,
or I kill you!
I don't got any!
I'm a kid!
Fine!
Then go tell your parents
to bring us their money!
I have a grandpa.
Okay, good enough.
Tell us his name,
and we'll go find him.
It's Garp.
[ALL 3 gasp]
Not "the Garp"!
And the kid's gonna be
staying with us from now on.
[BANDIT AA]
Why did you agree to this?
[BANDIT BB] We're
not running a daycare here!
[BANDIT CC]
C'mon, Boss, grow a spine!
That's enough!
It's dinner time, boys!
You can argue when you're done!
[BANDIT DD]
I want the big one!
[BANDIT EE]
Screw you!
I saw it first!
Save some for me!
You already ate your share, pal!
[BANDIT F]
Gimme!
I'm not losing
to you youngsters!
You share or you die!
It's survival of
the fittest, my friends.
[BANDIT FF]
You broke his arm!
[LUFFY]
C'mon.
[BANDIT GG]
It's your turn to do the dishes.
[LUFFY]
Old man.
Can I have some more?
I'm a woman,
thank you very much!
Do you even know
where you are right now,
you filthy little urchin?
[LUFFY]
Nope.
Okay, then I'll tell you.
This is the den of
the Dadan Family--
mountain bandits
that rule Mount Corvo!
Mountain bandits?
Bluh.
Mountain bandits are lame.
Well, you're stuck with us!
Or rather, we're stuck with you,
thanks to that pushy
grandfather of yours!
But if you don't want to stay,
that's fine by me--
go get eaten by a bunch
of wolves for all I care!
Easy, Boss. Easy.
I just wanted s'more rice.
[LUFFY]
Or meat.
Meat would be nice.
In case you didn't notice,
all this meat came from
that bison Ace brought back.
Even though he's a kid like you,
he has to work to earn his keep.
The bandit life's
a hard one, boy.
Tomorrow, you're gonna pay
in blood, sweat, and tears:
Cleaning, doing laundry,
polishing our boots and weapons,
robbery, fraud,
murder, and terror!
And if you go crying
to your dear old grandpa,
we'll string you up
without a second thought!
One bowl of rice
and one glass of water,
that's all I can promise you.
The rest you get for yourself.
You're gonna have
to grow up real fast, kid.
Or you'll go hungry
before the week's up.
No problem.
"No problem"? Not crying
and begging for mercy?
Grandpa threw me
in the jungle one time,
so I know how to
tough it out just fine.
There's plenty of water to drink
and I can eat frogs and snakes
and mushrooms
and stuff all I want.
I'm gonna be a pirate someday,
so I gotta be strong!
This is gonna be real fun!
[BANDIT HH]
Boss!
[BANDIT II]
You okay?
[BANDIT JJ]
Hurry! Help her up!
[BANDITS]
Heave-ho!
Huh.
Why is he leaving?
[BANDITS]
One more!
Hey, get back here, you!
Hold on, what d'you mean
you're gonna be a pirate?
And stop ignoring me!
[LUFFY]
Hey!
He just got here,
and he's already a pain!
It's gonna be like having
a baby Garp living with us!
Now, now, it's okay!
[LUFFY]
Hey!
Wait for me!
Hi!
My name's Luffy!
Everything's cool now!
I'm not mad about
you spitting on me!
[laughs]
Why are you all laughing?
But the guy just spilled
some booze on me.
It's not worth getting
bent out of shape.
bent out of shape!
I'd rather be friends!
So, can I come with you?
[screams]
[LUFFY]
It's a dead end!
[pants]
[LUFFY screams]
[BANDIT KK]
Ace is back!
You know what that means!
[BANDITS]
Food!
[DOGRA]
Huh? Wait. You're alone?
That's not good.
Uh, yeah.
Where's Luffy?
Wasn't he with you?
Beats me.
Come on, you snot-nosed brat.
Where did you go?
You think maybe
he died out there?
If he did, it's gonna
be our funeral, too.
The boss must be
worried sick right about now.
Get a hold of yourself!
This is serious!
No biggie.
Oh, and is that what
you're gonna say to Garp
when he finds out we
let his grandson die?
Why do you care?
One less crappy
brat in the world.
I have a feeling that
Garp won't see it that way.
Well, maybe the old jackass
should've thought about that
before he left him with a
bunch of bandits in the woods!
Come on, does this look
like a damn daycare to you?
If he can't take care
of the boy himself,
he has no right to talk!
You should tell
him that, not us.
Suck it!
[FLASHBACK PIRATE]
If Gold Roger had a son?
What are you talking about?
He'd end up just like his dad.
Off with his damn head.
Then he'd cry and
shut 'em down for good!
"I'm trash, just like my dad!"
"I should die!"
[laughter]
[DADAN]
Y'know what?
While we're at it,
screw Ace, too!
[DADAN] If he dies, we'll
tell Garp it was an accident.
I mean, that'd be
the truth, wouldn't it?
The devil's children
have the devil's luck!
How 'bout that?
'Cause Ace is
the devil's son, for sure.
What do you think
the Government would do
if they found out about him?
Hah!
I'll take my chances with Garp!
[MAGRA]
Hey, you don't mean that, Boss.
[DOGRA] Come on,
that's the booze talking.
Just sleep it off.
[NARRATOR] One week later.
[barking]
Damn dog.
Don't you know
we're trying to sleep?!
[shrieks]
Boss! Wake up! C'mere, quick!
[DADAN]
What?
Oh!
It's you!
[DOGRA] The little
bugger isn't dead after all!
[barking]
You're alive.
Why'd you scare us like that?
Huh?
Easy, easy, Boss.
Where the hell were you,
and what were you doing?
Now, now, just
give him a second--
he'll answer without all
the face stretching.
I was stuck at the bottom of the
valley getting chased by wolves.
Are you nuts?
What the heck were you
trying to do down there?
[DOGRA]
Well, whatever.
It's good you came back safe.
There's nothing good about it!
Another useless mouth to feed!
Get some sleep while you can.
We're putting you to work
bright and early tomorrow!
Hey, Ace!
You going somewhere fun today?
Take me!
I know I was gone for a while,
but I still wanna be friends!
Wait!
[DOGRA] Boss! He's
running after Ace again!
Hey!
Get back here--you
still have chores to do!
Nyah! I'm outta here!
I am gonna wring your
rotten neck, you twerp!
Easy, easy!
You shut your yapper
and go bring him back!
[MAGRA]
Yes, ma'am.
[LUFFY]
Hey!
Ace!
Come on!
I wanna be friends with you!
[screams]
[NARRATOR]
The next day.
Hey, Ace!
Let's be friends!
Do your damn chores, kid!
[DOGRA]
He's already gone.
Well, hurry up and
bring him back, then!
You're not getting
away from me today!
That's easy!
So, are we friends yet?
[screams]
[NARRATOR]
And on the tenth day.
Luffy!
You're too late again,
he's already long gone.
Then bring him back!
[NARRATOR] It was the
same thing every time.
[LUFFY screams]
[NARRATOR] But that didn't
deter him one bit.
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[NARRATOR]
A month passed.
Two months.
[LUFFY]
Wait up!
[NARRATOR]
In the rain.
Or in the wind.
[LUFFY shrieks]
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Let's be friends!
[NARRATOR] Ace would run
and Luffy would chase him.
[DADAN]
Again?
What does that moron
think he's gonna accomplish?
[DOGRA] He's getting
banged up pretty bad out there.
He's bound to lose
interest sooner or later.
Let's hope!
This nonsense is
really stressing me out!
You're worried
about him, aren't you?
[DADAN]
Don't be stupid!
I'm just mad 'cause
he's not pulling his weight!
[screams]
A beehive fell on my head.
Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Come back!
I'm not giving up yet!
I'm having a tough
time losing him today.
Stubborn punk.
Uh-oh!
Crap!
[LUFFY]
This sucks!
Got away again!
How'd he get so darn fast?
Hey, there you are!
[screams]
[ACE] That's gotta be the
nastiest monster in the forest.
Even I can't beat that thing!
[ACE]
Run away, stupid!
It's gonna eat you!
I wanna run away,
but my legs won't let me!
Damn it.
[pants]
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Three months
had passed, and although
he was covered with cuts and
bruises, Luffy did not relent.
[LUFFY]
It's the end of the forest.
What is this place?
[NARRATOR]
Mountains of discarded trash
reach toward the sky in the
criminal-infested junkyard
known as Gray Terminal.
With dreams of buying
a pirate ship in their hearts,
Ace and his partner
in crime, Sabo,
rob the thieves and scavengers
in this den of lawlessness.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Here Comes Sabo!
The Boy at the Gray Terminal!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!