[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates
are fighting hard to
reach the scaffold,
but the Navy has activated
the bay's encircling walls,
trapping the pirates
in a fiery ring of death.
[SENGOKU]
What's going on down there?
Why didn't the last wall raise?
Well, it's, uh, it's Oars' body.
The walls don't seem
strong enough to lift it, sir.
Also, it looks like his blood
is running into the system
and making it malfunction!
[ACE gasp]
Oars! You saved them.
We must be swift.
You know what to do, Akainu!
[LUFFY]
"Execution Order Issued!
Break Through
the Encircling Walls!"
[MAN AA] What's going on,
where's the picture?
[MAN BB]
We wanna see the war!
[MAN CC]
Hurry and get it fixed!
It looks like they're
having problems
with the video
transponder snails!
Maybe they got blown up in
the crossfire or something!
[MAN B] Is it true that
the Navy and Whitebeard
had some kind of
deal worked out?
[CROWD shouting]
[MAN DD] Did Whitebeard
really sell out his allies?
We all wanna know
how the war's gonna end!
Come on! The whole
world's at stake!
[CROWD continues shouting]
Just when I thought the Navy
couldn't sink any lower.
S'been nothin' but
a sideshow till now.
[ON-AIR PIRATE A] The only
reason we came back to Saobaody
was to watch the war.
Of course the
snail's malfunctioning.
Are you really buyin' that?
What? You mean you don't?
Course not.
What are you, stupid?
There's only one way the Navy
would allow that
feed to cut out.
They don't want the world to
see what they're about to do.
[BONNEY crying]
You okay, Captain Bonney?
Go away! Just shut up!
[LAW] Whitebeard sold out his
allies? What a load of crap.
The man's a living legend 'cause
all us pirates respect him.
Let's set sail, Bepo.
[BEPO]
Aye-aye, Captain!
[LAW]
You with us, Jean Bart?
Yes sir, you heard me right!
Seems like there's no chance
of recovering the signal!
I have no idea what's happening
at Marineford right now!
[AKAINU]
Meteor Volcano!
[AKAINU yells]
[yells]
They've got nowhere to run.
Now we'll melt that ice
and drown them all!
[PIRATES screaming]
[IVANKOV, PIRATES yelling]
[LUFFY gasping]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE B]
It's melting!
[PIRATES grunting, panting]
[PIRATES screaming]
It's so warm.
No, no! It's hot! I'm burning!
[PIRATE E]
The lava's boiling the sea!
[PIRATES groaning]
[PIRATE F]
Hurry and get on the ice!
Hey! Look!
[yelps]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATES]
Huh?
Ah! They're blocking us in here!
[PIRATES screaming]
We've gotta be able to take
down this wall somehow!
[PIRATES yelling]
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY screaming]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES yelling]
Ugh! Whitebeard!
How is it still standing
after a shot from Pops?
What is that thing made of?!
[WHITEBEARD growls]
All right. Let's hit 'em
where it really hurts.
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATES screaming]
[PIRATE CC] That bastard aimed
straight for the Moby Dick!
We've gotta put out the fire!
[PIRATE DD]
All hands on deck!
Grab a bucket and
put it out, damn it!
[yells]
[PIRATE EE]
We can't let her sink!
It just won't be the
same sailing with Ace
again without the Moby Dick!
Whitebeard, watch your
legacy go up in flames!
[grunts]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE N]
The Moby Dick. It's-- It's gone.
No! Damn those monsters! That
ship was the only home we knew!
Damn it! Don't give up now!
The Moby Dick has been carrying
the Whitebeard Pirates
for decades!
[PIRATES gasping]
[WHITEBEARD]
I'm sorry, old friend.
[PIRATE HH]
We've gotta get to the plaza
before this gets any worse!
[ACE grunts]
Listen to that. What the heck do
you think is going on in there?
You don't even
need to see to know.
They can't advance,
they can't retreat,
and now they've got death
raining down on them from above.
Those steel encircling walls are
none other than the walls of
the Whitebeard Pirates' casket.
[COBY gasps]
Their casket?
[SENGOKU] The plan is working
perfectly, so we'll proceed.
Phase two is the
immediate execution
of Portgas D. Ace!
[MORIA laughing]
[PIRATES gasping]
[LUFFY gasps]
[ACE grunts]
We gotta get up
there 'n stop 'em!
But how?
We're completely trapped!
No... There's still a way out.
Just look ahead and see.
The path that Oars made!
But that's like a death trap.
That's exactly where
the Navy's expecting us to go.
The more we think,
the more time we waste!
Yeah. It's the only
way we can save Ace,
even if it means our death.
[LUFFY yelling]
[PIRATES]
Huh?
Uh?
[LUFFY continues yelling]
[PIRATES gasping]
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[LUFFY yells]
Straw Hat.
We're right here
behind ya, kid!
[PIRATES yelling]
[LUFFY panting]
[VISTA shouts]
They're running straight
into the line of fire!
[SENGOKU] Not yet! Let them
get as close as possible!
Now!
[PIRATES screaming]
[LUFFY grunts]
There's only one way in
and one way out,
where else is the Navy
going to point their cannons?
It's a slaughterhouse!
[PIRATES shouting]
[SENGOKU]
Fire!
[PIRATES screaming]
[LUFFY panting]
[PIRATES shouting]
We're comin', Ace!
[gasps]
[PIRATES shouting]
[ACE grunting]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATES screaming]
[ACE grunts]
[gasps]
[PIRATES yelling]
We're picking them
off, one by one!
[PIRATES yelling]
[ACE grunting]
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[LUFFY grunts, shouts]
[LUFFY]
Ace...
[PIRATES screaming]
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
I can see him.
[LUFFY panting]
I'm here!
[ACE grunts]
And fire!
[LUFFY gasps]
[yelling]
Straw Boy, no!
Luffy!
[MARINE BB] All right, fire on
any pirate who climbs up Oars!
[ACE gasping]
I'm still gonna save you!
[SENGOKU]
Prepare for the execution.
[MARINES]
Whoa!
[SENGOKU gasps]
[MARINES gasping]
[PIRATES gasping]
[OARS JR.]
I'm here, Ace.
[ACE gasps]
[MARINES gasping]
[OARS JR. groaning]
Ooh.
[MARINES gasping]
[OARS JR. groans]
[MARINE CC]
How is Little Oars still alive?
Did nobody check his pulse?
Get away from Ace!
I'm gonna save you!
Ace... My friend.
O-Oars!
I won't die till you're safe.
Oars, no!
I'll be...
Oars Jr.'s still alive?
[PIRATES cheering]
Captain!
Now, that's a pirate.
Little Oars.
[PIRATE AG]
We're ready to follow, Captain.
[SQUARD gasps]
[SQUARD]
Huh?
Get back in the fight.
Even now?
[SQUARD]
I'm ready.
[LUFFY grunts, panting]
No more falling in
the sea, all right?
Honestly, you are too reckless!
[panting]
Prepare to open fire, men.
[SENGOKU]
Now!
[OARS JR. groaning]
Oars! Stop!
[OARS JR. groans]
They'll kill him
for real this time!
[PIRATES]
Oh, no!
[OARS JR. groaning]
Oars, please!
We gotta do something.
And we gotta do it fast.
There's no time left.
They already issued
the order to kill Ace!
Yes, but we need a strategy.
[LUFFY]
Jimbei...
I need a favor from you.
[OARS JR. panting]
Ace!
Well, he's a tough one!
[MARINE DD] He's just
about dead! Keep shooting!
[KIZARU] Save your bullets,
boys. I'll finish him off.
Admiral!
[KIZARU] We've dealt
with enough setbacks.
We need to get this
execution on the road.
A head shot seems appropriate.
Quick, easy, and
100 percent effective.
[PIRATE FF]
Oars!
[PIRATE GG]
Run, Captain Oars!
[OARS JR. panting]
Please, no!
[KIZARU]
Say goodnight, big guy.
[OARS JR. grunts]
[ACE gasps]
[JIMBEI]
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
[gasping]
[ACE]
Luffy!
[LUFFY panting]
I see. So, you found a way up.
You've done quite well,
son of Dragon.
You're standing tall now.
Ahh, youth... So much fire!
That's Straw Hat Luffy who
got thrown over the wall,
A-Ace's brother!
Well done, brat.
[LUFFY panting]
I do respect your tenacity, kid,
but it's not enough.
That's right. It's a fluke
you got this far and
you're too green
to go any further.
Whatever gives you
the idea you can defeat us?
[LUFFY panting]
Back off!
You're not gonna kill Ace!
He and his brother
are two of a kind.
They just dive right in
without even thinking.
Oars! Stay put! I need
your help one more time!
Sure, Pops!
[WHITEBEARD]
Jozu, the trump card!
Yes, sir!
Get ready to move, everyone!
We're charging
straight into the plaza!
[LUFFY yelling]
Gum-Gum Stamp Gatling!
[NARRATOR]
Luffy bursts into the plaza,
leading the assault
on the Navy forces.
However, the three
admirals block his path,
making victory all
but impossible.
Fortunately, Whitebeard has
one final trick up his sleeve,
if Luffy can survive long
enough to receive his aid.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump
Card for Recovery!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!