[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[LUFFY] Witch of Cocoyashi
Village! Arlong's Female Leader!
[YOSAKU grumbles]
What is he trying to say?
[YOSAKU groans]
[YOSAKU]
Hm?
Let me go already.
[YOSAKU grunts]
I'm trying to say that's mine!
[LUFFY] Oh really
and who decided that?
[YOSAKU] I did. I put it
on my plate. It's mine.
That's how it works.
[LUFFY] Well, I don't see
your name on it anywhere.
[YOSAKU]
I was saving it for last.
What's wrong with that?
[LUFFY] Okay sorry. How 'bout
you eat this thing instead?
[YOSAKU] I wouldn't feed that
rotten slop to my dog!
[growling]
[SANJI]
Shh. Quiet.
[growling continues]
There's something down there.
It's big.
[YOSAKU gasps]
[growling]
[screams]
[LUFFY]
What the hell is that?
[growling]
[YOSAKU]
Sea monster!
It's a cow!
Not cow... They don't swim.
A hippo?
Whatever it is, you can tell
it's from the Grand Line!
What is it doing all the way
out here in the East Blue?
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
Why is he staring at us?
[YOSAKU grunts]
[YOSAKU]
He wants the food!
[LUFFY]
What?
[YOSAKU] Quick, give it to
him before he sinks the ship!
[LUFFY]
Gum Gum Pistol!
Bad sea cow! Stay away
from our food!
Ha! Yes! You knocked it out!
[growling]
[YOSAKU yelps] Oh crap!
You made it mad!
You back for more?
[SANJI]
Dumbass.
There's no reason to punch
this poor hungry hippo.
She's probably just a baby
and can't catch food
for herself yet.
Huh? That right?
You're insane...
[SANJI]
Here you go. Eat up.
Don't be scared.
I won't hit you.
[growls]
[SANJI shouts]
[YOSAKU gasps]
What the hell are you doing?!
Damn, Jerk!!
[SANJI] It was gonna eat me
with the plate. What could I do?
[growls]
[YOSAKU screams]
[YOSAKU]
Here it comes!
Right.
[SANJI]
Stand back. This is my show.
Collier Coup!
[BOTH gasp]
That's that.
[MOMOO groans]
Yes! And back to the food!
That was refreshing.
[YOSAKU]
You guys are insane. Seriously.
[gasps]
Where am I?
[NOJIKO]
My house.
[USOPP]
H‐Huh?
Sleep well?
[USOPP]
Uh. Who are you?
I'm Nojiko. I grow
tangerines here. Want one?
That's right! You're the
one that hit me on the head.
Just when I was
going to save you.
[NOJIKO]
I'm the one who saved you.
[USOPP]
Huh?
[NOJIKO] If you had you
actually gone through with
attacking that Fishman, you
would have been killed for sure.
Stupid outsider.
You'd figure a kid from here
would already know better.
What would make a child
do something so reckless?
That's a question I'd really
like an answer for.
[CHABO]
I know... I know!
But they killed my daddy.
They took everything from me.
Those Fishmen destroyed
our town, killed my friends!
I had to make them pay for
what they did, no matter what!
Don't you get that?!
So I went to Arlong
Park by myself.
But this girl stopped
me from going in.
[inaudible]
[CHABO]
She's like an evil witch!
I can't stand this!
I have to avenge my father.
I don't care if I die.
Then die.
[NOJIKO] If you're truly
prepared to die, then go.
But you had better understand,
boy... I stopped you.
And this witch you hate kept you
from carrying out your revenge.
So far you've
cheated death twice.
[chair clatters]
[NOJIKO]
Just finish your tea and go.
Hey, you're being a little
rough on 'em, don't you think?
[NOJIKO exhales]
I don't care who he is.
If he wants to kill himself,
then so be it.
He doesn't have what it
takes to suffer for revenge.
[USOPP]
What?
[NOJIKO]
It takes time.
I suffer, as well.
Revenge is not an easy
path for one to carve out.
And to die just because
you're too foolish
for patience is
nothing but a coward's plan.
[CHABO]
Wh‐What do you want from me?
[CHABO] I can't stand
the way I feel but...
...but I don't know
what else I can do.
How's your mom?
She's alive.
Then go back home.
She's worried about you.
[CHABO]
Okay.
[USOPP chuckles]
For a chick with tattoos,
you're actually really sweet.
[NOJIKO] Piss off...
It's time you told me why
you decided to come
here to our village.
[USOPP]
Oh, right!
My name is Captain Usopp.
I'm looking for a
girl named Nami.
Nami?
[USOPP]
Hm? You know her?
No way! She's a part
of the Arlong crew?!
[NOJIKO]
It certainly looks that way.
Everybody here knows that cow.
Even the little boy.
It gets better though.
That cow is my sister.
We grew up here.
Well, technically she's
my adopted sister,
since we were both orphans.
But a sister's a sister,
you know what I mean?
[USOPP]
I don't believe it.
[gasps]
[USOPP]
Nami's house?!
[NOJIKO] It's mine too. We were
raised together in this house.
[NOJIKO] She's the closest
thing to family I have left
since our foster mother died.
[NOJIKO sighs] The three of us
used to be so happy together
in Cocoyashi village.
[USOPP growls]
So...
You're telling me that Nami
betrayed her mother,
her sister and her whole village
just to be a part
of Arlong's crew?
[NOJIKO] Yeah, pretty much.
A real witch, huh?
Damn. Nami is a total witch.
She had us completely
fooled the entire time.
To think she was just after
the treasure for herself.
Even after she risked her
life to save my village.
I don't understand.
She seemed so happy with us.
Yeah? She was happy?
Huh... My sister.
We came here to try to convince
her to come back with us,
but I guess now
that's pointless.
[gasping]
I just remembered that
a shipmate of mine
was taken prisoner by the
Fishmen before we got here.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I hope he's okay.
I hope he's at least not dead.
[NAMI]
I guess you finally get it.
I just used you guys
to get what I wanted.
You were skilled enough
to serve my needs,
but boy, were you guys
a bunch of suckers.
[ARLONG laughs] She had you
guys completely fooled!
It's no use.
She's cold‐blooded.
She betrayed her
family for money,
so you really shouldn't
feel too bad.
If I were you, I would
just admit defeat
and try to forget
the day you met her.
[ZORO]
I don't need to.
Heh. Because I never saw
anything in her to be trusted
in the first place.
If she turned out to be a serial
killer, I wouldn't be surprised.
[NAMI] Fine! Then why don't you
just get the hell out of here.
I'm tired of your face.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[ZORRO grunts]
[ARLONG]
Huh?
[ZORRO chuckles]
[FISHMEN gasp]
Hey... Anybody know why that
guy just jumped in the water?
It looks to me like he was just
trying to get away from Nami.
[FISHMAN E]
I don't blame him.
She can be really
mean sometimes.
[FISHMAN F]
Maybe he's trying to escape,
any of you geniuses
think of that?
[FISHMAN D] With his
arms and legs tied up?
I gotta say that looked
a lot more like a
suicide attempt to me.
Leave him.
[NAMI gasps]
[FISHMAN C] What an asshole.
Now I don't get to kill him.
[FISHMAN D] I thought he'd
have more self‐respect
than to do that!
[FISHMAN E] Seriously, life is
a precious thing.
[FISHMEN chuckle]
[NAMI]
That idiot!
[FISHMEN gasp, chatter]
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI, ZORRO grunt]
[FISHMAN C]
They're back up!
[FISHMAN D]
She saved him.
[NAMI pants] What do
you think you're doing?
[ZORO coughs] No, what do
[NAMI gasps]
[ZORO coughs]
You're really just a nice girl
who can't watch one guy die.
Why don't you quit pretending?
[gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
And you might want to jump in
a little quicker next time.
I thought I was dead.
[NAMI grunts]
You bastard!
[ZORRO groans]
[NAMI] Try that again and
I'll make sure you die!
[ZORO chuckles]
Really?
[NAMI]
That's a lot of bandages.
You must have been
hurt pretty bad.
[ZORO]
Actually, I forgot my shirt.
Grabbed these to cover up so
you wouldn't get distracted.
[BOTH grunt]
Tell me... What should
we do with this guy?
[NAMI]
Lock him up.
I'll take care of him
when I have the time.
Arlong! Hey, Arlong!
Yeah? Well, spit it out.
What is it?
Yes sir... This guy
didn't come here alone.
There was another long nosed,
weird looking guy with
him but he got away.
[ZORO]
What the hell, Usopp?
You left me for dead
and got spotted anyway?
[FISHMAN A]
I think...
I think he escaped into
Cocoyashi Village.
Cocoyashi, uh?
That's perfect. Now I
have two reasons to go.
It's time to go have some fun.
[VILLAGER A]
Hey Arlong's coming!
[VILLAGER B]
He is? But why?
We just paid him this
month's tribute, didn't we?
[GENZO] It's probably about
my weapons cache they found.
Everyone go home.
[VILLAGER B gasps]
Genzo...
[VILLAGER C gasps]
They're here.
So you're the fool who thought
he could horde weapons
on my island.
[GENZO]
That's me. I'm a collector.
Is there a new law that forbids
us from having hobbies now,
as well?
[sighs]
Next, you'll be telling us
that we can't read books
or play with our
children anymore.
No, hobbies are fine.
It would be weapons
that I have forbidden.
They make it difficult for me
and my men to keep the peace.
[USOPP gasps]
That's him?! Arlong's gigantic!
He's not even human.
Nope... he's a Fishman.
[USOPP]
For real?!
[ARLONG] I'm responsible for
twenty towns and villages,
including this one, and as
your leader I cannot tolerate
even a little rebelliousness.
Wiping out Gosa was just a small
example of what can happen
when you do not do
as you are told.
Tribute money must be
paid no matter what.
What? Tribute money?
It's just what it sounds like.
Money we pay him so
we can stay alive.
Adults and children...
If there is even a single
person who can't pay...
...then what happened to Gosa...
...will happen to everyone
in this village as well.
Our town, and the people in it,
will be wiped from existence.
[USOPP] H‐He destroyed an entire
town because of one person?
[NOJIKO]
That's how Arlong rules.
To them we're nothing
but a sub‐species,
so killing us has
always been easy.
[ARLONG] You pathetic humans
need to stop with all this
"thinking" you're up to.
It's your greatest weakness.
I'm allowing you to contribute
to greatness here!
Soon Fishmen will
conquer the humans,
and your tributes will
be a small part
of the beginning of the
glorious Arlong Empire!
[gasps]
[USOPP]
Arlong Empire?!
[USOPP] They're planning
on taking over the entire
East Blue!
[thudding]
[footsteps]
Get outta here quick.
Arlong's gonna be back soon.
[ZORRO]
Hm.
[clattering]
[footsteps]
[GENZO groans]
Genzo!
[gasps]
[ARLONG] The possession
of weapons is a clear affront
to my authority.
As an example to any other
would‐be rebels in this town,
I'm going to kill you right now.
So they can see the fate
that awaits them!
[gasps]
No way! That guy is insane!
He'd kill someone for
just having a weapon!
I won't let him!
[USOPP gasps]
Hey, wait! Don't go out there!
[NOJIKO] You have absolutely
no right to do this Arlong!
[ARLONG]
Heh?
We've paid your tribute without
fail for over eight years.
Why would we rebel
against it now?
Just think about it.
It makes no sense!
Now take your hands off Genzo!
[VILLAGER A]
Yeah!
[VILLAGER F] It's not
like he used the weapons!
[VILLAGER C]
That's right! Let him go!
[VILLAGER D]
Yeah, let Genzo go!
[ARLONG]
Hording weapons shows he was
planning a rebellion against me.
But on the other hand...
I could destroy you all.
Please, try to protect your
friend so you won't give me
an excuse to do that.
Either way is fine,
but rebellions will
not be tolerated.
[GENZO grunts]
Everybody just go home.
Do you want to waste all of our
work over the past eight years?
For what? The time for
you to give your lives
for this village was back
when they first came.
Now we must continue
to be patient.
The most important thing is
that we continue to live!
We swore we would
not let them defeat us
as long as we're alive...
Genzo!
No...
Well said! I agree with you...
Heh ...it's good to know that
even disgusting insects like you
enjoy being alive!
[groans]
Oh, no!
There is no way any of
you will ever come close
to the perfection
of the Fishman.
[laughs]
Damn you!
Don't move!
He wants you to attack.
[GENZO grunts]
We can't just stand here!
[gasps]
[GENZO]
Your deaths will mean nothing!
You must continue
to be patient...
[GENZO grunts]
...even if I die.
[ARLONG]
That's a good ending for you.
Pay close attention humans!
This is what happens
to those who defy me,
even if it is just
inside their tiny heads!
[USOPP]
Exploding Star!
[GENZO groans]
Huh? What was that?
Huh? Up there! Look!
There's someone on the roof!
[FISHMAN C]
Who the hell is that guy?!
I am... the great warrior
of the sea, Captain Usopp!
Usopp...
Also known as the
Demon King Usopp,
feared and hated by
almost half the world!
I command thousands of men!
Loyal and vicious men!
That's the guy
I told you about!
The one with the long
nose that got away!
[USOPP yelps]
[ARLONG]
Bring on your thousands of men!
I'll crush them one by one.
[gasps]
[USOPP] The Exploding Star did
nothing and now he's pissed!
[ARLONG]
Repulsive human.
What can a creature
like you do to me!
‐‐[USOPP gasps, shouts]
‐‐[ARLONG grunts]
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[yelps]
Arlong, hold on just a second!
After losing Gosa,
we can't afford to kill off
any more tribute money!
[FISHMAN H]
Villages are fun to destroy,
but ruling over them
makes us more money!
[ARLONG] If we lose some,
we can always get more.
Fishmen must reign supreme!
[ALL gasp]
He's destroying it all!
Usopp!
[USOPP gasps]
Am I... dead... yet?!
He's not dead yet!
[USOPP]
Aw, crap!
[FISHMAN F]
Get him!
Catch him and tear him apart!
[FISHMAN K]
Let's go back to Arlong Park
before he destroys everything!
[Fishman J]
Yeah, I'm with you!
[ARLONG growls]
Don't let him get away!
Who does that
chumsucker think he is?
We'll be back.
You can all live for now.
[GENZO grunts]
[GENZO] I'm so sorry everybody.
This has all been my fault.
What are you talking about?
You're not a Fishman are you?
[VILLAGER F]
Yeah!
But who was that
guy who attacked?
[panting]
[NAMI]
Hello everyone!
It's good to be back home.
[NOJIKO]
Nami?!
[VILLAGER B]
It's Nami!
[VILLAGER C]
You!
What's wrong?
You never just come walking
through Cocoyashi anymore.
I heard quite a commotion.
Arlong, huh?
[NAMI] I only have to get
seven million more berries.
Your already bad reputation
just keeps getting worse.
That's fine. I am a pirate.
Arlong can be a very reasonable
guy when he wants to.
I just need a little more money
to finish our agreement.
Just seven million berries
shy of the 100 million goal.
You know, it's really not that
high a price considering...
...that it's gonna buy
back our village! Heh!
[ZORO]
She tells me to run,
but I got nowhere
else to go but here.
Besides, I promised Luffy
I'd bring her back with me.
Man... what he's up to?
Cause things are getting
messy around here.
[LUFFY]
Yeah! Faster! Must go faster!
There it is! Arlong Park
is dead ahead!
Right! Next stop, Arlong Park!
♪All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[ZORO] Luffy?! Why are
you in a flying boat?
[LUFFY]
I was in a hurry.
[ZORO] That's not what I meant!
What the hell are you doing?
[LUFFY] I'm here to get Nami.
Haven't you found her yet?
[ZORO] Well... that's kind
of a long story.
[SANJI]
Hey, where's long nose?
[ZORO]
Crap! Arlong's got him!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
Usopp dead?! When is Luffy
going to Make Landfall?!
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!