[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
Hello?
[CHOPPER gasps]
[LUFFY] "Blue‐nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret!"
[NAMI]
Hm?
[NAMI] I think you've
got it backwards.
The hiding thing, I mean.
[CHOPPER gasps]
[NAMI]
Well, that is better.
But, it's a little late at this
point, and I can still see you.
[CHOPPER grunts]
Shut up, lady!
[gasps]
[CHOPPER] Oh, and can you tell
me how your fever's doing?
It's talking!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[CHOPPER grunts]
[NAMI gasps]
[KUREHA]
Keep it down, Chopper!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[KUREHA chuckles]
Your fever seems to have gone
down a little bit. That's good.
You happy?
[NAMI]
Hm?
[KUREHA]
Hm.
Who are you?
[KUREHA exhales] Yes,
it's gone down several degrees.
Should be all right.
I'm the only doctor
around here. Doctor Kureha.
But you can call
me Doctorine, okay.
Oh. Then that
means we're on...
Looking for how
I stay so young?
N‐No... that's not it.
[KUREHA exhales]
[KUREHA] Anyway, yes, you're
in the castle on the mountain.
In that case, there were
two other people
who showed up here
with me, weren't there?
[KUREHA] Yeah, they're
sleeping in the next room.
Yery deeply.
Two real tough guys.
[KUREHA] Hm... This is
what caused your sickness.
Wow... really?
[KUREHA] You were bitten
by a bug called the Kestia.
It's a poisonous tick
that thrives in jungles
with high heat and humidity.
When it bites you,
it introduces a type of
bacteria into your body.
These bacteria lay dormant for
five days, causing severe pain.
It causes a high fever,
a severe infection,
myocarditis and arteritis...
Not pleasant. Given the
infection's progression
in the affected area,
I'd guess you've been infected
for about three days now.
The pain you'd been feeling
must have been terrible.
But, still, it would have
eased up in two more days
without any treatment at all.
[NAMI] It would have
gone away in two days?
[KUREHA]
Mm‐hm.
You wouldn't be feeling
any pain whatsoever,
because you'd be dead.
[gasps]
[KUREHA] This particular
infection is known as the
"five day disease."
I had heard that kestia had died
out over a hundred years ago,
but I kept the
antibiotic just in case.
Where did you guys come
from that you may have been
exposed to this?
Were you walking around
some ancient jungle
with your belly showing?
He, he, he... No, ridiculous.
Uh...
Does this situation
sound familiar at all?
What a crazy girl you are, then.
Now...
Stay in bed.
The treatment for the disease
isn't completely finished yet.
Thank you so much.
I'll be fine as long as
my fever goes down.
My body will take care
of itself after that.
Well, aren't you
an optimistic one.
This disease normally takes a
course of treatment ten days
long to successfully cure.
Even with medicines as advanced
as mine are, your body will
still need at least three
days to fully recuperate.
If you don't want to risk more
suffering and possibly death,
get some rest girl.
[NAMI gasps]
I can't stay that long!
We need to get Vivi home.
Back to Alabasta!
[NAMI grunts]
When a patient
leaves this castle,
it's because she's either
cured or deceased.
He, he, he. You aren't
going anywhere, girl.
You better get used to it.
[whimpers]
[CHOPPER]
Huh...
[KUREHA] He climbed this
mountain with his bare hands?
That's almost three miles
of sheer rock to go up!
His entire body is on
the brink of frostbite!
What was he thinking dressing
like that for such a climb?
Draw some hot water
and throw him into it!
[CHOPPER] This guy is
bleeding a whole lot.
He has six broken ribs
and a spinal fissure.
Can I operate on him, Doctorine?
Apparently the most critical of
our three patients is this girl.
This one's dying. Chopper!
Have phenicol, cardiotonic,
and tialcillin ready for me!
[CHOPPER]
She has an infection?
Yes... And the infection isn't
from anywhere on this island.
[LUFFY grunts]
[KUREHA]
Don't worry, boy.
I'll make the bleeding kid
and the sick girl better.
You can rest easy, all right?
Those two are
my friends, okay?
[KUREHA]
I figured that, kid.
I'll save 'em, so don't worry.
Chopper! Let's begin treatment!
[LUFFY]
Those two are my friends, okay?
[LUFFY grunts]
I'm hungry.
So hungry.
Need meat.
[gasps]
[SANJI] Venison stew should
be simmered in a large pot
for three hours until all
the meat becomes tender.
[SANJI chuckles]
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[LUFFY]
Meat...
[gasps]
Venison...
[CHOPPER yelps]
[screams]
[CHOPPER]
Somebody help me!
[LUFFY, SANJI, CHOPPER yelling]
[LUFFY]
Hold on, meat!
[yelling continues]
[SANJI] Hold on, Luffy.
Let me cook this guy up first!
[yelling continues]
[LUFFY]
Nami!
[SANJI]
Nami, dear!
You look like you're all better!
[NAMI]
Getting there, thanks.
Right. One tasty venison
dish for Nami coming up!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[SANJI, LUFFY]
Come back!
[crashing]
[KUREHA]
I'm impressed.
Those guys are already
up and moving?
[NAMI]
Yeah, they are.
Can you tell me about
this talking deer?
[KUREHA]
Figured you'd ask about him.
[LUFFY]
Don't run away, meat!
[SANJI]
Don't eat it yet!
[CHOPPER yells]
[CHOPPER]
Leave me alone, humans!
[KUREHA]
His name is Chopper.
He's just a reindeer with
a blue nose, that's all.
[NAMI]
But normal reindeers don't talk.
[KUREHA] If he's different
from ordinary reindeers
in some way...
If he's different?
I am not food for you, okay?!
[KUREHA]
If he's different,
it's just because he ate a
Human Human Fruit, that's all.
A Human Human Fruit?
A Devil Fruit... right?
[KUREHA]
That's right.
He's still a reindeer,
but now he has the abilities
of a human, like talking
and walking upright.
[CHOPPER]
No! This way!
And also, he's a doctor.
I taught Chopper everything
that I know about the
field of medicine.
[ROBSON]
Hm?
[CHESS] Wapol, sir, that Straw
Hat is up there somewhere.
[WAPOL] Good. I'm beginning
to get a little hungry.
I'll eat the rubber
man for a snack.
Heh! Now, let's go!
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Dalton, please don't
die on us here!
We'll find him in time,
I'm sure of it! We have to!
Dalton, please hang
in there, okay?
So who's Dalton?
Don't just stand there!
Do something, Zoro!
Gotta bow...
Like I was saying,
don't stand there. Get a shovel!
Help us find Dalton!
[ZORO]
What was that thing?
Everyone! We found
Dalton over here!
What?!
Yea!
Fantastic!
[USOPP]
We're coming!
[VIVI]
Oh, Dalton!
Who's Dalton?
This is horrible.
I can't feel a heartbeat!
You should be one of my crew.
Please, old lady. We really
need to have a doctor on board.
[KUREHA] Luffy, you did
tell me that's your name,
isn't that right?
Yeah.
[KUREHA] And did you
just call me "old lady"?
Yeah, right. That's what
I said, old lady.
If I were you, I'd be a little
more careful of what I say!
[LUFFY yelps]
I'm still well within my
youthful 130s, thank you.
Jeez... You're a tough old hag.
[SANJI grunts]
Are you boys really asking
me to become a pirate?
Don't be ridiculous!
That would be an incredible
waste of my precious time.
Besides, I have no interest
in life on the sea.
[LUFFY grunts]
Those are all lame excuses.
It's about adventure, old woman!
[KUREHA]
Well, this one's a slow learner.
Didn't I just tell you to
watch what you say?
[CHOPPER]
So these guys are pirates?
[SANJI groans]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[ALL gasp]
[yells]
[LUFFY] Wait, food!
Come back here! Slow down!
[SANJI]
Get back here!
[KUREHA] That's enough
of that, idiots!
[CHOPPER yells]
[yelling continues]
[LUFFY]
One bite!
[SANJI] In just a few minutes,
I'm going to cook you
a delicious reindeer
dish you'll never forget!
[KUREHA]
I don't think so!
I'll eat you guys first
before I let that happen.
[LUFFY, SANJI]
Scary hag!
[SANJI, LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY] She's coming!
She's coming! She's coming...!
[NAMI]
I don't care about food.
I just want some
peace and quiet.
[NAMI] Snow? But that shouldn't
be inside the castle...
It's freezing.
[NAMI]
I'll close the door.
[CHOPPER]
No, you need to stay in bed!
After all, you still
have a fever.
[NAMI]
I don't think so.
It seems like it's
pretty much gone now.
I lost 'em... at least, for now.
Doctorine's medicine works
quickly to reduce the fever,
but the bacteria from the
Kestia will still remain
inside your body for a
little while longer.
So just take your antibiotic
shot and stay in bed.
[NAMI]
Thank you.
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
[NAMI] You're the one who's been
taking care of me, aren't you?
[NAMI chuckles]
[CHOPPER]
You just shut up!
I don't need thanks from you
or any other low‐life human!
[CHOPPER laughs]
Don't mock me!
Oh, never mind that!
I'm just being silly. Ha!
No, seriously,
I'm being such a fool.
[CHOPPER laughs]
He's not so good at
hiding his emotions.
[SANJI panting]
This castle's really strange.
It's freezing,
and filled with snow.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
It's cold in here!
[SANJI] Not the sharpest knife
in the drawer, are you Luffy?
Look at this.
[SANJI]
There's snow everywhere.
And look,
all the doors to the unused
rooms are frozen shut, too.
[LUFFY, SANJI yell]
[KUREHA] Come back
here just a moment, boys!
[KUREHA]
I said come back here!
[SANJI] You should rethink this
idea about asking the old hag
to join our crew. A real doctor
doesn't chase her patients
around a freaky snow‐filled
castle trying to kill them!
Is it true that you
guys are pirates?
Yes.
Really real pirates.
Real pirates.
So, you have a flag
with a skull on it?
We do. It's on our ship.
So you're really interested
in pirates, huh?
No, I'm not at all!
You idiot! Shut up!
All right, all right.
I get it. Now calm down.
But... one more thing.
Do you wanna come with us?
[yelps]
[NAMI] You could come sail
with us... out on the ocean.
Hm? If you did, that would
really help me out a lot.
If we had a doctor on the ship,
then I wouldn't have to stay
in this place three
more days, right?
I think you'd have a really
good time if you came.
[CHOPPER] No! That's crazy!
You realize I'm a reindeer!
I don't belong on a ship
with a bunch of humans!
[CHOPPER] I mean, just look
at me. I'm a reindeer,
but I walk on two legs and
I talk and everything.
Animals aren't supposed
to be able to do that stuff.
I know, but if you're trying to
scare me off, it isn't working.
[CHOPPER]
But I have a blue nose.
[LUFFY]
There you are, meat!
[LUFFY, SANJI]
Come here, deer!
[CHOPPER screams]
[SANJI, LUFFY]
Come back!
[NAMI]
Uh...
[clattering]
[KUREHA sighing] Those brats
sure can run, can't they?
I don't much like what you
were doing there, girl.
[NAMI]
Hm?
[KUREHA] Trying to tempt
my reindeer away from me
without my permission.
What, I need your
permission to make a move
on a man all of a sudden?
[KUREHA cackles]
No, I suppose you don't.
If you wanna take him away
from here, go ahead.
But I must warn you, it won't
be as easy as you think.
Chopper has a
scar on his heart.
A deep one my
medicine can't cure.
From the moment he was born,
everyone including his parents
turned their backs on him.
[NAMI gasps]
[KUREHA] All because he
was born with a blue nose.
He was forced to walk at
the back of the group,
separated from the
rest of the reindeer.
Even though he was just
a helpless, new‐born.
Then one day...
he ate a Devil Fruit
and he became even more of an
outcast than he had been before.
[KUREHA] The other reindeer
pressured him to leave the herd.
His blue nose already
made him different,
but now he wasn't like the
ordinary reindeer at all.
Still, he was lonely
and wanted friends,
so he went down to a village,
walking on two legs
as humans do.
[VILLAGER C] Hey. What is
that creature over there?
[KUREHA] But even
walking on two legs,
he didn't look anything
like the humans.
And for some reason, his nose
was still blue, as well.
[VILLAGER D]
It looks like a yeti!
[VILLAGER E]
It's dangerous, I'm sure.
Get the children inside quickly!
[VILLAGER C]
A gun! Bring me a gun!
[VILLAGER D]
Yeah, shoot him!
[VILLAGER F]
Quick, before he runs away!
[VILLAGER E]
Get 'em!
[VILLAGER F]
Yeah, got em!
Stay away from us, freak!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[KUREHA] He didn't
know what was wrong.
He couldn't understand why
they reacted to his appearance
with so much fear and anger.
[VILLAGER C]
Stay away, monster!
[KUREHA] He had gone to
the village seeking friends,
but they called him a monster
and drove him away.
He was no longer a reindeer,
but he wasn't a human, either.
He was something in between.
And so he lived
alone after that.
Caught between two worlds
that wouldn't accept him.
Now that you've heard his story,
do you think you can heal
the scar on his heart?
[SANJI] Luffy! Check out the
door at the front entrance.
It's wide open!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY grunts]
No wonder it's so cold in here.
[SANJI]
Anyway, let's close it.
With it open like that,
there's not much difference
between inside and
outside the castle.
[CHOPPER] Hey! Stop it!
Don't touch that door! Get away!
[SANJI, LUFFY]
Huh?
[SANJI] Never mind him.
Let's close it.
Or we're gonna freeze to death.
[LUFFY]
That's a good point.
Stop! Didn't you guys
hear what I said?
[CHOPPER]
Get back!
[gasps]
[CHOPPER growls]
What is with this guy? What the
hell is he so angry about?
[SANJI]
Hey! Come over here a second.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[SANJI]
Look up there.
[LUFFY gasps]
Uh...
[birds chirping]
[SANJI] It's a bunch
of baby snow birds.
See? If we closed
the door, they'd fall.
[LUFFY] So that's the reason
they're leaving it open.
[birds chirping]
[SANJI, LUFFY gasp]
It's freezing!
Hold up a sec.
[SANJI]
Yeah?
[LUFFY yells]
That weird reindeer guy.
Wasn't he speaking earlier?
Now that you mention it,
I remember him walking
on two legs, too.
[BOTH]
He's a monster!
[LUFFY]
Okay, let's get this straight.
He walks upright and talks.
[SANJI]
But not human.
[LUFFY]
Has fur...
[SANJI]
He's little...
[LUFFY]
...and becomes big.
[SANJI, LUFFY]
Clearly a monster!
[LUFFY] What a cool guy!
I bet he's really interesting!
Hey wait. I know!
He should join us!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[LUFFY] Hey, Nami!
Did you see the reindeer?
[NAMI]
Come on, guys.
Can't you just leave
him alone already?
[SANJI] What, just because
we were trying to eat him?
[NAMI]
You don't understand.
Chopper's had a really
difficult life.
[LUFFY]
Oh, yeah?
[NAMI] But apparently, he did
eventually find someone
who would accept
him for who he was.
[LUFFY]
Really? Who was that?
One the next One Piece!
"An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!