[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[yelling]
Come on! What are
you doing, giant guy?
Get this rock off me!
Hey, you've got some
pretty good timing.
So what are you doin'
in this area, anyway?
What's goin' on?
[USOPP] Get away, get away,
get away, get away!
[gasps, yelps]
[LUFFY]
Someone did this!
Someone else!
[DORRY grunts, groans]
But who?!
[DORRY groans]
You low‐lifes!
[USOPP yelps]
Ten thousand Kilogram Press!
[BROGGY]
Huh? What the‐‐?
I am Mr. 3...
That's a codename, of course,
which is necessary
in my line of work.
I am an artist of sorts,
and this is my assistant.
All the best artists
require assistants, you see.
Her name is Miss Golden Week.
Mr. 3? The Wax Wax Fruit man?
[MR. 5]
That's right.
Mr. 3 the "candle man."
His body creates wax, which
he can then control as he likes.
[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY]
You guys are gonna pay for this!
[yells]
[LUFFY]
"The Devilish Candle!
Tears of Regret
and Tears of Anger."
[MR. THREE cackles]
[BROGGY grunting]
[BROGGY]
What's going on here? Tell me!
Going on? Of course it's
lost on someone like you.
What's going on
is that I'm creating
a work of art
with your assistance.
[MR. 3 chuckles]
[gasps]
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
[MISS VALENTINE] Stand still
like a good little girl.
Did you actually think
that someone like you could
escape from an organization
like Baroque Works?
[VIVI growls]
After all, your
friend over there
has a big bounty on his head,
and look at what
happened to him.
[chuckles] Consider this
our "thank you"
for what happened
at Whiskey Peak.
You should learn to mind
your own business, you pathetic
group of wannabe pirates.
It would be quite
beneficial to your health.
By the way, we have
your swordsman friend.
And we've captured
the other girl
that you brought
along with you as well.
[LUFFY]
So you caught... Zoro?
[MR. 5]
Damn right.
[LUFFY] In that case, you're
in more trouble than I thought.
Well...
Let's see how big you talk...
...after one of my
Kicky Bombs blows up
that little face of yours.
[LUFFY]
Try whatever tricks you want.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
This should be fun.
[MR. 5 growls]
[gasps]
[VIVI]
Luffy, no!
[MR. 5 growls]
Die!
[explosions]
[MR. 5 pants]
[LUFFY grunts]
You weak little fool.
[VIVI]
Luffy!
No... please...
Luffy! Get up!
[MR. 5]
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Usopp! Karoo!
[BROGGY groans, growls]
[MR. 3 laughs]
Damn you!
Struggling is pointless.
Once my candle jacket
solidifies around you,
it'll become as hard as
iron, and it's impossible
to break through.
[BROGGY groans]
There's no denying
that you giants
are very strong. But once
you've been captured,
that strength doesn't
do you any good at all.
None.
All that I had to do
was use my brain.
There would be no sense
in trying to defeat you
in a physical fight.
You were so busy
enjoying your great win
that capturing you was easy.
[BROGGY growls]
[MR. 3]
Don't glare at me like that!
It's positively terrifying.
You should be celebrating,
shouldn't you?
At long last, your battle
with Dorry the Blue Ogre
has come to an end.
You fought on this
island for 100 years
for your precious pride.
Shouldn't such a long lasting
battle make victory
all the more sweet?
I mean really,
it's an accomplishment!
Even if it required
a little outside help.
Come on, give me
a little smile.
[BROGGY] Shut up! What would
you know about this?
[MR. 3 laughs]
[MR. 3] Of course, the real
victor in all of this is...
...me.
[MR. 3 chuckles]
The bounties placed
on your heads long ago
remain in place to this day.
Today you're worth
200,000,000 berries.
Quite a handsome sum.
Bounties?
[MR. 3]
Big bounties.
I feel as if I've uncovered
a long‐lost treasure.
[VIVI] So that's what
you're after here!
Mr. 3...
[gasps]
Here's the girl.
[MR. 5]
Alabasta's sneaky spy.
[MR. 3]
It's about time.
I was positively
sick of waiting.
You're full of nothing
but dirty tricks!
I can't believe you!
Putting a bomb in Dorry's
alcohol was low, even for you!
What?!
[MR. 3]
Uh...
The barrels?
You did something to the
drinks that I gave Dorry?
[BROGGY laughs]
Dorry, how was your drink?
Hit the spot, didn't it?
Yes.
It tasted almost
godly in fact.
[BROGGY] No! That must
be what Dorry meant...
[MR. 3] Hm. You're an
annoying little girl, Princess‐‐
giving away our
secrets like that.
But that's all right.
There isn't anything he
can do about it now anyway.
[MR. 3]
Candle...
...Lock!
[yelps]
[chuckles] Mr. 5!
Bring the swordsman
and the other girl.
Time to begin.
[yells]
Giant... Candle... Set!
[gasps]
[growls]
[gasping]
[MR. 3 chuckles]
[MR. 3 laughs]
[gasps] So this is what
Mr. 3's capable of?!
What is that thing?
[gasps]
[MR. 5]
Here are the others.
[NAMI, ZORO grunt]
[NAMI groans]
[MR. 5]
It's just sad.
[gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
[MR. 5]
Idiots like these shoulda been
a lot easier for me to catch.
Shoulda caught 'em
the first time.
How embarrassin'.
No need to be ashamed.
You can't help the fact
that you're weak, after all.
[MR. 5]
What was that?
It's nothing.
Now, please just hurry
and get the candles set up.
[NAMI]
Candles?
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI]
What is that thing?!
Nothing good.
I'm sorry, you guys!
But... Vivi...
What happened? I thought
you were with Luffy!
I was... but now...
[MR. 5] If you're wonderin'
about the Straw Hat,
I saw to that
little runt myself.
He didn't put up
much of a fight either.
Yeah, right.
[MR. THREE chuckles]
[MR. THREE laughs]
Welcome, one and all,
to my famous candle service set.
I guess this is
what it feels like
to be a candle stuck
on a birthday cake.
Guys...
What's that spinning up there?
I can't move. Great.
It's not surprising to me that
they don't want
us moving around.
That's what "captured" means.
Damn... That stuff's hard.
And I can't put much
strength behind my swing
from this angle.
Something's falling.
[laughs] I do hope you
enjoy my candle service.
You may have noticed
the wax flakes
that are falling from above.
You'll eventually be covered
and turned into wax figures.
You'll become perfectly lifelike
statues for my collection.
Something that even I
couldn't achieve on my own.
I will literally
capture your spirits
and encase them
forever in wax shells.
It will be a true masterpiece.
You will die for my art.
I don't think so, you freak!
I have no interest in
dying for whatever it is
you consider art!
Hey, giant!
Why are you laying
there doing nothing
when you could be beating the
crap out of this candle guy?
Now he is gonna make
one huge statue.
[MR. 3] Heh! You can
try to convince him,
but your efforts
will be useless.
He's a little blue
at the moment.
You see, he just realized how
unfairly he won his last fight,
and he's lost the
heart to celebrate.
He killed his dear friend Dorry,
with whom he had
fought for 100 years.
Dorry was injured.
But he didn't notice.
Just imagine how much pain
Dorry must have been in.
He didn't stand a chance.
You did shed
a few tears, though.
Perhaps you were crying
for your friend?
[laughs]
Now it's no use.
There's no undoing it.
He's dead! And it's
all your fault!
[MR. THREE laughs]
[BROGGY]
I should have seen it.
I knew something
strange was going on.
[BROGGY] From the moment
we first began to fight,
I knew Dorry was
hiding something,
but I couldn't tell what it was.
You say that you knew it?
You're lying!
If you knew something was wrong,
why didn't you stop the fight?
Why didn't you give him
a chance to rest?
I didn't see one shred of pity
in the way you ruthlessly
cut him down.
[MR. 3 laughs]
[BROGGY growls]
[BROGGY] You know nothing
about honorable duels!
Someone like you could
never understand my tears.
What do you know
about the way of Elbaf?
You think that I would shame
a warrior who hid the fact
that he was weakened so that
he could continue to fight?
Only a truly great warrior
would go to such lengths,
and such a man isn't
interested in pity!
Huh?
[BROGGY]
Now...
I know what really happened.
And I must do
something about it.
I'm going to finish this
with my own two hands.
[BROGGY growls]
[MR. 3 gasps]
[BROGGY] That's the least
I can do for Dorry.
He was a great warrior
and my dear friend!
[BROGGY yells]
[gasps] Broggy!
[groaning]
[NAMI, VIVI]
Broggy!
His chatterin' was
gettin' on my nerves.
[LUFFY]
U... Usopp... Usopp...
They have to... pay for this.
[weakly] Oh, yeah.
Those jerks have to pay.
[LUFFY]
You can't... take this either?
[squaks]
Heh. All right.
Then it's settled.
Let's go beat them senseless.
[NAMI]
Broggy!
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
Big fool!
[MR. 5 chuckles]
[MR. 3]
It seems that I miscalculated.
I forgot how freakishly strong
these dumb giants can be.
[BROGGY growls]
It looks like you're
going to require
more complete restraints.
Wax‐wax... Handcuffs!
[MR. 3]
Still going!
[NAMI, VIVI gasp]
And now for the finishing touch.
Take this!
[screams]
[MR. 3 cackles]
It'll be tough for you
to move now, won't it?
[laughs]
You really are despicable.
Now! Let's get these
candles going faster!
It's time to turn these
people into beautiful,
artistic wax statues!
[MR. 3 laughs]
[NAMI coughs]
My chest is starting to hurt.
The wax is starting
to get into our lungs.
At this rate, he's gonna turn us
into wax from the inside out!
That's it.
Make it look like you're
in as much pain as possible!
That's perfect.
Expressions of agony
are what I seek
to achieve in my art!
The finished product
will be simply splendid!
You must die filled with terror!
[NAMI] This is what you
call art, you creepy,
weird‐haired freak?!
You guys are gonna regret this!
You're gonna pay for what
you did to Broggy and Dorry
and for what you're
trying to do to us!
[MR. 3] Yell and scream
all you want to, little girl.
No one can help you now.
[BROGGY]
A century...
[BROGGY] For 100 years,
Dorry and I dueled
day in and day out,
fighting endlessly.
We battled for our pride,
as is the way of the
warriors of Elbaf.
We fought with honor
and with strength.
And still, we are
subjected to this.
Why has this happened to us?!
[BROGGY] Must we be
forced to meet our end
in such a way? Must we?
It isn't fair for a
warrior to die such
a dishonorable death!
Why can I not die in battle?!
[laughs] Hold that look.
Yes, that's it.
Such grief... Such sorrow!
And just the right
amount of anger.
How marvelous.
[MR. 3 laughs]
[BROGGY]
Elbaf, please!
This isn't good.
My hands won't move.
Can't we do something?
I don't wanna die like this!
My body's already
beginning to turn stiff.
What are we supposed to do?
[NAMI]
Zoro, do something!
[ZORO]
Hey, giant.
[BROGGY]
Huh?
You can still move, right?
[BROGGY grunts]
[ZORO]
Good. So can I.
I say we take 'em down together.
What do you think?
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[BROGGY grunts]
Hold on a second.
What are you doing? Are you...?
Yeah.
Quit messing around‐‐
your not gonna
cut your own legs off!
I'm not messing around at all.
It's the only way to get us
out of this situation.
Are you in or out?
Are you insane? No way!
Even if you get down from here,
you won't get far without legs!
[ZORO] There's no way to
know for sure until we try.
So are you saying you'd
rather just sit here and die?
Why should we make it easy
for those guys to kill us?
Dying quietly without a struggle
doesn't make you
any less dead.
Right?
The girl was right.
This guy's insane.
He's bluffing.
There's no way he would do
something as crazy as that.
He's just trying to act tough
so his friends will feel better.
[BROGGY chuckles]
[BROGGY] That runt's got spirit,
I'll give him that!
He's doing better than I am.
I had actually begun
to lose the will to fight.
All right, I'm in.
Let's cut them to pieces.
[NAMI] You're not serious
about this, are you?
How are you planning on
fighting them afterward?
[ZORO]
Who knows?
But... I plan to win.
[MR. 3]
Who are these people?!
They're completely nuts!
[VIVI] What kind of man
is he? And why...
Why do I feel like I've seen
that look somewhere before?
[IGARAM]
Princess Vivi!
[gasps]
Sometimes it takes more
strength to live than to die.
Wait. I'll fight with you!
You what?
Good. Get ready.
And now... Let's go!
Don't be foolish!
What can you hope to accomplish?
[ZORO groans]
[KAROO, LUFFY, USOPP screaming]
[yelling]
[ALL yelling]
[LUFFY]
Hey!
When I get back,
I'm gonna kick your asses!
Huh?
Let's get 'em, Usopp!
Yeah!
And bird... guy?
Luffy! Usopp!
Karoo!
We're here, Broggy.
Don't worry, we'll pick up
where you left off.
Thanks, Usopp.
[NAMI]
Beat them beyond recognition!
Show 'em "expressions
of pain and agony"
they won't soon forget!
[LUFFY]
Oh, I'm goin' to...
These guys messed up
the best duel ever!
They're in some serious trouble,
and they're gonna answer to me!
[MR. 3] So you're
the one with the highest
bounty in the East Blue?
My, how low Marine
standards have fallen.
It's almost tragic, really.
Is that... your hair?
You just shut up!
Dude it's... um... on fire...
Hush, you!
Yes, he has weird hair.
Now, could you
break this pillar?!
We're about to turn
into wax statues here.
Oh, you guys in trouble?
No, no trouble at all.
Wait... Zoro, your leg!
Yeah I made it about
halfway through, I'd say.
[NAMI] And how exactly is
that no trouble at all?!
So, Luffy, what do ya think?
Could you go ahead and take
care of this pillar for us?
I think I've done enough.
Yeah, no problem.
Hah! I wouldn't be so sure!
[LUFFY]
I don't know what it is...
...but let's break it.
[USOPP]
Right! Let's do it!
Usopp the brave warrior
of the sea is ready to fight!
[KAROO squaks]
[NAMI] Hurry, will ya?
We're dying here!
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... Mallet!
[USOPP] All right!
The pillar's broken now!
[LUFFY]
Hey, why didn't you run away?
[NAMI]
Because we can't move!
[ZORO]
We're kinda stuck in the wax.
[LUFFY] Oh. Well, that
makes sense, then.
[NAMI] Hurry up and get
us out of this thing!
[LUFFY]
Uh, no.
[NAMI]
Just quit joking and hurry up!
[LUFFY] What can I say? I don't
feel like saving you guys.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A Hex on Luffy! Colors Trap!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!