[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] In the ruins
surrounding Giant Jack
spirit and sword clashed as
battle lines were crossed,
and lives hung in the balance.
[OHM]
Eisen Whip!
[gasps]
Axe Dial!
[groans]
[NARRATOR] As this fierce
battle for survival raged on,
the persistent Shandorian
Warrior Laki fell
at the lightning rod
hands of God Eneru.
Laki!
[NARRATOR] After being swallowed
by the giant snake,
Nami, Gan Fall and Aisa
met someone they
never expected they would meet
in the serpent's stomach.
[LUFFY]
"Bursting Slash! Zoro vs. Ohm!"
[roars]
[ZORO] The first thing
I'm gonna have to do is
take care of that snake!
[WYPER]
Did it work?
[roaring]
[WYPER] Not enough.
I guess I'll just keep trying!
[WYPER growls]
[roaring]
[ZORO panting]
[ZORO]
This is getting really old.
That extendable sword
he's using is a pain.
And that snake...
I already know defeating him
first isn't exactly gonna be
a walk in the park.
But I have to get Nami
and the old Knight
out of that thing's
gut right now.
There's still time. Since
they were swallowed whole,
I would bet they're
not dead yet.
[SNAKE roaring]
[ZORO] But it won't be
that way for long.
[OHM]
Eisen Whip!
Not again!
[ZORO grunts]
That bastard. Where is he?
[OHM]
Eisen Whip!
It's impossible to escape
from my attacks.
Just as there's no one who
can escape the reality of death.
It would be futile to try.
Those who don't accept
that are foolish.
You're pathetic.
It's useless to
try to defeat me.
You don't even have enough sense
to realize you're about to die.
You're so focused on
the gold you seek
that you cannot see
anything else.
Not even the inevitable fate
that lies before you.
How sad.
[ZORO] All right. He's gotta
be around here somewhere.
Where's he attacking from next?
[OHM]
Eisen Whip!
[ZORO grunts]
What's goin' on here?
How come he always knows
exactly where I am?
It's as if he could see me
from behind that wall.
Who is this mad man?
And what's up with
those glasses?
[DIVINE H bleating]
Now prepare to die!
[yelling]
This has nothing to do with you.
[DIVINE H groans]
[OHM]
Another voice has disappeared.
There are only a few survivors
in the Upper Ruins now.
Just five people,
and two animals, remain.
No...
I'm wrong.
[OHM]
Eisen Whip!
You're dead!
Make that four people.
[SHANDORIAN A groaning]
[ZORO]
Two Swords Style!
[OHM grunts]
Hawk Wave!
Eisen Back Wall!
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
An iron wall...?
[OHM]
This sword is an iron cloud.
[OHM] You didn't think clouds
had a set shape did you?
You!
Eisen Fan!
Eisen Fork!
[ZORO yelps]
Eisen Rapier! Ha!
[groans]
[ZORO]
He's predicting my movements.
Why can't I avoid it?
What's the matter?
Keeping your distance
doesn't do you any good
when you depend on your sword.
[ZORO]
You're wrong about that.
Huh?
[growls]
Thirty-six Caliber Phoenix!
Eisen Whip!
[ZORO]
How could he block it?
[OHM grunts]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO]
Dammit!
[OHM] That's quite an
interesting technique
you've developed,
Blue Sea Dweller.
[ZORO panting]
[OHM] I wonder if
you'll try that again.
Unfortunately, even if
you lose sight of me,
I'll always know
where you are...
[ZORO panting]
...by using Mantora.
[HOLY growls]
Is that supposed
to intimidate me?
I'm a Shandorian warrior!
[yelling]
[HOLY growls]
[SHANDORIAN B groans]
[HOLY grunting]
[OHM] Looks like we just
lost another one.
Now there are two animals
and three people left.
[OHM] But soon there
will be two animals
and only two people.
[SNAKE roars]
[OHM] So you're the leader of
the Blue Sea People up here.
You and your comrades
all put up a good fight.
However, my sword is now
pointed directly at your heart.
[OHM]
Say your prayers, swordsman!
[ZORO]
Don't be an idiot.
I never pray for anything.
[OHM]
That's too bad.
What sets people apart
from one another
is their ability to survive.
You should use your resources.
I'm through listening
to your arrogant lectures!
I don't have to see you.
I can follow that
extendable sword of yours
and know exactly where you are!
[OHM] Hmph. Well, the moment
you find me, you die!
One life holds 36
worldly desires.
[ZORO]
Two lives hold 72.
Three lives hold
108 worldly desires.
Three swords...
108 Caliber Phoenix!
[OHM] He broke
through the iron clouds!
[OHM screams]
[SNAKE roars]
[LUFFY, NAMI, AISA, PIERRE
scream]
[LUFFY grunts]
[NAMI whimpers]
[NAMI screams]
Ew! Ew! Ew!
[PIERRE caws]
[AISA screaming]
[GAN FALL gasps]
[NAMI screams]
It's a dead end!
We're all gonna die!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
[LUFFY grunting]
Okay. This Mystery Cave is
getting really annoying.
[NAMI grunts]
I told you this isn't a cave.
We're in the snake's stomach!
Where are you?
Ahh! Nami!
Nami are you okay?!
Talk to me! Nami!
[LUFFY grunts]
I'm right here, you idiot.
[gasps] Let me go please!
You're gonna squeeze
me to death!
[GAN FALL] I'm glad to see
you're unharmed.
Let go!
Ah!
[gasps]
[NAMI] What are you
doing Aisa? Stop it!
He is our enemy!
He's responsible for
ruthlessly taking away
the Shandorian's homeland!
So now... I'm gonna
take his head.
I don't get it.
How is taking the head of the
Sky Knight gonna fix anything?
[AISA]
He's not just a knight.
He was the leader
of the Skypieans
before Eneru showed up!
The Skypieans were the ones
who drove all of us Shandorians
out of our homes!
The Shandorians were driven out
of their homes 400 years ago.
So there's no way he had
anything to do with it.
[GAN FALL] If taking my head
would satisfy your people,
I would gladly sacrifice it.
[gasps]
[GAN FALL] Unfortunately, just
my head wouldn't be enough.
The level of hostility between
the Shandorians and
the Skypieans hasn't changed,
and with good reason.
Our ancestors took
your homeland away.
What a horrifying thing
to go through.
I don't think I'll ever
be able to find a way
to apologize for that.
Time alone will not
heal this wound,
therefore I regret my
helplessness in this situation.
If at all possible,
I would like to apologize
to the Shandorians
who have spent
the last 400 years
searching for their homes.
I would like to apologize
to them all, one by one.
I am truly sorry.
Listen to him.
He's been trying to make sure
that everyone's getting along.
He wants the citizens to
live peacefully in the sky.
So you really shouldn't--
We will never be able to get
along and live peacefully!
Not with the bad guys!
That's just it, they're not bad.
What's bad is when
people can't coexist
because they belong
to different races!
Right?
[yells]
Aisa!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[gasping]
Why did you stop me?
Idiot!
[LUFFY]
He was apologizing.
Probably not the best
time to kill a man.
[whimpering]
[AISA cries]
[ROBIN]
Shandora. The City of Gold.
And if the golden bell
said to be in the middle
of the city isn't here,
where is it?
The belfry was probably
engraved with poneglyphs.
[ROBIN] If that's the case,
then the city probably fell
in order to protect them.
[ROBIN]
Even after all this time,
the belfry and the poneglyphs
should still be here.
They're hidden somewhere.
Hey, what's that?
A rail used to run
through this city.
[ROBIN]
But this is new.
Something was moved out of here.
I wonder what it was.
[ENERU laughs]
Isn't it amazing?
Even after being shot up into
the sky, the city of Shandora
still majestically
exists in this way.
[ENERU laughs] Even if it's a
city that everyone knows about,
how can it show off
its lovely figure
if it's covered by clouds?
[ENERU] I'm the only one
who could see it.
I discovered it. The former
Gods never even noticed.
And who are you?
I'm God.
[ENERU]
You're quite intelligent.
One might guess that you're an
archeologist from the Blue Sea
world by how fast you
found this city of ruins.
It took us several months
to find the same thing.
I suppose it's easier if
you can read the letters
on the ruins, right?
Unfortunately, the gold you're
looking for isn't here anymore.
I'm afraid you're a few
years too late for that.
The gold?
Well, you're right about that.
I couldn't find any.
You must've been
the one who removed it.
[ENERU] Gold is a wonderful
thing to have and
that glittering metal suits
me well, don't you think?
[ROBIN] Then you must also
have taken the golden bell
that was once here.
[ENERU]
Hm? There was a golden bell?
[ROBIN gasps]
He doesn't know!
Well I'm very intrigued.
What did you learn by reading
those letters on the bell?
[ROBIN] Actually, it's too bad,
I never got to read them.
If you say it wasn't here when
you arrived, it must not exist.
I guess the huge golden
bell and belfry that were
the pride of Shandora must have
only been another legend.
It's a shame that I'll never be
able to lay my eyes on them.
No, wait.
It's... It's actually
right here.
It's here in the sky!
When this island was blown
into the sky 400 years ago
and the Upper Yard was born--
Or, when "Godland" was born,
it was said that the
loud chimes of a bell
could be heard ringing
throughout the entire nation.
[bell tolls]
[ENERU] The elder
inhabitants of this land
called it the island's
singing voice.
But that wasn't it.
It was the bell!
The bell made of gold!
Amazing!
Soon the entire game
will be over.
Only eight minutes left.
That's not long at all. In fact,
it gives me plenty of time
to look for the golden bell.
[ENERU chuckles]
[ROBIN] So the golden
bell is in the sky?
Which means the
poneglyphs are, too!
[laughing]
Hm?
[MAN A panting]
Interesting.
It sounds like there's
a maggot on the island.
[gasps]
[MAN A panting]
[horn blares]
There you go. You two
are gonna be just fine.
I promise.
[PAGAYA]
Hm. They're still unconscious?
They are, but I think
they'll wake up soon.
Their condition
has been improving.
Yes, dear, I'm sure.
You've taken such excellent care
of them and good things happen
to good people.
They'll be better in no time.
Conis...
When the sky finally
becomes peaceful,
I'd like to be able to show
everyone the hospitality
they once knew to
my heart's content.
Including you.
Thank you, Father.
[SUU]
Suu!
Suu! Suu! Suu!
[PAGAYA]
What's the matter with you, Suu?
Did we forget to feed you?
Oh, Suu, are you in pain?
Or did something happen?
[SUU chirping]
[MAN A groans]
[PAGAYA]
Are-- Are you...?
[MAN A]
Yes, I'm one of the men
who used to serve Gan Fall
when he was God.
[PAGAYA] So you're one of
the Divine Warriors!
[MAN A groans] We were in a
closed off area, and then...
[PAGAYA] Goodness, what on
earth happened to you?
Conis, he needs
your help right away!
Yes, of course father!
[MAN A]
No wait!
My family's on Angel Island.
Please... Please help.
[PAGAYA]
I will.
I know everyone's worried
about all of you.
Let everyone know Eneru--he's
planning to return everything!
[PAGAYA]
What?
[MAN A] Skypiea will be dropped
back into the Blue Sea world,
and this entire nation
will no longer exist!
But that... can't be true!
[CONIS gasping]
There's no time to lose.
You must tell everyone.
Do it, now!
[MAN A]
Our lives will soon be over.
Eneru is planning to eliminate
every living person
from the sky!
Eliminate everyone from the sky?
But wait... If he succeeds
in that then...
...he won't have
a place to live.
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would he want to do that?
He built a ship.
The Ark Maxim.
[PAGAYA]
Ark Maxim...?
Hey, what are y--?
[gasps]
We were forced to spend
the last six years of our lives
building that ship!
[CONIS yelps]
[gasping]
Father!
When the sky finally
becomes peaceful,
I'd like to be able to show
everyone the hospitality
they once knew to
my heart's content.
Including you.
[CONIS]
Father!
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[LUFFY]
Let's break out of here!
[ENERU]
It's almost time.
I will finally put an end
to this survival game.
[ZORO] Hold on! The ground!
It's breaking apart!
[WYPER] Is this the homeland
we've been fighting for?
For over 400 years?
[ENERU] Well, it looks like
we have another player.
[ZORO, WYPER, GAN FALL]
You will die!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Collapsing Upper Ruins!
The Quintet for the Finale!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!