Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Shut up! Just let me go!
I'm guessing Lucci's
that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's him.
From what that freak told us,
he's the only one they've
got guarding Robin.
Our best bet's to
send Luffy after them.
Luffy, since you're
raring to go,
you can hunt down
that pigeon guy.
Let me go! Let me go!
Excluding Luffy, we've
got a headcount of six.
And he said there're only
five CP9 agents with keys.
So I say we spread out,
take them down,
then catch up with Luffy.
If they drag her across those
gates, we'll never get her back!
It's a race against time!
Then let's get going!
Take 'em down, or we die trying!
Yeah!
Good luck!
There's no help
for you, Nico Robin!
You can keep wishing
for them to come,
but they'll never find their
way to the Gates of Justice!
Quit hiding from me,
you pigeon loving jerk!
Chapapapapapapapapapapa!
You've come face to face
with the gossip
loving Silent Fukurou!
I suppose you want my key?
Great, just before
I could refill my cola.
Chapa.
Yoyoi! You damn
despicable pirate!
Your hopeless quest for your
friend's freedom has doomed you
to die a dreadful
death by my hand!
So you're too afraid
to face the mi--
It's not empty.
This room better not be empty!
Dammit. I'm getting'
real tired of this.
What's wrong? Just relax.
Yo! Yoyoi! Ha! Yoyoi!
Dear girl. Are you ready?
That is--Ready to die?
Yeah right, like I'm gonna
fight you to the death.
All I need to do is get
the key and get out of here!
Here goes nothing!
Hey assassin! Where's your key?
Let's see.
Yes. As you say. The key.
Yeah? Yeah? Go on.
Yes. The key.
Right, right, the key.
Yes, the key.
Good, that's it.
Why, the key is
right here, of course.
Oh, how peculiar!
Where did it go?
I thought I had it here.
Or was it here?
Jeez, this guy is annoying.
That won't do at all, I fear.
The water needs
to be much warmer
if you want to make
good tea, Mademoiselle.
You can't ever ignore
the golden rules, right?
Warm your teapot beforehand,
boil fresh water and pour it in.
Now, you let it set
until the bubbles
are the size of little coins.
By doing that, you give
the leaves some time
to dance around in the water.
Spreading their flavor and
aroma everywhere they go.
After that, you quickly
place a cover over the pot,
and let it steam for one minute.
Finally, you pour it into
warm teacups and enjoy.
A bit of consideration
makes a world of difference.
Wow, you're an expert!
Well, I am a chef.
Thank you, for the lesson.
My pleasure!
Wow, looks like I made it.
Well, at least I hope so.
I've had enough of these stairs.
Robin! Hey! Robin! It's me!
Hey! Hello?
Damn. Too late.
Guess they left already.
Ugh, that jerk. Oh!
Wait a second. Right!
It doesn't matter, since
I know where they're going!
All I gotta do is head
to the Gates of Justice
and I'll catch 'em in no time!
Why don't you save me the
trouble of cutting you down?
You have the key? Or not?
Don't be a fool.
You may have been a
bit of a disappointment
back at the Galley-La mansion,
but I expect to be
entertained this time.
If you pirates
could make it this far,
then you're far more capable
than I gave you credit for.
Humph. Got that right.
Make that mistake again,
and you'll be dead.
Maybe so. You're like a beast.
That savage look in your eyes.
But I can be
pretty beastly myself.
You know, for the record,
I'm the strongest
swordsman in all of CP-9.
This won't be easy.
Hmph. Two Sword Style?
Tempest Kick.
Sorry, I use four swords.
Well that's fine by me.
Your whole body is a weapon,
isn't it? What's the difference?
Hmph.
Seventy-two Caliber--
Tempest Kick White Thunder!
--Phoenix!
Shave!
This is fun!
Yeah? Well, I don't have
time for fun right now.
Shame. Guess you'd better
kill me quickly, then.
Tempest Kick Slaughter!
He's throwing out
everything at once.
What is this?
Bastard. Are you
taking this seriously?
Of course! I'm quite impressed!
But you said you were
in a hurry, didn't you?
My new power should
speed things up for you.
Wh--what the hell?
This sure isn't
what I was expecting.
A little gardening is nice and
all, but this is way overboard.
It's like we're outside!
Okay whatever.
I gotta focus on getting
the key to Robin's handcuffs!
Here we go!
Careful. Carefu--
No, don't stop.
Just keep quiet
and you'll be fine!
One step at a time.
Easy does it. Eas--
That was scary!
Okay, time for round 2.
Move in quietly.
Run away quietly.
Take the key and leave
a hero. No need to fight.
That's right.
I'm Sniper King, but today,
I'm Lucky King, too!
Hey! Heart!
You're beating too loud!
Cut it out! Stop!
That's not what I meant!
You stupid heart!
Do your job, damn it!
You trying to kill me?
Wait, heart massage!
Yeah heart massage, here we go!
That was scary!
Okay, pull it together.
I got this. I can do
anything I put my mind to.
I'm a miracle worker!
A magic man! Probably.
I can do it. I can do anything.
I can. Huh? What is that? A bee?
Go away! Shoo! Shoo! Huh?
That's not a flower, you know!
There's no pollen
in there! Trust me!
Go away! I said go!
What's with that look?
Oh, you're kidding me.
Oh no, you don't.
Don't you dare.
Don't. Don't do it. No.
My nose! Why?
Damn it!
Now I'm right back
where I started!
But hey, he still
didn't wake up!
This guy's seriously out cold!
If I can just go a few steps
without anything ridiculous
happening, I've got this!
Tiptoe. Tiptoe.
Easy does it, Usopp.
Here we go.
Still asleep. Still asleep!
Just a bit more. An itty
bitty bit. Almost there.
A rooster? Are you kidding me?
I'm right there and
the noisiest bird
in the whole stinking
world shows up?
If he crows, I'm finished!
That assassin guy will wake up
and wipe the floor with me!
What's that look?
Are you gonna crow?
You're gonna crow,
aren't you? No, please.
Please. Sh. Sh.
Rooster. Mr. Rooster.
Master Rooster, sir.
I'm begging you, don't crow!
Don't say a word!
Just-- just take some time
and think it over! Please!
Chirp!
Roosters don't chirp! Come on!
Oh. Hey pirate.
Curse you rooster!
Guess it's time to
kick your ass, then.
Curse you!
He's strong.
So it's you, huh?
You're the slingshot guy that
burned down the flag, right?
Too bad sniping
won't help you here.
He just woke up from his nap
and he's already
hitting that hard?
Sorry pal, that punch
was kinda sloppy.
Not my style.
Bet it hurt, though.
I know I look scary,
but I'm no sadist.
I like my fights
clean and simple.
He's got Devil Fruit powers?
The Dog-Dog Fruit, Model Wolf!
I'll just tear out your
windpipe, and that'll be that.
You're gonna die anyway, so no
need for you to suffer, right?
See? Simple.
A wolf?
Damn.
Hm? Hold on, you sure?
You don't look all that tough.
D-don't try to intimidate me!
I'm not giving up!
Got it?
I came to save Robin and
that's what I'm gonna do!
The ceiling? What's going on?
Damn! I was trying to
use my man-beast form,
but I messed up on the man part!
There's a talking giraffe
falling through the ceiling!
Your power is so
awesome. I love it!
A wolf?
What the-- Is this
place some kinda zoo?
Ox-Ox Fruit. Model Giraffe.
Kaku, you poor bastard.
I told you not to eat
that fruit, didn't I?
And what's so wrong with
being a giraffe, huh?
For your information,
I happen to like it, okay?
That pigeon guy was
a leopard, wasn't he?
That makes three people
that transform into animals.
Does that mean the rest of
CP-9 has powers like that, too?
A wolf-man is one thing,
but now a giraffe-man, too?
This is insane!
How am I supposed to
deal with two Zoan types?
Actually, now that Zoro's here,
it's two-on-two, isn't it?
Or more like two on one,
with this guy cowering in
the corner and watching.
"For your information,
I happen to like it!" Huh?
I mean, who can
blame you, right?
Since giraffes are
so cool and all!
Yeah, they are!
You gotta problem?
Do giraffes and wolves
not get along or something?
'Cause they sure
hate each other.
What's that? Looks like
someone left a safe open.
Wait! Are those weird looking
handcuffs what I think they are?
That's enough! Stop laughing!
Hey, giraffe!
Could you shut up?
I'm in a hurry.
If you zoo animals wanna argue,
do it on your own time.
But if you just
wanna stand there,
your neck is an easy target.
You fool!
Don't underestimate
the limitless
destructive
power of giraffes!
Behold my Man-Beast Form!
I have been reborn
with unspeakable power!
Whoa, that is lame!
But I-- What? No!
Wh-why did I say
something so stupid?
I mean, he does look
pretty ridiculous,
but that's not the point.
If I lose my composure,
he'll have the advantage.
Are you going to sit there
and laugh all day or what?
S-- sorry.
Hmph.
Can't do it! Too funny!
Damn it. This is
harder than I thought.
Why does he have to be so
square and funny looking?
Huh? Wait, where did
these handcuffs come from?
Oh no. Whoops! Sorry!
What the hell are
you trying to pull?
Well, I was thinking
those are probably
the same Sea Prism
handcuffs they put on Robin.
Our enemies both have
Devil Fruit powers, y'know?
So I thought if I cuffed them,
they'd be easier to beat!
Then why didn't you put the
handcuffs on them? Why me?
Be-- because I--The giraffe
guy's face is too funny!
My hand slipped!
"I'm not square,
I'm cool, right?"
That's brilliant!
You're going to pay for this!
You're all going to pay!
I'll show you the
power of my devil fruit.
Then you'll be sorry!
Tempest Kick.
Oh boy, he's mad now!
Sky Slicer!
This isn't good.
Usopp, get down!
Damn it, now's not the
time to be having tea!
Oh, that's too bad.
Are you in a hurry?
Robin's life is at stake here.
If you get in my way,
I won't go easy on you,
no matter how beautiful you are!
In that case, I suppose
tea time is over.
On the next One Piece:
"I Won't Kick, Even If It Costs
Me My Life! Sanji's Chivalry!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!