[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
I'm sure you're cold,
but just hang in there
a little while longer.
I'll get you there,
don't you worry.
You just stay alive,
both of you.
Please just hang on.
Nami... Sanji.
[LUFFY] "The Island Where Snow
Lives! Climb the Drum Rockies!"
[LUFFY pants]
I see them up ahead, Wapol sir!
Just a little further.
[LUFFY grunts]
Huh?
[WAPOL]
Found you!
What the... Who are you guys?
I've had enough
of you Straw Hats!
I'm getting rid of you
for good this time.
I'm gonna chew you into little
pieces and spit you out!
[LUFFY]
Move it.
[WAPOL]
Heh. I don't think so.
Why would I wanna do that?
[WAPOL] I have no intention of
making it easy for you and those
half‐dead friends of yours to
get away from here, Straw Hat.
[LUFFY grunts]
[WAPOL]
Hm?
Hey!
[CHESS]
Stop right there!
Ah! Got it.
Hey, Chess, I've thought up a
new law to celebrate my return.
Write this down.
Right!
Anyone who ignores the
king will be executed!
Those three are guilty!
Chess, Kuromarimo!
I want them to be
punished immediately.
Deal with the two
unconscious ones first,
since they're ignoring
me the most!
[CHESS, KUROMARIMO]
Sir!
What did he say?!
[CHESS] I've got the
woman on his back.
[KUROMARIMO]
I'll take the man.
Prepare for...
Marimo's Surprise!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
[SANJI]
Listen, Luffy!
I don't want you fighting
these guys, all right?
Nami will be able to feel
every move you make.
She's too sick to be able to
handle something like that.
It would be too much.
She could die.
[LUFFY growls]
Can't fight!
[LUFFY] You're gonna regret
this later! Don't follow me!
Humph... What a coward.
It's no use!
[LUFFY gasps, grunts]
It's time he learned... what a
battle in the snow is like.
[LUFFY pants]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
There's no one.
That's weird. I wonder if
they've already given up.
[LUFFY grunts]
Here's what a snow
battle's really like.
Snow Powder Make Up!
The white disguise!
Those two are so
incredibly weak
that just one shot
should be enough.
[KUROMARIMO, CHESS]
Now it's Check... Mate!
No!
[BOTH yell]
[LUFFY]
Polar bears?
[CHESS, KUROMARIMO grunt]
Lapins?!
[ROBSON]
Hm?
Did those things
just protect him?
That's impossible! Lapins never
form bonds with humans.
They're nothing more
than wild beasts.
[LUFFY gasps]
I know you.
[BABY LAPIN whimpers]
[growls]
[LAPIN whimpers]
[thudding]
[gasps]
[cheers]
Thanks a bunch!
You guys saved me!
[WAPOL]
Don't let him get away!
[KUROMARIMO, CHESS]
Right!
Hm?
What the hell are those stupid
bunnies doing standing there?!
[LUFFY grunts]
Doctor.
[LUFFY]
This is it.
It's tall... and straight up.
[LUFFY]
But the doctor's up there.
So I... gotta climb it.
All right, Nami and Sanji.
There's just a little
further to go.
[LUFFY grunts, groans]
[grunts] What happened?
[VIVI gasps]
[VIVI] The avalanche...
It must have buried us.
Usopp!
[VIVI gasps]
There you are, Usopp!
Come on now, wake up!
You have got to wake up!
[USOPP grunts]
[VIVI gasps]
He's still alive!
I'm going to get you out
of there, Usopp, okay?
Just hang on a bit longer.
‐‐[VIVI grunts]
‐‐[USOPP groans]
Come on, Usopp!
Please just wake up!
Snap out of it!
Just give me a few more
minutes here, Vivi.
I was in the middle of
such a lovely dream.
We were in a world far away
from here, sitting in a field
of flowers with a beautiful
river flowing next to it... Oh!
You're crossing over into
the afterlife, Usopp!
You need to get out of
that dream! Now wake up!
[yells]
[gasps]
Ah, look at the Usopp Pirates,
all seventy‐four
thousand of 'em!
They're such good,
brave warriors!
Okay... Get up now!
You have to wake up!
Do you hear me?
[VIVI grunts] Usopp! Usopp!
Usopp! Usopp! Usopp! Usopp!
Oh, wow! You saved
my life, Vivi!
I was almost a goner
there for a second.
I'm lucky to be alive!
That was a close one,
really, so close.
Except that... my face... feels
kinda swollen... why's that?
Oh, it's the cold.
That happens.
It's an unfortunate side
effect of a snowy area.
What matters now is
figuring out where we are
and what to do next.
[VIVI]
Huh?
[USOPP yells]
Monster!
[ZORO]
Whoa... That was a close one!
Why do I feel like I dreamed
about a field of flowers?
[BOTH gasp]
[ZORO]
Hit by an avalanche
in the middle of a
training session!
Not exactly an ideal work out.
But I guess it is kinda
like swimming in snow.
[USOPP]
Zoro?
[ZORO]
Oh, hey Vivi, what's up?
Huh?
[USOPP]
Eh...
[ZORO]
Uh...
Oh, it's you, Usopp.
What are you guys doing all the
way out here in the snow?
[VIVI, USOPP] That's exactly
what we were gonna ask you!
[WAPOL laughs]
Take that you stupid bunnies!
You pathetic creatures got
exactly what you deserved
for going up
against a king.
Still, It annoys me that I had
to expend so much of my power
against a pack of
overgrown rabbits.
[CHESS]
There was no helping it, sir.
They are the fiercest
animals in Drum Kingdom.
And you're next... Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
Doctor...
Doctor.
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY gasps, yells]
Sanji!
That was... a close one.
[USOPP]
Winter swimming?
[ZORO] Yeah... that was
the idea, anyway.
But after swimming in
the river for a while,
I had no idea where
I was anymore,
so I started walking
around and doing some
strength training workouts.
Dressed like that
in cold weather?
You're real stupid,
aren't you?
That isn't the point.
Now would you shut up and
give me your coat, Usopp?
Not a chance.
[VIVI] Maybe Nami's sick
from the mental exhaustion
of dealing with these two.
[ZORO]
Then how 'bout your shoes?
‐‐[USOPP] No.
‐‐[ZORO] Just one, then!
[USOPP] I said no!
You did this to yourself!
[VIVI gasps] Look at that, guys.
There's some people over there.
[USOPP] Huh? Uh, hey!
Look at those buildings.
They seem familiar, don't they?
[VIVI]
Huh?
[VIVI] You're right, Usopp.
This place is Big Horn.
We just came back.
It looks a lot different
buried in snow, though.
[PIRATE B]
Stay back... all of you!
Dalton's already dead, anyway!
It'd take more than a couple
flimsy arrows to kill him!
You're his men!
Or used to be, at least.
Don't you care at all about
what happens to Dalton?
Things have changed!
We're all Wapol's soldiers now,
and any one of you who opposes
Wapol is as good as dead.
[ZORO]
Hey. What's goin' on here?
What's going on here?
[gasps] Wait, what's
goin' on with you?
Why are you dressed like that?
[VILLAGER 4] Dalton is
buried under the snow
that came down
with the avalanche.
[USOPP]
What?!
Dalton's under that?
That's right. And we can't get
over there to dig him out
because those guys
are blocking us.
[PIRATE A]
For the last time... stay back!
But if you really want
to dig your friend up,
I guess you can go ahead
and try fighting us all!
[laughs]
Hey, Usopp. I think I
remember their clothing.
Those are the same exact
guys who attacked our ship
when we were out
in the ocean, right?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
[ZORO]
Then they're the enemy.
Bad guys. Not our friends.
You follow me?
Yeah, but‐‐ Wait a second.
I know that look.
[PIRATE B laughs] You aren't so
brave without Dalton around.
[laughing continues]
[PIRATE B groans]
No! Zoro! What're you doing?
Who's that guy?
You need to be careful!
Nothing good will come
from attacking them!
[ZORO] Ah! This is so warm,
I really like this thing.
[USOPP] That's why you wanted
to know who they were?!
Watch out, Zoro!
They don't look very happy.
[PIRATE F] I know you! You were
on the ship with that guy
who beat up Wapol,
weren't you?
That's right. You're a
little slow, aren't ya?
[PIRATES yell]
[PIRATES]
Huh...?
[ZORO]
Are you looking for something?
Maybe... these?
[PIRATES gasp]
Men, let's get this guy!
[PIRATES shout]
[ZORO]
Heh!
[PIRATES groaning]
[ZORO]
Hawk Wave!
[PIRATES yell]
What a shame... already over?
Well that was
disappointing wasn't it?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Amazing...
Right. Zoro,
that was a good job!
Just like I told
you to do, yeah!
Great! Now we can go over
there and look for Dalton!
[VILLAGER 6]
Let's go!
[VILLAGER 7]
Thank you, sir.
[VILLAGER 6]
Hurry! Dig everywhere!
So, what's going on here?
Why are they all so worked up?
I'll explain it
all to you later.
For now, let's just
give 'em a hand.
Come on, Dalton.
Please still be alive.
[grunting]
[LUFFY grunting]
Doctor... Doctor... Doctor!
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY] Hang on, you two.
We're almost there.
Don't you die on me!
[grunting continues]
We're here.
Doctor...
[CHOPPER]
Doctorine...
the antibodies seem
to be responding.
[KUREHA] Yes... as I'd
guessed they would.
The treatment worked, but what
was the cause of the illness?
[CHOPPER]
Kestia.
Kestia, that's exactly correct.
Now you go and attend
the girl, all right?
[CHOPPER]
Yes.
[CHOPPER grunts]
Hello?
[CHOPPER gasps]
[whimpers]
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[SANJI]
You, reindeer, come back here!
[LUFFY]
Don't run away, food!
[SANJI]
Nami, I'm going to cook you
a tasty reindeer dish
for your recovery!
[NAMI]
I don't care about food!
I just want some
peace and quiet.
[LUFFY]
Hold on a second.
Did I just hear that
reindeer talking?
[SANJI] Come to think of it,
I saw him standing on two legs.
[SANJI, LUFFY]
He's a monster!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Blue‐nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!