[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[GROUP panting]
Sanji? Did we lose 'em?
Looks like they gave up!
I don't see anyone!
Really?
Well that's good!
To be honest, their giant
cannon really scared me!
Where were they
hiding that thing,
and how come they
didn't use it against Eneru?
Their cannon?
Yeah, you know,
that huge thing the warriors
were carrying towards us?
Didn't you see it?
Oh, you mean that thing.
Yeah, that thing!
What's wrong with you?
It's not funny!
Why do you think we're running!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, Robin! Usopp's right!
Don't laugh, okay?
We made it!
There's Nami and Conis!
Where? Nami! Hey, Conis!
[grunts]
[ROBIN]
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah!
[LUFFY] "Off to the Blue Sea!
A Heartfelt Finale!"
[CHIEFTAIN] What? They ran
away and left the island?
[ISLANDER A]
Yes.
We couldn't even
give them our gift.
[CHIEFTAIN]
How disappointing.
And after all they did for us.
I wonder if they realize how
much we appreciate them.
I agree.
They don't know how we feel.
You know, Aisa, it's not fair
that you were the only one
that got to say goodbye to them.
Everyone's really upset
that we let our heroes
just run away.
[AISA laughs]
Sorry! Luffy and the others made
me promise to keep it a secret!
Did you say anything
to them before they left?
Yeah! I said, "Thank you, all."
[AISA]
Hey, Laki? Didja see?
Luffy can stretch
his body really far!
He's like a "Gum-Gum Pistol!"
Kapow! Yay!
Aisa, please!
You've got to hold still!
I never knew there
were warriors like him
in the Blue Sea!
I wanna be just
like him when I grow up.
A Gum-Gum warrior!
[LAKI]
Aisa.
[AISA]
Hm?
I'm just going to
trim your hair a little.
You need to let it grow.
[AISA]
Huh?
Hey, it'll look good.
I think you've
forgotten you're a girl,
and girls should look cute.
What? Cute? Me?
Are you nuts?
[LAKI laughs]
I'm not!
With the war over, there's
no need for kids like you
to carry weapons anymore.
Now you can enjoy life
the way it was meant to be
and as a proper young lady.
I never knew you
were so ladylike!
[laughs]
[LAKI] Come on, Aisa!
Now hold still!
[AISA]
Laki's ladylike!
[LAKI]
Aisa!
[AISA, LAKI laugh]
[WYPER]
Great Warrior Kalgara.
We were told that
the Shandorians' role
has been fulfilled.
As for your last wish
it was delivered
to your best friend.
Our future generations will
no longer have to shed blood.
We are finally at peace.
The war may be over.
But one thing that will
never end is our pride!
Please continue to guide us,
Mighty Kalgara,
and watch over us as well.
We solemnly swear, The Fire
of Shandora will never die!
I-I cannot abandon my duties!
I am the Sky Knight, after all.
Yes, but this land
no longer has any need
for that role.
What it does need, however,
is someone who can govern it.
Someone who is kind and just.
I believe that duty
is best suited for you.
Perhaps you should
be looking at yourself.
Remember, this city originally
belonged to your people.
[CHIEFTAIN]
It did, long ago.
But that means nothing now.
In fact, with this battle, all
of us realized something.
Vearth belongs to no group.
It must be shared.
Our world has two sides.
The land is called Skypiea.
The city, Shandora.
They have been torn
asunder by war for ages.
Only a man who has
long lamented that war
can unite them,
and that man is you.
So Sky Knight, Gan Fall.
I'd like you to take
Skypiea's throne again.
Only you can heal
the deep wounds
that scar this land of ours.
We'd like you
to do it, too, sir!
Gan Fall, please!
We Shandorians are
behind you all the way
Yeah!
[SHANDORIAN C]
Gan Fall!
[ISLANDER B]
Our god!
[ISLANDER C]
Please come back!
[GAN FALL]
Well, well.
And here I was thinking
that I'd finally be able
to get some rest and
tend to my pumpkin patch.
[CROWD cheering]
Okay! We're almost there!
Everyone! See that up ahead?
That's Cloud End!
[USOPP]
Whoa, lemme see!
[LUFFY]
Huh.
So that's where we
go back down from?
[USOPP] We got here
sooner than I thought.
Aww. We really have
to go back already?
You know, it sounds crazy,
but I'm actually gonna
miss this place.
I think it's time we said
goodbye to the White Sea.
[CHOPPER]
Sky island sure is fun.
But scary, too.
[USOPP]
We just go through that gate,
and there'll be a Milky
Road that'll take us
to the Blue Sea, huh?
[NAMI] Wonder if we'll ever
visit this place again.
Well, you never know.
[horn playing reveille]
[PAGAYA] I'm sorry, but this
is as far as we can go!
Goodbye, my friends!
Take care of yourselves!
[SUU]
Suu!
We will! Thanks for the escort!
Conis! Don't forget me, angel!
[USOPP] Say goodbye
to the others for us!
See ya!
It was nice meeting you guys!
Thanks for everything!
No! You've got it wrong!
We're the ones who
should be thanking you!
We'll never forget you!
Thanks to you all!
Goodbye, Conis,
old guy, furball!
Take care now!
[PAGAYA, CONIS]
Bye!
Now take in your sails,
and hold on tight!
You're in for a bumpy ride!
Right! Let's do as the man says!
It feels like we're
already picking up speed!
[LUFFY] Yeah, and we're sliding
down from thousands of feet
in the air! Hurry up!
[GROUP]
Aye!
--[SOUTHBIRD calls]
--[GROUP] Huh?
[SOUTHBIRD squawks]
[LUFFY grunts]
[USOPP]
Wh-What the--?
[SOUTHBIRD squawks]
He says,
"Don't leave without me."
[NAMI]
Oh.
That's the Southbird we
brought up here with us.
[NAMI] Captain! It looks like
the log pose has the coordinates
for the next island!
Great! Let's go!
Once we get to the bottom,
we're gonna start
a brand-new adventure!
Who's up for finding some gold?
Guys! Get ready!
Blue Sea, here we come!
[GROUP]
Aye!
[GROUP yells]
[GROUP laughing]
Everyone grab hold of something!
The freefall's about to start!
[GROUP]
Freefall?
[CONIS]
Heso!
[GROUP screaming]
Just hang on!
One Octopus Balloon, on the way!
[whistle blowing]
[USOPP yells]
[USOPP]
Octopus!
What the--[grunts]
[NAMI]
Oh! Oh, that hurt.
What... happened?
Hey, guys! Get a load of this!
[ZORO]
What the hell is it?
[CHOPPER]
A balloon!
[LUFFY laughs]
Yeah! Ain't it great?
[NAMI]
We're not falling!
[USOPP]
Oh, good!
For a minute there,
I thought we were goners!
All of us!
[bell ringing]
[ringing continues]
[LUFFY laughs]
[MCKINLEY]
Keep ringing it!
Let the departing
heroes of this land
know how much
we appreciate them!
[ISLANDER D]
Heso!
[SKYPIEANS cheering]
Luffy! Come back soon!
[ISLANDER A]
You're always welcome!
[ISLANDER B]
Thank you so much!
[SHANDORIAN D] We wish you
safe passage to the Blue Sea!
[CROWD chattering]
[NARRATOR] When you look up,
you see the sky.
Though some believe
it to be only a legend,
there is an island
floating thousands of feet
in the air.
If you listen carefully,
you can hear the
tolling of a bell.
It rings today, and it
will ring again tomorrow.
That bell rings
from the heavens,
from a land that wandered.
It sings of its pride,
and proclaims
to the rest of the world,
"We are here."
[LUFFY laughs]
This is so great!
[USOPP]
Tell me about it!
What a way to travel!
I love it!
[SHOJO]
You're calling off the search?
[CRICKET]
Of course.
The City of Gold has been
in the sky this whole time.
There's nothing else to be
found at the bottom of the sea.
Sorry, fellas.
This dream's over.
No point in staying
here anymore.
Old man.
Cricket.
[CRICKET] I wanna thank
all of you for helping me
pursue my dream
for all of these years.
You never stopped believing.
That means a lot.
[MASIRA]
Does this mean...
[SHOJO]
...you're leaving the Alliance?
[CRICKET]
Hey, guys.
Since this dream's done,
which one are we
gonna pursue next?
[CROWD cheering]
[MASIRA] We'll all follow you to
the ends of the earth, Old Man!
Yeah!
[cheering continues]
[GROUP]
Gold! Gold! Gold! Gold!
[LUFFY laughs]
We finally struck it rich!
What should we buy
with all this loot?
Hey! I know!
A huge bronze statue!
Moron!
Only an idiot would
exchange gold for bronze!
How stupid!
What we need are more cannons!
Ten of them! Ten!
[SANJI] Nami, I want to buy
a refrigerator with a lock!
[LUFFY]
Uh-uh!
If you get one with a lock,
there'll be no way
for me to get a midnight snack!
[SANJI] That's exactly why
I want one, you pig!
[NAMI] Would you guys
just hold on a second?
We need to land first.
Then we can divide
up the treasure.
Please buy me books!
If we buy everything
you guys want,
we're gonna be broke
again in no time.
[ROBIN]
Miss Navigator?
The ship.
Just where is it headed exactly?
Where else?
The next island, of course.
[NAMI screams]
--You okay?
--What's wrong?
Need a hug, Nami?
[NAMI]
Dammit!
We've been blown off course!
We must have hit an air current!
[USOPP]
Huh?
Well, I definitely
feel a breeze.
Is that a bad thing?
Of course it is!
Now we have no idea where we
are or where we're gonna land!
And with the octopus up there,
we can't set the sails
or control the ship.
What are we gonna do?
Hey, don't worry about it.
Once we touch down, we'll just
head to the next island,
easy as that!
There you go, running
off at the mouth as always.
[SANJI]
Hey.
Sanji, what is it?
Nah. Guess I was wrong.
[USOPP]
Huh? About what?
No. Never mind.
[ZORO gasps]
We've got a problem!
[ZORO yawns]
Oh, yeah, it was just a dream.
[NAMI]
Thanks for scaring us!
[SANJI] I'm gonna fillet
you for that! I swear!
[GROUP arguing]
[LUFFY laughing]
The sun's completely set now.
It's still a nice view.
[USOPP]
You're right. It really is.
Uh, mornin'.
It's still evening, dummy.
This is taking longer
than I expected.
[NAMI]
I agree.
I'm really worried about
how far we've drifted.
We could be anywhere.
[SANJI] What if I sang
you girls a romantic song
to take your mind off th--?
[NAMI]
Buzz off!
[USOPP laughs]
You know what?
I betcha we get blown
all the way to Raftel!
Do you really think so?
[ROBIN]
Uh, guys?
Unfortunately,
that's impossible.
We'd have to sail
across more than half
the Grand Line
just to get there.
[USOPP]
Uh... Yeah, um, I knew that.
This conversation's boring.
How much longer
is this gonna take?
Go to sleep.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Zoro!
If you're really bored,
I've got something you can do,
and it's fun!
Uh? Luffy?
Where'd his voice come from?
Good question.
He did sound kinda far off.
Luffy! Where are you?
[LUFFY]
I'm up here! C'mon, guys!
This thing's a blast!
[laughing]
What? Is he nuts?
[LUFFY laughs]
Whee! Awesome!
This is awesome!
[laughing]
Hey, don't do anything stupid!
All our lives depend
on this balloon!
You hear me, Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Don't worry! Don't worry!
[SANJI]
Luffy, stop! Get down!
Right now!
Sanji, what are
you yelling about?
[SANJI]
The octopus is shrinking!
If we don't do anything,
we'll fall!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[SANJI]
Hey, Luffy!
What's that? Huh?
[NAMI]
The octopus is shrinking!
Shrinking?!
You know, now that I look at it,
it does look smaller
than it did before.
[NAMI]
What are we gonna do?
We're still really
high up in the air!
[SANJI]
Luffy! Something's wrong!
You've gotta come down now!
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY, SANJI yelling]
[GROUP]
Huh?!
[laughing]
That was scary!
Wonder why the octopus
isn't bouncy anymore.
[SANJI] I told you,
it's shrinking, bonehead!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Uh... That's weird.
How'd the ship get below us?
[USOPP] Agh!
We're falling! We're falling!
We're gonna hit the sea so hard,
we'll sink to the bottom!
Only if the ship
doesn't shatter first!
Shatter? No way!
Usopp, what are you gonna do?
[USOPP]
What I always do!
Save our lives, of course!
[USOPP grunting]
What are you doing?
[SANJI]
Don't be crazy, Usopp!
[USOPP]
Usopp...
[yells]
[GROUP]
Huh?!
[USOPP yelling]
Hey! Look, it worked!
All right.
Come on, now.
Breath dials! Do your thing!
Now float! Float, I say!
[yelps]
We've slowed down.
All right!
Are we safe now?
It sure seems like it.
[USOPP laughs]
Just leave it all up
to Usopp to save the day!
[CHOPPER]
Usopp, you're so brave!
[LUFFY laughs]
I was actually scared
there for a second!
[NAMI]
Me, too!
Looks like we're finally safe!
Or not!
[GROUP yelling]
[LUFFY]
Usopp!
Everybody hold onto something!
[GROUP yelling]
[CHOPPER, USOPP grunting]
[LUFFY]
Agh! That's cold!
[SANJI]
Nami! Robin! Are you okay?
[NAMI]
That was really scary!
What happened to the octopus?
[ROBIN]
Guess it ran out of air.
[SANJI]
Wonder how that happened.
[LUFFY]
Hey, come on!
Don't whine.
We did make it down here alive!
You're right.
And we got to see
an incredible place.
[ROBIN] Now that we're down
here, it looks so far away.
[NAMI]
Like something out of a dream.
It's a dreamland.
Think we'll see it again?
Well, you might see some
place similar when you die.
Not you.
I doubt you're going
any place good!
You jerk!
[SANJI] You guys keep
discussing the afterlife.
Me? I'm gonna go
put on a pot of coffee.
[LUFFY]
Make dinner instead, Sanji!
[SANJI]
Are you ever not hungry?
Have some coffee first
and be patient, will ya!
[LUFFY]
Okay.
Hey, by the way...
[sirens blaring]
[LUFFY]
...does anybody know...
...just where the heck we are?
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[CHOPPER]
Where are we?
[NAMI] What are all
these spotlights for?
[USOPP]
My one-man show?
[LUFFY]
Moron!
[ZORO] An emergency siren!
That means...!
[SANJI] I can't believe we
landed here of all places!
[ROBIN] The first thing we need
to do is get off the ship!
[LUFFY]
Hey! What about dinner?
On the next One Piece!
"A State of Emergency is Issued!
A Notorious Pirate Ship
Has Infiltrated!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!