[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope,
and others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era
in the country's history
that will forever
be overshadowed by sadness.
With the help of the
Supersonic Duck Squadron,
Zoro and the others act
as decoys to draw away
the Baroque Works
officer agents.
Meanwhile, Vivi
sets out on her own
to try to stop Koza
and his rebel forces.
However, her voice
is drowned out
as the sand rises around her.
The anticipated battle
has finally begun
as the rebel army attacks
the capital city of Alubarna
and the royal army
seeks to defend it.
[LUFFY]
"Alubarna Grieves!
The Fierce Captain Karoo."
Vivi is in real danger!
Usopp, you go and
see what you can do
to help Chopper, all right?
Chopper?
Get to the southeast gate!
Vivi, please just hang
in there a little longer.
I'm on my way.
Please just hold on.
It's a rebel!
They're here!
A rebel? Yeah, right.
[REBEL SOLDIER A]
Hey! It's a royal soldier!
Shoot him now!
Easy there.
I'm not a part of either the
rebel army or the royal army.
[SANJI]
I only fight for the ladies!
[CHOPPER]
They're gone.
They gave up too quick.
I don't trust it.
Where could Mr. 4
and Miss Merry Christmas
have disappeared to?
[CHOPPER yelps]
Hey, what's going on here?
I don't understand.
Who are you guys, anyway?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS laughing]
The question is who are you
and why are you
talking to yourself?
Let me introduce you
to our number four batter!
[MR. 4]
Four!
Number four?
[MR. 4]
Four!
Batter?
[MR. 4]
Four!
[CHOPPER]
Okay.
Right now, I just have
to do whatever I can.
I just have to remember...
...that I am a pirate!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Time to die!
[MR. 2]
Poor Princess Vivi.
You see, this desert is where...
...you'll die!
[KAROO squawks]
[MR. 2]
Un. Deux. Ora!
[VIVI]
Karoo!
Oh, no.
You see, you two...
...can't get away. Swan Dash!
[MR. 2]
You hear me?
There's no escape for you!
Just give up now, okay?
I'm going to trample you
both with all the grace
of a ballerina.
[VIVI]
Karoo.
You saved my life.
[VIVI] You're in no shape
to be running like this now.
[KAROO squawks]
[VIVI]
No! If you go straight,
we'll be cornered
on the stairway!
[MR. 2]
Fools, listen to me!
Just give it up
and stop right there!
Let me off here.
I'm going to fight him.
What are you doing?
That way's a cliff.
[KAROO squawks]
Oh! What are you doing?
[KAROO squawking]
[MR. 2]
You can't be serious!
That duck is actually running
up the sheer face of a cliff?
[MR. 2]
Huh?
[KAROO squawking]
[MR. 2 laughs]
Dumb duck!
Nice try, but now you'll
fall back down here
and my Ballet Kenpo
will finish you off.
[KAROO squawking]
[LUFFY]
It's a sign of our friendship!
[KAROO squawks]
What? Hey, Karoo,
what are you crying about?
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[KAROO squawks]
Hey, just leave it to us.
Vivi is our friend, too,
'kay, Karoo?
[KAROO squawks]
How'd he do that?!
[VIVI]
Karoo, that's amazing! You flew!
[KAROO squawks]
Surely Mr. 2 won't
be able to follow us
at this point.
[KAROO squawks]
[MR. 2] That was
a cute little move, duck,
but it's no use!
There's nothing I can't do!
With the help of my
incredible Ballet Kenpo,
I can relevé right
up this cliff.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Karoo.
Do you think you can make
it through the battlefield?
[KAROO squawks]
We'll never be able to find
Koza in all this confusion,
so we'll look for Chaka instead.
We need to reach
the royal palace.
And we have to make it
before the rebel army
reaches the center of the city.
We must!
[MR. 2]
Oh, my. I'm here!
[KAROO squawks]
A stray bullet, oh, no! Karoo!
[LUFFY] Vivi is our friend
too, 'kay, Karoo?
[KAROO squawks]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Ah! Got ya!
[VIVI]
Karoo!
[KAROO squawks]
[MR. 2]
Just give up!
I told you, it's no use!
[VIVI]
All right.
[MR. 2 laughing]
Stay out of my way, duckie,
and maybe you
won't get hurt, okay?
[KAROO squawks]
[VIVI]
No, stop!
[MR. 2 grunts]
[MR. 2 yells]
It's you guys.
[DUCK A squawks]
[SANJI]
Nice work there, Captain Karoo.
You did a damn good job.
[KAROO squawks]
Oh! Sanji, you're here!
[SANJI] At ease, ducks.
You can stand down.
[DUCK A, DUCK C squawk]
[SANJI] Now, Vivi, don't you
have a rebellion to stop?
[SANJI]
Go on.
I'll take care of this creep.
[SANJI] So I take it
you're that ridiculous,
face‐changing freak, huh?
You really should
stay out of my way.
But first, just who are you?
[SANJI]
Go on.
You guys, watch Karoo.
[DUCK A, DUCK C squawk]
Ah! No! She's getting away!
Oh! You gotta be kidding me!
Gimme a break here!
Well... Now you get to die!
I think I'll get started
by having you return
our sharpshooter's
prized goggles.
[SANJI]
And that's just the beginning.
[MR. 2]
Huh?
Hope you didn't think
I would be as easy
to beat as him.
You're with the straw hats, huh?
Well, then, that must make
you the mysterious prince.
My name is Sanji,
and I'm the best cook
in the entire ocean.
Cook? I happen to be
a super first‐class
top‐rate cook as well.
But I use my skills to support
an underworld organization,
not some useless kingdom.
[SANJI] You're not the only one
who knows the underworld.
I happen to be
a cook and a pirate.
[MR. 2]
Hmm.
Well then, this should
be quite interesting.
I'll make this clear.
Keep your hands
off this country.
[NAMI]
Go get 'em, Zoro!
What are you waiting for?
Punch 'em out!
Knock them on the floor!
You can do it!
I don't need a cheering squad!
Go hide somewhere!
All right, you guys.
Do you think you could
make this a little challenging?
[NAMI] Come on, Zoro!
This is why we keep you around!
It's the only thing
you can do well, right?
Hurry up and finish
off those ugly‐looking,
really bad, evil people...?
What do you think you're doing?
Hold up.
The primary rule
to assassination
says all weaker targets
are to be eliminated first.
We'll show you how professionals
handle these sorts of things.
What, you mean me?
Hold on just a minute.
Getting rid of me won't
accomplish anything at all.
Sure, I'm pretty,
and I know how to dress.
But that's it. I really don't
have any fighting skills.
Yes, we know.
It's fairly obvious.
As we said, picking off
the weak ones first
is the fastest way to work.
Sure, of course it is.
Well naturally, I know
you're right about that one.
I'd do the same thing
myself in this situation.
[NAMI screams]
[ZORO] And that's exactly
why I told her to shut up
and hide somewhere.
[USOPP] Well, this is the
southeast gate that Sanji meant,
right?
Well, it looks like
the fight is over.
Where's Chopper?
Chopper!
Chopper! Hey, Chopper!
Come on, wake up!
Open your eyes!
Oh, Usopp.
It looks like you're
all right. That's great.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're the one we
need to worry about.
No, it isn't serious.
So.
This is all that's left
of the Mr. 4 pair, huh?
And here I came to help you!
I, the great Captain Usopp,
the champion of the seas,
the hero of the world,
was going to demonstrate
my fighting skills
by bravely coming
to a friend's rescue.
Be careful, they're still
here waiting for us.
What?! Why didn't you say so?
What was that?
How did that happen?
There's no one even out there!
That's because
they're underground.
Miss Merry Christmas ate
the Mole‐Mole Devil Fruit,
and now she's a mole woman.
[USOPP]
A mole woman?
[CHOPPER]
The other one,
Mr. 4, is a fourth batter,
and his dog's the pitcher.
What? None of that jibber
jabber made any sense.
What the hell does it mean?
‐‐[CHOPPER] Look out!
‐‐[USOPP yells]
Four!
[CHOPPER coughs]
[CHOPPER]
Are you okay, Usopp?
[USOPP coughs]
Man. That was really close!
I'm glad you were
there, Chopper.
What exactly was
that thing anyway?
Like I said.
That's Mr. 4's thing.
He's a fourth batter.
He works together with his dog.
Which brings me back
to my earlier point.
None of that makes any sense.
Ah! Look, he's over there!
A dog?
Gah! What is that weird thing?
That's not good!
What? Huh? What's that?
[LASSOO sneezes]
[USOPP yells]
Here it comes!
Not good!
[MR. 4]
Four!
Usopp, you have to get
away from there quickly!
Hurry, now!
Usopp, no!
[USOPP coughs]
[CHOPPER]
Are you all right, Usopp?
Okay, one more time.
What is that?
The ball is a time bomb.
It explodes when it's set to,
whether or not it hits anything.
Basically, Mr. 4 can
calculate the time needed
and then hit the ball.
The ball will then explode
when its time is up.
I tried to catch one
before it exploded
and throw it back at him,
but it's as heavy
as a wrecking ball.
There's no way to catch it
and it's impossible to throw.
The fact that Mr. 4
can hit it with a bat
at the speed he does
is absolutely incredible.
His strength is extraordinary.
It's beyond anything
I've ever seen before.
Four.
Lassoo...
That bat of his just
knocked down a brick wall.
How much could that
thing possibly weigh?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Hey! Mr. 4! Mr. 4!
What are you doing, moron?
You moron!
Go and get 'em instead
of just standing there!
Come on let 'em have it already!
Go now! Go on, moron! Kill 'em!
Smoke 'em! Blow 'em up!
Moron. Moron. Ron. Ron. Ron.
Now! Do it now!
Uh...
Over there!
It's the mole woman!
She is a mole!
I haven't even changed yet,
you... ron, you moron.
Chopper. You'll have
to take it from here.
Do me a favor and have
my body buried at sea
when I'm gone, okay?
You cowardly jerk!
You just got done saying
you had come here to help!
Look here, you!
How do you expect me to fight
against a freaky muscle man,
his weird dog‐gun hybrid,
and a mole woman?
There's no way! I'm a human!
Do you think you
can understand that?
I'm a human too, jerk!
No, you're not!
You're a big, furry monster!
What about you? Have you
seen that nose of yours?
Well at least
my nose isn't blue.
All right, long nose.
Now you've done it!
Do you really think
this is the best situation
in which to be arguing?
[USOPP, CHOPPER yell]
[USOPP, CHOPPER]
Very sorry.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Anyway, his name is Lassoo.
He's a gun that ate
the dachshund variety
of the Mutt‐Mutt Fruit.
Are we clear?
Let me get this straight.
Are you saying that
a gun ate a Devil Fruit?
It's a new technique
here in the Grand Line.
Even inanimate objects
can eat a devil fruit.
Ha! You call that lying.
If he was originally a gun,
how could he eat anything?
A gun can't even
move on its own.
You're just making all of
this up, you mole woman!
Shut up!
It's top secret, anyway,
and I wouldn't have told you
except for you're going to die!
A gun can't help it if it moves!
So there, there, there!
There! So there!
Now, isn't that right, Mr. 4?
[MR. 4]
Mm‐hmm.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Anyway, like I was saying,
you're gonna die here.
You have no hope of escaping
now that you've
entered our territory.
Nope, nuh‐uh. No hope at all!
You should enjoy this.
Welcome to a territory
we call Molehill, Block 4.
Look!
Now she's turning into a
mole‐woman‐thing for real!
Penguin?
Not a penguin, I'm a mole!
Now, you shut up!
[USOPP]
She's underground.
‐‐[USOPP] Now's my chance!
‐‐[CHOPPER] Wait, hey!
[USOPP] You can handle
it from here, I'm sure!
Watch out, Usopp!
[CHOPPER]
It missed!
Close!
Four!
[CHOPPER]
Oh, no!
Usopp, look! It's above you!
It's a fly ball!
[USOPP]
Ha! No problem!
Looks like their cleanup
batter can't clean up
very well, huh?
[USOPP laughs]
How sad.
I could dodge this one
with my eyes closed!
Spin ball!
Look out behind you!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
He's fourth in our line‐up
for a reason, moron.
You haven't seen anything yet!
[USOPP yelling]
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[USOPP]
They've gone into the molehills!
‐‐Watch out for the holes!
‐‐[CHOPPER] Huh?
What're they planning this time?
[CHOPPER]
Usopp, behind you!
[USOPP yells]
[CHOPPER] I just have to
think of a way to beat 'em!
[USOPP] I can't take
any more! We're gonna die!
There's no way we can take 'em!
[CHOPPER]
No, we can't run!
We'll never escape
from these guys!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Sworn on a Friend's Dream!
The Battle of Molehill,
Block 4."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!