[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
Now, Gum‐Gum...
[LUFFY yells]
And what... does that mean?
I can only work for one week!
[FULLBODY groans]
Don't you mess with me!
[SANJI] You could've eaten it if
you had just taken the bug out.
It took three full
days of hard cooking
to prepare that soup for
you, and you wasted it.
I'm the customer here!
Do you understand me?!
I'm paying you!
Can your money...
...truly satisfy your hunger?
Whaddya mean?
[SANJI]
I'm asking...
Can it satisfy your hunger?
[LUFFY] "Unwelcome Customer!
Sanji's Food and Ghin's Debt!"
[toilet flushes]
[MAN A]
Just hold it... almost there...
[PATTY]
Customer service equals love!
And love equals restaurant!
[PATTY]
The customer...
...is the king! [screams]
Pleasant greetings to the
customer is what it's all about,
the customer is always right,
and we stand by that!
Hello and welcome,
you damn crooks...
But don't you ever come back!
Awfully sorry about that...
You're all so pathetic, I laugh!
[laughs]
[PATTY]
Done!
‐‐[PATTY] Ah! Yes, indeed!
‐‐[MAN A gasps]
Today will be a great
day for everyone!
Oh, hello there and
welcome, you damn crook.
That's our service
motto around here,
no doubt about it, the
customer is‐‐ Ah! Huh?
[PATTY]
Oh, no! Our customer!
Dammit! Not again, Sanji!
What do you think you're
doing to our customer?!
Can't you see he's
a Marine Lieutenant?!
[FULLBODY choking]
You're a terrible cook.
What makes you think that
you can talk to me like that?
[PATTY grunts] A crappy cook
like you is calling me bad?
Restaurants can't exist
without their customers!
They're our lifeblood, so
we don't want to hurt them
the way you seem to keep doing!
But he deserved it.
He didn't treat the food
or me with respect...
...and he insulted
all the cooks.
‐‐[FULLBODY grunts]
‐‐[SANJI] So I simply
taught him a lesson.
[FULLBODY grunts]
You're gonna to regret this...
All of you...
No restaurant should treat
its customers like this...
I'll shut you down...
Do you understand me?!
I will shut you down!
This entire place!
This whole restaurant is
finished! Do you hear me?!
Then, maybe I should
just finish you off now.
[FULLBODY gasps]
[COOK LI]
Sous Chef Sanji, stop it!
‐‐[COOK LI yelling]
‐‐Arrogant assholes like you
who think they're such big shots
they can push anybody around
really piss me off!
You can't keep doing this in
the restaurant every other day!
[SANJI growls]
You're not such a big
shot now, are ya? Are ya?!
[FULLBODY growling]
[ZEFF, LUFFY grunt]
[CUSTOMERS gasping]
[USOPP sighs]
‐‐[CUSTOMER A] What happened?
‐‐[CUSTOMER B] Are they okay?
[ZEFF growls]
[LUFFY gasps]
I can breathe again!
Boss Zeff,
what's happening here?
You didn't hurt
yourself, did you?
Dammit!
My ceiling!
Another thing that's gonna have
to get fixed because of you!
This is all your
fault, you brat!
How is it my fault?!
You attacked me!
Boss, can you stop messing
around and give us a hand?
Sanji's gone crazy again!
[COOKS, SANJI growling]
‐‐[ZEFF] Hey, Sanji!
‐‐[SANJI growling]
[ZEFF]
Don't tell me you
went on another rampage
in here, you idiot!
Put a cork in it, old man!
[ZEFF] Oh, now you're
ordering me around!
Just who do you think
you're talking to?!
Do you want to
sink my restaurant
to the bottom of the sea?!
You punk!
‐‐[FULLBODY laughs]
‐‐[ZEFF] You, too!
Get your ass out
of my restaurant!
[FULLBODY groans, grunts]
[FULLBODY groans]
[FULLBODY] What kind
of restaurant is this?!
That boss is like a gangster.
It's almost as if... if...
...this were a pirate ship!
How can you deny our motto
that the customer is king?!
The only kingly customers are
the ones who stomach the
slop that you call food.
That's it.
If you two wanna fight,
you'll keep it in the
kitchen, you understand me?!
[FULLBODY grunts] Are all
these idiots really cooks?
[MARINE B]
Lieu‐Lieutenant!
Lieutenant Fullbody!
[FULLBODY gasps]
[MARINE B panting]
We've... We've got trouble!
Wow, this restaurant is crazy.
Sir, he's escaped!
Pirate Krieg's henchman
attacked us and vanished!
He what?!
Well, sir, we've already
lost seven of our men,
and the only thing we wanted
out of him was a lead
on finding Krieg...
Impossible...
When we picked him
up three days ago,
he was right on the verge
of starving to death.
And we haven't fed him anything.
Where'd he get the strength?
Krieg Pirates?
[CUSTOMERS murmuring]
[CUSTOMER D] They're the one's
who're said to be the fiercest
pirates in the East Blue!
I'm sorry, Lieutenant, I‐‐
[gunshot]
[CUSTOMERS gasp]
[footsteps]
[ZEFF grunts]
[SANJI]
Huh?
[LUFFY gasps]
It would seem we have
a new customer, sir.
He'd do well to mind his manners
and not start any
trouble on my ship.
A pirate, huh?
[FULLBODY grunts]
I don't care what it is...
Just bring me something to eat.
Come on... This is a restaurant.
Hello and welcome,
you damn crook!
[CUSTOMERS gasp]
I'm just gonna say
this one more time.
Bring me something to
eat and make it quick.
That cook is gonna
get us killed.
Of course, right away,
but might I be so bold
to inquire how you're
paying for your meal?
Will a bullet be enough?
So you don't have
any money then.
‐‐[FULLBODY] What?
‐‐[CUSTOMERS gasp]
That dumb ass, Patty,
broke another chair.
Whoa... What power...
Sorry, pirate, but our policy is
to only serve paying customers.
‐‐[CUSTOMERS whistle, cheer]
‐‐You tell him!
Kick his ass, Patty.
Show that pirate we
cooks don't screw around!
[stomach rumbles]
[PATTY]
Aww, I can hear
your stomach grumbling
from here, pirate.
That was a fart, jerk.
Now, listen...
Get me... something...
to eat now...
We're not getting you
anything, so beat it!
[CUSTOMERS cheering]
[GHIN grunts]
[FULLBODY]
I can't take anymore.
All of these cooks are insane!
I've gotta get outta here.
I don't want anything to do
with this place ever again!
[cheering continues]
[PATTY]
And now, you damn crooks...
If you need anything,
just ask, okay? [laughs]
And please, never come back.
[PATTY grunts]
[GHIN groans]
Dammit,
if I wasn't so weak from hunger,
I'd be inside eating...
[grunts] And he'd be lying here.
Hey, you're not hungry,
by any chance, are ya?
[GHIN] No... I'm not...
Just leave me alone...
[stomach rumbles]
‐‐[door creaks]
‐‐[LUFFY] Hm?
[GHIN gasps]
Huh?
Eat up.
[GHIN gulps]
[GHIN]
Take it and leave me alone!
I won't accept charity;
it doesn't matter how
down and out I may be.
Just take this stuff away, now!
Stop your whining
and eat it already.
I don't care what
they say in there.
To me, if anyone's hungry,
they're a customer.
Sorry, but I'm
not your customer.
[stomach rumbles]
[SANJI growls]
[SANJI] It's amazing
how beautiful and cruel
this ocean can be, how it's
almost a death sentence
to lose your food
and water out here,
how difficult it is to survive.
I know what it
means to go hungry
because of the sea
more than anyone.
You can die for your
pride if you want.
But listen, if you
and eat and survive,
won't that give
you the opportunity
to fight for pride
truly worth having,
now and in the future?
[GHIN gasps]
[GHIN gulps]
[GHIN sobbing]
I'm sorry...
Thank you so much...
I thought it was over, I truly
thought I was going to die.
[GHIN sobbing]
This food...
...it's delicious.
I've never eaten food
this good before.
[GHIN sniffling, snorting]
Of course it is...
[LUFFY laughs]
I think I just found my cook!
You're lucky he
gave you some food!
You weren't lookin' so
good there... [laughs]
I thought you were a goner!
So listen, Mr. Cook,
why don't you leave this
boat and join my crew?
[SANJI]
Huh?
I could use a cook like
you on my pirate ship!
[SANJI, GHIN]
Huh?
[SANJI]
So you're a pirate?
Uh‐huh.
Is that why you went and
did a crazy thing like
shoot a cannonball
into the restaurant?
[LUFFY]
That was an accident!
It was self‐defense that
turned into a stray shot!
[SANJI]
A stray shot?
In any case, you
really don't want to
do anything stupid
to this place.
The owner used to be a cook
in a famous pirate fleet.
Ohh... So the old man...
used to be a pirate...
This restaurant is everything
to that crazy old man.
It's the only treasure he'll
need for the rest of his life...
He'll do anything to protect it.
On top of which,
all of the cooks who
joined him out of
respect and admiration
are just as hot‐headed
as any pirate...
Which helps since
pirates are always
coming and going
out of this place.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, I've noticed that.
This is a really wild
restaurant, huh? [chuckles]
So true... And this is
how it is every day.
It's gotten so bad that
customers are coming
here just watch fights
between the cooks
and the pirates.
Every day, it's been a new
pirate ship and a new rampage.
It wasn't long till all the
waiters got scared and bailed.
Ah, that makes sense!
So that's why the old man wanted
me to work for him for a year.
So, you joining my
pirate crew or what?
I'm sorry, but I can't...
There's a reason I have to
work here in the restaurant,
and so I can't just
walk away from it.
No way!
I don't accept!
What? You don't accept?!
It's very simple.
I refuse to accept your refusal!
You're a good cook,
and I need one,
so it's obvious that we
should be pirates together.
[SANJI grunts]
Listen to what I'm saying.
I can't leave here, all right?
What's your reason for staying?
I don't have to
tell you anything!
What the...?
But you just said
to listen to you!
I told you my answer was no,
and that's all you
need to hear from me.
Now take you pirate ship, and
find a cook someplace else
before I cut you up, Straw Hat!
You listen to me, jerk.
No one makes fun of my straw hat
unless they're
ready for a beating!
[GHIN]
I'm sorry to interrupt...
[LUFFY, SANJI]
What is it?!
My name is Ghin,
and I'm a crew member of
Don Kreig's Pirate fleet...
And you say that you're
a pirate yourself...
What is it you seek?
Oh, the One Piece!
And pretty soon, I'm gonna sail
the Grand Line and find it!
[GHIN]
Huh?
Well, you can't have been
seeking it for long.
If you don't even
have a cook yet,
your crew can't be all that big.
Nope, he's only
the fifth member.
I told you I'm not going,
so don't count me!
You seem like a nice kid,
so let me give you some
friendly advice, okay?
The Grand Line is a
place you want to avoid.
You're still young, there's
no need to rush into anything.
Remember, the Grand Line is one
small part of this entire ocean.
If you want to be a real
pirate, there are plenty of
other places out here
on the seas to explore.
[LUFFY]
Hmm... I see...
Well, why don't you just
tell me what to avoid
in the Grand Line now?
I can't...
I don't know anything.
I don't understand it.
And that is why I fear it.
[SANJI] For being a
crewmember of Don Kreig's,
you're a pretty
wimpy pirate.
[LUFFY]
Hm? Who's Don Kreig?
[COOKS chattering]
[COOK B] The appetizer
for table three is ready!
[COOK D] Yeah, well you're gonna
have to take it out yourself,
the last waiter's gone!
You think more of them
will be comin', Patty?
Who knows?
I heard the guy
you beat up earlier
in the restaurant was
one of Don Krieg's men.
I don't think that will make
the rest of them very happy.
Heh... I don't care
whose man he was.
All I'm saying is, the stories
I've heard say Don Krieg is
the strongest,
fiercest and most evil
pirate in this
part of the ocean.
He is.
[PATTY]
Eh?
[CARNE]
On these waters,
his grip of fear
reaches far and wide.
He commands over
50 pirate captains,
one of the largest
pirate fleets ever seen.
He is truly...
...a monster.
He doesn't scare me.
I've heard that his
extraordinary fleet
of ships has more than
five thousand pirates.
This could be bad
for Boss Zeff...
If that guy you beat up
goes to Don Krieg and
tells him what you did,
and he sends just one ship...
There won't be enough
of us to fight them off.
We'll be crushed, like
a grape under an elephant,
and left to sink to the
bottom of the ocean.
Eh...
You're saying I should
have just served him,
so he could experience our
great customer service
and meals for free?
You don't think that
would have been rude
to the other damn
crooks who pay money?
I would never stoop that low!
This is the Baratie.
The fighting cooks have a
reputation to uphold, don't we?
I'd never ruin that. I don't
care who that pirate cries to.
Let them send their ships.
I'll fight them all off.
If you're scared, quit and
let the real cooks work.
Don't you dare say that to me!
I'm tired of all that
big talk you spit out,
which is why all the
waiters jumped ship!
Everything that's happening
now is all your fault, Patty!
[PATTY]
Please!
Those waiters
were worthless wimps
the moment a customer
showed up! Worthless wimps!
‐‐[COOKS cheering]
‐‐[COOK B] Go for it!
‐‐[COOK A] Take him out, Carne!
[COOK D] He doesn't
stand a chance, Patty!
All right, what's all this?
Get back to work already!
[ALL]
Yes, Boss Zeff!
[GHIN sighs]
So long, then.
Thanks for the warning,
but I'm still gonna
go to the Grand Line.
I know.
Do whatever you want.
I'm just a stranger,
and I can't stop you from
going anywhere you wanna go.
I just wanted to give
you a fair warning.
And to you, Chef...
Thank you for everything.
You saved my life,
and I owe you for that.
Your cooking skills are
the best I've ever seen.
I hope to come
back again sometime.
I'll have a seat for you.
Chore Boy, get up
here right now!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Boss Zeff!
You're hard to find.
Hey, Ghin... Go.
Sorry...
You'll probably get
yelled at or fired
'cause you gave me
that food for free...
[SANJI]
Whatever...
[ZEFF]
Hmm...
[GHIN gasps]
Now there's not proof,
so there's no way for
me to get yelled at.
[GHIN gasps, sobs]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[SANJI] Try not to get
caught again, you hear?
[GHIN]
Thank you again, Chef Sanji!
I will never forget
your kindness!
[ZEFF]
Sanji! Chore Boy!
Get back to work already!
[COOK E]
Hey, table three is ready!
[COOKS chattering]
[LUFFY]
Hey, guys!
My name's Luffy,
and I'm gonna be the new
chore boy around here.
Nice to meet all of you!
What happened to that dessert?
Which one of us was
supposed to make that?
It was supposed to be him!
I don't have time to
make that, I'm too busy!
You're too busy being a jerk!
Say that again, I dare you!
[COOKS] Don't just sit
there picking your nose!
Go wash the dishes or
something... Right now!
[PATTY]
Has anyone seen Sanji?
[COOK I] I think I saw
him hittin' on a customer.
Again?!
I wish Boss Zeff
would get rid of him!
It's bad enough
he's the Sous Chef,
but he's never in the
kitchen doing his job!
[COOK J]
I think we're stuck with him.
He's worked here
longer than any of us.
[COOK J]
He was working the kitchen
and the dining room
even before I started.
[COOK L] Yeah, but even so,
I just don't get it.
‐‐[dish shatters]
‐‐Why does he stay here when
he and Boss Zeff
are always fighting?
[COOK J] I think he's
wants to be the Head Chef.
[COOK O]
Huh?
‐‐[PATTY] Hmm?
‐‐[dish shatters]
Chore Boy!
Just how many of these dishes
have you gone and
broken into tiny pieces?!
‐‐[LUFFY] You know what?
‐‐[dish shatters]
I forgot to count! Aw, man...
[PATTY] I wasn't being
serious, you idiot!
Why are you breaking them?!
[COOK P] Stop screwing around,
and clean up your mess.
[LUFFY]
That, I can do!
Ahh...
Stop! Don't take the food!
What's wrong with you?!
[COOK J]
That was a perfect entree!
[LUFFY laughs]
Yep! Pretty tasty!
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY]
Ow ow ow ow!
[COOKS]
Get out of our kitchen!
Why don't we have you take
orders in the dining room?
Just ask the customers
what they want to eat.
Is that simple enough?
[LUFFY]
Yes.
These chores sure are boring.
Wonder if Coby got tired
of all this work, too.
Chore Boy!
[LUFFY gasps]
What are you doing?!
We heard you had to work
here for a whole year.
Is it okay if we redraw
the flag for our ship?
[LUFFY gasps] You're eating all
this delicious food without me?
What kind of crew are you?
How could you do this to me?!
Hold on... I think that's our
business, isn't that right?
[ZORO laughs]
[LUFFY]
Take this.
Oh, boy... This is
gonna be so good.
[USOPP, NAMI snickering]
You know, I have to say the food
here is really quite delicious.
Good stuff...
Yes, it is...
[NAMI snickering]
I feel bad for you, but...
You should be
drinking this yourself!
[ZORO laughs]
‐‐[LUFFY choking]
‐‐[USOPP, NAMI laughing]
[LUFFY]
I can't believe you did that!
Yeah, well, I can't
believe you did that!
[LUFFY screaming]
Aw, that was nasty!
‐‐[CUSTOMERS murmuring]
‐‐[LUFFY coughing]
‐‐[CUSTOMER F growling]
‐‐Aren't they... quaint...
I wonder if that's
the rest of his crew.
‐‐[LUFFY screaming]
‐‐[GROUP laughing]
[NAMI laughing]
Finish pouring it yourself.
Oh, dear ocean, thank
you for this treasure
you have shared
from your depths.
[NAMI]
Huh?
Ah, yes, my love...
I can't bear this hardship
of loving you from afar.
It is too difficult.
I am now prepared to sail to the
ends of the earth as a pirate
if it means someone of your
rare beauty will be by my side!
‐‐[ZORO growling]
‐‐[LUFFY chuckles nervously]
To be together sailing the seas!
But how tragic a great
obstacle blocks our way.
[ZEFF] And that great
obstacle would be me, right?
Sanji...
[SANJI sighs]
Stupid geezer.
This is an opportunity you
don't want to pass up.
Why not join them
and become a pirate?
[SANJI gasps]
I have no need to keep
you here at my restaurant.
[SANJI growls]
[squawking]
[KRIEG]
I see...
This cook saved your life,
and you were able
to return here to us.
Is that what you
are saying... Ghin?
[GHIN]
Y‐Yes... but you see...
I had no idea the main ship was
in this condition, Don Krieg...
No idea.
[KRIEG]
So, what now?
Now, I believe I'll take you
to the Sea Restaurant Baratie.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[LUFFY]
Customer is king!
[USOPP] That's right! Give a
smile no matter who they are!
[ZORO]
Hey, there's a big fish here!
[NAMI]
That's...
[USOPP]
Krieg's Pirates!
[NAMI] They're a huge
fleet with five thousand men!
[LUFFY]
Five thousand?!
Hope we have enough chairs...
[USOPP]
You idiot!
They're going to attack this
place! Close the restaurant!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"The Strongest Pirate Fleet!
Commodore Don Krieg!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!