[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[DRAGON] Follow your own
beliefs to the end, Luffy.
With a will such as
yours and a little luck,
the masses may learn to
question this world, after all.
[DRAGON] Ride the winds
of change, my son.
That day you and I meet will
come soon enough, I'm sure.
[ZEFF] Enies Lobby is the
gateway to the World Government.
Once you've gone
knocking on that door,
I'm afraid there's
no turning back.
[ZEFF] You can bet your life
that pirates and Marines alike
have got their blood
boiling over this mess.
It won't be long before
everyone in the world will know
the names of the
Straw Hat Pirates.
[ZEFF] Their faces,
on the other hand...
[raucous laughter]
[PATTY]
Lookin' good there, Sanji!
[PATTY laughing]
[CARNE] This is one
of our former chefs!
[TEACH]
Zehahahaha!
That crazy bastard!
Get a load of this!
It's about Straw Hat!
He and his crew
went wild on Enies Lobby.
His bounty should go through
the roof after that one!
That's next to Water 7, yes?
I wonder if they hijacked
a sea train to get there.
That island
isn't far from here.
At this rate,
we might meet them again.
If fate is kind enough
to place them in our sights,
we're obligated to pull
the trigger, aren't we?
[coughs]
Wiiihahahaha!
What're we waiting for?
Nothing. Let's go!
Zehahahaha!
[TEACH] We'd better cut
them off before they leave,
or before the Navy
gets to 'em first.
[ACE] Hey. Hold on
a second there, Teach.
We need to talk.
[TEACH] Huh?
[NARRATOR] Three days
before the Straw Hat Pirates'
new bounties shocked the world,
another history-changing
event was about to occur
not far from Water 7.
[NARRATOR]
This is Banero Island,
a small settlement that will
soon be turned upside down
in a duel between
fire and shadow.
[LUFFY] The Most Heinous Power!
Blackbeard's
Darkness Attacks Ace!
Oh! What d'you know!
It's Commander Ace!
[ACE] You have no right
to call me that anymore.
Use that title with respect,
or don't use it at all.
I won't have you mock me.
[LAFITTE] Ooh! So this is
the famous "Fire Fist Ace."
[ACE] Yep, that's me.
You guessed it.
So this is your crew.
And it looks like you've
become a captain now, huh?
[ACE] Captain Marshall D.
Teach of the Blackbeard Pirates.
Zehahahaha!
C'mon Ace, lighten up!
It's good to see you again!
What brings you here?
You weren't looking
for me, were ya?
Let's stop beating around
the bush now, shall we?
Even if you play dumb,
I know you're a crafty bastard.
There's only one reason
for me to be here,
and you know what it is.
So spare me the chit-chat.
Fine, have it your way.
But there's one question
I'd like to ask first.
Instead of fighting,
why don't you become
a member of my crew?
I have the perfect plan
to rise to the top.
If you stick with me,
I swear, we can rule the world!
Whitebeard's days are
numbered and you know it.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
First, I'm headed off to Water 7
to kill Straw Hat Luffy
as a special gift
to the World Government.
Wouldn't hurt to have
you along for the fun!
Luffy, huh?
You're out of your mind.
[TEACH] Oh? You know him?
[ACE] Of course I know him,
you sack of crap!
I'm not gonna let you
kill my little brother!
And I'm not
joining your crew.
You can take your little
offer and shove it up your--
[gunshot]
Well, you get it.
Heh.
Looks like you need to teach
your crew some manners, Captain.
[ACE] Fire Gun!
[ACE]
Flame Commandment...
...Fire Pillar!
Auger, Burgess!
Both of you,
stay out of this fight!
Until you get stronger,
this guy's out of your league!
Do you hear me?
Oh, sorry.
[ACE] Fire Fist!
[screaming]
[TEACH] Hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
--Are you okay?
--[TEACH] Oh! Hot! Hot hot hot!
--Captain!
--[TEACH] Hot, hot, hot, hot!
[TEACH]
Ohhh!
Oh! Hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot! Ohhh!
[TEACH moaning in pain]
[AUGER] Here!
Get offa me, I'm fine!
Just stand back!
[TEACH chuckling softly]
[TEACH]
Zehahahahaha!
[TEACH] All right, Ace.
I get it.
You want to
finish me, don't you?
The murder of a fellow crewmate
is a serious crime, after all.
And yes, I killed fourth
division commander Thatch
with my own hands!
But there wasn't
any other choice!
Wasn't personal,
but he had the Devil Fruit
I'd been searching for!
You know the rules
on Whitebeard's ship.
Whoever finds one
of those gets to eat it.
I memorized the
shapes and colors
of all the Devil Fruits
that they've discovered,
so I knew that
was the one I needed.
[TEACH]
Whether I liked it or not,
I spent decades biding
my time on Whitebeard's ship,
because that was
the best shot I had
at finding that
one single fruit!
[TEACH] But just when I
thought there was no hope left,
there it was, right
in the hand of my friend.
Then you murdered him
in cold blood and stole it.
Without a second thought.
Bad luck for him.
There's no other way.
This ability has chosen me.
Zehahahaha!
And its power has made me
the strongest man
in the world!
[TEACH] Watch.
Even among the Logia Fruits,
there's nothing quite like it!
[TEACH] Ace, your body
is made of fire, right?
Zehahahahahaha!
My body is darkness!
[TOWNSMAN 325A] Look!
It's that weird
black smoke from before!
I thought those
pirates were leaving.
What're we gonna do now?
I don't know what they want,
but it can't be good!
They're gonna wreck the
entire town at this rate!
Well, we sure can't stop them!
It's best just to run away!
[CITIZENS panicking]
[ACE] Darkness?
[TEACH] You'll see soon
enough, Commander Ace.
I think you'll want
to reconsider my offer.
In the history
of all Devil Fruits,
this is said to be the most
dangerous power of them all!
The Logia-Type
Dark Dark Fruit.
In other words,
I've become a Darkness Man.
I'll give you a
taste of its power.
I wouldn't blink if I were you.
Stop yapping and do it.
Now ain't the time for a nap!
Captain's on a rampage!
If we don't high tail it
outta here, he'll kill us, too!
Not you, too, damn it!
Zehahahahaha!
[TOWNSMAN 325D] Look, it's
crawling on the ground.
It keeps pouring
out of him more and more.
[TOWNSMAN 325E]
This is too creepy.
It's pitch black,
like a bottomless pit.
What if it sucks us up?
Everyone, make a run for it!
Get out of here!
[TOWNSMAN 325D] Run to the
forest, run to the coast--
Just get away, quick!
[TEACH] Darkness is gravity.
It swallows
everything around it!
Even light itself can't escape!
Its power is infinite!
[ACE] That's nice,
but it's nowhere near me.
Are you sure you
got the hang of this?
[TEACH] Calm down.
I'm not aiming at you yet.
You'll be glad when you
see what I do to this town!
[TEACH] Black Hole!
[MAN 325A] Our town--
It's being swallowed
into the Earth!
[MAN 325B] Why is he doing this?
What's going on?
[TEACH] Within these shadows
lies the limitless power
to compress
anything and everything.
To crush whatever they touch!
[MAN 325C]
No, this is a nightmare.
My home!
[TEACH]
But that's just the beginning.
Now I'll show you
what happened to that town.
Or whatever's left
of it, I should say!
Liberation!
It's all gone...
Nothing left
but a pile of wood...
Zehahahahaha!
So do you get it now, Ace?
This was what I was
willing to kill a friend for!
Huh?
Firefly Fiery Doll!
[TEACH yelling]
[TEACH] Oh! Hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
The darkness part I get,
but this, not so much.
I wonder what's going on here.
If you're a Logia-Type,
that shouldn't hurt you.
Or rather,
it shouldn't even hit you.
I already told you.
My darkness swallows
everything around it.
Whether its punches, blades,
bullets, lightning, or fire!
[TEACH] Unlike you,
I can't just turn into an
element and dodge an attack.
And the pain
I absorb when I get hit
is much greater than
what a normal human feels.
But the tradeoff
for that inconvenience
is more than worth it.
'Cause there happens to be
one other thing I can absorb.
Black Vortex!
[TEACH] First, I use
the gravity of darkness
to pull a Devil Fruit
power holder into my grasp.
[ACE]
Too... strong...!
[TEACH] And then,
when I touch them...
[ACE groaning in pain]
You're smart.
Have you figured out
the secret yet? Huh?
It can't be...
Zehahahahaha!
Ahahahahaha!
It's been so long
since you've been hit,
I bet you forgot
how much it hurts, Ace.
[TEACH]
But you understand now.
You understood the
second I grabbed you.
Not only can my
darkness pull you in--
It can also absorb
your Devil Fruit power!
[TEACH] In other words, as long
as they're in contact with me,
someone with Devil Fruit powers
is no different
than a normal human.
Logia. Zoan. Paramythia.
All those with
Devil Fruit powers
who have become dependent
on them are in for a surprise.
One little touch will remind
them how weak they really are!
Then all I have
to do is avoid you.
[TEACH] If you think you can
escape gravity that easily,
I'd like to see you try!
Black Vortex!
[ACE] St. Elmo's Fire!
[TEACH] Damn it!
Get this offa me!
That bastard
almost broke my neck!
His ability's gonna be
a bigger pain than I thought.
[ACE] Cross Fire!
[MAN 325D]
Banana Rock is falling!
Nothing's safe anymore!
[MAN 325E] No human should
have this kind of power!
Who are these monsters?
Forget about the town,
they'll destroy
the entire island!
We're done for!
[AUGER]
This is quite a surprise.
Most Devil Fruit power holders
with one such as his
would be rendered ineffective
as soon as their trump card
was taken away from them.
Not so with Ace.
His powers are not a crutch,
but an aid to his own talents.
We should expect no less from
one of Whitebeard's Commanders.
We're at the
crossroads of fate.
It's no coincidence that these
men have been brought together.
Everything falls
before darkness.
Even you can only
struggle for so long.
[TEACH] Still,
finishing you off here
would be a waste
of your talent.
Don't fight it, Ace! Join me!
If I surrendered to you,
then I could never
call myself a man again.
I won't submit, and I won't live
with regrets, no matter what.
You got that, stupid?
Once you die,
your morals are useless.
I'm sorry you can't
understand that, Ace.
Darkness take you!
[ACE] Great Flame Commandment!
[ACE] Flame Emperor!
Zehahahahaha!
The sun against darkness, huh?
Only one can win!
I'll make Whitebeard
the King, or die trying.
[NARRATOR] Although no one
realized it at the time,
the duel at
Banero Island that day
was not merely a struggle
between Whitebeard
and Blackbeard;
it was a catalyst.
This was the beginning
of a chain of events
that would change the world.
[LUFFY] Full speed ahead!
Time for a new adventure!
[SANJI] Beautiful mermaid
island, here we come!
[USOPP] Whoa-whoa-whoa
whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
We're in dangerous waters here!
Would it kill you
to use a little caution?
[LUFFY] Look, Sanji!
It's another ship!
[SANJI]
With no sail and no flag.
[USOPP] See, I knew it--
We're in trouble already!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
The Mysterious Band of Pirates!
Sunny and the Dangerous Trap!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!