Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Auugh!!
[CHOPPER]
Zoro's falling towards us!
[ROBIN] Cien Fleurs!
And Spider Net!
[USOPP]
You might be huge,
but you're still a zombie!
Special Attack: Salt Star!
[USOPP]
Taste good?
It wasn't...
It wasn't enough!
He's too big!
[CHOPPER]
Now, Heavy Gong!
[USOPP]
Luffy you jerk.
[OARS]
I don't know you.
My name's not Luffy.
I'm Master Moria's servant,
the name is Oars.
[LUFFY]
"You're Going Down, Absalom!
Nami's Lightning
Attack of Friendship!"
[OARS] One. Two. Three.
Four. Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
And...
[OARS] Dunno those two,
but whatever.
So let's see here.
There's that Straw Hat guy.
Orange hair lady.
And awesome super-hero.
That's five down
and three to go.
Wonder where they're hiding.
[PERONA]
No!
Not roaches! Anything but
roaches! Stop it Please!
[USOPP]
Usopp.
Ten Ton... Hammer!
[ZOMBIE PURPLE THING]
Hey, she's up!
[ZOMBIE GREENBEAR]
Are you all right, Mistress?
[PERONA freaking out]
I can't take it anymore!!
Mistress Perona!
Calm down, milady.
It's just us,
your loyal servants!
We brought you to safety,
but you've been crying
about roaches in your sleep
for a while now.
Where are we?
[ZOMBIE PURPLE THING] We didn't
see any signs of the enemy.
We just found you laying down,
foaming at the mouth.
[ZOMBIE KANGAROO] Who in the
world could've done that to you?
Was it that
nose guy from before?
Why's the mansion falling apart,
what's that rumbling?
Don't tell me those pirates
are on a rampage again.
[ZOMBIE PURPLE THING]
The pirates are still
going on a rampage, I think,
but it's actually Oars that's
causing all this destruction.
[PERONA]
You're kidding me!
This is not good.
[ZOMBIE HELMETAPE] I hate to say
this, but from what we heard,
Oars didn't just
wreck the mansion--
He crushed the
Zombie Generals, too.
But they're the
strongest zombies we've got!
So it turns out Moria
can't control Oars after all?
[ZOMBIE PURPLE THING]
Well he is really big, so--
[screaming]
Oh no, you guys!
He got my bro!
I heard a girl.
Wha... What does he want?
This might be a
good time to tell you
that he kinda stomped
on Doctor Hogback, too.
He did what?
[OARS]
Girlie?
I was wrong.
Hey, lady!
I can't take this!
If he's looking for a girl,
who knows what
he'll do if he finds me!
Between him and the pirates,
this place is doomed!
I'm outta here!
I need you guys
to grab all the treasure
and all the food you can carry!
I'm gonna steal
their pirate ship and run!
What pirate ship?
The Straw Hats'!
Now before we all get crushed,
let's go!
--As you wish, mistress!
[PERONA]
Aw, jeez.
[OARS]
Where's da girl?
--Mistress Perona!
[ZOMBIE PRIEST]
You may now kiss the bride.
[ABSALOM]
Finally!
I've been waiting long enough!
What? What? No! Stop it!
What're you doing?
Where am I? Cut it out!
Damn it!
So she finally woke up, huh?
Well, that won't stop me!
[ABSALOM]
Come on, my dear.
I already went through
all the boring stuff!
Just let me kiss you
so we can be husband and wife!
[NAMI]
I said no!
Those aren't even human lips!
And I'm a pirate!
I'm into adventure, not romance!
[ABSALOM]
But I'm the Graveyard King!
You'll be the Graveyard Queen!
Doesn't that sound wonderful?
[NAMI]
What does that even mean?
[LOLA]
Curse you, Namizo!
Lo...
Lola! No!
[LOLA]
Namizo. You...
[LOLA] How dare you
do this to me, you traitor!
You said Master Ab and I
would make a beautiful couple!
Then I turn around for five
minutes and you're marrying him?
You said you were my friend,
but all you wanted was my man!
I should've known better
than to trust a thief like you!
Hold on a second Lola,
you've got this all wrong!
I mean, for one, I was
knocked out this entire time.
I don't have a clue what--
Is this a wedding dress?
Why am I wearing this?
It's pretty, though.
[LOLA]
Oh, it looks pretty, huh?
How wonderful for you!
[NAMI] This is all
a big misunderstanding!
That is enough!
Why don't you just
bury your rotting carcass
in a hole somewhere,
so I can get married already!
If you wanna get married,
marry me!
I would rather die!
My poor little Ab,
ignorant of
the terrifying truth.
And what is that
supposed to mean?
[LOLA] This so-called woman's
real name is Namizo
and she's really...
A man!
Whaaaaat?!!
No, that can't be true!
[NAMI thinking]
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot I told her that.
So how's that?
Still wanna get married, Ab?
You into guys now?
And to think,
if she hadn't burst in,
I would've married a man.
I was just a few seconds away
from kissing him
right on the lips!
[ABSALOM]
But wait.
I saw her in the bath.
I know I did.
[ABSALOM]
I made it just in time.
[NAMI]
Looks like this is it.
[NAMI] All right you two,
wait out here for a second.
--Okay.
I could've sworn
I heard something.
[USOPP] Hey Nami,
need some help in there?
I'm fine--
Just watch the door for me!
[USOPP]
'Kay.
[ABSALOM]
That was a close one!
That was some bo-yo-yoing
if I've ever seen it.
[LOLA] Get the hell out of here,
you filthy traitor!
[NAMI] I'm telling you,
it's not my fault!
[ABSALOM]
No cutting up my bride, Lola!
[LOLA]
I said, get out of here!
[NAMI thinking]
She keeps missing me.
[LOLA]
Namizo.
[NAMI]
What?
[LOLA whispering] Run for
it while you still can!
I'll hold him off, but I
don't know how long I can last!
I came here to
save you, my friend!
[NAMI]
Lola!
[LOLA]
Come here, Master Ab!
That's right, sweetheart,
if you're looking for
a kiss, then pucker up,
because Lola's got a big
wet one right here for ya!
[NAMI]
Lola.
Damn it,
my bride's getting away!
[LOLA] Wrong! Your bride
is right here, baby!
Nice try,
but you can't convince me
that my bride's a man.
Now move. Or suffer!
Lola!
[ABSALOM] You're nothing
but a lowly zombie.
How dare you make me waste so
much strength disposing of you!
Ah, that's a good girl.
Finally wised up and
stopped running, did you?
You can't hide,
and you can't escape.
Because wherever you may go,
I'll hunt you down.
And I can assure you,
you'll never see me coming!
Now Thunder Charge.
How dare you.
I think you and that Ab
Guy make a super cute couple.
You two should totally
hook it up, girlfriend!
[LOLA]
Huh?
You think?
[LOLA] To be completely honest,
I was beginning to lose hope.
All this time,
no one has ever offered me
a single word of encouragement.
You don't know
how much it means.
Thank you. Thank you.
[NAMI]
Raise your head up high.
It's okay.
You don't have to
thank me for saying that.
We're friends.
My name is Namizo.
But you can call me Nami.
[LOLA]
We're friends? Nami!
Namizo.
[NAMI]
What?
[LOLA]
Run for it while you still can!
I'll hold him off, but I don't
know how long I can last!
I came here to
save you, my friend!
You can't do that to Lola!
Yes, my dear.
Come flying into
your husband's arms.
Swing... Arm!
I know this isn't
enough to beat you,
but I'll be damned
if I don't try!
Huh?
Ab-sweetie!
Yes, my dear.
Come flying into
your husband's arms.
Darling!
Huh?
I don't get it.
It hardly seemed to hurt him at
all the last time I did that.
[ZOMBIE PRIEST] It's only
natural, I suppose.
That pervert he was fighting
earlier really wore him out.
He was already
well past his limit.
Well, whatever, right?
I win! Yeah!
I guess I must've hit
his weak spot or something!
[NAMI]
Lola!
Are you okay? Hang in
there!
Thank you!
I don't know what I would've
done if you hadn't shown up.
You don't have to
thank me, Namizo.
We're friends, right?
I owe you an apology, Lola.
When I first saw you, I was
scared and I told you a lie.
It's just that...
I thought if I said I was a
man, you'd leave me alone.
You big silly.
It was pretty obvious.
I guess so.
Wait just a second,
Absalom is completely
helpless right now!
[LOLA]
I'm gonna make you mine, baby!
Under here? Hello, Straw Hats?
[LUFFY]
Get back here!
You big, dumb onion!
Stop running away from me!
At least give me
a chance to kick your ass!
If you're so tough,
why do you have to run, huh?
Man.
[LUFFY]
Great. Now I lost him.
Gum-Gum... Whip!
Don't think I'm
giving up that easy, damn it!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Whip!
One more!
[LUFFY]
Found you!
Not so fast!
Whoa.
What was that all about?
I dunno, but wasn't
that Straw Hat Luffy?
Are you sure?
I thought he said he was going
to the mansion to beat Moria.
What's he doing
all the way out here?
He says he's gonna
kick his ass, then he runs away?
Well, I guess
you're just going to
have to kick
Moria's ass yourselves!
[MORIA]
Kushishishi! Kushishishi!
Oh crap, it's him!
Now let's be honest
with ourselves here.
Straw Hat says he can
beat me, and you believe him?
Just like that? Kushishishi!
[MORIA] Sorry, but that's
not gonna happen.
Not now, not ever.
And if you don't wanna
take my word for it,
you can stick around
and watch your
precious little "savior"
get his face pounded
into the ground.
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
[OARS]
Anybody in there?
Straw Hat, maybe?
Orange hair lady? Hero guy?
[FRANKY]
Crap.
This guy's gonna be
a real pain in the ass.
[ZORO] He's not just strong,
he's fast as hell for his size.
[SANJI]
What was his name again?
[CHOPPER]
Oh, uh...
[ZORO]
Think it was "Roast", right?
[USOPP]
No, not even close.
I think it had an "s"
at the end, didn't it?
[CHOPPER]
Hughes?
[USOPP] Eh, I think you're
getting colder, actually.
[SANJI]
"Fours"?
[USOPP]
Hm...
No, wait, that's close, but...
[ROBIN]
It's "Oars."
[CREW] That's it!
[BROOK]
Uh...
I'm sorry, but my injuries
are quite terrible...
[FRANKY]
It's fine. We understand.
You can still
move around though, right?
[BROOK]
Yes.
[FRANKY] Then move
yourself outta the way.
[BROOK]
Of course.
[SANJI]
Hey. Oars!
[OARS]
Huh?
[SANJI] If that's really Luffy's
Shadow you've got inside you,
then I probably shouldn't
have to tell you this,
but you should
never underestimate
the strength of your own crew.
[CHOPPER] How can Oars
replicate all of Luffy's moves
with that massive body?
[FRANKY]
He's left us no choice.
It's time for you-know-what.
Let's show him the strength
of our powers combined
and teach him a lesson.
[CHOPPER] You wanna do
you-know-what right now?
[FRANKY] All right guys!
Let's do this!
Tactic fifteen!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Knock Him Down!!
Special Attack:
Straw Hat Docking?"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!