♪ opening song ♪
[crackling fire]
So how's our
bearing looking? All good?
Hmph! It's perfect.
Just like you,
Nami-swan!
[banging hammer]
[satisfied sigh]
I've just about got
these holes patched.
We'd be in a
whole world of worry
if I hadn't had
the foresight to
grab all this scrap
lumber back at the dock!
You're the best, Usopp!
[USOPP chuckles] This should
hold her together for a while.
Huh?! It's out!
Fuel burned out, huh?
[ZORO] Hey, Usopp!
We're going down!
We gotta move it, Chopper!
Hurry and grab those boards!
Uh, sure.
[LUFFY] Just hang in
there octopus balloon!
[SANJI] Get down, moron!
[whistling air]
[loud splash]
[USOPP] Ughh!
That was way too close.
That should help get
rid of the stinging.
That's two times
now you've helped us
out of a real tight spot!
Thanks, buddy!
Thank you again
for all of your help!
I hope you make lots of new
friends out in the Blue Sea!
Stay strong!
And don't take any crap
from those Grand Line octopi.
You travel safe, sushi-platter.
Careful out there!
Thanks for everything!
Now then! Set the sails!
Hop to! Let's find
the next island!
[USOPP] Whoa, hey, c'mon, Luffy!
Can't we rest a little while?
[NAMI]
You're a little too relaxed.
Listen, that attitude
isn't going to get us
very far on these seas.
I don't think
I want to hear this.
The waves look a little
too strange for comfort,
so it's back to work!
Turn to port!
[SANJI] Anything
for you, Nami dear!
You see?
[USOPP] Full speed ahead!
[CHOPPER] This
doesn't look good for us!
[SANJI] There's something
in the wave. Is that debris?
[USOPP] What? No!
Those are Sea Monkeys!
[PIRATE 207X] What's
all the ruckus out here?!
Make way!
Quit pushing! C'mon!
Stop it! Lemme go!
Why are they fighting?!
Bellamy!
Sarquiss!
Isn't someone gonna stop them?!
[SARQUISS pants heavily]
No more! I'm begging you!
Why are you making me do this?!
What the hell is going on?
I've never seen
Sarquiss plead like that.
[DOFLAMINGO] Why you ask?
Why am I making you?
Sarquiss. Bellamy.
I'm making you do this
because you've made a mockery
of this symbol. Heh heh heh...
[DOFLAMINGO] Does the
Sky Island exist or not?
Is the legendary
City of Gold real or not?
The truth doesn't
really matter, now does it.
You play the opposing
sides off each other,
to twist them to your will.
That's what I told you.
Right, Bellamy?
[PIRATE 207F] I think that's,
Don Quixote Doflamingo!
[PIRATE 207G] He's one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
I heard his bounty's
over 300 million.
What's a guy like
him doing here?
You've really let me down
and I've got zero tolerance
for useless punks like you.
No! Not again!
My body's moving,
on its own, I can't
control it! Please, nooooo!
[slicing sound]
--Bellamy!
[BELLAMY] Please.
Huh?
[BELLAMY] Just give me one more
chance, to set things right.
I swear we will loyally
follow your every command.
Bellamy!
Let it go, Bellamy!
[breathing heavily]
I might've lost
but I have never once acted
against your principles.
I swear on your
symbol! Please!
I had reasons for my actions!
I couldn't just let the
Straw Hats get away.
They were bound to find you
someday if I didn't stop them!
Ahhh... What a
touching sentiment.
Such genuine loyalty.
Your concern for my well-being
is duly noted, Bellamy.
Heh heh heh... There's a
New Era quickly approaching,
so your actions here
won't really matter.
But, I still have
no use for you.
Doflamingooo!
[slicing sound]
[DOFLAMINGO chuckles]
He wiped out
Bellamy as easily as
stomping on a baby!
He was worth 55 million!
Hehehehe...
The beginning is upon us!
I suggest you prepare. We're
drawing close to a new world
in which only true
pirates can survive.
The weak should
run while they still can,
or be swept away
by the tides of time
as they roll back to reveal
a New Era of Champions!
Ha ha ha ha ha!!
[seagull calling]
Seems pretty calm now.
It's too soon to
lower our guard.
Emergency alert!
Unknown ship
spotted at 12 o'clock!
Are they bad guys?
They picked a bad time.
[USOPP] Well, they don't
have a single flag or sail up.
I don't know what
kind of ship it is!
It's naked?! Who would
do that their ship?
What are they doing
out here without sails?
[USOPP] How should I know?
What's even weirder,
the crew is way too
small for a ship that size.
Also, they look like they're
catatonic or something.
They're just sitting
around in a daze!
[LUFFY] Full speed! Sea Monkeys!
[USOPP] Again?!
[ZORO] They must've followed us!
[SANJI] Aw, crap,
there's no wind!
[NAMI] Hurry and furl the sails!
[USOPP] C'mon, start rowing!
[SANJI] What's wrong with them?!
They're headed towards
the Sea Monkeys!
[ZORO] That wave's
gonna swallow them whole!
Hey! Wake up!
There's a giant wave filled
with Sea Monkeys! Turn around!
Huh?!
A ship! Whoa!
It's a pirate ship!
[FROG CREW 207B]
C'mon, men! On your feet!
We gotta raid that ship
and swipe their treasure!
[FROG CREW 207C] Wait!
We're gonna get crushed
by that giant wave!
[FROG CREW 207D] Yeah,
but we can't let them get away!
[FROG CREW 207B]
Ready the cannons!
[FROG CREW 207E]
You ain't the boss!
Why don't you do it?!
[FROG CREW 207C]
Turn! Somebody turn!
Wow, that's got to
be the worst crew ever.
Forget about those idiots.
They only want to
steal our treasure.
Which way do we turn?!
Who knows?!
Where's the navigator?!
Give orders!
--What navigator?!
Captain!
--What captain?!
What the? Who
fired the canon?!
[FROG CREW 207A]
It's too late, we're going down!
[FROG CREW 207B] You're a
bunch of worthless morons!
[FROG CREW 207D] No!
You're a bunch of morons!
[FROG CREW 207A] What a
stupid way for us to die!
[ZORO] Man, it's just
one terrible thing
after another these days.
At least it's calm.
Those gargantuan waves earlier
were actually caused
by the Sea Monkeys.
The humidity and
temperature seem like
they're pretty stable now.
So we've gotta be in the
next island's climate zone.
You hear that,
Robin? Any islands?
We've been approaching
one for a while now.
[USOPP] Why didn't you tell us?!
[LUFFY] Why didn't you tell us?!
You are way too secretive! Look!
Maybe tell us next
time you see an island!
You know, like this!
Land ahoy! Land!
I see land! Yea! Yea!
Now you say it!
The fog looks pretty thick.
Don't ignore me!
Heavy fog? That's not good.
Hey Chopper, I need you
to stand forward watch!
[CHOPPER]
Right!
[LUFFY] Robin! Do you
have any idea how long
we've been waiting
to see another island?
[ROBIN] Sorry,
won't happen again.
[LUFFY] Well, as long
as you mean it. Okay.
You know, I can't stop
thinking about that ship.
They didn't have a captain
or a navigator or even sails!
It was like they had no
idea what they were doing!
Now what kind of
self-respecting pirates
would head out to sea like that?
I'm guessing they
got in a battle and lost.
Captain probably got killed and
then their ship got plundered.
But that can't be it.
I got a look at their ship.
It was in perfect condition.
No signs of battle but it was
still completely stripped clean
of anything a pirate
would need to survive.
They probably weren't
even pirates then. Forget it.
Hmmm... They looked
like pirates to me.
Crummy pirates,
but still, I don't know.
I got a bad feeling
about this somehow.
[SANJI] Have you
ever had a good one?
[LUFFY] Anyway!
I wonder if there's a town.
I hope they've got a shipyard.
[NAMI] Luffy! Don't
jump off right away!
I hope we can find
a knowledgeable
shipwright to join us.
Get the anchor ready!
We're near the shore!
That feeling just got worse.
[SANJI] Hey, Chopper,
Usopp's come down
with another bout
of "Scaredy-Cat-itis."
Well, there's
no cure for that.
[LUFFY] Alright,
let's go, let's go!
Hmm?
You're kidding.
[LUFFY] There's nothing at all!
It's like a blank slate! Cool!
All I can see is
grass and trees!
Man, this place is
kind of depressing.
I wonder if anyone
actually lives here.
[LUFFY] Yahoo!
[NAMI] Hey!
[CHOPPER] Me too!
Jeez, it's like they have no
concept of unknown danger.
You can see clear
across the island
and there's no threat in sight.
[startled shriek]
You see something, Chopper?
[thinking]
Human?
Have you ever seen a
human this furry and enormous?
It's got to be
some kind of bear!
[USOPP] Whoa, it's so
long! It's a long bear!
[CHOPPER] I'm
getting dizzy up here!
Hey! Check out how
long this apple is!
Whoa!
I'm just realizing it, but
the trees are long too!
Hmm...
Hey, look! Is that
a house over there?
Yeah, I guess it
looks like a house.
Let's go check it out.
Are you guys related?
That's a deer
and I'm a reindeer!
Shake!
Hey, Chopper! Watch this.
Go for it, Usopp!
[LUFFY] Down.
Now, beg!
It's miles long!
[USOPP] Wow! I can't
even see its head!
Huh?
[ZORO] Where the hell
did they run off to?
[NAMI] They were right
there just a minute ago.
[SANJI] We might
as well disembark.
There's got to be
food on this island.
Hey, earth to Robin!
We're gonna jump ship, okay?
Right.
[USOPP] Everything on
this island is so long.
How'd it get this way?
Maybe it's the gravity?
[CHOPPER] My body
feels all stretched out
just from thinking about it.
[USOPP] And what is the
point of a place like this?
[LUFFY]
Hello? Anyone home?
[USOPP] What do you
think you're doing?!
You can't go in there!
For all we know,
the boss of the island
lives in this house
and he's probably
some terrifyingly
long man-snake monster
that'll swallow us whole!
It's empty. No one's home.
[CHOPPER] Hey, Luffy! Usopp!
There's a giraffe out here!
--Really?!
[neighing]
Chopper that's not a giraffe.
It's just a horse with a
long neck. A long horse.
You're a horse?
Wow, what a pretty horse!
She said thank you
and her name is Shelly.
Going by the saddle
she's got on her,
her owner must be close by.
Hey what are you looking at?
Over there.
There's something up with
those two bamboo trees.
[USOPP] Huh? Yeah, you're
right, talk about tall!
I can't even see the top!
That's not it look closer.
Huh? AHHHH!
They're moving!
Huh? They must be part
of some long animal!
That thing's attacking
Luffy! Are you okay?!
Get back here, bamboo!
Be careful, Luffy!
Gum-Gum whip!
Alright! You did it!
Yeah! I beat it!
Why are you alone?
Where's your owner?
You don't know where?
That sounds awfully lonely.
[loud crash]
It might be bad guys!
Stay there and hide!
What's going on?!
Well, uh. I think
that bamboo tree
was possessed by this spirit.
[blast then whistling sound]
Huh?
[SANJI] Hey, what's the deal?
They blocked in our ship.
This can't be good.
[thinking]
That's the ship I saw earlier.
You looking for a fight?
Cause we'll be happy
to give you one.
[FOXY CREW 208A] We are the
notorious Foxy Pirates!
We want more than
just a fight from you.
We want a showdown!
[CHOPPER]
A spirit?
[LUFFY] Well, yeah what
else pops out of a tree?
[USOPP]
Hey, can you speak?
Quit acting like
I don't remember you,
of course I do!
What've you been up
to all these years?
Huh? You guys know him?
Never seen him.
Same here.
[TONJIT] Ah, Well
that would explain why
I don't remember you then.
Who are you, old man?
And tell us the truth!
If you want my
name, it's Tonjit.
But what I intend to
give you is my gratitude.
I've been hoping
someone would
knock me down
off of those stilts.
Off what? Uh...
Oh! They are stilts.
We didn't realize
cause they were so long.
We couldn't even see you.
[TONJIT] I'm not surprised.
I couldn't even see
the ground up there.
So then, just to
get this straight,
you're not a
bamboo tree spirit.
You're just an
old guy whose stilts
I happened to think
were attacking me.
What were you doing walking
around on those stilts anyway?
Well, I've always
been a stilt enthusiast
so I decided to
break some records
and make the
world's longest stilts
by using the
bamboo on this island.
I managed to get on
them with a little effort,
but then I was too
scared to climb down!
That's just plain crazy!
I was up there ten years.
Really crazy!
Wait, you were up
there on those stilts
for ten whole years?!
That's right and to
make matters worse,
the bamboo kept
growing the entire time.
It just kept getting harder
and harder to climb down.
So terrifying.
How'd you live up
there for ten years?!
[TONJIT] Well most of
the trees on this island
are just as tall as
my stilts, if not taller,
so I was well fed
from their fruit.
He talks about it
like it was no big deal,
ten long years of his life.
And speaking of
stuff that's long.
How come every
living creature
on this island is
so insanely long?
It might seem
crazy to an outsider
but there is a reason.
As I'm sure you've noticed,
the island is nothing
but grass and trees.
It's dull. So
everything grew long
out of a longing
for excitement.
[LUFFY thinking]
He can't be serious.
You see that over there?
[TONJIT]
Plaaaaaatypus.
[USOPP]
You just said it longer.
[TONJIT] That one is
a daaaaaachshund dog.
[CHOPPER] Whoa!
Is that the same dog?
[bark]
[USOPP] It's still
passing? Oh, man.
And there are dangerous
animals as well, see?
Over there is a snoooooow
leopard I'd steer clear of it.
Huh?
[growls]
[USOPP] Why is its head
the only thing that's long?
[FOXY] Hmmm...
Feh-feh-feh-feh...
Hello. We found the captain.
♪ ending song ♪
[FOXY]
Feh-feh-feh-feh!
My name is Foxy and
I take whatever I want,
whenever I want!
[ZORO]
Ah, great, another weirdo.
[FOXY] I've come to
challenge you, Straw Hat!
[LUFFY] Are you sure you
wanna do that, split-head?
[FOXY]
What'd you call me?!
[LUFFY]
I accept your challenge!
I'll give you the
fight of your life!
[USOPP] Slow down, Luffy!
Don't just agree like that!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Davy Back with
the Foxy Pirates!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!