[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
With the aid of
the Whitebeard Pirates,
he pushes toward the scaffold,
only to be halted by
massive encircling walls,
activated by the Navy.
But with a helping hand
from Jimbei,
Luffy is able to propel
himself over the walls
and land inside the plaza!
Luffy!
I'm comin' for ya!
I'll save you!
[LUFFY yells]
What is that?
[PIRATE JJ]
They've closed us in!
[PIRATE KK]
What the hell's going on?
[SENGOKU]
You know what to do, Akainu!
Meteor Volcano!
[AKAINU shouts]
Holy crap... That's lava.
They've got nowhere to run.
Now we'll melt that ice
and drown them all!
[PIRATES screaming]
[WHITEBEARD gasps]
[WHITEBEARD]
I'm sorry, old friend.
[SENGOKU] The plan is working
perfectly, so we'll proceed.
Phase two is the
immediate execution
of Portgas D. Ace!
[PIRATES shouting]
[LUFFY]
Jimbei.
[panting]
I need a favor from you.
[JIMBEI]
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
I see. So you found a way up.
You've done quite well,
son of Dragon.
You're standing tall now.
Ahh, youth. So much fire!
Back off!
You're not gonna kill Ace!
[LUFFY yelling]
Gum-Gum Stamp Gatling!
[LUFFY]
"Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's
Trump Card for Recovery!"
[LUFFY yelling]
[COBY gasps]
I knew Luffy was nuts,
but he'll join his brother
five feet under at this rate!
He signed his own death warrant!
He'll be dead before
the ink can dry!
[YAMAKAJI]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Now for Second Gear!
[AKAINU grunts]
Straight to Ace. I don't have
time to fight these guys!
[KIZARU] Hmm. Trying
to sneak by us, huh?
[gasps]
[KIZARU]
Huh.
You almost made it.
[LUFFY yells]
Luffy!
He is so dead!
[LUFFY coughs, groans]
Damn it!
[grunts]
Get ready, men!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[LUFFY gasps]
Now, do it!
Ace, no!
You monsters!
No! Stop!
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[LUFFY gasping]
[GARP gasping]
[SENGOKU gasps]
[MARINES scream]
[MARINES grunting]
Who did that?
[MARINES gasping]
[CROCODILE grunts]
[SENGOKU]
You bastard!
[SENGOKU] I thought
it would be advantageous
to have you here for the battle,
since you hold a grudge
against Whitebeard.
Curse you, Crocodile!
[LUFFY gasps]
No way!
What's goin' on? Thought I'd
have a chance to show off.
Just a short while ago
Crocodile was trying
to murder Whitebeard.
Wonder what transpired to
make him change his mind.
[CROCODILE] I can kill
that old, dying buzzard
whenever I feel like it.
But as for right now, I'm not
gonna let you taste victory.
You and your crooked operation.
[MARINES gasping]
Hey, pal. Do you remember me?
I-It's Doflamingo!
First you turn me down,
and now you wanna
team up with Whitebeard?
You've got some nerve
playing me like that.
[chuckles]
Don't be foolish. I'm not
teaming up with anybody.
Either way, you're giving my
friendship a cold shoulder.
I can't say I appreciate that.
Deal with it.
Those two are distracting
everybody else. Now's my chance!
Hey, Straw Hat! You're mine!
--[LUFFY gasps]
--[MARINE D] Die!
[LUFFY grunts]
[MARINES groan]
Better get outta my way...
...or else!
[MARINES yelling]
[LUFFY panting]
[KIBIN]
Not another step, Straw Hat!
Your temper tantrum
ends right now!
[LUFFY]
Move it!
[KIBIN]
Shave!
Moon Walk!
[LUFFY panting]
Iron Body Smash!
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Bullet!
[KIBIN groaning]
[MARINE DD]
Don't let him come any closer!
Admiral Sakazuki, sir!
[AKAINU]
Hm?
[AOKIJI grunts]
[LUFFY yelling]
Damn it! That hurts!
[AOKIJI] I still owe your
grandfather a favor, Straw Hat,
but you've left me no choice.
You chose to risk your life.
You gotta face the music.
You fiend! I won't let
you hurt my darling!
[gasps]
[MARCO grunts]
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINE EE]
Admiral!
[MARINE FF]
Aw, crap.
[MARINE GG] Whitebeard's
First Division Commander, Marco!
[panting]
Thanks, buddy! Ya saved me.
Ahh, don't mention it, pal.
[MARINE HH] There are
three invaders in the plaza!
They're using their
Devil Fruit powers
to go straight over the walls!
Huh? Did he say "three"?
Could they be referring to me?
Or am I just being paranoid
because they said "three"?
No, that can't be right.
When would they have
learned about me?
I barely escaped Admiral
Aokiji's freezing attack!
In fact, I've barely survived
a slew of close calls!
It's a miracle
I've gotten this far!
But even down here
I'm at risk of being exposed!
Are there no safe havens
in this wretched place?
[MR. 3 gasps]
I've been spotted!
Good grief.
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE AA] Everyone swim
across the bay towards Oars!
[PIRATE BB]
We have to get to the plaza,
no matter what it takes!
Excuse me, Fleet Admiral!
The pirates inside the bay are
beginning to swim towards us!
[SENGOKU]
Hmm?
[SENGOKU grunts]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE AA]
Come on, everybody!
Don't stop swimming
until you get to Oars!
[PIRATE BB]
We have to get to the plaza,
no matter what it takes!
They really think they
can get to us, huh?
Guard the gap and
don't let them through!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[PIRATES shouting]
They've got nothing to lose
now that we've sunk
the ice and their ships.
Talk about an easy target.
Now fire away while
we still have the chance!
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATES panting]
Don't let it rattle you!
Swim, swim, swim!
[PIRATE CC]
We've almost made it to Oars!
[PIRATE DD]
Get to the plaza!
What? Why aren't they stopping?
They should've turned around
or been killed a long time ago!
Keep going!
[MARINES gasp]
[PIRATES grunting]
[MARINES gasping]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE EE]
Grab ahold and get on board!
[PIRATE FF]
Don't let go!
I-It's another pirate ship!
Sir, we have a problem! Another
coated pirate ship's about to
enter the bay,
and it's coming fast!
You've gotta be kidding me!
It must've been hidden
underwater the entire time!
[SENGOKU growls]
[PIRATES grunting]
[PIRATES shouting, cheering]
We caught those punks off guard.
I never said they had
sunk all of our ships.
It looks like a paddle boat,
and it's heading straight
for us at full speed!
No! Whitebeard!
Now, sink that thing!
Drop it like the Moby Dick!
Cease fire! The ship is too
fast. Aim your fire at Oars!
Wha--? Oars, the giant?
Too late, Sengoku.
Everybody, ready!
[yelling]
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINE II]
That's insane!
He plucked the ship
right outta the bay!
[MARINE JJ]
This is bad.
They've broken through
the encircling walls!
[SENGOKU growls]
[PIRATES shouting]
We made it to the plaza, guys!
[PIRATE GG]
Ace is right there!
[PIRATE HH] Let's burn
their headquarters down!
[PIRATE II]
Hold on, Ace! We're coming!
[GARP]
Hm, impressive.
That space could barely
fit one ship through,
yet here we are with
a boat full of pirates!
The walls were
supposed to trap them,
and they might end up
trapping us instead!
That's enough!
He just won't give up.
Lucky break. We got here
right on time. Sit tight, Ace.
[panting]
Yeah, we did it!
The platform... Ace is on
the platform. We can sa--
[OARS JR. yells]
[PIRATES]
Oars, no!
[OARS JR. groans]
Save Ace for me, guys.
Don't let them kill him.
Oars, why?
[panting]
[AKAINU]
Huh?
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINE KK]
It's Whitebeard!
Whitebeard has
entered the plaza!
[WHITEBEARD]
My sons, please, stay back.
[WHITEBEARD yells]
[MARINES yelling]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
Listen up, pirates!
Bring Ace to safety!
And once you're done with
that, destroy the Navy!
[PIRATES shouting]
[SENGOKU]
Are ya with me, Garp?
[GARP]
Yeah.
I fear we can't
hold back any more.
This battle may be our last.
[LUFFY panting]
Don't worry, Ace!
I'm comin' for ya!
[NARRATOR]
His adoptive son within reach,
Whitebeard charges
forth undeterred
by the strongest warriors
the Navy has to offer.
With both sides swinging
between victory and defeat,
the battlefield
plunges into chaos.
Then Marco takes to the sky
and soars to Ace's side!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy at the End of His Tether!
An All-Out Battle
at the Oris Plaza!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!