[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain
has fallen in the desert
kingdom of Alabasta,
the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other.
Luffy separated from
Vivi and the others
in order to defeat Crocodile.
However, the Straw Hat
captain could not best
the Warlord of the Sea,
and he sank
beneath the sand.
With the unexpected help
of Miss All Sunday,
Luffy escaped with his life,
but he was badly injured,
and his wounds
made a quick recovery
seem all but hopeless.
Meanwhile, Vivi and the
others headed for Alubarna.
The vastness of the
desert presented them
with no small challenge,
but the unique creatures
that inhabit the land
offered the travelers aid
and sped along their journey.
Vivi desperately hopes
to prevent a battle.
Time is not on
her side, however,
as a rebel army of
two million strong
is about to close in on
the capital city of Alubarna.
Moment by moment,
the sands of the hourglass
of fate run down
towards the final hour.
Need meat!
[LUFFY]
"Rebel Army vs. Royal Army!
Showdown at Alubarna."
[LUFFY coughing]
[PELL]
Hey, kid! Are you all right?
[LUFFY]
Need meat!
[LUFFY grunts]
Meat.
Meat? You don't need food now.
That's the least
of your worries.
Hang on.
I'll get a doctor for you.
[LUFFY] I am going to make
sure Crocodile pays for this.
[LUFFY] He insulted Vivi,
and that old man
with the shovel
who gave me water.
He's definitely gonna pay!
Who is this person?
[LUFFY]
Meat.
[REBEL SOLDIER A]
There it is!
It's still in the distance,
but it's Alubarna!
Koza! We're less than
thirty minutes away.
Yeah.
We're nearing Alubarna now!
The time has come, men!
[GROUP yelling]
[ROYAL SOLDIER A] Chaka,
we've sighted the rebel army.
They're about ten
miles to the south!
Their forces are bearing
down on the southern gate
as we speak!
[CHAKA] East. West. South.
Southeast. Southwest!
Guard each gate with your life!
Do not let even one of them
set foot within our walls!
[GROUP]
Right!
[MR. 2]
Hey, take a look over there!
The rebel army is approaching!
And there are so many of them!
The princess is
such a little idiot
to think she can stop them!
But then, is the little
idiot even coming?
Really, now will she show up?
Or will she not? Or will she?
Or will she not?
The outcome is vague!
What, what, what, what, what?
Are we sure about this?
Shouldn't we be sure?
The princess and the pirates
are really coming, right?
At this rate, the rebel army
is going to beat them here!
I thought those idiots wanted
to stop the fighting!
Shouldn't they at least
try to be on time?
I think it's entirely possible
that they won't
make it soon enough.
It might even be likely, really.
After all, they did
lose precious time
when they were in Rainbase.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
What? They did?
[MR. 2] All right, then.
Let's suppose the rebellion
does get started first.
What are we supposed to
deux if that does happen?
We wouldn't have to "deux"
anything, would we?
Think about it. Once the
rebellion gets under way,
there's nothing even
the princess will be able
to do to stop it.
All we need to do is eliminate
whoever we're told to.
Can't you even manage
to figure that much out
on your own?
[MR. 2] It sounds like
you're just dying to see
some of my dance moves.
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] Just calm
down and let it go, you two.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
My back. It hurts!
Get over here and
massage it, Mr. 4!
[MR. 4]
They're... com... ing... now.
Really?!
Why didn't you tell us
that earlier, you idiot?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Ducks! They're on ducks?!
They're on ducks?
Are you sure?
Do you see anything else?
Seems like their
number's gone up, too.
There are six of 'em.
With Straw Hat out of the way,
I thought there was only
supposed to be four left.
Not quite, Miss Merry Christmas.
Don't you remember
what the boss said?
He told us there's that
Mr. Prince guy, too.
And apparently there's
more than one of him,
so the numbers do add up.
Just do the math.
It doesn't matter.
Vivi is our only target.
What are you so worried about?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Well, Mr. 1.
You say Princess Vivi is the
only one we need to eliminate?
Okay.
Then how 'bout you
take a stab at guessing
which one she is!
[MR. 2 gasps] They're all
wearing identical outfits!
Even worse, those birds
are the quickest
in the whole kingdom.
Supersonic ducks!
[MR. 2]
Those sneaky rats!
How're we supposed
to tell which one is Vivi
like this?
It's just not a fair thing
to do, you know?!
Let them have it now, MR. 4!
Dodge it!
Missed them!
Those damn birds!
They're too fast!
Two just broke off
from the rest!
They're splitting up!
Looks like they're planning
to go for the south gate.
Those two are heading straight
toward the rebel army.
Which means one
of them must be Vivi.
We'll go ahead and
take care of those two.
Move it, Mr. 4!
[USOPP]
Special attack! Fire star!
[MR. 2] Two more of them
are breaking off that way,
Mr. 1. That could be Vivi.
Seems they're planning to
go in through the west gate.
Damn brats. Let's go!
[MR. 2]
Un... Deux!
[USOPP] Okay! Let's head
for the southwest gate now!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] So they're
going to approach three
of Alubarna's five
gates from the west?
If they're gonna split
up and enter that way,
then we'll do the same thing.
We can wipe them
out inside the city!
You're not getting away from me!
[ROYAL SOLDIER J A]
Hey! Someone's coming!
Is it the rebels?
[ROYAL SOLDIER B]
No, wait!
It's the Supersonic
Duck Squadron!
Let them in!
[MR. 2]
I'm not kidding here!
There's no way you're
getting away with this!
[MR. 4]
Four. Four. Four. Four.
[USOPP] Tee hee hee! Thank you
so much for following us
all the way here.
[MR. 2]
Say what?
[NAMI]
Now! Stop!
[DUCK B squawks]
[NAMI] Wow, you guys
are very good, you know?
That's right.
I'm the real Princess Vivi.
[ZORO] What are you‐‐I mean,
what are you talking about?
I am the real Princess Vivi!
[SANJI] I wonder if this
is far enough now.
[SANJI] I have to say, it's
really entertaining how easily
you all fell for this.
Now. We can go ahead and
take these silly cloaks off.
[GROUP] Too bad! It looks
like your guess was wrong!
[GROUP]
What?!
[VIVI]
Thank you so much, everyone.
I have to hurry now.
The rebel army
is almost to the city!
Let's go, Karoo!
[KAROO squawks]
[CROCODILE] Whatever the cost,
Vivi and her friends
must be prevented
from making contact
with the rebel army.
Camel?!
And I recognize you from
the ship, too, don't I?
Sorry!
Yeah, come on, Zoro,
let 'em have it!
[ZORO]
Would you keep quiet over there?
[MR. 1]
They fooled us.
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Quite a farce.
[ZORO] I don't owe that
anymore! You cleared me!
[SANJI] It looks like there
won't be any rebellion now.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
What did you say?
[VIVI]
I have to stop them at any cost.
If I don't, then all of this
struggling has been for nothing!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
Secure the cannonballs!
I don't want them rolling away!
[ROYAL SOLDIER B]
You heard him, men!
Man your posts! Keep the
artillery under control!
The ground is
really moving, huh?
The enemy army is made up
of two million angry men.
Even the ground shakes
a little before them.
Stay strong!
[yelling]
[KAROO whimpering]
[VIVI] It's okay, Karoo,
you don't have to be here.
[KAROO whimpering]
You could get trampled,
so just be careful.
[VIVI]
Please, Leader.
Please listen to
what I have to say.
You must hear it.
[yelling]
Everyone listen!
Close your ranks
and stay together!
We'll knock through the
guards at the southern gate!
The rest will fall from there!
Do not lose heart!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VIVI]
Rebel army, you must stop!
This fight is pointless!
It's all a set‐up!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Please slow down!
You have got to listen to me!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VIVI]
Rebel army! Stop!
[KOZA] Hey! Did you see a person
standing in front of us
just now?
[REBEL SOLDIER O]
Person?
That isn't important right now!
The enemy is already
shooting at us!
[KAROO squawking]
[VIVI]
Why did they do that?
Neither side can
see anything now!
[VIVI]
What is the royal army thinking?
What the hell?!
I haven't given anyone
the order to open fire!
Do not act without my say‐so!
Uh, sir!
I'm terribly sorry about that!
I guess my hand just slipped!
Sorry!
[CROCODILE chuckling]
[CROCODILE laughing]
[KAROO squawks]
[REBEL SOLDIER B]
Don't back down!
Charge through!
It's just a cloud of sand.
No, everyone!
You have to stop now!
[REBEL SOLDIER B]
Fight for the country!
We'll make the king pay!
Leader!
[VIVI]
[REBEL SOLDIER B]
Koza. What is it?
[KOZA]
Nothing. It's nothing.
Was I imagining it?
[VIVI]
Leader.
[VIVI gasps]
[KOZA]
Remember, men!
Today will be our final battle!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Wait! Listen to me!
Leader!
[VIVI gasps]
[KAROO squawks]
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
They're here!
Cannons ready!
Fire!
[KOZA]
Save the country!
Tear down Alubarna!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VIVI]
No, Karoo!
[KAROO groans]
Karoo!
You shielded me from them.
I'm sorry.
We've come so far.
We've done so much,
but the rebellion has started.
I'm so sorry.
But I will still stop it.
No matter how many
times they refuse to listen.
No matter how
loudly I have to yell.
I will not let mindless
fighting destroy
what we've worked so hard for.
That's something I learned
while I was onboard the ship.
Do not ever give up.
‐‐[USOPP] Vivi!
‐‐[horse neighs]
At last! I found you!
[VIVI]
Usopp!
[USOPP]
We can still make it in time!
Hurry and hop on!
Right!
Hang in there, Karoo!
Oh, forget about that bird.
What's the matter, Vivi? Come
on. We need to get going now!
Hurry it up!
[VIVI]
That... bird?
[KAROO groans]
[USOPP]
Let's go, Karoo!
[KAROO squawks]
Come on!
The rebellion will
only get worse.
[VIVI]
Usopp...
Prove yourself.
Hm? Really?
You don't believe that it's me?
See?
[VIVI]
No!
[SANJI]
Usopp! Hey, Usopp!
Eyelash! Wake up!
[USOPP groans]
Oh, it's you, Sanji!
Is it morning already?
[SANJI]
Uh, sure.
[USOPP] So, this is how
our fight turned out.
The part of the mission
where we lured them away
went really well,
but then...
Well, you see...
Then it was over in two seconds.
One second each.
You couldn't have
held out longer?
[USOPP]
What are you doing here anyway?
[SANJI]
Your ducks got me.
They came to get
some help for you two.
But that aside...
You let Mr. 2 get
away, didn't you?
Yeah.
[ZORO]
Listen up.
That creepy ballerina's
transformations are perfect.
There's no telling
when he might pose
as one of us and make
an attempt on Vivi's life.
Does everyone understand?
If you ever feel like one
of us is acting suspicious...
...ask them to take
off this wrapping,
reveal their mark.
If they can't do that,
they're an imposter.
Whoa.
Having such a well
thought out plan like this
seems uncharacteristically
smart for you.
So how can we be sure you
aren't already an imposter?
I'll stab you!
Yeah, that's him.
Whew! Definitely Zoro.
You're lying.
You're not really Usopp.
[USOPP chuckles]
Well, that's too bad.
Now, really! You knew? How?
I thought my imitation
was perfect.
We even had a helpful
report from the boss
that you all had the same
bandages wrapped up
on your arm like this.
So smart of you.
[SANJI]
This isn't good.
Vivi's in danger!
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[SANJI]
That creepy ballerina freak!
If he hurts Vivi at all,
I'm gonna kill him!
[USOPP]
Hey, Chopper! Wake up!
[CHOPPER] Watch out!
She's under the ground there!
[NAMI screams]
[ZORO] Look, just find
someplace to hide!
[VIVI]
I have to do something!
I can't let myself
die here like this!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Alubarna Grieves!
The Fierce Captain Karoo."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!