Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[ACCINO] The flag of the
notorious Straw Hat Pirates,
whose collective bounty
is more than 600 million.
Isn't that right...
...Mr. 120 million
Berry bounty, Roronoa Zoro?
What the hell are you doing
with our flag, you bastard?
[LUFFY] Mansion of Great Chaos!
The Enraged Don
and the Captured Crew!
Oh, no...
Luffy!
That was close!
I almost fell into the water!
[BRINDO]
It doesn't matter what you do.
[CAMPACINO] Even a man with
a 300 million Berry bounty
is no match for our
glorious brotherhood!
Blah, blah, blah.
Enough talk!
Gimme back our flag, you jerks!
[CAMPACINO] If you manage
to best our brotherhood,
then and only then
will we honor your request.
[BOTH]
And show you where the flag is.
[BRINDO and CAMPACINO laugh]
Fine then!
Slippery!
[BRINDO] Looks like you're
going to have some trouble
fighting on the ice.
[LUFFY] So what? You will, too!
[CAMPACINO]
I wouldn't be so sure.
[BRINDO, CAMPACINO] The Accino
family knows The Frozen Highway
like the back of our hand.
There's no way that
you or anyone else
could defeat us here.
We have the
home field advantage.
Besides, the strong
magnetic power
that binds us together
makes us unstoppable.
Not even the infamous Monkey
D. Luffy could overcome it!
Twin brothers!
I don't care about
any of that crap!
Come on! Let's fight already!
I'll beat the hell outta
both of you! Let's go!
Cocky punk!
Now Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Now, Monkey D. Luffy!
Our brotherhood...
...is coming for your head!
Prepare yourself!
[BRINDO] Very impressive!
Let's both have a go
at him at once, Campacino.
Yes, Papa is waiting for us.
You're going--augh!
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
What're you guys, a comedy act?
Stop laughing!
Should have expected treachery
with a bounty that high.
How dare you do that to us!
No way. I didn't do that.
You two fell on your own.
You filthy, stinking pirate!
We'll teach you
to make fun of us!
[BRINDO, CAMPACINO]
You miscreant! You'll pay!
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke!
Hoh ke ke ke ke ke!
Hey, turd!
You're gonna regret screwing
around with my Shark Submerge
when I get outta here!
I'll shove that hockey stick
where the sun don't shine!
[HOCKERA]
Hoh ke ke ke ke!
I'd like to see you try!
Soon, you'll
all be frozen solid!
Now that you're trapped,
it's only a matter of time!
[FRANKY]
Ugh, I hate that guy!
[NAMI] It's colder in here
than it was in the sub!
What's up with this place?
[USOPP] Help... me...!
[NAMI] Sanji! Usopp!
Nami! Please, save me!
I'm so sorry, Nami.
Bastards got the drop on me.
[FRANKY] Are you two all right?
[SANJI] Yeah.
You got here just in time.
[ARBELL] Good. Now all we need
are the other four bounties.
Ugh! I'm so sick of all
these stupid bounty hunters!
Why is this place so cold?
It's like an icy hell.
The ice that makes up
the walls and floor
of this cavern
has been hardening
for the past 400 years.
[ARBELL] Anything inside it
will be frozen within minutes.
You could say it's like
a gigantic freezer.
Understand?
Your explanation
was amazing, Arbell!
So easy to follow!
Which happens first?
We capture your friends, or the
rest of you freeze to death?
I look forward to finding out.
By now, I'm sure
the rest of your crew
has fallen into the
capable hands of my family.
Damn. What a shame.
Guess I'll just
have to cut you down.
And you were being
so hospitable, too.
[ACCINO] Cut me down?
You don't have
what it takes, boy.
I take it you have
Devil Fruit powers.
Every single thing I touch
can be melted
down into liquid.
And, of course,
that would include
those splendid
swords of yours.
[ACCINO] That is the ability
of the Hot-Hot Fruit!
[ZORO] So all I have to do is
not let you touch me, right?
[ZORO]
Thirty-six Caliber Phoenix!
[ZORO] What?
[choked screaming]
You bastard!
Be careful where
you swing that thing!
You could have
harmed my collection!
[ZORO] What the hell
is going on here?
[SANJI] Troisieme Hache!
Hey, let me take a crack at it!
Strong Hammer!
[USOPP] Gunpowder Star! Usopp
Hammer! Rubber Band of Doom!
Gunpowder Star! Usopp Hammer!
Rubber Band of Doom!
[ARBELL] There's no point
in trying to escape.
You'll never crack those walls.
--Just lie down and die!
--[USOPP shouting attacks]
Looks like the only
way outta here is up.
[NAMI]
Franky!
[USOPP]
Gunpowder Star!
[USOPP] This ice thinks
it's a real tough guy!
Guess that's enough
damage for one day.
Hey!
Yeah? What's up?
Look. Think you can make it?
Sure!
I think I got just enough of the
good stuff for one last shot.
[FRANKY] Here we go!
Is everybody ready?
Yeah!
1 Liter Cola Cannon!
Coup de Boo!
[USOPP] Fart power!
[FRANKY] Ah! Crap, I'm out!
[NAMI] What?
[SANJI] Leave the rest to me!
Dammit!
Hoh ke ke ke ke ke!
Fool! Never underestimate us!
[ARBELL] Do me a favor
and freeze already!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 332B]
Arbell! It's terrible!
Come quickly! Mister Accino
is out of control!
Right! I understand!
I'll be right there!
[SALCHOW] Seems we have more
pressing matters to tend to!
Sit tight, keep quiet.
We'll be back!
[ARBELL] Hurry up, darling!
Look, guys!
We gotta find a way outta here
before we really do
freeze to death!
[HOCKERA] Papa, wait!
[ARBELL, SALCHOW, HOCKERA]
Papa!
[ACCINO] Ah!
This is bad!
It's like a sauna in here!
Honey? What do we do?
It's impossible
to control Papa's temper
when he gets like this!
Just keep on smiling.
What's wrong, Papa?
[ACCINO] You!
Why are my birthday
presents running around free?
Why haven't they been
properly imprisoned yet?
[ARBELL] Papa! Listen!
I assure you, they're--augh!
[HOCKERA] It's Roronoa Zoro!
[SALCHOW] Why are you here?
All right. You're going down.
Stop ignoring us!
Two-Sword Style...
[HOCKERA] Think! Where was it?
[ZORO]
...Hawk...
[yelling]
[ARBELL]
I'm terribly sorry, Papa!
One rat managed to avoid the
trap, but it won't happen again!
Yes! My darling
is absolutely right!
Don't worry! We'll round up the
rest of them in no time at all!
Your flag collection
is already so impressive!
And it just grew by one!
[SALCHOW] And our
brothers are bringing in
the last members of
their crew as we speak!
[ARBELL] It's true, Papa!
[LUFFY]
Damn. You sure are tough.
Even after you split in two.
We're not clones, we're twins!
Pay attention to
what people tell you!
Come along, now.
Our papa is waiting for us.
It's time to end this game.
Ready, Brindo?
Ready, Campacino!
Crap!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Your head is ours!
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
[LUFFY yelling]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL
Click.
What is it now?
Yes. Right.
I understand, then.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[LUFFY] Come back, cowards!
Stop running away!
[CAMPACINO] You've avoided
death for the time being!
We'll deal with you later!
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
It's Papa. It seems he's
gone berserk once again.
We've gotta get back there fast!
I won't let you
get away! Come here!
Damn it!
Hey! Gimme back our flag!
[NAMI] Stay awake, you idiot!
If you fall asleep, you'll die!
Come on, Usopp!
[USOPP] Nami... Stop it.
I'm in the middle
of a beautiful dream.
Ahh! Just listen
to those birds chirping!
Merry!
You came back to take me
to the other side with you!
How nice!
[NAMI, SANJI, FRANKY]
Wake up!
Are you trying to kill me?
[metallic thud]
[ZORO] Where the hell am I?
Zoro?!
Oh! There you are!
Where have you been?
We should be asking you that!
But more importantly,
I just saw our flag
in their bosses' hands.
How'd that happen?
So it is here!
Now to get it back.
And we need to do it quick,
before Luffy
notices anything.
Geez. Can't you
even manage to protect
one tiny little flag,
imitation cook?
You're one to talk, aren't you?
You were too busy being
lost to protect anything.
You're pathetic.
Now is not the time for that!
It's good to see
you're all energetic.
Hey! Robin!
Robin!
--[ZORO] Moron.
--[SANJI] What?!
Robin! Help us outta here!
Yeah! We could use a hand!
[LIL] As much as I
don't want to admit it,
you should be down there
with them, big sister.
[LIL] But I think my new
friend Robin is special.
That's why I'm going
to ask Papa to spare her.
Good thing, too.
Because Papa will do anything
I say as long as I ask nice.
Oh?
[LIL] So, are you coming
to the party with me?
What kind of party?
For Papa.
A gigantic birthday feast!
Well? Have you said
your goodbyes to everyone?
--[NAMI] Robin! Robin! Look!
--[USOPP] No! Don't go!
--[SANJI] Save us, please!
--[NAMI] Robin!
[ALL calling after Robin]
Right. Shall we be going then?
[LIL] You mean it?
[LIL]
Come on! Follow me!
Let's go! It's this way!
Wait! Why are you leaving us?
Robin! Come back!
Please don't
abandon me, my love!
[LUFFY] Chopper!
[CHOPPER and JIRO screaming]
I'm back!
I think you need to
work on that landing!
Are you trying
to sink our ship?
Sorry!
[LIL] What's the matter?
Does it seem hot
in here to you?
Oh, no.
[LIL] I was afraid of this.
Papa's angry.
Let's leave for now.
When Papa gets like this,
it's better to just
stay away from him.
I see.
[LIL] At this rate, everything
around here is gonna melt away!
[LIL] Come on!
Let's go play in my room!
Say, would it be all right
to bring those snacks
and that juice with us?
They don't taste very good
when they're hot, you know.
Thanks, but I don't mind.
And besides,
it's part of another favor
I'd like to ask of you.
All right, pirates.
I've got some
provisions for you.
Compliments of Princess Lil's
new partner, Robin.
New partner?
[SANJI]
Robin, huh?
My love!
You do still care for me!
Hey! Franky! We got some cola!
Sweet! We'll get it right
this time for sure!
Super Recovery!
Wah!
[FRANKY] Here we go! Coup de...
[FRANKY]
...Vent!
[FRANKY] Coup de Boo!
We gotta make up
for lost time, you guys.
Now let's go get that flag!
[ALL] Yeah!
[LUFFY] Time to go, Chopper!
[CHOPPER] Right!
No! Hold on!
I wanna come with you!
I'm begging you!
[CHOPPER] Jiro...
[PUZZLE] Wait!
[PUZZLE] Don't go.
Please, stay here.
[JIRO] Captain!
There's no reason for
you to risk your life over this.
It's not worth it.
It's all right.
I know that if we
reclaim our flag,
our captain will
rise like a phoenix
and be who he was before.
Just you wait!
I'm gonna save us all!
Don't talk nonsense.
No. I've already given up.
It's over.
So you've
already given up, huh?
How can you say that?
That isn't the captain
I used to know.
Those aren't
the words of the man
who's gonna be
King of the Pirates!
Listen up.
I still believe in you, Puzzle.
You're the man who will be
King of the Pirates someday!
I know I'm small and not
very strong, but I don't care!
I believe in you!
You'll see!
I'll bring back
the flag and...
What?!
Luffy!
What did you do that for?
[LUFFY] I'm sick of
hearing all that nonsense.
[STANSEN] What's wrong with you?
[JIRO] Yeah, what gives?
I thought we were friends!
[LUFFY] And listen, you!
A pirate doesn't give up
til he can't stand anymore!
You're just a big coward!
[JIRO] That's enough!
[LUFFY] There's no way
that guy could ever be
King of the Pirates!
There's only one man
who can claim that: Me!
You're wrong!
I decided Captain Puzzle
will be King of the Pirates!
No matter what you say, I won't
let you step on his dream!
No!
Look, Jiro.
You're a lot stronger
than you think.
And your strength is
right where it needs to be.
Luffy, I...
All right.
I say we beat those guys and
get our flags back together!
Yeah!
Anyone who thinks they can steal
my pirate flag's
got another thing coming!
[PUZZLE] Stop it!
There's no reason
for you to fight them!
Please. Stay.
Don't worry!
I won't let those guys hurt me.
This is the only way
we can move forward, right?
Besides, that's what pirates
are supposed to do.
What a bunch of fools!
Jiro's risking his life and
it's all because of me!
[PUZZLE yelling]
I'm sorry to make
you worry, Captain.
I want you to go after Jiro.
[LAGO, BASIL, SUTTON, GUYLE]
Yes, sir.
Hey, Nami...
Is it really a good idea
for us to follow Zoro?
Shut up, jerk!
[CAMPACINO] We're planning the
party to end all parties, Papa.
Come on. Cheer up for us, okay?
Hey you!
Gimme back our flag!
What the...
Great.
Sounds like Luffy's here.
We don't have any time to waste!
[NAMI] Come on, guys!
Let's get moving!
See, Papa?
It's like I told you.
Your birthday present is
coming together as planned!
I see that.
Sorry for getting mad.
[SANJI] Hey! Mosshead!
Are you sure you know
where these jerks
are keeping our flag?
[ZORO] Shut up!
Let me think for a second!
I think it's... this way.
[SANJI] We must be insane to
follow an idiot like you around.
[ZORO] Here! This is
totally the place! I think.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
The Return of the Phoenix!
The Dream of the Pirate Flag
Sworn to a Friend!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!