[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!
[ERIC]
Whirlwind!
Creep really packs a punch.
[NAMI]
Finally! It's time.
Let's go!
[APIS screaming]
Nice try.
[APIS laughing]
[LUFFY]
Woo! Yeah!
Guys! We're goin' to
Lost Island! Set sail!
[LUFFY] "A Solitary Island
in the Distant Sea!
The Legendary Lost Island!"
[MARINE A]
All squad captains!
Assemble on the deck of
the flagship! On the double!
[MARINE B]
Where's the quartermaster?
[MARINE C]
Turn the yard this way!
[MARINE D]
No, no! To the right!
[MARINE E] We're gonna
need all the repair planks
from the other ships!
[MARINE F]
The flagship has to be fixed
and ready to sail
within the hour!
Move it!
Damn those pirates.
We'll lose them if these
repairs take too long.
[ERIC]
No, we won't.
In fact, letting them go now
would be to our benefit.
[LT. COMMANDER]
What do you mean?
[ERIC]
It's simple, really.
They went to dangerous lengths
to escape from this island.
Now why do you think
they did that?
Have you forgotten that
this island has a legend?
Let me refresh your memory.
It's about dragons and
a fabled nest on Lost Island.
[LT. COMMANDER]
Wait. Are you saying that‐‐?
Mm. It's only a guess.
But it is an educated guess.
If I'm correct, those Straw
Hats will lead us right to it.
[ERIC] Making a report to
Commodore Nelson, are we?
There's no need for that.
[MARINE G]
Um, but, Sir, I‐‐ Understood.
[ERIC] Dragonite,
the Elixir of Immortality.
It's finally within my grasp.
I'm not about it to turn it
over to a slob like Nelson.
It's mine and mine alone,
and with it, Eric the Whirlwind
will become Eric
the Unstoppable!
Where is it?!
[MARINE H] Y‐Your lunch,
Commodore. Here it is
[NELSON]
No!
That's not what I meant!
[COMMS]
I have news for you, Sir!
[NELSON] It's about time!
It took him long enough!
That's a report from
Eric, I assume?
Uh, no, Sir.
It's a message from
one of the Marines
at Warship Island that states:
"Eric has found a
Millennial Dragon."
He goes on to say that the
fleet's busy repairing damage
that the flagship sustained.
[whimpers]
[NELSON]
Curse you, Eric.
You find a legendary
Millennial Dragon
and you don't report it to me?!
Why?!
You're planning to take
all the Dragonite
for yourself, aren't you?!
You've got some nerve,
you mercenary!
[chuckles]
We'll see who has
the last laugh!
Captain, deploy the fleet
to Warship Island!
All ships, move out!
[NAMI] No wonder
it's called Lost Island.
It's not on any of the charts.
Its description doesn't even
match any of the islands
in the waters around
Warship Island.
[USOPP] Hey, Grandpa Ryu!
Which way should we go?!
Where's Lost Island?!
Hey.
I think he went to sleep again.
[APIS]
Sorry for the wait, everybody!
I hope you're all hungry!
Oh, no. Don't tell me
she cooked again.
No one was waiting for her food.
[USOPP]
Oh, Sanji! What a relief!
For a minute there,
I thought you weren't the one
who made the meal!
I'm so hap‐‐ Ah!
Lunchtime! Now eat up,
Grandpa Ryu!
Food! All right!
Yummy!
[LUFFY]
Uh?! Hot!
No. You... moron!
[screams]
Hold on!
Apis!
[APIS]
Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu! Are you okay?!
[SANJI]
Perfect!
I go through the trouble
of making that food
and it all goes to waste!
You can make more
though, right?
Yeah, but the point is
we should never waste food.
What? What is it?
I know where Lost Island is.
The Dragons' Nest is somewhere
to the east of Warship Island.
[chuckles]
That's great! How'd you
know where to find it?!
Grandpa Ryu just remembered!
[BOTH laughing]
[LUFFY]
We know where it is!
Lost Island lies to the east
of Warship Island, guys!
Yeah! Grandpa Ryu said so!
[LUFFY]
Let's go!
[NAMI]
Usopp! Take the helm!
[USOPP]
You got it!
Right! We've spent
enough time here!
Now... to Lost Island!
[SANJI] Dammit!
You'd better eat all of that!
[LUFFY]
Oh! No problem!
[ERIC]
So they've changed course?
Yes.
The pirate ship
appears to be headed
for the waters east
of Warship Island.
They're making their move.
[LT. COMMANDER]
Turn the bows eastward! Now!
Full speed ahead!
We're going to show those
Straw Hat Pirates
what Marines are made off!
Cannoneers, get to
your gun batteries!
All hands, prepare for combat!
This is not a drill.
Our destination is‐‐
Lost Island, of course.
[LT. COMMANDER]
All ships, move out!
[SANJI]
Here, Zoro.
[ZORO]
Thanks.
[SANJI]
And another.
[ZORO]
Yeah.
[SANJI]
Here ya go.
[ZORO] Okay.
[SANJI]
Zoro.
[ZORO]
Right.
[SANJI]
And this one.
[ZORO]
Uh...
Can you hand 'em over to me
without talking please?
So Lost Island's supposedly out
in this direction somewhere.
Wonder what it looks like
and when we're gonna see it.
Hey! Can you see anything
from up there, Usopp?!
Nope! Not a single thing!
[LUFFY]
Oh.
We've come a long way,
but there's still no sign
of this Lost Island.
I hope this doesn't turn out
to be a wild goose chase.
[NAMI]
Mm...
And then there's Grandpa Ryu.
I wish there was some
way we could help him
remember a few more details.
Ah! That should do the trick!
So what say we bonk him
on the head with this anvil?
That should loosen some memories
in his old noggin all right!
No, that's mean!
[USOPP yelps]
[APIS]
Can you believe it, Grandpa Ryu?
We're almost there!
We're almost to Lost Island!
And it's there, right?
The Dragons' Nest you
told me about?
And if you go there, you'll
get all better, won't you?
What?
You're so nice, but you
don't have to thank me!
We're not even there yet!
So they followed us, huh?
[LUFFY]
What's that? Smoke?
[LUFFY] Oh, well. Guess we'll
know when we get closer.
[APIS whines]
[APIS] No, Grandpa Ryu,
that's not true!
I don't think you're
troubling me at all!
What's your problem?!
Hey! Are you...
At some point it turned
into an argument.
It sounds like Apis is the
only one who's arguing.
Listen to her.
Should we...?
A... ship?
It looks like one, but
something's weird about it.
Whoa! Awesome! Hey,
Nami, do you see this?!
Yes. But I don't believe it!
Watch this! Help!
[chuckles]
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
[MARINE L]
What the‐‐?
[LT. COMMANDER]
What's going on?!
[MARINE K]
The ship...
[MARINE J]
It just...
It vanished!
Are we seeing things?
Hey! What just happened?!
How'd they disappear like that?!
[MARINE L]
I‐I have no idea, Sir!
Drop anchor!
Yes, Sir!
All ships are to stand by
until further orders!
Sir!
[ERIC]
Continue moving forward.
Are you mad?!
There's no telling what's
in those waters up ahead.
No!
That again?
Have your men prepare
a small craft for me.
You mean... you're actually...?
That's right.
I'm going after them.
What gives? It's just fog.
From the way Nami was screaming,
I thought we were in danger.
[NAMI]
What in the world is going on?
[USOPP] Can somebody
please explain to me
what just happened?
I mean, our own ship
was in front of us,
but somehow we passed
straight through it, right?
This stuff's so thick
I can't see a thing!
[USOPP] It was almost like a‐‐
Well, a mirage...
That's it! A mirage! I remember
reading about it once!
When warmer air in the sky
collides with cooler air
near the ocean's surface,
it can create mirages at sea.
What about this?
Is this a mirage too?
Ah! What's the deal with
this stupid ocean?!
[BOTH yelp]
Dammit! Thanks for
knockin' me over!
We didn't do it
on purpose, jerk!
It's the storm's fault!
[NAMI]
Sanji! Zoro!
Quit fighting and raise
the sails! Hurry up!
[SANJI]
Yes, Nami dear!
You'll be safer inside.
No! I have to stay out
here with Grandpa Ryu!
[ZORO]
Don't be an idiot!
It's too dangerous for you
to be out in this storm!
[APIS] I just can't leave him
alone in this! I can't!
[ZORO]
See?!
[ZORO] Now get in there
and shut up, kid!
Get moving.
If we keep drifting, that
lightning's gonna hit us!
[LUFFY]
It almost seems like the ocean's
trying to push the ship back
from something, but what?
[APIS]
Grandpa Ryu!
Hold on!
We'll get you out of this
storm as soon as we c‐‐ Ah!
Zoro!
Wh‐What?! Grandpa Ryu,
what are you saying?!
No! We will not let you
go to save ourselves!
[inaudible]
We're going to find your
nest like I promised!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Lasso!
[gasps]
[SANJI]
Nami! I see a light over there!
[NAMI] That must be
the eye of the storm!
[USOPP]
Guys, do you see that?!
There's an island
below the light!
Then that's where
we're headed! Come on!
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Don't worry, I got 'em!
We're gonna take him
to the Dragons' Nest,
just like you said, okay?!
[APIS]
Okay!
[NAMI]
An island hidden by a mirage
and surrounded by stormy seas.
Well, that certainly explains
why no one's ever found it.
It's not lost anymore though.
Now that we found it.
[LUFFY] Looks more like a
castle that sank into the ocean
instead of an island,
if you ask me.
[USOPP]
Whoa! Check out that stonework!
It actually looks like a dragon!
You know, I betcha those
Millennial Dragons
built this place themselves!
[LUFFY]
Wow!
I never knew dragons were
so good at building stuff.
[SANJI]
They're not, you morons!
It's pretty obvious that
humans built this place!
[ZORO]
Well, whatever. Who cares?
[LUFFY]
Yeah! Who cares?!
We made it to Lost Island!
No signs of life.
I wonder if anyone
lives here anymore.
Looks like this place has
been reclaimed by nature.
Does anyone know where
the Dragons' Nest could be?
[APIS]
Hey!
Grandpa Ryu! Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Jeez! We're on the island
with the Dragons' Nest!
Would you wake up and
tell us where it is?!
Mm?
[LUFFY]
What'd he say?
Well, he said he's not sure.
But he said that this place
might not even be
the actual Lost Island.
What?
You can't be serious.
So we went through
that freaky mirage
and that storm for nothing?!
[LUFFY]
Hey, Apis!
See that?
If the Dragons' Nest
is on the island,
I bet we could spot it
from up there!
Right!
We can't see anything down here,
so why don't we go take a look?
What do you say?
Yeah!
Great! Let's go!
Agh! It's not fair.
We men have to do all the work
while Nami gets to
take a stroll!
She should be back
here pushing with us!
[NAMI]
Hey back there!
Less caterwauling and
more dragon‐hauling!
[USOPP] Sure, that's
easy for you to say!
[SANJI]
Would you shut up and push?!
Nami's so gorgeous when
she's ordering us around!
[USOPP]
Oh, brother!
[NAMI]
It's a city.
Whoa, check it out.
It looks all abandoned
and broken down.
Do you guys think people
really used to live here?
[ZORO]
Of course.
Who else do you think lived
in all these houses?
[USOPP] Well, why did they leave
then, and where did they go?
[SANJI]
Who knows?
Maybe they just found a
better island to live on
and moved away or something.
[APIS]
It's a Millennial Dragon emblem!
I wonder if the children
who lived here
played with dragons like
I do with Grandpa Ryu.
Hi! Do you know if
there's a place here
where dragons might nest?
Hey! Apis!
Come on, you don't
wanna get left behind!
Guess what!
I was just talking to the birds
and they told me
there's a building
with a dragon emblem on it.
What?
Really?!
It could be the Dragons' Nest!
What are we waiting for?!
[LUFFY] Hey, Nami!
Are you comin' or what?!
Uh... Of course! Wait up!
[LUFFY]
Heave.
Please tell me we don't
have to push anymore!
[APIS] Thank you so much
for showing us the way!
[SANJI]
Wow, what do you know?
We traveled a lot further
than I thought.
[APIS]
Thank you all so very much.
Yeah, nice work, guys.
[NAMI] That painting must be
the dragon emblem, huh?
[LUFFY]
Yep. Guess so.
Wait. This little building's
the Dragons' Nest?
This is it?
Even if it is, where's the door?
How we supposed
to get inside it?
The door's right there!
Ugh! No, it's not!
There's no handle or keyhole!
If it's a door, how are we
supposed to open it, stupid?!
Hey!
Apis, that pendant of yours.
You mean it's a‐‐?
So it's a key that opens the
door to the Dragons' Nest, huh?
[APIS]
I...
I can't reach it!
Heh! That's 'cause
you're so short, silly!
[APIS]
Yeah, so?!
Here, let me do it.
Let's see.
Uh. Uh‐oh.
[yelps]
[ALL screaming]
[USOPP] Um. Hey, guys?
We're still alive, right?
[ZORO]
Well, sure feels that way.
[SANJI] Who was it again
that claimed to have a key
that would open the door for us?
[chuckles nervously]
[LUFFY]
Here.
Well, we didn't come in
the front door, but we're in.
So it all worked out.
Yeah, but just what
is this place?
Hey. Up there. Look.
What is that?
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪
[USOPP] Hey! Is this place
really Lost Island or what?!
[NAMI] See! Look at that!
This could only mean‐‐
[ZORO]
Look out!
[SANJI]
That nutjob!
He actually followed us
all the way here, huh?!
[LUFFY] All right, let's fight!
You, too, Zoro!
[ZORO] Just go!
I'll take care of this guy!
[NAMI] Oh, no, look!
Now there's a huge armada!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Showdown in the Ruins!
Tense Zoro vs. Eric!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!