Have they made the order
for the Buster Call yet?
We're still on standby.
Hurry!
Run to the evacuation ship!
So this is a Poneglyph, huh?
Yeah.
I heard even if we shoot it
with a cannon it won't leave
a single scratch on the thing.
I can't believe
these creepy things
are hidden all over the world.
I don't like it.
Is that so?
Yes.
The evidence is clear.
This calls for nothing
short of the death penalty.
We're waiting for your order.
It's unfortunate.
But seeing as they've
broken the law so blatantly,
there's really no other option.
We must enforce our own rules.
We don't need your mock
sympathy, Elder Stars.
Save your breath.
You're talking to the leaders of
the world, you damned criminal!
Show some respect!
That must be Professor Clover.
Ohara's foremost authority
on archaeology.
I'm familiar with your work.
You've contributed much to
the world's cultural heritage.
It's sad to see a man of
your intellect go astray.
The history of this planet
belongs to all of mankind.
No matter what
that history may be,
you don't have the right to
forbid us from learning it.
No one does.
Professor.
If one can read the Poneglyphs,
then it's also possible
that they can revive
the ancient weapons
and place the
world in serious peril.
Even if you have
the best of intentions,
someone else could come along
and use your research for evil.
Be it good or bad, mankind
has the responsibility
to accept whatever
their history may hold.
As long as we don't succumb
to fear and ignorance,
we will be prepared for
anything that may come.
That's idealistic.
Is it?
Or are you just making
convenient excuses
to suit your needs?
In truth, there are two
mysteries left unsolved.
Of course we want to
read the Poneglyphs,
but the reason
why they were made
in the first place is
interesting as well.
Why was their
message so important,
that they had to inscribe
it on unbreakable stone
to pass on to
future generations?
Why were they hidden and
scattered across the world?
Why were they not
stored in a library?
The only logical conclusion is
that they feared their message
would be too easily destroyed
if they had written it on paper.
In other words,
they had an enemy.
Someone who was
afraid of the information
they wanted to pass on.
What are you trying to
imply, Professor Clover?
Since the Ancients
have disappeared,
we must assume that they
were defeated by this enemy,
and that whoever they were,
they survived through history.
It may be no coincidence, that
roughly 800 years in the past,
when the Blank Century came
to an end, the organization
we now call "The World
Government" was founded.
Therefore, if this unknown enemy
was indeed the World Government,
it might be in
their best interest
to "erase" this inconvenient
piece of information and let
the ancients disappear into a
fabricated "Blank Century".
By analyzing ancient manuscripts
and piecing together what we
could from the few Poneglyphs
we were able to find, we
discovered the existence of
a previously unknown country.
Although the details we
found were a bit scarce,
we believe it was a
grand and powerful kingdom.
And yet, despite their
strength, not a trace remains.
Or rather, those traces
were deliberately erased.
But they were prepared
for this possibility,
even as they faced
the threat of extinction.
And so they etched their
history in stone,
before their kingdom was
crushed under the might
of the allied nations now known
as the World Government.
Thus, the reason why
the Poneglyphs were made
becomes quite clear.
I see.
That's a bold hypothesis.
It's true that the
ancient weapons
would be a
threat to the world.
But more so than weapons,
what I believe the World
Government is afraid of
is the history surrounding
this lost kingdom.
Its existence and its ideologies
are so dangerous to you,
that you would kill
to keep them secret.
Although we still don't
know what makes you
fear this kingdom, we do
at least know its name.
Since we've gone so far already,
perhaps you'd like me
to share it with you now?
Kill him!
Professor!
You left us no choice.
You bastards!
How dare you!
Professor!
Ohara knows too much.
You may give
the order to attack.
Don't move an inch!
You mustn't let anyone escape.
Now then, with the golden
transponder snail entrusted
to me by Admiral Sengoku.
Professor!
Robin, you fool.
I told you to run. Hurry!
I invoke the Buster Call!
And, that's a wrap.
He pressed something!
What is that?
Get out of here! Go!
No! I don't want to be alone!
You have to stop
being so selfish.
This isn't the time!
Robin.
It's the Buster Call!
All battleships,
to your positions!
Prepare to open fire!
What? Hey, look!
The Tree of Knowledge
is on fire!
Damn it! What're you doing?
Are you insane?
Isn't it enough
to take our lives?
Hey, it's not my fault.
Must've caught fire when they
bombed your secret basement.
Stop this! Right now!
You can't replace
the documents in there!
Don't you realize that?
You! Don't move!
Whoa, we don't
need guns anymore.
Time for the government
agents to pull out.
Protect the books.
Let's put out the fire! Hurry!
Pass the water over here!
Carry as many books
outside as you can!
Bring that woman with you.
Get up.
There's still some info we
have to wring out of her.
She can't die yet.
Just make sure she
doesn't escape again.
Mommy!
Please Robin,
run while you still can!
You can't die here!
Not like this!
Funny nose!
Go! We're done for!
There's no point in staying!
Robin!
Robin, don't.
You're my mother, aren't you?
Make up your mind, Olvia!
Are you going to
board this ship or not?
Mommy!
I'm holding her back!
Just hurry and get on!
Mommy! Mommy! No! Mommy!
I'm sorry, Robin.
I can never call myself
your mother again.
After all these years,
after all I've done,
I don't have the right anymore.
Monster!
She's so scary her mom ran away!
Hey, that's my daughter's dress!
You take it off!
I'm sorry, Aunt Roji!
I just wanted to try it on!
You sure eat a
lot for a freeloader.
Please, answer me.
Are you my mom?
Hm? Hold on.
That girl your daughter or what?
No.
Olvia.
I'm sorry, little girl.
You must be confusing
me with someone else.
Even if it comes to this,
I don't want you to be
the daughter of a criminal.
Olvia.
What a weird little brat.
Right, let's go!
It's me! It's Robin!
I've grown since the last time
so maybe you don't recognize me?
I've been waiting
for you all these years!
Are you sure?
You're really...
..not my mom?
Just once, someday,
I wanted to hold your hand,
and walk together like a family.
I studied hard to
become an archaeologist,
so I could go to sea with you!
I can read the Poneglyphs, too!
What did she say?
Robin! No!
So please, look at me!
Let me stay with you! Mom!
Robin!
I've waited so long.
We're finally together.
Don't leave me alone again!
Oh no! Now what's going on?
Now commencing the Buster Call.
All ships, fire at once.
Everything on the island
of Ohara is your target.
Let nothing remain.
The research conducted here
was far more extensive
than we anticipated.
Make sure that knowledge
is not passed on.
Do not allow it
to leave the island.
Annihilate the devils of Ohara!
Burn it to the ground!
In the name of justice!
Damn it!
What the hell?
Can't you wait 'til
we leave the island?
You're gonna kill us! Stop it!
The Tree of Knowledge
took a direct hit!
They're using their
highest power against us.
They stage their investigation,
but they were planning
this from the start.
Bastards.
Hey, chief.
That girl said she can
read the Poneglyphs.
Yeah, she did, didn't she?
I don't know if it's
true or not, though.
Probably safer to wipe
her out, just in case.
Don't let her leave the island.
Remember her face, all right?
We're retreating!
Then I'll grab Olvia.
Screw it!
The situation has
changed. Just run!
I'm not gonna
get blown up
trying to follow
some stupid order!
Our number one priority
is keeping me alive!
Retreat!
Everyone, back to the ship!
Put out the fire on that
side before it spreads!
Protect the library
at all costs!
I've been waiting a
long time to do this.
I'm glad.
Robin!
Mommy!
Robin, forgive me.
Please.
This is my fault
for not watching over
you with more care.
Is it really true that you
can read the Poneglyphs?
I had to learn.
Since, I wanted to be a scholar.
I never knew my little
girl was an archaelogist!
That's amazing!
You must've studied hard
while I was gone, huh?
These aren't things that just
anyone can do!
I'm so proud!
Fortunately, the
only ones who know
about this are the officials
who were here earlier.
We can't afford to
waste any more time!
Olvia! Take Robin and run!
If you can sneak her
onto the evacuation ship,
she might still be able
to leave the island!
Robin!
I've been looking
all over for you!
It's Saul!
So you met with
your mother after all.
Saul!
Why in the world are you here?
Guess it must be fate!
I just happened to wash up here
and your little girl was
the one who found me.
Anyhow, we ain't got
time to chat right now.
You gotta get off this island!
I'll be fine,
but I need you take care
of Robin for me, please.
Huh? But why? What about you?
Aren't you going
to come with me?
Olvia, are you?
I can't leave yet.
There's something left to do.
No, Mom! You can't leave me now!
I'll stay here with you!
I don't want to lose you again!
Robin, if you're
a scholar of Ohara,
you should know that history
is mankind's greatest treasure.
Now that it's been passed on,
it will illuminate
the path to your future.
However, you must
pass it on as well.
Or its light will disappear
with the next generation.
Save those books!
Someone take these!
We weren't trying to
uncover some dark secret.
We simply wanted to hear
the voices of the
past and protect them.
Unfortunately, our
research ends here.
But time marches on,
even if Ohara is destroyed.
And as surely as we
believe in the past,
we believe in the future
that you will inherit!
What does that mean?
Someday, you'll know.
Hurry. Take her and go, Saul.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Stop it!
I wanna stay with you!
Mommy! No!
I was happy to hear
you call me that again.
Thank you. From now on,
for my sake as well.
You must live, Robin!
Vice Admiral Kuzan!
What now?
It looks like-- no,
wait, it's gotta be!
So are you gonna
tell me, or not?
Spit it out already, man!
It's the deserter.
Vice Admiral Saul!
Please, Saul, you
have to take me back!
I can't!
There's no way!
Don't cry, Robin!
Be proud! Your momma's
a wonderful woman!
Ohara's a wonderful place!
You gotta remember that!
It's up to you to
pass it on, okay?
Ohara was so brave they
fought against the whole world!
Are you crazy?
Capturing them is enough!
They ain't even pirates,
they're scholars!
Are you so weak you can't reel
'em in without blowing 'em up?
We shoot down these researcher
ships one after another,
but I still can't find any sense
in killin' these poor folks.
Vice Admiral Saul!
We found a survivor!
You're nothing but murderers!
You're scholars.
Why do you need ancient weapons?
You don't know a thing!
You don't even why
you're killing us!
That's a Vice Admiral
you're speaking to!
The weapons are just an excuse!
Why don't you try thinking about
what you're doing for once?
You're just afraid of a past
that you know nothing about!
This is a top-secret mission.
The Buster Call?
It's an all-out attack in
which Five Vice-Admirals
command ten battleships.
I want you to take part.
They're just scholars, right?
Why do we have to go so far?
Even the ones we've captured
before don't seem like
they care about weapons--
they just wanna learn
more about history!
If their research
is so dangerous,
why don't we help them
so nothing goes wrong?
Least you can do is give me some
proof that these folks are bad!
'Cause to me it seems like
we're the criminals here!
Are you questioning
the government?
Just follow your orders!
I got some questions for you.
You think we can talk?
This is an emergency!
Vice Admiral Saul has taken
the prisoner and deserted!
This won't do.
He knows too much
about our next operation.
After them.
Stop Saul and Olvia at any cost.
Open fire if necessary.
Troops'll be showing
up any minute now,
but I'll take care of 'em.
You know, you won't be able to
return to the Navy after this.
Fine by me. Now that
I got this doubt in my heart,
ain't no point
in staying anyway.
I know the law's the law,
but the way they're acting
this time is downright cruel.
So I'm following my
own sense of justice.
Now, you get to that island
and warn your friends.
I'm not going to thank you.
Well, good luck
to you, either way.
Fire!
They're not targeting the
island, they're targeting me!
Saul!
Ah! It hit him!
I'm sorry!
Don't apologize!
He's a criminal's
accomplice now!
My apologies, Robin.
That musta scared you.
Wait here a sec.
Are you the one firing at us?
What if you'd hurt that poor
little girl, you damn fools?
Vice Admiral, please stop!
What're you doing?
I don't know about
justice anymore.
But I do know
I can protect my friend!
Stop it, Saul!
You're scaring me!
Hope you're ready 'cause if
you make an enemy outta me
there's gonna be hell to pay!
Robin, there's still something
I want to hear you say.
Tell me you want to live!
Robin.
Robin!
Dear Robin.
Robin.
If I'm allowed to
say it, then I--I--
On the next One Piece:
"Say You Want to Live!
We Are Your Friends!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!