[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[CROCODILE]
Hm?
So who are they?
Kicking Claw Force!
[grunts]
[gasps] Those bruises!
They drank the fatal elixir.
It grants incredible strength,
but then kills the host.
...this country!
[laughs]
And if you're all
going to die anyway,
I don't have to bother
killing you myself, right?
[gasps]
You bastard!
[laughing]
Behold, the very
definition of stupidity!
[CHAKA]
Howling Fangs!
[gasps]
[CROCODILE] I see you share
the same flaw as these fools.
You'll die for others.
[REBEL SOLDIER D]
Wait, stop!
[REBEL SOLDIER A]
It's Koza!
[KOZA]
The battle is over!
Quiet your anger and
lower your weapons!
The royal army will stand down!
Let no more blood
stain the streets!
Is this the truth, Koza?
Yes. The battle's finally over.
[gunshots]
[VIVI]
Koza!
[LUFFY] "Where Vivi's Voice Gets
Heard! The Hero Descends!"
Koza!
[KOZA] You just wait
until it's finished.
This town will bring
good fortune and joy
to so many people!
It's gonna be the
best town ever!
When it's up and running,
I'll personally give
you the grand tour.
[KOZA]
Don't fight, rebel army.
Don't fight them.
[REBEL SOLDIERS chattering]
[REBEL SOLDIER E]
How could they shoot Koza?!
[REBEL SOLDIER F]
Get them!
[REBEL SOLDIERS yelling]
[BAROQUE WORKS
MEMBER A chuckling]
[VIVI]
It's Baroque Works!
What did you do?
Why did you shoot?
Listen to me now,
rebel army. Do not fight.
[ROYAL SOLDIER K]
What's goin' on?
Where'd this
sandstorm come from?
Listen, rebel army...
[gunshot]
They're shooting at us!
How dare they!
[growling]
Where did all this sand
come from so suddenly?
We can't see anything!
[gunshot]
Damn it! Bastards!
[ROYAL SOLDIER H]
Don't shoot carelessly!
[REBEL SOLDIER C]
What's going on?
Heh! They still don't
know what's happening.
What's going on, you idiots,
is that Baroque Works members
are posing as soldiers
in both your armies.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Stop! No!
Come on! Just hang in there!
They aren't surrendering.
Thought they'd ambush us by
raising a phony white flag, huh?
So this is how the royal
army plans to win.
By using dirty tricks like that?
Stop it!
No, don't do this!
Please stop fighting!
Soldiers! Look up here!
[KOZA]
Stop... rebel army.
Stop this! This battle is‐‐
[inaudible]
Hey, are you okay?
Damn!
Now, royal army!
Launch counterattack!
[inaudible]
[VIVI]
Stop it...
Stop fighting!
Please don't fight.
Stop now!
Please just stop...
You fought long and hard,
Princess, and did well.
But now... give up.
Your voice will no
longer reach them.
So this is it.
You have to run away, Vivi!
Get away from him!
Before it's too late!
I won't.
[chuckles]
You made this dust devil.
It's your doing, isn't it?
But still...
There's time.
If I stop the explosion that's
scheduled in 15 minutes,
I can still reduce the
number of casualties.
If I try this, the
rebellion will stop.
If I try that, the
It's time to wake up, Princess.
I'm tired of your useless
idealism. It's gotten pathetic.
What good are your happy ideals
if you can't do anything
to make them reality?
Then they're nothing but dreams.
And your dreams don't
stand a chance.
I don't care what you
think of my ideals.
I'm never going to
give up on them.
You would never understand!
I'm this country's Princess.
I won't give up! I won't
give in, no matter what!
You really are
a sad little girl.
[VIVI]
I refuse... to give up.
I will save... Alabasta!
Vivi!
[chuckles]
You have only 15 minutes until
the Square is blown up.
More of the rebel
forces are gathering
as reinforcements arrive.
One after another,
without even realizing
they're marching to their death.
You know, you could've
let the royal army
know about the coming
explosion earlier.
If so, maybe there
would've been a panic,
but then you could've saved tens
of thousands of innocent lives.
Stop it!
Please, Crocodile!
Just let her go!
In the end, your plans
for saving this country
have done more harm than good.
Your wretched failures
have only ended up
hurting the precious citizens
who you love so dearly.
[CROCODILE] From the beginning
of my operations here,
the sheer stupidity of your
country has amused me.
So pathetic. So easy
to manipulate.
[CROCODILE] You did a decent
job of spying on our company
for the past two years,
I will grant you that much.
[TOTO] It's me, Vivi.
Don't you recognize me?
I look different.
I lost some weight, I suppose.
[CROCODILE]
Heh.
But when it was all
said and done,
you really had no hope
of changing anything.
Stopping the rebellion.
Saving the kingdom.
All those worthless ideas
you've clung to for so long.
In the end, they just created
more victims for me.
Let me tell you something.
You're never going
to save this country.
Goodbye, Princess.
[screams]
[CROCODILE laughing]
[laughing continues]
[CROCODILE]
It can't be.
[LUFFY]
Crocodile!
Luffy!
[growls]
It can't be!
Just in time.
[crying]
[VIVI]
Luffy. Pell.
There isn't much time left
until the Square is blown up.
[VIVI]
Everyone is already down there.
My voice can't...
it can't be heard,
no matter how loud I yell.
At this rate, the
country will fall apart.
[LUFFY]
Don't worry, Vivi.
As long as we're here, your
voice will always be heard.
[ZORO]
I'm telling you again.
My injuries are a whole lot
more severe than yours are.
[NAMI] Oh, quit whining
and act like a man!
My leg is hurt,
so I can't stand!
Oh, no! I'm gonna faint!
[ZORO]
You're such a liar!
[yelling]
Best of luck, Luffy. Be careful.
[LUFFY] I ate tons of meat,
bird guy. I'll be just fine!
[LUFFY]
I won't...
...lose to you.
How did he make it out of the
quicksand with all his injuries?
[screams]
It's Luffy! He's alive!
Tony's here, too.
[USOPP]
What? Luffy!
Luffy!
[CHOPPER]
And Vivi's here, too!
See! See! He's still alive!
What did I tell you?!
I knew it all along!
Really?
[SANJI] For someone
who knew it all along,
you sure look surprised.
[EYELASH grumbles]
Usopp! Sanji! You're all right!
[SANJI] Ahh! Vivi, what
happened? Are you okay?
You look like you've been hurt!
[NAMI yells]
Nami, too. And Mr. Bushido?
Everyone... is alive.
[NAMI]
Usopp, who asked you to create
some useless prop for parties?
Oh, come on! You're
standing up just fine!
[SANJI]
Nami, my love!
Well, it did have a powerful
attack. Right, Nami?
Just shut up. I am going
to deal with you later.
Vivi.
What's going on?
What's up with all this
dust flying everywhere?
Explain yourself, idiot!
How could you let Nami
get injured like that?
What happened?
She's fine, let it go.
[USOPP groans]
Listen, Chopper, do me a favor.
Bury my body out
in the wastelands
when I'm dead and gone. Agh!
No, Usopp! Don't die!
I'm sorry, you guys.
I know I lost to
him once already.
This time....
[LUFFY]
...I'm gonna win!
The rest is up to you!
So get goin' already.
[chuckles]
If you can't beat this guy,
then I don't know
anybody who can!
[LUFFY]
I'm gonna put an end to this.
For good!
[USOPP, NAMI, CHOPPER]
Yeah!
Thank you.
After all that's happened,
all of you are still with me.
[growling]
[LUFFY]
Crocodile!
[growling]
Try all you want.
But no matter how many times
you swing, you'll never hit me.
I guess you didn't get
enough the first time, huh?
[yelling]
[chuckles]
[groans]
Now Gum‐Gum...
What the‐‐? Who's that?
[yelling]
How can he... hit me?
[LUFFY]
...Buzzsaw!
[chuckles]
He hit Crocodile!
[LUFFY]
Get up.
I figured something out
when some of my Yuba water
dropped on your hand.
Once you touch water,
then you can't turn
into sand anymore.
You took away all the rain
because you're afraid
of water, didn't you?
I know how to defeat
you, Crocodile.
Our real fight is starting now.
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[LUFFY] I'll get you
this time, Crocodile!
[NAMI] Try not to lose
against this jerk again!
[ZORO] You sure took your
time getting here!
[USOPP] Okay, then I'll
leave the rest to you!
[SANJI] Hey! Don't run away.
We gotta look for the cannoneer!
[CHOPPER]
Is he nearby?
[VIVI] There's no time left!
This is our last chance!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Sand Croc and Water Luffy!
The Second Round of the Duel!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates.