[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever
dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
Luffy.
[ZORO] Even if this wound
would kill a normal man,
I am not allowed to fail.
[HATCHAN]
New Year's Open!
[ZORO]
Dragon Twister!
[ZORO] I think it's
time to go rescue Luffy.
Hahahahaha!
[NOJIKO] Sorry but this is
the best I can do for you.
[SANJI]
I see.
They couldn't move the stone
so they just moved
Luffy's head above the water.
[ARLONG] Hahahahaha!
This is more like it.
Somebody else do something
entertaining! Hahahahaha!
[LUFFY] "Proud Warriors! Sanji
and Usopp's Fierce Battles!"
Ha! It's that old man
from the village...
What a waste of time.
[GENZO]
Dammit! He sees me.
Such a pathetic attempt
at trying to keep
rubber‐boy alive!
Guess I'll just kill you too!
[SANJI]
Where do you think you're going?
You... foolish human! Hya!
[KUROOBI] Are you really
trying to fight me under water?
You can't even
breathe down here.
What makes you
think you can fight?
[KUROOBI]
As you wish, foolish boy...
Fishman Karate...!
Dueling Hair Tether!
[KUROOBI]
Too bad...
Your kick is
powerless down here.
That's more of
your human weakness.
But my Fishman Karate loses
nothing in water. Hahahaha!
Quite the contrary,
it's much more powerful.
[KUROOBI]
Fishman Karate!
Underwater
Bladder Buster!
[KUROOBI]
Fishman Karate!
Flaming... Axe Kick!
Back Foot Jawbreaker!
Guffaw...
...Palm Bomb!
Hmph!
[SANJI] Air! Air!
Air...! I let out too much!
I can't breathe...
Suffocating...
[KUROOBI]
Impressive.
[SANJI]
Crap! Let me through.
I need to breathe. Move it!
You have amazing stamina...
You sure you're human?
[SANJI]
Le me through now!
[laughs]
[KUROOBI]
Didn't you say something like,
any man who hurts a
lady is just a piece of crap.
And yet...
Look at what your precious love
of women has gotten you.
[KUROOBI]
You have no escape
and you'll die by my hand.
The old man and the
boy he's trying to save,
they'll die too.
I'll kill Zoro and
the long‐nosed guy.
Then I'll massacre
the entire village!
And as my final pleasure,
I'll murder that
traitorous bitch, Nami!
Don't you see?
You're "love" is worthless.
If it can't save you,
then you protect...
...no one!
Not even your little girlfriend
Nami! Hahahahaha!
I'll admit that
you have some skills...
...but still...
...in the end
you're just a human.
Your body doesn't react well
to a sudden change
in pressure, does it?
Let's see...
I have a theory about
what's gonna happen to you...
Your organs are going
to explode from the inside out.
Pulverizing...
...Pressure Plunge!
Hahahaha!
[SANJI]
I can't let him do this!
If I want to save Nami,
the first thing I have
to do is save myself!
[chuckles]
Huh?
What's with him?
He just won't die!
[KUROOBI] Very well, I guess
we'll just have to try it again!
[SANJI] Fishmen use
lungs to breathe air on land.
But they use their gills to
breathe water down here,
which means a fish's gills
are useless on dry land.
Ready for your second go round?
[SANJI] And there lungs
are useless underwater...
...which means forcing air
into his gills should
suffocate this bastard.
Hmm?
You...
Is he...?
[SANJI]
Don't worry. He's okay.
Are you sure?
[SANJI]
Half of him.
Wait, half?
[SANJI]
I'll explain later.
First... Get your
ass up here...!
I want to fight
where I can breathe.
[KUROOBI]
You still don't get it, do you?
It doesn't matter to me if
I'm on land or in the water.
I am just as strong either way.
Now you will witness the
true power of Fishman Karate...
When I punched you before,
that was just a sample
of things to come.
My ultimate attack,
is ten times as powerful
and the chances
you'll survive it...
...are zero!!
Your neck!
You said my love was worthless?
Shoulder!
I can't protect anyone,
is that right?
Ribs! Back! Chest! Legs!
Son of a bitch...!
Thousand Brick Fist!
And now... Face Shot!
Now it's done...
He won't be back.
[GENZO]
What was that?
What's happening up there?
Kuroobi...
Hachi...
[SANJI] In the end
they're all just seafood.
A fish can't fight a cook.
I don't know what
he was thinking.
This game is ours.
[ARLONG]
You bastards...!
You've killed my brothers
one after the other.
I'm afraid I've let you
get too carried away!
[ZORO]
All right explain.
Luffy's half okay...
What does that mean?
It means he's alive
for the time being...
but if we want him
fully back on dry land,
I've got to go
back in the water.
[SANJI] But something tells me
ugly over there won't let me.
Amazing... really amazing...
Those guys ... beat two
of Arlong's best fishmen.
I'm done...
I can't hold my breath.
[NOJIKO]
Take my place. I'll go.
[GENZO] He's looking better.
Not so pale.
[NOJIKO]
He spit out a bunch of water.
Did I miss anything?
They're doing great.
Everyone's fine.
For the first time...
...I think I have hope...
These guys have fought so well.
We may actually be set free!
Choo. What a pain in the ass!
That long nose freak
sure could run forever.
But it took just one blast
from my squirt gun to
take him out completely.
[CHOO]
I guess I should head back.
It's all over by now, for sure.
[USOPP]
It worked! I'm alive!
I am so glad I made the
Ketchup Star for such occasions.
He thinks he killed me
with a water blast.
Run along now! Go home!
[USOPP] These guys
are totally freakin' nuts.
I don't even know
what I'm doing here.
[USOPP]
They destroyed an entire village
and killed everyone in it.
I know Nami can't do this
all on her own but seriously...
I'm hearing things.
[USOPP]
I don't mind hiding from death.
Death is scary.
[USOPP] Let's see.
I'm covered in fake blood
but I need to look
a little more beat up
like I fought bravely.
[USOPP]
Hey I know what's missing.
Dirt. Yeah, I'm too clean.
Hey... "I'm sorry, I got lost."
Yeah, that's good.
No. "I did my best,
but he got me." Maybe.
"I was this close to the
bastard, and he got away."
That sounds better. Nah.
Sounds like I'm trying too hard.
[LUFFY] We're friends...
Right...? So get on.
How 'bout... "Don't cry Nami.
We all did the
very best we could."
[ZORO] Never in my life
did I imagine I'd lose.
Or... "Everybody
fought very bravely."
[SANJI]
But the truth...
...is that our idiot
Captain is far better
than a gang who'd
prey on a lady.
[USOPP]
Maybe... "I nearly died myself."
[NAMI]
It's for my business.
This was my only choice.
"Nami... No,
to tell the truth, my injuries
aren't bad at all, really."
[JOHNNY]
Big Sis Nami was crying.
[YOSAKU]
Do they need any more reason
than that to put
their lives on the line?
[NOJIKO] To make a choice
like that when you're only ten.
Do you know how hard that
must have been for Nami?
I fought... bravely...
I never quit... Yeah... that's‐‐
[USOPP]
I'm just...
...a liar!
I'm nothing but a coward!
Stop right there,
you son of a bitch!
[CHOO]
Oh...? You're still alive. Choo.
That's right, Big Lips...!
It takes more than water
to kill someone like me!
Choo.
[USOPP] When I left
home, I left everything behind.
Peace... Safety...
[USOPP] When you live
your life on the edge,
you savor every moment.
That's why they're
able to laugh so much!
[USOPP]
That's the reason I went to sea.
I want to laugh that way too.
[USOPP] And if I don't
fight with all I've got,
then I don't deserve to be on
the same ship with them.
And I will never be able
to face my friends again!
Fool... You were better
off pretending to be dead.
The human brain is
an absolute waste of meat.
Choo
I... don't feel good.
[CHOO] Oh, yeah...
I'm just getting started.
[USOPP]
Stop it.
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Choo. Arrrgh!
Crap...! Where'd that
stupid son of a bitch go?!
I can't believe this!
[USOPP]
Special Attack!
[CHOO]
Saké?
[USOPP]
Lead Star!
[CHOO] Is this the only way
you can fight, you coward!
There is no place to hide
from my squirt cannon.
[USOPP]
Stupid, coward or whatever.
I can't run from this fight...
I'm supposed to be a man...
Although it doesn't really feel
all that great to be manly.
If I lose, I'll die.
At least I'll die a pirate.
Squirt Cannon!!!
Ohhh!!
No way...! This sucks!
Damn it.
Why should I have to waste
my time with such an idiot?
[CHOO]
It's too easy.
I'll shred you to pieces...
[CHOO]
Squirt Machine Gun!
How did he find me?
Crap! Crap! Holy Crap!
I wanted to be a real pirate
and now that I've
finally gotten my chance.
I know I can do it.
I know I can...
I promise...
If I survive this ordeal,
I'll never pretend to
be a pirate ever again!
I won't be a coward
and run away!
My fake pirate days...
...are over!!
What did you say is done?
This whole fight...
Alcohol lights on fire.
Usopp Flaming Star!
[CHOO]
Aaahhh!
Hot, fire, hot, hot!
[CHOO]
Water! Must find water!
Water! Water, water!
[USOPP]
Wait a minute!
[CHOO]
Water, water, water, water!
[USOPP]
Usopp Hammer!!
Choo!
[CHOO]
Bastard!
[USOPP] Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer!
Rubberband of Doom!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer!
[USOPP]
I did it! I beat... a fishman...
You see that, loser!!
I beat your ass!!
I can't believe
I actually did it...!
Who's a pirate now...?!
I am Usopp the Pirate!!!
Hahahaha!
[GENZO]
Please breathe!
You need to come back
now before it's too late...
...for your friends.
[DOCTOR]
I must have been dreaming.
For a moment there, I thought
we actually had a chance.
Uh... So what did
that shark guy just do?
I don't know.
It looked like he was just
throwing water around...
...but then they both
started to bleed.
I don't even
have to touch you...
You humans are so
fragile that I can kill you
just by playing around
with a little water...
That's the difference
between you and me.
Shut up!
[SANJI]
He's not kidding.
[SANJI] That's why the shark
is king of the fishmen.
[SANJI]
He's on a whole different level.
[ARLONG]
You should just die.
Your lives are
not worth that much...
There's no one who will
miss you when you're gone?
Arlong!
[JOHNNY and YOSAKU]
It's Nami!
[SANJI]
You're here...
[ARLONG]
Hey, Nami... I was just teaching
one final lesson to these
pathetic little pirates.
What are you doing here?
I'm here... to kill you.
♪All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[ZORO]
I'll hold onto the fishman.
You go in the sea.
[SANJI]
Yeah! Leave Luffy to me!
[USOPP]
All right! I've got your back!
[ZORO] Hey! Aren't you
kinda far away for that?
[USOPP]
Ahh...
Well,,. I've got this thing
about fighting Arlong...
[ZORO]
Of course you do.
[LUFFY laughs]
Ahh! I'm saved!
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy at Full Power!
Nami's determination
and the Straw Hat!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!