Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Tempest Kick Lotus!
Cry out! Song of Willow!
What the hell--
--is that?
A voice?
Hey! Keep movin'.
I don't remember telling
you to stop, Nico Robin.
Are you listening to me?
Don't forget who's
the boss here!
Alright, Lucci. Just drag her!
Pull her by the
hair if you have to!
It's an order.
Now come on. Start walking.
You're delusional, aren't you?
Oh, my. You're
honestly convinced
that the Straw Hats are still
on their way to rescue you.
Moron!
I've never seen such a
weak-looking pirate crew.
If that's your only hope,
that's pretty sad.
The only feeling left
in your body will be
an overwhelming and
eternal sense of guilt.
You will spend your days
in ceaseless atonement
for your arrogant
crime of existing.
You know it's true, Nico Robin.
Robin! Robin! Robin!
Wh-wh-what was that?
I heard someone!
Did you hear that?
Who was it?
It's big in here. Where am I?
I found you, pigeon-bastard.
"Resounding Bad News!
Buster Call Invoked!"
I must admit,
I underestimated you.
I never imagined you could
have made it this far,
and by yourself no less.
Who says I'm by myself?
Hm?
I couldn't have made it
here without my friends,
and even if I could,
I wouldn't want to.
But you wouldn't
understand that,
because all you people
think about are yourselves.
Soon, my whole crew will be here
and we'll put an end to this!
Tempest Kick!
Shave!
I'm starting to get
the hang of this.
Yeah? 'Cause I'm
starting to get sick.
I don't wanna hear that
crap coming from a sailor!
What? I'm a hero
from Sniper Island--
you must be mistaking
me for someone else.
My good buddy Usopp
is the sailor, remember?
Well, you're a sword
now--so deal with it!
Nice dodge.
Scary!
Don't let your guard down!
Yeah, uh, right!
And stop doing stupid stuff.
Uh, yes sir!
Wait, what do you
mean "stupid stuff"?
That's rude, you jerk!
No good.
My legs are too
slippery for me to stand.
I hope you're proud,
'cause this power of
yours sure is creepy!
Say whatever you like,
I know you're jealous.
After all, you scarcely
possess a fraction
of my beauty and power.
I thought, if only out of pity,
I could at least give you
a pair of silky smooth legs.
You should show some gratitude.
How considerate of
you to think of me.
But really, what
good are silky legs
if I can't even walk with them?
Well, sometimes you have
to make sacrifices
to be beautiful.
If that's how you feel,
then why don't you
try it on yourself?
Why? I'm not an
ugly duckling like you.
I'm plenty gorgeous
already! Isn't it obvious?
Whoa, what a bitch.
What was that?
Oh, nothing.
Please, brag all you like.
It'll just make my
victory that much sweeter.
Damn it. What the hell was that?
Stupid deer gorilla going nuts.
I'll deal with him
when this mess is over.
I still gotta get the key
from that secretary lady.
Hey wait, you dumb monster.
Stop stealing my thunder!
Emergency! Repeat--
We have an emergency at
the front of the courthouse--
all available units
please report here now!
Let's go!
Eliminate the traitors!
You call us traitors?
Ha! Don't make me laugh!
You guys've betrayed
us every single day
for the past fifty years.
Give us back our
freedom, you liars!
You had a leash
on us for so long,
that you forgot,
but we're pirates and
pirates hate the Navy!
Let's crush 'em, Oimo!
Sounds good to me, Kashii!
Here we go!
Focus your attack on
one giant at a time, men!
Take aim at Kashii's feet. Fire!
Good!
Now charge and bring him down!
We may lose in size,
but our numbers
give us the edge!
Keep it up!
Oi! That's bad! Kashiii!
Move on to Oimo! Aim and fire!
Sounds like bad news out there.
Those giants have
been holding back
the Marine forces
for a long time.
I'm sure they're wearing down.
Hey, hurry it up, will you?
Damn it!
I never thought a pirate
would make it so far.
This has turned
into a real disaster!
Hey, CP9, this is
your chief speaking!
What the hell are you
morons doing out there?
I've got one of the
Straw Hats right on my heels!
Are you even listening to me?
You answer when I speak to you!
Wait!
You didn't press
that button, did you?
No! This is the golden
transponder snail!
The silver transponder snail
has received a signal!
It's an emergency!
A Buster Call has been requested
under the authority
of Admiral Aokiji!
What's the location?
Enies Lobby!
Contact the five Vice Admirals
closest to that location!
All things considered,
it may be faster to reach
there from headquarters.
How long, then?
No more than
thirty minutes, sir.
In that case, prepare ten
battleships for departure
and inform the Vice Admirals
of the situation.
Make it quick!
Yes sir!
A Buster Call
has been requested!
The destination is Enies Lobby!
Prepare ten battleships
for sail immediately!
Hello? Hello?
What is it, Chief?
Oh, now I get through.
This is the one
I was trying to use.
Not that it matters anymore.
There's no turning back now.
I pushed the button.
Of all things!
I triggered the Buster Call!
Did he say
"Buster Call"? No way.
Is he supposed to
be talking to us?
You have to cancel
it right away!
Don't you realize
what you've done?
Hey! That's Robin's voice!
Everyone is going to die!
Robin?
"Cancel it"? Are you kidding?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
You can't boss me around!
Why are they broadcasting this?
Hey! You! Don't move!
I can't--I'm tied up!
And so what?
I mean, what's wrong with
the Buster Call, anyway?
That's Chief Spandam
talking -- I'm sure of it.
There's no reason for me
to get worked up over this.
Making that call was
well within my power!
I'm the Chief of Cipher Pol
Number 9, after all!
To ensure that your transfer
goes over smoothly,
I requested a Buster Call.
There's not a thing
wrong with that!
Who cares if it's
a little overkill?
Better safe than sorry!
It's a small price
to pay to make sure
those pirates get eliminated!
You're a fool!
I told you before,
that won't be the end of it!
This is an attack without mercy!
Without humanity!
I know that's the chief talking,
but I don't recognize
the woman's voice.
The Buster Call
will burn everything
on Enies Lobby to the ground!
The people, the buildings,
even the island itself!
It will sacrifice anything
and everything in its path.
The nightmare won't
end until nothing remains!
That's the power
you're invoking!
If you had any idea what
happened in Ohara years ago,
you would not be doing this!
The government is well aware
of the sacrifices involved.
That's how important
this mission is!
Since Cutty Flam burned
the blueprints to Pluton,
we can't afford
to make a mistake.
You're the last hope we have
of reviving the ancient weapon.
We're talking about
a military power
that can turn this
whole era upside down!
Even if we have to sacrifice
a few thousand soldiers,
it's better than letting you
slip out of our hands again!
I know the consequences,
I just don't care!
Don't think of this as murder--
it's a sacrifice to
protect the future!
And speaking of
"protecting the future",
my promotion is
depending on this as well!
Hey, wait a second,
can we vote on this?
What does he
mean by "sacrifices"?
Are they gonna kill us?
Think about this!
Human lives are at stake!
Allow me to remind you,
CP9 can kill in
the name of justice.
Therefore, if we think
100 deaths are needed
to save 1000 lives,
then we will kill
those 100 people
immediately, without question.
For true justice, you
must be merciless at times.
Besides, if those idiot
soldiers couldn't even stop
a few pirates from invading
a government base
of this size, they're
better off dead anyway!
I think the line
is still connected
on your transponder snail.
Ah, you gotta be
freakin' kidding me!
Everyone heard all of that?
By the way, this is uh,
Straw Hat Luffy speaking.
Like we believe that!
Everyone get off
the island! Hurry!
A Buster Call has been
invoked on Enies Lobby!
If you don't get away from
here immediately, you'll die!
Hey!
Don't tell them things
they don't need to know!
Well, what should we do now?
I can't say I'm happy, but
there's nothing we can do.
Shoulda seen it coming
with that idiot in charge.
Sounds like they're
in some sort of trouble.
The one in trouble here is me!
You poor, miserable things.
All of your hopes
completely shattered.
I wouldn't worry too much.
When it comes down
to the wire like this,
we always pull together!
Poor Pirate Boy,
you musta been born
under a bad sign to
have luck like this.
But on the other hand,
you probably like
it this way, don't ya?
We're gonna get hit
with a Buster Call!
Battleships are coming!
Get away from Enies Lobby!
I get that battleships
are coming,
but why are the
Marines running away?
She said the island was
gonna be burned to the ground.
Why would they burn
down their own island?
I don't know! Don't ask me!
Hey, if you're gonna run,
at least untie us!
It's a Buster Call!
If you stay here, you'll die!
Bring as many ships as you can
and get ready to set sail!
The battleships could
be here any second!
Guess they left us behind.
Hey! This is dangerous!
Get us outta here, dammit!
Are you kidding?
It's been dangerous ever since
we set foot on this place.
What about our big bro?
What's gonna happen to Franky?
There's no way we're
leaving without him!
We'll wait as long as it takes!
The Straw Hats are coming, too!
W-wait.
Are you saying we
should just sit here?
Get blown up?
Come on, guys.
There's gotta be
something we can do!
We can't afford to
screw around anymore.
Then let's finish them off quick
and get to the Gates of
Justice while we still can.
I just thought of something.
Huh? Oh yeah?
Like a way to get
the handcuffs off
without any blood?
Or maybe a way
to get out of here?
As a sword, you will be known
as the great blade "Nose Storm".
That's kind of awesome,
but now's not the time!
Chopper! Where are you?
Why couldn't you keep
your damn mouth shut?
Now the whole
island's in a panic!
What if those pirates
get away, huh?
You realize they're gonna
blame me for that, right?
Hey, wait a second!
If that was Robin talking,
then where is she?
Right behind these
doors, of course.
As you seem to have surmised,
you'll have to go
through me first.
Outta my way.
I'm not gonna let you keep
me from Robin any longer.
Say what you like.
This is the end.
You'll never see her again.
I made a promise, and
I'm not gonna break it.
I'm coming for you, Robin!
What did you do to me?
My whole body's slippery!
I'm sorry, but now
that the Buster Call
has been requested,
I'm afraid playtime is over.
Tempest Kick!
What? How did I miss?
I call that my "Mirage Tempo."
Pretty handy, huh?
On the next One Piece:
"Five Namis?
Nami Strikes Back with Mirages!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!