[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[GARP] The name of your
father is Monkey D. Dragon.
The revolutionary.
What's the deal, you guys?
Why's everyone
freaking out so much?
But there is one group
that is directly
opposing the authority
of the World Government.
The Revolutionary Army.
And the man at the head
of that group is Dragon.
[GARP]
Ah, that was a mistake, huh?
I probably shouldn't
have said all that stuff.
[GARP laughing]
[GARP] I take it all back.
Forget it, okay?
[ALL] What?
Anyway Luffy,
since you're my Grandson,
I won't capture you and
turn you over to the Government.
It's fine.
If I tell 'em that,
I'm sure everyone'll understand.
Can't put work
before family, right?
That's not an excuse, sir--
Let's just say they got away.
[GARP] I mostly just came here
as a favor to Coby and Helmeppo.
You boys take your time
and chat it up all you like--
I'm heading back
to my ship for now.
[LUFFY] All right, so long.
Is that all you're gonna say?
[GARP] At least
pretend like you care!
I'm your grandpa and you
haven't seen me in ages!
[LUFFY]
But I'm happy you're leaving!
All you've done
is yell and hit me!
[GARP] I still want my
grandson to love me, you idiot!
I'm not as heartless as you!
[CHOPPER] Uh...
[NAMI] I see stubbornness
runs in the family.
Immaturity, too.
[SANJI, CHOPPER] Mhm.
[LUFFY]
Its Name is the New World!
The Fate of the Grand Line.
[SANJI] That old man blew in
and flew out like a storm.
I admit, the part about
Dragon certainly surprised me.
And here I thought my
family history was odd.
Where's Luffy?
He's out front with Coby
and that other guy.
You don't wanna see him, too?
You're old friends, right?
Well, this does
bring back memories.
But Luffy's the one
who saved Coby, not me.
Huh. I wonder
where Nami ran off to.
She said something about
getting info from the Navy,
but I guess
she changed her mind.
She said she went to the pool
with Kokoro and the others.
The pool?
Galley-La has a
company pool in the back
for all of its employees to use.
Does that mean
Nami's in a swimsuit?
I'd better bring her a drink!
[LUFFY] So you guys
went over that mountain
to get to the Grand Line, too?
[COBY] "That mountain?" Oh!
You mean Reverse Mountain.
No, we went a different way.
I thought everyone
who came to the Grand Line
was supposed to go
over that mountain.
Like it was the only way.
I swear I read that
somewhere before.
Yeah, but that's actually a lie.
Hey! Coby!
Don't tell him that!
It's a secret!
[laughing]
But it's just Luffy--
It'll be fine!
[HELMEPPO] Wha--What do
you mean "it's just Luffy?"
He is a pirate, isn't he?
[COBY] What harm could it do?
Stop arguing
and tell me already.
Uh... Well, it's top secret,
but there is another
way for the Navy, at least.
That is to say,
they have ships at headquarters
that can sail through
the Calm Belt.
What? That's not fair!
Of course, the method
isn't 100 percent guaranteed.
Yeah, but what's the trick?
How the heck is anyone
supposed to get through
when the whole ocean there
is packed with Sea Kings
as big as battleships?
That place gave us a lot
of trouble, you know!
The catch is the hulls
of the Navy ships
that sail through there
have a bunch of sea prism
stone strapped to them.
[LUFFY] What does that do?
Uh, I'll try to explain it.
The sea prism stones put off the
same "energy" as the sea itself,
so when the fish see
the bottoms of the ship--
The same energy as the sea.
So that's it!
That way, even if
they go straight through
a nest of Sea Kings,
the monsters won't attack,
because they won't
notice anything!
[NAMI] So even if they
didn't take the entrance
at Reverse Mountain,
they can still slip into the
Grand Line without any trouble.
Interesting.
Those Navy scientists
are really something else!
Keep talking guys, this is good.
Hey, Pirate Lady,
are you gonna swim or not?
--Huh? Huh?
--Meow! Meow!
[CHIMNEY] Hello?
Could you can it
for just a second?
A chance like this
doesn't come very often!
I thought you were cool,
Pirate Lady,
but you're nothing
but a big, stupid jerk!
I'm trying to wiretap here!
[KOKORO] Is that something
you wanna yell out loud?
[COBY] The Navy has the
greatest inventor in the world
working for them.
His name is Dr. Vegapunk.
He's the one who came up
with this plan.
[HELMEPPO] And that's only
the tip of the iceberg for him.
You know that Devil Fruit
you ate, Straw Hat?
He's the one who
identified its power.
He also figured out how
they transfer their abilities.
He even developed a way
to "feed" devil fruits
to inanimate objects!
That was his
biggest project last year.
[NAMI] Dr. Vegapunk...
[LUFFY] I don't get it,
but that sounds pretty cool.
[COBY] The world is
full of amazing people!
You know,
if I had never met you,
I'd probably still be living
in a narrow little world.
I wouldn't know a thing
about the Grand Line.
It seems like forever ago
when you burst out of
that barrel on the ship.
[COBY] But who knows
how long I would've been
swabbing decks for Alvida
if you didn't show up.
[laughing]
I forgot!
You were on her ship,
weren't you?
Man, that's really funny!
And the reason you were
there in the first place
is even funnier!
[laughing]
I haven't heard this one!
You gotta tell me
the story, too!
Oh, uh,
really, it's nothing.
He was gonna
go on a fishing trip,
but got a
pirate ship by accident!
[HELMEPPO laughing, snorting]
[HELMEPPO] Who does that?
What a dumbass!
I didn't have the courage
to do anything back then.
I wasn't even brave
enough to run away!
But if I hadn't
been on that ship,
I never would've met Luffy,
so when I look back on it,
I think of it as fate.
So even if it was
kind of embarrassing,
since I made a friend that day,
I shouldn't have
any regrets, right?
[HELMEPPO]
Huh. So that's how it is.
Well, something like that. Mhm.
It hasn't been long, but it
seems like you've grown up.
[laughing]
Actually, people
tell me that all the time.
[HELMEPPO] Well,
we owe it to your Grandpa.
That guy puts us through
the ringer every single day!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, I know what that's like.
Sure, but I think the
Vice Admiral's an amazing guy.
We--We had
nowhere else to go,
but he took us in
and made us stronger.
I'll always be
grateful for that.
Learning from him
at Marine Headquarters
is an incredible opportunity.
Who knows what might
have happened otherwise...
I mean, the training
is pretty tough, but--
Really tough, but still,
I'm glad the Vice Admiral
is looking out for us.
[COBY] That's why we
have to try our best
no matter what we do,
so we can pay him back someday.
[HELMEPPO] Yeah, I'd like
to pay him back all right.
Pay him back for all
those punches to the head.
[LUFFY] Good luck with that one!
[HELMEPPO] Maybe not today,
but give it some time!
I don't think
I'll ever get used
to seeing her like that.
Not that I'd really
want to, I guess.
Hey, Pirate Lady!
Let's play volleyball!
[GONBE] Meow! Meow!
[LUFFY] What? You guys're
going back already?
Stick around for
dinner, at least!
[COBY] At the end of the day,
we're still enemies.
We can't be too
friendly with each other.
By the way,
I was wondering if you've
ever heard the name
they use for the second
half of the Grand Line...
[COBY] On the other
side of the Red Line,
at the far reaches of the ocean,
is a place that few pirates
or marines have ever seen.
They call it--The New World.
The New World.
[COBY] There's a new era coming,
and the people who can guide it
are gathering on those seas.
They say the one who
can master those waters
will become King of the Pirates!
And I believe
that one of these days
you and I will meet
on those waters!
[COBY] When that time comes,
I'll be even stronger!
Strong enough to capture you!
Because I promised myself
that I'll keep trying 'til--
'Til I become a Marine Admiral!
[COBY] No...
[COBY] I--I'm sorry,
I got carried away!
This is so embarrassing.
I just wanna dig a hole
and bury my head in it!
That was really arrogant of me.
I got worked up after
seeing you again and I just--
[LUFFY] Coby.
You said you're
gonna fight me, right?
Then you will
become that strong.
You'll have to.
Yeah, but a Marine Admiral?
Next time I see you,
we're gonna be stronger, too.
A whole lot stronger.
[COBY] I don't get it.
[COBY] I just blurted out
some ridiculous dream,
something I don't even
have a right to follow,
but he didn't laugh.
He believed in me.
Look at that--
Turns out you're still
a crybaby after all.
Huh, Coby?
[COBY] I'm truly grateful that I
was able to see you again today!
[COBY] Keeping up with them
is going to be a real challenge.
I can't kid myself about this.
Just you wait!
We're gonna get
tougher and tougher!
You'll see next time.
When we all meet
in the New World!
Farewell!
Hey, wait!
You two better
prepare yourselves,
'cause Coby and I
are gonna blow you away,
you hear me?
[HELMEPPO] Coby, slow down!
[COBY] I can't slow down!
I'm gonna run all the way
to the New World!
[HELMEPPO]
What? You've lost your mind!
Well, Luffy,
you've done it again.
You've found another powerful
rival for our crew to fight.
[LUFFY] If Coby says he
can do it, then I believe him.
[chuckling]
I'm glad those two are okay.
But now, after what
happened at Enies Lobby,
I wonder how
the world will react.
It might get messy.
As far as I'm concerned,
the island's gone
and that's the end of that.
Though I gotta admit,
I was pretty surprised
when I found out
they decimated CP9, too.
We won't be seeing
that part of the story
in the news, since CP-9
was a secret organization
to start with.
[COBY]
It just doesn't seem right
that the Navy burned
down their own island
with the Buster Call and now
they're blaming the Straw Hats.
Luffy would never
do something like that!
[SPANDAM] I had the
power of Enies Lobby--
The power of CP9!
I even had the power
of a Buster Call!
They practically burned
the whole island down!
[SPANDAM] And yet,
even after all that,
even after all I've done,
I can't take a single woman away
from a tiny band of riffraff!
It's not fair!
Even if it was
only to uphold justice,
nothing good can
ever come of this.
If I were you,
I'd be happy those guys
made it out alive at all.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[HELMEPPO] But seriously,
what were those idiots thinking?
Starting a war with the
whole World Government
just to save one crewmember?
Now what'll they do?
I knew it--
You're worried about them, too!
You can't fool me!
No, that's not what I
was trying to say at all.
What do I care if they
get themselves killed?
[GARP]
What're you yapping about?
I didn't give you numbskulls
permission to come up here!
[COBY and HELMEPPO screaming]
[GARP]
I do you one little favor
and you get all
full of yourselves!
Training resumes right now!
Get down here
and gimme 500 pushups!
[HELMEPPO, COBY] Yes, sir!
[NAMI] Here ya go!
Nami-Sweet!
The water-water meat
is all ready!
'Kay!
Granny, that was awesome!
Meow, meow!
That meat sure smells nice!
I know! Now say "ah!"
--Hey Sanji, this is yummy!
--Yummy!
Yummy!
Water-water meat barbecue!
Sniper King--
Where'd you come from?
Eat all you want.
I don't care anymore!
What the hell're
you crying for?
[SANJI] I'm not crying!
I just got smoke
in my eyes, that's all!
So how is it, Robin?
Nice and juicy, huh?
[ROBIN] Yes, it's heavenly.
[ZAMBAI] Look, it's them!
Hey Straw Hat!
Are you finally awake?
Oh, it's the Franky Family!
Get over here and eat!
Barbecue time, boys!
[FRANKY FAMILY SILVERHAIR]
My favorite!
[LUFFY] We got too many guys
and too little meat!
Someone get some more!
It's Sodom and Gomorrah!
Hey, save some for me!
Me, too!
Guys, over here! Hey!
[TILESTONE] Straw Hat!
Feeling better now?
[LUFFY] Galley-La's here, too!
Who said you could use
the company pool, anyway?
Put on some clothes! Jeez!
Have you never seen
a swimsuit before?
Well...
--Something smells delicious.
--[PAULIE] Don't look, sir!
This perverted harlot
is going to corrupt your eyes
with her filthy body!
Really, now.
We can't take a break
once we start building the ship.
[FRANKY] That's why we're
gonna get all our partying done
right now!
I know you got a seat
set aside for me!
'Cause big bro's
the star of the show!
[FRANKY] Wow!
We're glad you
could make it, bro!
[USOPP] All right, let's rock!
How would you like to
hear Sniper King's #1 hit?
Yeah! Party time!
[USOPP (song)] ♪ Oh, the
wind carries my name ♪
♪ From Sniper Island,
far away ♪
♪ When I take aim,
it's straight and true. ♪
--♪ Lulu lala lu. ♪
--[ALL] Ow! Ow!
A little more for the lady?
Here!
Thanks!
[song continues]
Okay, next batch is up!
Could you keep it down?
[USOPP (song)] ♪ No one
knows what secrets hide ♪
♪ behind this mask
and my cape. ♪
Yummy!
[raucous laughter]
[AOKIJI] Stay where you are
and listen, Nico Robin.
[ROBIN] It can't be.
Aokiji?
Why didn't you try to
escape like you usually do?
If you'd acted on your own, you
could've gotten away from CP-9.
Even you should know
that this time was different.
I couldn't just abandon my crew.
I couldn't leave them to die.
You might not know this,
but your friend, Jaguar D. Saul,
that I was forced to kill
in Ohara, was my friend, too.
[SAUL] Kuzan, wake up.
You can't tell me
this nonsense is justice!
[SAUL] Can you take pride
in something like this?
[AOKIJI]
Although I carried out my duty
as a Marine that day,
I also honored his
wishes by sparing you
and helping you escape.
After that, I still felt
responsible for your life.
But when 20 years had passed
and you still
hadn't found a home,
I began to fear Saul
had made a mistake.
[AOKIJI] In the end,
even I had decided you were
too dangerous to live.
[AOKIJI]
I was certain that Enies Lobby
would end the story
of Ohara once and for all.
[AOKIJI] Of course,
I never anticipated
that Straw Hat's little gang
would have defeated all of CP9.
[AOKIJI]
So, have you finally found
the place where you belong?
[ROBIN] Yes.
In the end, I don't
know if Saul was right.
I don't know if what I've done
is right or not, either.
So now,
I need you to show me
the answer to that question.
I intend to.
[AOKIJI] Then live
your life with courage,
and prove that
Ohara is still alive.
[ROBIN] Aokiji!
[LUFFY] Hey, Robin!
Check this out!
[CHOPPER] Hurry Robin, look!
[LUFFY] Robin!
How much meat can you eat?
[CHOPPER and USOPP laughing]
[CHOPPER]
That's the best ever, Luffy!
[NAMI] Seriously,
could you guys grow up already?
[LUFFY] Whatever.
You were stuffing
your face a second ago, too.
You wanna try?
[NAMI] As if!
[CITIZEN 315A] Look! Over there!
[CITIZEN 315B] The pirates
are having a party!
[AOKIJI]
I hope these are the friends
you've been searching for.
[SAUL] No matter who you are,
ain't no one born into
this world to be alone!
[ROBIN] You were right, Saul.
[SAUL] Share your life with
them, and never let them go.
Hey! Robin!
[RANDOM CITIZEN 315A]
Here! Check it out!
[ROBIN]
Maybe I should try that myself.
[LUFFY] Yeah, Robin!
Do it! Do it!
[SANJI]
You're a bad influence, Luffy!
Don't encourage her!
[LUFFY] You just cook the meat!
Don't tell us how to eat it!
[SHANKS]
Pardon the big entrance,
but this is an
enemy ship, after all.
Anyway, Whitebeard,
there's something
I need to discuss with you.
[SHANKS] It's about your
Second Division Commander, Ace.
I want you to stop him.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Shanks Makes a Move!
The Linchpin
to the Reckless Era.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!