[NARRATOR]
Two years have passed
since the war between the
Navy, the Seven Warlords,
and the Whitebeard Alliance,
but its repercussions are still
felt throughout the world.
This is the deserted
island of Ruskaina,
northwest of Amazon Lily.
[MARGARET]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Yeah! I'm coming!
[LUFFY] Time really
sneaks up on you, huh?
Two years already.
[gasps]
[roars]
[LUFFY]
Hey!
[gasps]
[LUFFY] Find someone else
to eat. She's my friend.
[ALL gasp]
[sighs]
Luffy, the ship is
all ready to sail.
Give the word, and we'll be off.
[LUFFY]
Got it. Thanks.
[HANCOCK laughs]
I should've known.
He's the boss of
the whole island now.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, it's kind of a shame.
I was planning on
eating these guys,
but since we're friends now,
that would be weird, huh?
They still look
pretty yummy, though.
Don't you worry about food.
I have all of your favorites
ready and waiting on the ship.
Since I'm so thoughtful,
I wouldn't blame you
if you wanted to get
married right away.
[LUFFY]
I'll pass on the marriage,
but thanks for the food.
Ah! Cold as ever, and yet
my heart is on fire!
[SANDERSONIA]
I heard that Rayleigh left
a whole six months ago.
I assume he's waiting for
you back on Sabaody now.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, I learned the basics
a little ahead of schedule.
All that's left is to say bye
to my friends here, I guess.
[LUFFY]
So long, you guys.
Time to go!
[NARRATOR] Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained every treasure that
the world had to offer.
Smiling, even as he
stood upon the scaffold,
he issued a challenge
to the world.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] Now, those who dare
to dream hoist their flags
and sail into the
Great Pirate Era!
[SHAKKY]
It's been two whole years
since Monkey's crew came here.
Seems like only yesterday.
[RAYLEIGH]
Yeah.
[SHAKKY chuckles]
We haven't changed, but
I bet they've all grown up.
Can't wait to see.
[RAYLEIGH] Heh. Well, I
wouldn't get ahead of myself.
For all we know, they might
not even make it here.
They're not small fries anymore,
thanks to their captain--
the whole world is after them.
[door opens]
Well.
Ah. I didn't think
you'd be the first.
[ZORO] Oh, yeah?
Nobody else has shown up?
Well, damn. Guess they got lost.
[LUFFY] "The Beginning
of the New Chapter!
The Straw Hats Reunited!"
[BARTENDER A] Did you hear?
They relocated Navy HQ.
[NAMI]
Oh? Did they now?
Yeah. They traded locations
with a branch called G1.
That moved them to the
other side of the Red Line.
Their new fleet admiral's a lot
more cocky than Sengoku was.
Moved right into the Four
Emperor's territory.
He's not afraid to stare
down the toughest pirates
in the world.
On the upside, that keeps
them out of our business,
but on the downside,
we've got a lot more
criminals running around
and nobody to stop them
if things get ugly.
Oh.
It did seem like there were
an awful lot of thugs
compared to two years ago.
[GOSSIPING MAN A]
Hey, did you catch this?
[GOSSIPING MAN B]
Yeah, it's a shocker, huh?
I had to do a double take,
but it looks like the Straw
Hats are back after all.
I never heard word of them
dying or anything,
but two years is a
long time for anyone
to just disappear like that.
[GOSSIPING MAN A] Either way,
looks like they're recruiting
some new members.
[GOSSIPING MAN C]
This is a good place for it.
If you made it here,
that means you survived the
first half of the Grand Line,
and those guys keep pouring in.
[GOSSIPING MAN B]
His crew's pretty small.
Makes sense that he'd
wanna pick up some more
before heading to the New World.
That sounds like fun to me!
I'd make a great
Straw Hat, right?
[GOSSIPING MAN B]
Fat chance.
There's guys with
100 million Berry bounties
all over the place here.
[GOSSIPING MAN C] Ha. What would
they want with a chump like you?
[GOSSIPING MAN B laughs]
[GOSSIPING MAN A]
That's cruel, man.
[GOSSIPING MAN A gasps]
[laughs]
[MAN] Hey, grandpa,
how 'bout some drinks?
And some food! Gimme
everything you got!
[BARTENDER A]
Uh. Yes, sir!
Hey. I think that's them!
I know that's them! Just look!
He's got a straw hat.
It's gotta be.
[BROOK, SINGERS]
♪ Bone to be wild! ♪
Aw, come on, bro.
There's gotta be
something you can do!
Like what? We're sold out!
This is the Soul
King World Tour!
You can't waltz up
and buy tickets
when the show is about to start!
This is the final concert
of the tour, too!
Can't you hear 'em?
The crowd is ready to rock!
[SOUL KING FANS cheering]
Hey, manager!
Let's make this the greatest
show of my afterlife!
[LONGARM BOSS]
Well, of course! Of course!
Now would be the time!
Your TDs are at the
height of their sales.
In fact, we just
broke a million!
You certainly earned your
title as the King of Soul.
Just listen to those fans
chanting your name!
[SOUL KING FANS] Soul King!
Soul King! Soul King...!
[BROOK]
I can dig it, boss man.
But one thing
before the concert.
I got somethin' heavy
to lay on ya.
I'm all ears, friend.
[SOUL KING FANS cheering]
[music playing]
Come on, baby!
[SOUL KING FANS]
Yeah!
I love you down to my....
[SOUL KING FANS]
...bones!
[BROOK]
♪ Bone to be wild! ♪
[SOUL KING FANS]
[BROOK]
♪ Bone to be wild! ♪
[SOUL KING FANS]
♪ Bone! ♪
---♪ Bone! ♪
--[SOUL KING FANS] ♪ Bone! ♪
--♪ Bone! ♪
[BROOK]
♪ Bone! Bone! Bone! ♪
[SOUL KING FANS cheering]
♪ I don't need a lot of muscle ♪
♪ 'Cause the ladies
love my hustle, baby! ♪
♪ It's no mystery. ♪
♪ Just rock with me. ♪
♪ And you'll see why
I'm the king! ♪
[BACKING VOCALS]
♪ Bone to be wild! ♪
[LONGARM BOSS growls]
[LONGARM BOSS] I'm gonna
wring his sorry neck bone!
How selfish can he be?
Hey! Grab me a
transponder snail!
I'm not gonna let you
walk all over me, Brook!
[BROOK] Today is a reunion, an
anniversary, and a celebration!
[SOUL KING FANS cheering]
[SANJI] I never thought I'd
miss this place so much,
but I sure am glad to be back.
[yelps]
[SANJI laughs]
Women! Real women!
No stubble! No hairy
legs! No giant chins!
Just honest to goodness
beautiful girls!
How I've longed for your
delicate features.
Your soft skin.
To hear the intoxicating words
resting on your sweet lips!
Viva Sabaody!
I need lady!
[laughing]
[PINK-STRIPED QUEEN]
Sanji, dear!
It looks like this is farewell.
I hate to part, but we'll
meet again someday.
[SANJI]
Uh!
I hope not!
Thanks for the ride and say
hi to Iva, but go away!
What's up, ladies?
I'm fresh outta hell and
lookin' for a good time!
Like they say, if a
boy picks on a girl,
that means he has
a crush on her.
Oh, I know. Happens
to me all the time.
Love is patient, Sanji!
We'll wait! We know
you'll come back!
I'm on my way, Nami-swan!
Robin, my love!
[gunshot]
[MAN]
What's the matter, can't read?
Or are you just stupid?
I know preschoolers with
higher bounties than that.
How 'bout you check
that poster again.
If your bounty is under 70
million, then we don't want you.
So why don't you take your weak
ass back to pirate daycare?
If that's all you're worth, it's
a wonder you made it this far.
Bastard!
[FAKE LUFFY]
Now scram.
I'm the son of Dragon
the Revolutionary!
I ain't got time for this!
[chuckles]
We're the chosen ones, boyo.
No chumps are gonna
run with this crew.
We're in a league of our own!
If you can't get with us,
you better get the hell
out of our way!
Too late.
[gunshot]
That's rough.
Straw Hat is fierce.
'Course he is. He's a legend.
What's the count, Franky?
How many recruits we got?
[FAKE FRANKY] 'Bout a hundred
last time I checked.
Three whole crews joined up
along with ten guys
running solo.
They've got some
nice bounties, too.
[chuckles]
I know two of 'em.
Pair of high-profile rookies
joined at the same time.
"Wet-Haired" Caribou
and "Blood Splatter" Coribou.
They love killin' Marines.
Brothers and captains worth
210 million and 190 million.
Ha! Now, they answer to us!
And there's more where
they came from!
Hey! Bring another round!
Uh! Yes, sir!
Better make it quick.
Ah. I see you sittin'
alone over there, missy.
[gasps]
If you wanna have
a good time,
why don't you party with us?
She's a real looker, ain't she?
[FAKE LUFFY laughing]
[FAKE LUFFY]
Eh?
Hey! Sister! I'm talkin' to you!
Lady, d'you hear him?
[sighs]
I'll pass. I'm here
waiting for a friend.
This is about to get ugly.
Listen, I would not
turn that man down.
You realize that's Straw
Hat Luffy, right?
Yeah, the same Straw Hat
that burst into Marineford
and went head to head
with the Navy Admirals.
He's nuts.
[FAKE USOPP laughs]
Waitin' for a friend?
Captain Luffy is a star, baby.
Your "friend" would probably
piss his pants if he saw him.
Come drink with some real men.
I'm only going to say this once.
You can take your
offer and shove it,
'cause I'm way out
of your league.
What?
You understand?
Mister... whoever you are.
You don't know me?
[BARTENDER A gasps]
I'm Straw Hat Luffy, you wench!
Ah!
Hey, come on! Say
you're sorry! Hurry!
Nobody disrespects me!
Let me handle this.
Har-har. You think you're
real cute, don't you?
I'll make this super
simple, okay?
Either you come drink with
Captain Luffy, or you die.
[FAKE NAMI giggles]
For your info, I have
a bounty, myself.
I'm the Straw Hat's
navigator, Nami.
You scared yet?
Special Attack... Green Star...
..."Devil"!
[FAKE NAMI screaming]
Huh?
Whoa. What the hell?
[FAKE NAMI]
Captain! Save me!
[FAKE LUFFY]
Save yourself! Get away from me!
A giant plant?
Where'd that come from?
Hey there, beautiful.
Can I buy ya a drink?
[NAMI gasps]
[chuckles]
Ah!
Look at you! Those
muscles! And that hair!
You tough guy! You
look great! I missed you!
[USOPP] Uh, thanks. Uh, your,
uh, hair looks nice, too.
[chuckles]
That hot girl was waiting
for that pencil-nosed geek?
What does he have that we don't?
New special move, huh?
[USOPP chuckles]
[USOPP] Yeah, they come from
seeds called "pop greens."
Needless to say, I wasn't just
sitting around on my tail
these past two years.
It's a new me!
I'm not part of the
"weakling trio"
with you and Chopper anymore.
That means no more
running and hiding.
I'm a real warrior now!
Uh. Hey, dude? If you did
this, could you undo it?
What the--?! Sniper
King?! But how?
Usopp, forget about them!
Let's get outta here. There's
something we need to talk about.
You stop right there!
--Luffy?
--[NAMI] Ignore him!
Ma'am, you haven't
paid your tab yet!
[USOPP]
Keep the change!
Crap! They're makin'
fools of us!
Gun 'em down now!
Son of a--
Huh?
Um, guys? What are those
weird bubble things?
[popping]
[FAKE LUFFY] I have a feelin'
this ain't gonna be pretty.
[thunder rumbles]
[WOMAN A screaming]
What the hell's going on here?
Yeah, so I picked up some
new special moves myself.
You show off! Can't you
let me be cool for once?
[MAN C gasps]
[FAKE FRANKY coughs]
Who do they think they are?
Hunt those bastards down
and murder 'em.
[MARINE A]
I have a report, sir!
From Sabaody Archipelago!
What? You say the
Straw Hats are back?
Yes, sir!
Word is that they're recruiting
new crew members
before they head
to the New World.
Had a feeling Straw
Hat was still alive.
Inform Headquarters
of this immediately.
Send in as many backup
units as we can spare
and begin a search of
the entire archipelago.
[BOTH]
Sir!
I think I shook them off.
[ROBIN]
Brook is holding a concert
and the Straw Hats are
looking for new recruits?
Goodness, I've been
gone for too long.
[ROBIN] "Soul King" does have
a nice ring to it, though.
[FRANKY]
Well, I'll be damned.
Not a scratch on the whole ship.
Sorry to keep you
waitin', Sunny.
We'll be sailin' off soon.
I almost forgot, the food
stalls here are great!
I hope everyone's okay.
I sure do miss them.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[YOUNG GIRL A]
Ooh, I want the big one!
[YOUNG BOY A]
Thank you!
[squeals]
[gunshot]
Oh! Hey! Are you all right? Hey!
Why did he do that? He just
shot her out of the blue!
[WOMAN B]
That's awful!
Come on, we'll get a doctor.
You! What is wrong with you?
She didn't do a damn
thing to deserve that!
[FAKE LUFFY] Ugh. I thought
you were someone else.
I said sorry. So,
here's the deal.
I'm lookin' for some
punks who crossed me
and made a run for it.
A red-haired woman and
a guy with a long nose.
So you just shot her?
That's normal for you?
This won't end well.
Straw Hat's a monster.
Eh? You wanna fight about it?
'Cause I got plenty
more bullets.
Your choice, pal.
[MAN I screams]
Don't blame me. Blame your nose!
Hey. We'll get some
help! Stay with me!
Find those punks now,
or I'll shoot you, too!
We got a reputation
to uphold here!
We gotta show this
place who's boss!
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Uh?
Oops. Didn't see ya there.
Sorry 'bout that. See ya.
That's guy's insane!
Either that, or he doesn't
know who Straw Hat is.
He's a dead man either way!
Get back here!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[NARRATOR] A crew of fake
Straw Hats has formed,
taking advantage of
the disappearance
of the real Straw Hats.
Luffy, in disguise, crosses
paths with the fake Luffy,
who casues a scene in
the middle of Sabaody.
Unaware of who he's facing,
the imposter finds himself
on the receiving end
of a mysterious power.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!