[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[CABAJI]
Die!
[ZORO]
Oni...
Giri!
[CABAJI] Defeated...
by petty thieves.
[ZORO]
We aren't sneak thieves...
...we're pirates!
[NAMI]
The chart of the Grand Line!
Yes!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY yells]
I'll never ever forgive
you, Shanks, ever!
[LUFFY]
"Who is the Victor?!
Devil Fruit Power Showdown!"
[BUGGY]
In all my life,
I've never been as mad
at someone as him!
That bastard, Shanks, stole
countless riches from me!
I don't know how you
two are connected,
but I can say whatever
I want about him!
I've earned that!
[BUGGY growls]
[PIRATES shouting]
The North Pole!
South Pole!
That's what you say!
Right, and I'm gonna
keep on saying it
because I'm right, clown!
[BUGGY]
Oh, you got guts!
I'm gonna settle this
once and for all!
[SHANKS]
Go ahead and try!
[BUGGY]
All right, you bastard!
I'm gonna bust you up flashily!
[SHANKS]
Counter attack!
[BECKMAN]
Knock it off!
Nobody but you two
cares which is colder,
the North Pole or the South.
If you wanna know so badly,
then why don't you go
to both and find out!
Now cool it!
[LOOKOUT]
A ship!
[ALL]
Huh?
[LOOKOUT] Enemy ship to
the north‐northeast!
Right! Get ready! Time to fight!
[PIRATES]
Yes sir!
Yes... I can't wait to plunder!
You seem happy, Buggy.
[BUGGY]
Obviously!
Enemy ships are just like
big floating treasure chests.
It's only natural for
pirates to raid 'em!
Am I wrong?
Well, there's some
truth to that.
You're too weak!
You and everyone else
here just don't have
the pirate's natural hunger and
desire for plundering treasure!
You don't know what
it means to be a pirate!
[PIRATES yelling]
[BUGGY]
What's this?!
It's... a... treasure map!
I've never seen one before!
It's incredible!
Is the treasure on the
bottom of the ocean?
Yes!
Now my life's path is
flashily decided! [laughs]
[PIRATES cheering]
[BUGGY laughing]
[SHANKS]
Hey, Buggy!
Aren't you gonna come
celebrate with us?
We found a whole lot
of really neat stuff.
It's no map!
I... don't have...
anything hidden...
Go away!
What are you talking
about, Buggy?
Oh, uh, nothing.
[SHANKS sighs]
[BUGGY] You said you were gonna
leave this ship sometime, right?
So, what do you plan to do?
[SHANKS]
I'm gonna get my own ship,
then gather a reliable
crew and see the world.
I'm gonna take my time. Heh...
...All as a pirate, of course.
[BUGGY laughs] What a bunch
of sentimental nonsense!
[SHANKS]
Say what?!
[BUGGY] I do admire your
fighting skill, though.
If you weren't such a softy,
I'd make you one of my henchmen.
[SHANKS]
Your henchman?
Heh, I don't think so.
[BUGGY]
Huh?
We have completely different
outlooks on life,
so I think we should just
follow our own paths.
That's what pirates do.
Heh! You think you're such
an expert on pirates.
But if we ever
meet on the ocean,
and we'd have to have
a fight to the death.
Yeah... Pirates do that, too.
You never make sense.
Anyways,
you said something about finding
some interesting loot, right?
Huh? Oh yeah, We
found a Devil Fruit.
A Devil Fruit?
I heard that the
different fruits
are incarnations
of the Sea Devil.
Supposedly, if you eat one,
you gain devil powers
but the sea will hate you
and take your ability to swim.
You'd have to be stupid
to eat that thing!
[BUGGY]
I'd never get that treasure
on the ocean floor
if I couldn't swim!
[SHANKS]
But still...
I bet you could
sell that fruit for
at least a hundred
million berries.
[BUGGY]
Heh..
What?!
I, pirate apprentice Buggy,
am about to devour
this Devil Fruit!
[laughing] You gotta
love the kids.
Never thinking of consequences.
[BUGGY laughing]
[PIRATES gasp]
[PIRATE F]
Well, Buggy?
Do you feel any differently yet?
[BUGGY]
No... Not really...
[PIRATE E]
Aww, was it a fake?
[PIRATE F]
I'm not surprised.
I've never seen a real
Devil Fruit before.
[BUGGY chuckles]
[BUGGY]
Yes! That worked flashily well!
These guys are so gullible.
I can't believe I was able to
trick them so easily. [laughs]
Now, to jump ship before
they find out the truth!
With the money I get from
selling this Devil Fruit
and finding the sunken treasure,
I'll easily be able to form
my own crew. [chuckles]
Hey there, Buggy!
Were you just saying something?
[BUGGY]
Oh, it's you!
Don't scare me like that!
Don't be so jumpy.
And don't steal too much
food from the kitchen.
You don't wanna
make the cook mad!
[BUGGY]
Whew, that was close...
‐‐[SHANKS] Oh yeah!
‐‐[BUGGY yelps]
The captain told
me to tell ya‐‐
[BUGGY snorting]
‐‐[BUGGY] Damn you, Bastard!
‐‐[SHANKS] Hey, what's wrong?
Why? Why? Why?!
[SHANKS]
What's that piece of paper?
[BUGGY]
Ah! Not my map! [screams]
Hey, Buggy!
[BUGGY]
What the?
W‐What's going on?
I can't move.
Is it true that you lose
your ability to swim?!
Damn it!
[SHANKS]
Hey! Hey, What're you doin'?
What's going on?
Why aren't you swimming?
Buggy!
[BUGGY]
Help... Help me...
[SHANKS]
I'll save you Buggy!
[BUGGY grumbles]
So... are you telling me
that Shanks saved your life?
No, that's not the point
I'm trying to get across!
Because of what he did to
me I was unable to swim,
and therefore unable to
obtain my sunken treasure!
Then, I had a revelation!
If I couldn't go underwater,
then I'd just obtain all
the treasure on dry land!
Using my brand new
Chop‐Chop Powers.
And now I won't let anyone
who touches my treasure live!
Death to those who try to
pilfer my hard earned treasure!
Get back here you beast!
[gasps]
‐‐[BUGGY yelling]
‐‐[NAMI screaming]
Damn it! He spotted me!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
You don't stand a chance
of escaping from me!
Now, I'm going to
flashily chop you up!
[BUGGY wheezes]
[NAMI gasps]
[LUFFY]
Hm.
[BUGGY grunts]
Oww...
My balls... My balls...
That was a cheap shot!
Don't run off yet,
we're not done.
What's wrong? The mayor's never
been gone for this long before.
I hope he's all right.
It sounded like a battle
was going on in town.
There's been a lot more
cannon fire than usual, today.
I'll go to town
to check it out.
You all just stay here.
I'm going with you.
No way.
There are still pirates in town.
It's too dangerous
of a situation.
Yes, Exactly. That's why
you'll need our help.
[CITIZEN F]
What kind of citizens are we
if we don't help?
We have got to find
out what's happening!
[CITIZEN D]
You can't stop us from going.
We wanna do all we
can to help out.
Then it's settled.
We all go together!
[CITIZEN cheer]
[LUFFY]
Hey!
You better drop that treasure
and get outta here, Nami.
You don't want him
coming after you again.
No!
Drop the money and go?!
No way!
Why should I leave
my treasure behind?
[BUGGY growls] Did you just
call it your treasure?!
That's right, you heard me!
I'm a thief who
steals from pirates,
and I just stole
a lot of treasure
from a really annoying one!
So that makes this my
treasure now, Understand?!
[LUFFY]
Ah! That makes sense!
That's pure nonsense!
That's my treasure and just
because you stole it from me
doesn't make it yours,
you dirty, sneaky thief!
Honestly! What did your
parents teach you?
A criminal trying to lecture
another criminal? Ridiculous.
What's that?!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Whatever, the day I take
a morality lesson
from you, is the day
I stop being a thief.
[BUGGY grumbles]
I hope you're ready
for the consequences.
Now, Here comes,
Chop, Chop...
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Festival!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY whimpers, yells]
[BUGGY laughs]
[BUGGY] I'd like to see you try
to save your friend from me now,
Gum‐Gum!
Damn it... He broke up
into smaller pieces!
[LUFFY]
What the...?
‐‐[BUGGY] Nami?
‐‐[NAMI whimpers]
Give me back my treasure!
No way!
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
‐‐[BUGGY] Huh?
[LUFFY]
Coochie, coochi, coo!
‐‐[BUGGY laughing]
‐‐[NAMI screaming]
[LUFFY]
He,he...
‐‐[BUGGY yells]
‐‐[NAMI screaming]
See how you like... this!
[BUGGY, NAMI screaming]
[BUGGY]
Damn it! Knock it off!
[NAMI]
No, you knock it off!
[NAMI yells]
[LUFFY]
Woah!
[BUGGY laughs]
[NAMI gasps]
Thanks for giving me my
treasure back, Nami.
[NAMI grunts]
[NAMI]
Let go!
You, let go!
This is my treasure so get
your grubby hands off it!
Just give me back my treasure!
[LUFFY grunts]
[BUGGY giggles]
[LUFFY panting]
‐‐[BUGGY] Die!
‐‐[NAMI screams]
‐‐[BUGGY laughing]
‐‐[LUFFY] I already told you,
You haven't finished
dealing with me yet!
‐‐[BUGGY groans]
‐‐[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI gasping]
Consider that finishing move
a little gift from
the old mayor guy!
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI]
Thanks a lot, I owe you one.
[LUFFY]
Sure! No problem.
[NAMI laughs]
‐‐Oh yeah! The map!
‐‐My treasure! [gasps]
[BUGGY]
This isn't over yet, Gum‐Gum!
[LUFFY]
Ah! He's still alive!
[BUGGY]
Shut up!
How dare you flashily
do this to me!
You'll pay for this!
[LUFFY gasps]
[BUGGY]
Assemble, Chop‐Chop Parts!
Ha! Ha!
[BUGGY]
Eh?
Looking for these, Buggy?
Gah! My parts!
‐[LUFFY laughs]
All right! Way to go thief!
Stop it, now!
See ya, Buggy!
‐‐Now, Gum‐Gum...
‐‐[BUGGY yells]
[LUFFY]
Bazooka!
[BUGGY yelling]
[LUFFY]
I win! [laughs]
Whoa! That kid sure sent
Captain Buggy flyin'!
So, What do we do
without the captain, huh?
[PIRATE B]
Keep acting unconscious.
[PIRATE A]
Good idea.
Sorry your hat's all torn up.
Don't worry, I can
still put it on.
And I got Buggy out of here,
so I'm satisfied for now.
Bastard...
When I have time, I'll fix
it for you, if you like.
[LUFFY]
Huh? What's that?
Oh forget it.
I split this into two bags,
so give me a hand
and carry half of it...
It's too heavy for me.
That sure is a lot.
If anything, that clown
Buggy knew quality treasure
when he saw it,
and now it's all mine.
I bet I can sell this for at
least ten million berries!
[NAMI]
Eh...
Here you go.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
It's the chart to
the Grand Line.
You do want it don't you?
[LUFFY]
You're giving it to me?
Because you saved my life.
[LUFFY]
Ha! Thanks, Nami!
Now I finally have it!
A map of the Grand Line!
Hurray!
Oh, does this also mean
you'll be joining me
and my pirate crew?
I told you, no matter what,
I'll never join a pirate crew!
But, okay...
Hanging around with you
seems profitable enough.
Just remember this,
I'm only joining you...
cause it's in my interest.
Sure!
[ZORO snoring]
[LUFFY]
Hey, Zoro! Wake up!
Zoro!
We're leaving!
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO]
Did we take care of everything?
Yeah! And we got a Navigator
and we got a chart
of the Grand Line.
[ZORO]
Huh?
Hmm.
[NAMI gasps]
I'm not sure about this.
I feel light headed.
[NAMI] Of course you do. It's
always something with you two.
Honestly!
Hey, wait a minute.
What did I do?
Are you kidding me?
You're the worst of them all!
Anyways, let's go
help the mayor.
[LUFFY]
Oh, yeah.
I guess we should wake the old
guy up, now that it's all over.
‐‐[CITIZEN D] You there!
‐‐[NAMI, LUFFY] Huh?
You're not residents
of this village!
[LUFFY]
Nope. And who are you?
What was all that
cannon fire we heard?
It sounded like there may
have been a battle here earlier.
If you know anything,
please tell us.
Oh good, they're just citizens!
I thought that maybe
they were more pirates.
Oh, Mayor!
[CITIZEN A]
Oh, no! Say something!
[CITIZEN B]
Can you hear me?
[CITIZEN C]
He's out cold.
[CITIZEN E]
The pirates definitely did this.
[CITIZEN F]
How horrible!
No, I'm the one who
kicked that old man's ass.
[CITIZENS]
What?
Hold on! You didn't have
to tell them that, did you?
It's true.
Maybe you should explain to them
so they don't get angry! [gasps]
[CITIZENS grumbling]
Tell me, Why exactly
did you knock our
mayor out and leave him
in the street to die?
You better explain yourselves!
[CITIZEN E] Who are you?
Are you with the pirates?!
[NAMI] They're getting
really bloodthirsty.
We can't let them know that
we're thieves and pirates.
We're pirates.
[CITIZENS]
Just as we thought!
[laughing]
‐‐Idiot!
‐‐But it's the truth!
[CITIZEN E]
Pirates!
How dare you ravage our town!
[CITIZEN D] We won't show you
any mercy for what you've done.
[ZORO]
What now?
Doesn't look like they're
up for a discussion.
[LUFFY laughs]
‐‐[NAMI gasps]
‐‐[LUFFY] Run!
[CITIZENS yelling]
[CITIZEN D]
There's no escape!
[CITIZEN F] How dare you
hurt our beloved mayor!
[yelling continues]
[NAMI gasps] How do you
always make things worse?!
[LUFFY]
This is a good town.
[NAMI]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Everyone's so mad,
just because of
the old mayor guy!
[yelling continues]
[NAMI gasps]
Something tells me
they're not gonna listen
to our side of the story.
We're turning here.
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI] Wait, hold on!
You gotta let me know sooner!
[CITIZEN F]
They ran into the alley!
[LUFFY]
Ha!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[LUFFY grunts]
[NAMI gasps]
Chouchou?!
Doggie?!
‐‐[barking]
‐‐[CITIZENS gasp]
[CITIZEN F]
Hey! Move, Chouchou!
Get outta here!
[CITIZEN D]
Those three are pirates!
[CITIZEN F] You're barking
at the wrong people!
[barking continues]
Why isn't he letting
us pass through?!
Chouchou, get outta here!
[barking]
‐‐Chouchou!
‐‐[barking]
[LUFFY laughs]
[CHOUCHOU growls, barks]
[LUFFY]
Later, doggie! [laughs]
[NAMI sighs]
[NAMI]
That was close.
We only made it
because of Chouchou.
Why do we have to
put up with this?
[LUFFY] Does it matter now?
We're done here anyway.
[NAMI]
\Yeah, Maybe so, but...
[LUFFY]
Hey! Is this your boat?!
It's great!
It's nothing special,
but I guess it'll do.
I stole it from some dumb
pirates a few days back.
[HENCHMAN C]
That's a big mouth you got!
‐‐[NAMI yells]
‐‐[HENCHMEN] He! He!
We been waitin' for
ya, ya little thief.
Never thought you'd run into
us here, now didja, girlie?
[NAMI]
He.He.He.He....
You know these guys?
[NAMI]
Yeah, sort of...
[HENCHMAN A]
Hey, It's not just sort of!
We're bound together by fate!
So, these are your friends.
I guess we'll have to punish
the two of them as well.
It's time you
learned what happens
when you steal other
people's stuff.
Hey, you. Ya' hear me?
Time for your medicine. He. He.
[ZORO]
Huh?
[HENCHMAN gasp, scream]
[BOODLE groans]
Hey, look! He's waking up!
[CITIZEN D] Ah...
Thank goodness he's fine.
[CITIZEN B]
What happened here, Mayor?
[BOODLE sighs]
[BOODLE]
What in the...
[CITIZEN B] It was like
this when we got here...
There were a few pirates when we
arrived, but they all ran off.
Can you tell us what happened?
[gasps] Where are
the young ones?
What's that? Are you talking
about those three kids?
So they're... still alive?!
Those fools. Treating a
senior citizen like that.
How rude.
We drove those pirates
out of town, Mayor.
You don't have to worry
about them anymore.
But it's not enough.
We have to make them pay
for what they've
done to our village.
They deserve to be punished
for destroying the peaceful
town we all worked
so hard to build.
[CITIZEN E]
Yeah! She's right!
[CITIZEN F] There's still
time to go after them.
If we hurry‐‐
‐‐[BOODLE] Shut your mouths!
‐‐[CITIZENS gasp]
I'm the only one who's allowed
to complain about those kids!
I won't let anyone else
bad‐mouth them! You hear me?!
What? Why are you protecting
those pirates, Mayor?
Damn it! They think they can
just disappear and that's that?
Where did they go?!
Well... I think they were
running toward the port.
[BOODLE]
Damn kids!
[BOODLE grumbling]
[BOODLE]
They can't just leave like that!
I have a lot of things I
want to say to you all!
[LUFFY]
All right! Let's get going!
[ZORO]
Can I ask you somethin'?
Isn't that Buggy's
mark on your sail?
Well this did used
to be Buggy's boat.
Think I should change it?
[BOODLE]
Hey! Wait!
Young ones!
It's the old mayor guy.
[BOODLE pants]
[BOODLE]
I was ready to die.
I was ready to die,
filled with despair...
Thanks! Thank you!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
Don't worry about it!
Take it easy!
[BOODLE]
Damn you, young ones.
Damn you, young ones...
I have no words...
[BOODLE]
Huh?
What'd you do, Luffy?! Huh?!
Don't tell me you left that
bag of treasure back there!
Yeah...
That bag was worth around
five million berries, you idiot!
That's right. And they're
gonna need that money
to repair their destroyed town.
But that was my treasure, jerk!
Do you know how hard
I worked to steal it?!
‐‐Why did you do that?
‐‐[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Stop! I can't swim!
[NAMI]
That's the whole idea!
[LUFFY] If you want it,
just go back and get it, then!
[NAMI] I can't do that!
You go get it!
‐‐[LUFFY] No! That's dangerous!
‐‐[ZORO laughing]
I could die, you know?!
[NAMI] I don't care!
And if you do that again,
I really will throw
you in the ocean!
[ZORO]
Well, for better or worse,
looks like we finally have
a navigator in our crew.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[LUFFY]
Wow! We actually found land!
[NAMI] Of course we did!
We followed the map!
And it looks like
there's a village ahead!
[ZORO] Hope there's
a good place to eat.
[LUFFY] Yeah,
I want some meat!
[NAMI]
Forget about food, you guys!
[ZORO]
Hey, who's he?
[LUFFY]
Where?
[NAMI]
He says he's a pirate captain.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"The Honorable Liar?
Captain Usopp!"
[LUFFY] I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!