Good evening, ya buncha filthy jailbirds.
Rattling in your cages, just waiting to die.
Since you ain't got nothin' better to do,
whaddaya say to a good, old- fashioned fight to the death?
And I'll be your judge... right here, right now!
Whoever's left alive gets to see the outside world again,
sailing the sweet seas of freedom as a member of my crew!
Huh?
Take the others but leave that one.
So he's still alive, huh?
The man they call the "Demon Heir."
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove countless souls to the seas.
"Ya want my treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered together in one place.
Now ya just have to find it!"
And thus, began the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
It still haunts me. That was the day that I died.
Same as you.
Am I right?
But now, together, we can take our lives back.
I, Buena Festa, have happened upon a deep secret.
Gold Roger's hidden treasure is within my grasp!
You follow me, and you'll have everything you desire.
I guarantee it.
So let's do this!
We'll usher in a new era with the
greatest party the world has ever seen!
Made by pirates for pirates!
Yeah, we're bringing the Pirates Fest back, baby.
Ahem.
"My dearest pirates, hailing from far and wide,
you are cordially invited to the world's largest banquet,
where we shall share a toast
between allies and enemies alike.
Come as you are, leave as you like,
but you won't want to miss the one and only Pirates Fest.
Sincerely, Buena Festa, Captain of the Festival Pirates."
It's party time!
We're almost there!
I've heard whispers of this
event, but never attended myself.
Every few years, the invitations appear quite
suddenly and then it's off to a world of rare ships,
fine cuisine, deadly weapons, and secret intel!
Every wonder you could dream of gathered
together from all corners of the world!
Like a pirate black market? I'm down with that!
Bet they'll have some good booze, too.
"Also, we have a special event planned this year."
Oh, boy! Is it a treasure hunt?
That it is, my friend. Featuring
a lost relic from Gold Roger!
And it's gonna be ours!
This really is the ultimate party!
They sent us this Eternal Pose,
but why should I believe it's leading
us to a party and not some elaborate trap?
And as for this Gold Roger thing.
The treasure hunt?
Yeah! It's too good to be true!
Buena Festa was the king of all parties.
A famous pirate said to hold many dark secrets.
His network of merchants and informants
would make this festival possible,
but it could also just be an imposter using his name.
The man is long dead, after all.
A dead man and the Pirate King's lost treasure.
Well, we'll figure it out soon enough.
Luffy's all fired up.
So we're going.
A treasure hunt with pirates is gonna be crazy!
Who cares if it's a trap?
It's time to party!
Full speed ahead to the pirate festival!
Marvelous.
The stars of the show are finally starting to line up.
Excuse me, Mr. Festa.
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Monkey D. Luffy.
Havin' fun already, huh?
That's good. I want everyone fired up.
We're celebrating the start of a new era, after all!
Hello, party pirates!
Are you having fun at our pirate festival, or what?!
Now here's a quick little disclaimer.
I'm sure this comes as no surprise,
but anything goes as long as you're here!
That goes for fights, kidnapping,
stealing or whatever else!
The only rule is that you gotta
keep this party secret from the Navy!
Anyone who spills their guts
will be branded the enemy of all pirates,
and we'll chase you to the gates of hell itself
to take our sweet revenge!
Whoo. Scary!
Oh, forgot to introduce myself.
The name is Donald Moderate.
I'll be your host and MC today!
And with me
is the lovely, talented and
widely beloved songstress, Ann!
Hi, everybody!
Oh. If you didn't know, she has Devil Fruit Powers.
Viso-Viso Vision!
Fire! Fire!
The Viso Viso Fruit allows her to transform any image
she touches into a giant-sized, fully functional illusion.
For a short time, at least.
Cool, huh?
Now, it's been 20 long years since the last
Pirates Fest, so you might be wondering why
we brought it back today
and why we decided on this particular island.
It's said that just before the
dawn of the Great Pirate Era,
Gold Roger, the famous King of the Pirates,
discovered this place and hid an invaluable
treasure here for the next generation to find.
He left us with this hint:
"In a deep, lofty darkness, you will find your answer."
Intriguing!
So there you have it, my friends!
A challenge from the King of the Pirates himself!
We've got a powerful lineup of competitors here today,
so let's solve the mystery and find that treasure!
Hey, hurry! Something's happening!
We're late for the party!
Yeah? And who's fault is that?
I told you shopaholics the treasure
hunt was about to start without us.
But you just had to keep stuffing your dumb faces!
You were shopping, too!
But anyway, judging by the turnout,
it looks like this treasure could be the real deal!
All right, then! It's time for a fight!
Don't you worry, my friends!
When it comes to finding hidden
treasure, I've got a sixth sense!
Assist me, Chopper!
Yes, sir!
Let 'em have their fun for now.
Yes. Until they take a good look at the competition.
Before long, this place is gonna be a blood bath.
Hey, Captain!
The Sunny's ready to take off
as soon as you give the word!
Any second now, Franky!
My "Can't Go On Treasure Hunts" disease is flaring up.
Do I need to operate?
What were you doing?
Picking your butts?
How could you let this happen, you buncha morons?!
Don't pin this on me! He was slacking off!
I was with you the entire time!
Less shifting blame and more searching!
You're the one who's running security here!
Indeed!
Who could possibly be more dependable than me?
Why, I'm a Warlord of the Sea, after all!
A living legend known as the Genius Jester,
the one and only, Captain Buggy!
We had 200 security pirates on the job!
Can't they catch one annoying little rodent?
They're gonna dock our pay if he escapes!
Search harder! And be flashy about it!
I knew this wouldn't be easy, but
things are spinning out of control.
That's Straw Hat's ship.
Ah-ha!
You're mine now, Trafalgar Law!
Room!
Shambles!
He's gone!
I don't know what I was expecting.
But even for a pirate festival, this is a lot of pirates.
I wish I could arrest them all.
But that's not likely.
As long as we can capture Buena Festa, we'll be good.
He was a famous pirate way back in Gold Roger's day,
but we thought he'd been swallowed by a Sea King.
This guy is the one who worries me.
Navy Headquarters won't even admit he's alive.
Douglas Bullet.
An escapee from Level 6 of Impel Down.
I don't know what he and Festa want,
but something bad's going down at this party.
What's that?
Something's happening!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Turn the ship around right now! We are done!
Hold on.
Is that...?
Look at the current!
Uh-oh!
Seems like things are getting crazy already!
But what the heck is going on?
Wait. Could it be? The answer to Roger's riddle?
"In a deep, lofty darkness, you will find your answer."
Those ships are definitely falling into a deep darkness.
But the lofty part is... a waterspout?!
Would you look at that!
Well, there you have it!
From the darkness of the deep
sea, it climbs to the heavens above!
Awesome!
It's the shooting sea current!
A Knock-Up Stream!
And what's this?
There's some bubbles, but I don't know why.
Something big is coming!
Something very, very big!
I-I can't believe it!
It's an island!
Or rather, a giant bubble with an island inside of it!
How pretty!
There's no way this is a mere coincidence!
Roger's treasure lies on the island in the sky!
The question is,
how are these courageous pirate
competitors going to make there?
Let's go, Franky!
I thought you'd never ask!
Time for my secret weapon! Would you like to see it?
You bet I would!
Better get out of my way!
What's that I see?
Why, it's the infamous Kid Pirates from the
Worst Generation, shooting to the head of the pack!
Their captain, Eustass Kid, and his crewmate,
"The Massacre Soldier," Killer,
are a force to be reckoned with!
Things are about to start heating up for our competitors!
This is the greatest treasure
hunt the world has ever seen!
Nuh-uh! 'Cause this isn't a
treasure hunt, it's a treasure fight!
Go crazy!
I'm surprised you're buying into this, Kid.
You expect me to lose?
A-pa-pa!
But Captain Kid's not the only one
with his eyes on the prize in this battle!
The On-Air Pirates are grooving their way to the lead!
And there's their captain, Scratchman Apoo!
Yo! What's the big hurry? Hm?
Uh-oh! Better look out!
The Drake Pirates are comin' in hot!
The X Drake is taking no prisoners!
Huh. The Red Flag, and the Sea Roar, too.
Next up is the only female
captain in the Worst Generation!
Leading the Bonney Pirates, it's Bonney the Glutton!
Gimme more pizza, now!
Hey, watch it, you dumb oaf!
Pardon me, young lady, I didn't see you there.
The Fallen Monk Pirates have muscled their way in!
And there's their captain, Urouge!
Yikes!
It's a surprise attack from the Firetank
Pirates, lead by their captain, Capone "Gang" Bege!
I got a whole stinkin' army here.
And the Hawkins Pirates are right behind!
Is he reading fortunes in the middle of a battle?
If you dare lay a finger on
Mister Luffy, you're gonna die!
Everyone, look! Pay attention to me, too!
Hey! Save some intros for me!
Fine!
The next two, neck and neck, are Bartolomeo
the Cannibal and Cavendish the White Horse!
And right behind them...
Eh, looks like a bunch of nobodies.
You've never heard of us?!
The pirates have reached the Knock-Up
Stream and they're racing to the skies,
but what awaits them on the floating island?
The treasure.
It's up in the sky?
Keep watching.
You can handle things from here.
Report the situation via Transponder Snail.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm infiltrating Festa's hideout
while everyone's distracted.
We get the ringleader, we end this.
I kept you in suspense, didn't I?
Well, the wait is over!
This is the Thousand Sunny's new flying equipment!
The Emperor Penguin Form!
So cool!
Now, step on it! We have to catch up!
Not so fast, Straw Hats!
Long time no see, rubber boy!
Now hand Law over to me!
Oh, it's you.
Are you bros ready?
Coup de Burst!
Buggy!
Here we go!
They're flying!
The Straw Hat pirates are literally soaring to the lead!
No surprise, since their captain loves to make a scene!
He's a man with a 1.5 billion bounty on his head...
...Monkey D. Luffy!
With the Straw Hats flying into the fray, this high-speed
hunt for treasure is really starting to heat up!
I'm cheering for you and your crew, Straw Hat!
Mister Luffy!
Don't steal the spotlight from me!
That's cheating, Straw Hat!
We're blasting straight through! Let's go!
Marvelous.
Now, friend, I think it's time for your part of the plan.
You ready to party?
Are you kidding me?
The Straw Hats have taken a decisive lead!
Can anybody stop them?
Always gotta keep it interesting now, don'tcha?
Splashdown complete!
I wasn't scared.
That move gave us a good lead.
But we'll have to watch out for attacks from behind now.
Franky, that was too cool!
That's the point, bro!
All right! Let's find us some hidden treasure!
I'm so ready!
Is something the matter?
Huh?
Hm?
Traffy!
Hello, Straw Hat.
My first aid kit!
What happened to you?
We'll fix you up.
No, don't bother.
I'll be leaving here soon.
And if you value your lives,
then you'll be doing the same thing.
It's Festa. He...
The man who's hosting this party?
Yeah, he's plotting something.
And he's got some dangerous friends helping him out.
I've already evacuated my crew.
This whole island is about to become a war zone.
Well, you heard the man! It's time to go!
Hey, take it easy!
Traffy, please, let me patch you up!
Forget I was here.
I don't need your help to see this through to the end.
Don't be ridiculous! Look at yourself!
Don't worry. I'll make 'em pay for this.
Jeez! That didn't take long!
The guys behind us are catching up!
What should we do now?
We need a plan!
We'll keep pushing forward!
But we'll help Traffy, too.
Chopper, take good care of him.
You got it!
Hey, I said I'm leaving!
Then I'll come with you.
We shouldn't run away.
You mentioned Festa's "dangerous friends," right?
And some nefarious plot, as well?
If this is some sort of trap,
then lives could be at stake.
Besides, you've piqued my curiousity.
Any objections?
I don't mind, as long as I can come as your bodyguard.
If it's a covert mission, I might come in handy!
That works for me.
Hold on!
Sounds like my kinda party.
And my nightmare!
I was promised treasure, so keep your eyes peeled, 'kay?
Anything for you!
We're teamin' up again, huh?
Not like I can stop you.
You guys need a ride, right?
I got your back.
What happens when we land?
Then we all die!
Well, that's not anything new for me.
Time for Mil Fleur!
Nice one, Robin. That was close.
If anything happens, call us on the transponder snail.
Roger.
Let me treat you first, Traffy.
Sorry. There's no time.
We're heading underneath the island,
and putting a stop to Festa!
The island's dead ahead!
I'm taking that hidden treasure and nobody can stop me!
The competitors are pushing towards the finish line,
but it looks like the Straw Hats will maintain their lead!
That's it! Almost there!
But how are we supposed to land?!
Guess we'll just have to wait and see!
They've reached the top of the Knock-Up stream,
high above the island!
Now they're coming down! What a sight!
Pirate ships scattered across the sky like birds!
But what happens next? Someone has to take the lead!
Ah-ha! There go the Straw Hats, hitting the bubble!
And they're in!
Time to find that treasure!
Ha!
I see it! Far up on the ledge!
It's a giant galleon, sparkling in the sun!
Wait! Sparkling? Could it be?
Yes! It's overflowing with treasure!
Oodles of it! A veritable mountain!
Mountains of treasure? Be still, my heart!
You ready?
When am I not ready?
That old chest looks fishy.
That's the one we want, I'm sure of it!
I've got a nose for treasure, and that smells heavenly!
Luffy! There's a little old wooden chest inside the ship!
Forget the other stuff! That
has to be Gold Roger's treasure!
Cool! Got it!
Right! You heard her! Grab that prize!
Go help them, you little coward!
...Don't be a fool!
...Huh?
I'm a sniper, remember? I'm here for support.
Yep. Coward.
This just keeps getting better!
Outta my way!
Hurry to the ship!
This is it!
The final stretch where the true
battle for the treasure begins!
You go on ahead!
All right, thanks!
Hope you're ready for a fight.
Hello, Pirate Hunter.
Boom!
What's goin' down?
Get outta my way!
Boy, you're crazy, runnin' wild.
I'm gonna put you in your place with style!
Better make this one quick!
Too late!
You keep fighting! Leave the treasure to me!
Wait a sec!
Don't wanna play fair?
This is a battle between pirates.
There's no such thing as fair.
All right, then. No mercy.
Outta my way! Comin' through!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Hey! Get back here!
It's the strongest versus the
strongest in a battle of captains!
Who will lay claim... Uh!
Who will lay claim to victory?
Better not blink!
Time to move out and surround 'em!
C'mon, boys!
Move it, chumps!
Uh?
Like candy from a baby.
Why you! Get down here!
Captain, can you speed it up?
If we attempt to steal it, our chances are 40 percent.
Ya ready? Here we go!
Special Attack Green Star!
Impact Wolf!
Thunderbolt Tempo! Eat this!
Time for Franky Radical Beam!
Move it, move it, move it!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
That's it!
A lotta strong pirates today!
Well, keep it comin'!
Shush, they'll notice us!
Who needs a security gig if we can score some treasure?
These guys are monsters!
Suck on that!
The secret base is right up ahead but be careful.
That's where I got ambushed the last time I was here.
Uhh...
You couldn't hold it in a second?!
I don't even have butt cheeks!
Would you shut it?
My apologies, Sanji.
Let's stop and scope out the area.
Ya got this?
Of course.
I can help, too.
Don't worry,
I wouldn't dream of causing trouble for my sponsors.
Everything's going smoothly.
All the pirates're lined up on the island.
Just in time for the Buster Call.
What's wrong?
Well, spit it out!
A Buster Call? That means...
Yeah, the Navy's gonna eliminate
everything and everyone on the island.
We'll be burnt to ash before we
even have a chance to fight back.
That's mass murder!
They want us dead that bad?
Hard to say, but we need to warn everyone.
Straw Hats!
How do you know about this place?!
Let us answer before you attack, please.
Careful, Brook.
His weapon's made of Sea Prism Stone.
Can you blame me?
Seems like half the pirates I
fight have Devil Fruit Powers.
And since I can't throw all
of you into the sea, this'll do!
I can handle this on my own.
Find Luffy and tell him the news.
You're not going anywhere, ya punks!
Take Robin with you and go!
Just try it!
Get away from her!
Haki, huh?
Out with it, already.
What are you plotting?
You got some nerve asking us that!
Ooh! This is a close one!
The pirates are dropping left and right in this bloodbath!
But for those who refuse to submit, the fight rages on!
Outta my way!
I'll quit when you do!
Too late, losers!
While you were busy punching each other,
I got Gold Roger's treasure!
Why'd it have to be that clown?
Buggy!
If you want that treasure, then fight me!
Ehh?
Stupid, rubber bastard!
Never mind, just run!
Get back here!
After that clown! He's got the treasure!
Yes, sir!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Don't be sore losers!
Now, let's see what you left us, Roger.
Knowing you, it's gotta be good!
What the...?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, is this thing for real?
The treasure chest has been claimed by one of
the Seven Warlords, the Genius Jester, Buggy!
But the other pirates are still...
What now?
Uh-oh!
The bubble popped!
Someone help, please!
Come back, you belong to me!
That doesn't look good!
This is not part of the program!
Hang in there, Sunny!
Luffy!
I never asked for this!
His Iron Arm is as powerful as ever.
Twenty years in prison is a long time,
but I had faith it wouldn't slow him down much.
Now make sure everything else is in place.
You all right, Kid?
C'mon, High Priest, you gotta get up!
Well, this is a big mess!
Captain!
The Shadow of Death is not upon us yet.
What in the hell was that?
Hang in there.
I thought I had the treasure for sure.
Captain Buggy!
Hooray, I'm not dead. And I got the treasure, too!
No way.
This actually exists?
A galleon suddenly appeared, took
to the sky, and destroyed the island!
Chaos!
Where has the treasure gone in all of this wreckage?
That sucked. Damnit! What the hell was that?
Kid.
Yeah?!
This isn't funny.
It can't be.
Usopp, no!
This stained sea is a battlefield and a grave.
Let him go, right now!
Luffy!
You bastard.
You the jerk who beat up Traffy?
I don't like you.
Oh? You want more?
I have a feeling this is about to get ugly.
Should I know that man?
Bah! I thought I was dead for sure!
Oh, you're not?
Do I look dead?
Who did this? Did someone take my treasure?
'Cause I will kill them!
Huh? Gah! Why's he here?
Do you know him?
Yeah. We used to be on the same crew.
That is to say, Roger's crew.
His name's Douglas Bullet.
He's a beast.
Used to be as strong as Rayleigh, even.
Rayleigh? The Pirate King's right-hand man?
All right. Round two, then.
Whoa, what's that?
Heh.
No. No! Ah!
This is bad!
They found us!
I thought this party was kept secret from the Navy!
What gives, Festa?!
I thought you had this stuff under control!
No way. The Navy?
They brought a whole fleet! A big one!
Run away!
Wait for me!
Which one of you snitched on us?
The first fleet of battleships has arrived.
They're right on time, sir.
We just received a message from the Navy.
"We appreciate your cooperation."
Ah. That must be Momonga.
What now, pirates? It's up to you.
So are you gonna fight? Or are you gonna run? Heh.
Ugh! Festa sold us out, I bet!
Sorry excuse for a pirate!
Uh?
Whoa, hey, wait for me!
No way out now.
He got Roger's treasure. Isn't that enough?
I don't care who you are.
Nobody messes with my crew.
I hope you're ready for a fight.
Crew, you say?
He couldn't even protect that treasure.
You're better off without him.
Heh.
I heard you kids from the Worst Generation are strong.
You came to fight for Roger's treasure, didn't you?
Then come at me.
He's got the Conqueror's Haki.
Quite the demon, aren't you?
I am not down with this.
This is interesting.
Something wrong? Too scared to move?
Come at me... I'm right here.
Don't worry about the rest of them.
Let's do this!
Zoro!
Hm?
As soon as we can get in touch with Sanji, we'll
meet up and plan an escape with the rest of the crew!
It won't be easy getting past all those
battleships, so I'm open to suggestions!
I can protect Usopp. You watch the Sunny.
Roger that!
Mister Zoro!
If you need help, I'm here for ya! I'm always here for ya!
Ugh! Your ship!
Heh. Glad you're here!
All right! Come with me!
Zoro! Wrong way! Wrong way!
No, stop!
Mister Zoro, you're perfect just how you are!
I've come to help as well!
You'd better show some gratitude!
Run before this gets ugly!
You break out of your cage and you think
you can pick a fight with us, old man?
We'll send you packing!
Your choice.
One at a time, or all of you at once.
The stage has been set.
Ten minutes to have your fun out there.
I know they don't call you the "Demon Heir" for nothing.
Entertain me.
Something bad must've happened.
Usopp.
What was that Vice Admiral doing?
It's like he was sneaking in.
Just like old times.
Hello there, Miss All Sunday.
Crocodile. Why are you here?
For the treasure?
It must be something important
if it captured your attention.
Something that could change the world,
if I had to guess.
As perceptive as ever.
I will say that Douglas Bullet is
involved, if that gives you a hint.
From the Tragedy of Galzburg?
The pirate who caused that massacre? Is he here?
Yes, and as you know, his power is a bit of a nuisance.
What do you want from me?
Nothing at all.
You on the other hand, I need.
I have a plan.
Now come along.
Why're you snooping around here?
What are you plotting?
You're one to talk!
You're making a Buster Call?!
Huh? What're talking about?
Cu-lick!
Smoker, it's an emergency!
Bullet showed up and the whole island's in chaos!
He took Roger's treasure.
And now he's about to fight Straw Hat!
So that's how you want this?
Captain Buggy! What's the plan?
Clearing out, of course!
You're clearin' out all those Navy battleships?
I'm with you, Captain!
Let's do it!
You'd almost think I put wax in their ears.
Never mind the Navy.
Bullet's worse than the whole fleet combined.
The sooner we get outta here the better.
Even if that treasure was One Piece itself,
it wouldn't be worth facing that bastard.
You guys stay out of my way!
Get in line, Straw Hat. I'm fighting him first!
Gonna sit and chat all day?
Demon Face!
Bam!
Boom!
Huh?
Get off!
Let's see how tough you are once I turn you into a baby!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Hey, stupid!
Get outta my way!
Why don't the both of yous clear out?
Here comes Big Father!
Awesome!
Hm?
Boom! Pow!
Huh?
Retribution!
I'm gonna crush you!
Gum-Gum....
...Red Hawk!
I can beat him on my own! Y'see that?
You got to him first. Big deal.
You brats are pretty good, but not good enough.
Training, strategy, determination.
I find you lacking in so many areas.
So let me to give you a demonstration
of what the real deal looks like.
You won't forget.
Why're you here? What the hell do you want?
To be the strongest in the world.
Glad you're taking this seriously now.
Don't die on me too quickly.
I wanna clear out some of those Navy Ships.
Make an escape path for Usopp and Luffy.
You look after the Sunny!
Mister Zoro trusts me!
I'll protect the Sunny with my life!
I promise, you can count on me!
Let's see, which one of these ships do we cut down first?
It's Fujitora!
We got the boss already, huh?
Make no mistake.
The others may follow me if they so choose,
but I've come to fight for my own sense of justice.
Capture every pirate in sight!
Admiral Fujitora will lead the way!
Ugh! That's the last thing I need right now.
Straw Hats! Heed my words!
Please save us!
Save yourself! We've got enough problems!
I caught Robin's scent!
Robin!
You made it!
I was so worried!
How sweet of you.
Smoker's gone?
Yeah. I guess.
Something ended up spooking
him, then he took off in a flash.
Convenient, but it does trouble me.
Wait, did you lose Law?
It might take a moment to explain.
Huh?
All right, let's split into groups again.
Chopper. Brook. You check up on Luffy.
Let him know there's a Buster Call coming.
Right.
You're with me, Robin.
All right.
Listen, everyone! Luffy's
gonna get that treasure for sure.
So let's believe in him and form our plan around that.
Right!
We're... toys to him.
You get it?
To become King of the Pirates,
you'll need to be as strong as me.
As strong as you?
I'll be even stronger! I'll do whatever it takes to win!
Now, Fourth Gear!
Form of Snake Man!
Ha! You're using your Devil
Fruit Power with that much Haki?
You're gonna burn out in no time at all.
Then I guess I should hurry!
Ha!
Run! Python!
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Jet Culverin!
Gum-Gum...
...Black Mamba!
No wonder your bounty's so high. You got some spunk, kid.
Come on, don't tell me it's over already!
That's right! 'Cause I'm ending this!
Gum-Gum...
With talk like that, you better not let me down!
I want everything you've got and then some!
...King Cobra!
"Former Crewmate of the Pirate King Defeated!"
"Straw Hat Luffy truly is the Fifth Emperor!"
That would make one hell of a headline!
Not a bad start.
But this party's got plenty of twists and turns.
On Standby! Brachio Head! Change!
Iron... Pirate!
General Franky!
Run away!
Capture every last one!
That pirate. What's the idea,
teamin' up with someone like him?
They didn't volunteer that information, so I can't say.
Perhaps we must carry it through before we
can decide if this war is worthwhile or not.
You're starting a war?
Barrier Bulls!
Blade of Beauty! Saint Exupéry!
Y'think I'm scared of a bunch of chumps like you? Ha!
Show 'em what's what, Boss!
Now! Slow-Slow Bea...
That's enough of you!
Stop the ship!
You moron!
Captain Buggy dove straight into the front lines!
Is everyone in the entire crew stupid?
Brace yourselves!
Zeus Breeze Tempo!
You're pretty tough indeed, Straw Hat.
I like to see a strong pirate.
But if I'm gonna be the strongest...
...I have to kill all of you.
The road to the top is paved in blood, after all.
Go be the strongest somewhere else.
I won't let you lay another finger on my crew!
Nothing but drivel.
The sea is a battlefield!
Power's the only thing that matters in this world.
What the hell?
This is my ship, the Catapult.
Unlike any other. Constructed of solid iron.
Filled to the brim with weapons.
Union Armada! Engage!
A Devil Fruit?
I am a Combinable Human who ate the Clank Clank Fruit!
I can combine all sorts of objects
and transform them into something deadly!
My body has been honed to perfection,
but this power is even greater!
You mean, all this time he was only toying with us?
What's the plan now?
The weak cannot survive in these turbulent seas.
If they try, they end up like your "friend."
You can only rely on yourself. Cut off anyone useless.
You don't know anything.
If you don't have friends, then what's the point anyway?
Don't you get it?
I see. Seems you're hopeless, after all.
If old Whitebeard couldn't survive, then how can you?
He saw his crew as a family,
but all they really were was a weakness,
just like your "friends."
It was the same with Roger.
If you're dead, then it's over... you've lost!
Your friends are a chain around your
neck... one that hangs you in the end.
My strength is mine alone.
Because there's only room for one at the top!
I'm about to show you how wrong you are!
Ha!
If you wanna talk big, then let's
see if you can take this treasure back!
And let me tell you before you die,
this isn't a fake.
It really is Roger's treasure.
Having what's in this box
is the same as having One Piece itself.
One Piece. No way.
Here lies your grave.
Now struggle to the bitter end!
Gravity Blade! Raging Tiger!
One Thousand Eighty Caliber Phoenix!
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
By the time those jerks get backup, we'll be home free!
Not him, too!
They sent the Warlords to help us?
Fine, then. Commence attack! Pacifistas!
Negative Hollow!
I'm nothing but a lowly slug.
Not very cute are you? Pity.
Uh? What was that?
How unsightly!
Who put this thing in my path?
I'll just have to remove it.
It's really her! Oh, boy!
Empress and Warlord of the Sea! Boa Hancock, in the flesh!
I shall do whatever I so please,
and you shall allow it all, without objection.
Why you ask? Because I am beautiful. Any questions?
This should be easy with your help!
Now go give 'em hell!
Silence! Lead me to Luffy!
The Warlords are so cool!
And we've got three of 'em here. I can't believe it!
Are you kidding me?
Y'think I'd stick around for this?
Not even if I had nine lives! Later!
Admirals and Warlords?
Are you trying to start a war over there, Festa?
You're close, but not quite.
That's the Navy for ya.
Had a feeling they'd go all out.
They sure want that treasure, don't they?
Sorry, brats. It's over!
Look out!
I'll grind this lesson into your bones!
You okay?
Killer!
You'll pay!
This strength cannot be reached
when you're shackled by dependence!
And those who lack it will surely lose everything.
Do you see now?
Many will lose before the battle is done,
but only one can win in the end.
Only one can be King!
An Eternal Pose?
That leads to Laugh Tale?
And this is no hoax?
A scoop like this could flip
the world upside down, you know!
It's true.
The treasure is a guide that leads straight to Laugh Tale.
The island where One Piece rests.
There was a shortcut all along,
but that idiot Roger buried it in the darkness.
It's the spark that will light the way to a brand-new era.
A festival of madness, burning bright!
Now die.
Hm?
This fight's not over yet. Not while I'm here!
What's this nonsense?
Not only are you weak, but stupid as well.
Huh?
My captain is risking his life.
I have to return the favor, don't I?
This is no time to be a coward!
All bark and no bite.
A yapping dog.
With a foolish master.
A festival invites one to abandon restraint.
And my festival
will plunge the world into a state of madness!
We'll call it a stampede!
You won't wanna miss it.
Hmm...
Turning into a real mess, I must say.
Admiral! I have a report!
Huh. So the treasure was real.
Can't ignore that, can we?
Let's show 'em what we're made of!
There's lots of us. We got this!
Go!
One! Two!
Django!
Kimono Sleeve Cage!
Lock!
Forget these guys. Go for Bullet.
Help me, Hina.
Whoa, what's that outfit? Is there something I don't know?
Smoker! There you are!
I need some answers before we go.
Well, for starters, HQ is hiding the truth from us.
Huh?
It has to do with Roger's lost treasure.
From what I've seen, depending on
what it is, they may do something crazy.
I see. You're acting on your own.
Suck it, Marine! Ah!
Can you just do your mission, please?
I can do both.
Outta the way!
What is this stuff?
You're all under arrest!
Let's make this quick!
Buggy.
Why're you here?
Watch where you're aiming that, ya big dope!
Not you guys!
Uh. I mean, I'm a Warlord, you can't treat me like this!
We're on the same side!
Wait a sec. You saw what was inside that chest, right?
He did?
You have to tell us what it was! This could be bad!
What?! Isn't it bad enough already?!
Just save yourself and get the hell out of here!
Stop squirming and spit it out!
I can't breathe!
Smoker!
All right, all right, fine, I'll tell you!
It's an Eternal Pose! An Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale!
It can't be.
Charge!
Capture the pirates!
The course of this battle is changing.
Let us postpone our duel for now.
Huh?
Farewell, then. You may consider this a parting gift.
Get back here!
That doesn't look good.
A meteor?
Retreat! Retreat!
Mister Zoro, help!
Nine mountains and eight seas make one world!
Huh?
One thousand worlds make one chiliocosm!
One chiliocosm to the power of three,
and there's nothing I can't cut!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
The Billion-fold World.
Trichiliocosm!
We're okay!
Not okay!
There's no time.
What?
Anything beyond this is outside of my contract.
Let's go, Ghost Girl.
Uh! Since when do I answer to you?
And next time you slice up a meteor, warn me first!
That startled me!
We'd better hurry!
Luffy! Where are you?
Usopp! Are you here?
Ready! Fire!
You wanna fight me? Are you sure?
Fine.
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Pull out your soldiers and your ships!
He's trying to gather us all in one spot!
Too late now!
Have a taste of my awakened power!
I've been waiting for this!
What's that?
The awakened power of my Devil
Fruit extends to the world itself!
There's nothing I can't absorb.
Nothing I can't reassemble!
What's happening?
It's a bunch of purple stuff!
He's absorbing our ships!
How are you supposed to fight that thing?
This keeps getting worse!
No! It can't be!
He's trying to trap us here on the island!
Luffy.
So what'cha gonna do now, Navy?
Only got one choice, I'd say!
I'll crush you.
The vice admirals are down in one shot!
Run away!
It's gonna drop on us!
Ultimate Faust!
He's splitting the island in two!
Twenty-four years ago, I lost to the
Navy and was imprisoned in Impel Down.
I asked myself then:
"How can I obtain power so overwhelming
that I'll never lose to anyone ever again?
How can I surpass Gold Roger?
How can I become the strongest in the world?"
Heh.
Are you here, Fleet Admiral?
I've got the Eternal Pose that'll
lead you straight to One Piece.
Come and fight me, just like
you did before! See if you can win!
At least the treasure is close.
I have no idea what's going on.
There must have been hundreds of ships out there.
I can't believe he swallowed nearly all
of them with that awakened power of his.
That power's a nuisance, but his Haki is worse.
Every inch of that giant body of his
seems to be coated in Armament Haki.
Without a good plan, we're finished.
There has to be something.
He made all that with his Devil Fruit power, right?
So if Luffy takes him out,
it'll disappear and we can bail.
Then we'll just have to put our faith in him.
What now? We're trapped down here!
Bullet still has the Pirate King's treasure,
but we can't stop him 'cause he swallowed our ships
and got all big and now we don't know what to do!
Ahh!
Cu-lick.
I can see that for myself.
It's pretty hard to miss.
It's the Fleet Admiral!
I see. An awakened power.
I didn't think he'd grown quite so strong.
Listen, Borsalino.
There are some troublemakers
looking to complicate this matter,
but evil must be eliminated thoroughly,
till nothing but ash remains.
If they want it so bad, give 'em a Buster Call.
Marvelous!
You really are somethin', Bullet!
I bet the rest of my life on
you and it was the right choice!
That bastard Roger launched
the Dawn of the Great Pirate Era.
It was the biggest festival the world's ever seen.
It's not fair.
Even Buena Festa had no way to top that.
It took time.
But now I have a weapon.
I can make a whole new era.
A better one.
I'll bury Roger's legacy!
This world's future belongs to me!
Is that really the best you can do?
Come on, Fleet Admiral! I know you're tougher than this!
Give me all you've got!
There's no turning back now!
A Buster Call is the symbol of the
World Government's absolute power.
If Bullet challenges that power and overcomes it,
he'll prove he's the strongest, without a doubt!
The whole world will get turned upside down!
Now that's a scoop!
All right.
You buncha underworld scumbags.
We possess the key to One Piece.
An Eternal Pose to lead us to Laugh Tale.
So in other words...
It's time for the pirates to die and you along with them!
Absurd!
Roger is dead, and his era, too.
The tides that swept across the world grow still.
The pirates who command these seas will be buried!
The new era, forged in the fires of war,
will be my masterpiece!
An endless festival!
A world-wide stampede of hysteria!
You want my treasure? Come and get it!
Steal it if you can!
Wealth, fame, power.
All the world has to offer is right here!
I promised hysteria, didn't I?
And there you have it.
D'you see this, Roger?
It's the end of your dull little era of treasure hunting.
I killed it.
I surpassed you!
The treasure's in plain sight!
They'll fight, and they'll bleed, in a festival
where only the strong survive!
That's my masterpiece!
This is my era!
Not only has he invited a full-scale battle with the Navy,
he's made a declaration of war on all the world's pirates.
That may sound like suicide, but it seems their
only purpose is to destroy the current world order
and plunge everything into chaos.
Douglas Bullet is our main target.
He was a war orphan born in the
Grand Line's militarist nation Galzburg.
He served as a child soldier and
quickly became recognized as a hero.
However, his superiors grew fearful of
his strength and tried to have him killed.
Bullet, enraged by this, retaliated so fiercely
that the entire nation was destroyed.
After that, he took to the sea and challenged
Gold Roger, apparently as a means of testing himself.
Roger was victorious, and eventually,
Bullet joined his crew, at least for a time.
Eventually, the Navy caught up to him,
and the then-Admiral Sengoku, along with...
Betrayed by his superiors,
then betrayed by his friends, as well.
How could he trust anyone?
How could he do anything except fight in
order to protect his place in the world?
But Roger taught him defeat was not the end.
That there were other people in this world
Bullet could still put his faith in.
And so he became the "Demon Heir,"
supporting the very man that had bested him.
Though he never gave up on challenging Roger.
But then Roger died,
and Bullet didn't know what to do.
He returned to a life of violence and death.
Losing his rival and dream in one fell
swoop, he became a monster without purpose.
Of course, we couldn't let him run wild.
But the only way to stop him, unfortunately,
was a Buster Call.
We can't sympathize with him.
He's trying to drag the world into a war.
It's our job to stop that from happening.
No, you're right.
But the thought of spilling so much blood a second time.
Well, it doesn't put a smile on my face.
I can't help but wonder.
If Roger could stop him before,
could another pirate like him come along and do the same?
Did ya see that, Luffy? He ran away.
The bastard got one good look at me and fled in terror.
I say he's not worth it. Let him go for today.
Please, Luffy. Don't die.
You gotta stand up again.
It can't end here.
Our journey isn't over.
You think I'm giving up?!
Not a chance!
I won't rest
until the day that Luffy becomes the King of the Pirates!
The Chill of the Underworld: Soul Solid!
Usopp!
Are you okay?
That looks bad. I'll fix you right up!
Forget about me. Treat Luffy.
He lost a lotta blood back there.
But if I leave you, then I...
Chopper, please.
All right, then.
We gotta move, Robin. This place isn't gonna hold.
Here we go! This is all we need!
Retreat! Everybody, pull out, right now!
Disengage and go!
Admiral Kizaru says you have five minutes!
Get to the remaining ships, immediately!
Pull out!
I need more details. That doesn't make any sense!
I'm sorry, ma'am, but we don't have
time to stand here and discuss this!
The Admiral ordered a Buster Call!
Are you kidding me?
Admiral Kizaru's second fleet is on standby at sea
and will begin a barrage of cannon fire in five minutes!
That's so soon!
Anyone who stays behind is as good as dead!
We still have enough ships to retreat on if we hurry!
He's lost his mind.
Attention!
Everyone retreat immediately!
Retreat! Back to the ships, now!
Five minutes isn't nearly enough time!
What's going on? This is nuts!
Don't push!
Finally.
You decided I'm worthy of your Buster Call.
But I won't lose again!
I'll prove that I am the only
absolute power in this world!
And when I'm done, the Four Emperors will die next.
Then I'll be King!
I'm not happy either, but we have to go!
Go on without me.
No way! If you're staying, then I am!
I'll stay, too... I can still fight!
Uh. Me, too, I guess.
You're a lost cause.
Hina! Let me go!
We can't just leave him here!
Smoker! Help!
All I gotta do is steal Roger's treasure from Bullet.
I'm not gonna let our own men get caught in the crossfire.
I'll put an end to this stupid operation before that.
All right, you filthy pirates.
It's time to put an end to your party!
Heat Haze!
I agree that Bullet needs to be taken care of, Marine.
But there's no way you can pull that off on your own.
Revolutionaries are here, too?
If I recall, you're Straw Hat's friend.
Older brother, actually.
I know he can be quite a handful,
but take it easy on the kid.
First, you get outta my way!
Let's hurry!
Pull out! To the shore!
Look at that!
The Navy's freakin' out down there!
Miss Nami!
Let us help! What's next?
We can't make our move until Luffy gets back here.
For now, just keep the faith
and see if anyone else needs you!
You are such a boss, Miss Nami!
Praise me later, just go!
Yes, ma'am!
Where are you, Luffy?
There has to be some sort of clue.
It's his red shirt!
Luffy, are you in there?
I'll rescue you! Be brave!
Huh?
Don't touch me, you cur!
Hey, Chopper. That you?
Yeah, I gotcha, don't worry.
We're lucky we found you when we did!
You and Usopp were in terrible shape!
This has turned into a real mess.
And we've got bad news.
The Navy's about to do a Buster
Call and blow up the whole island.
That guy ate a bunch of ships
and got huge and beat everyone up!
And we still haven't heard from the rest of the crew.
Thanks, Chopper.
You can put me down now.
Huh?
Wait, are you sure about this?
You guys head back to the Sunny, okay?
And don't worry. I'll be fine.
Luffy.
Usopp.
Hey, thanks for saving me back there.
Just hold on a little bit longer...
I'm sorry!
Every time... when it really matters...
...I'm useless.
I'm not strong enough at all.
I just...
I don't even deserve to be on your crew!
I'm so sorry, Luffy!
I tried!
I just want to...
Hey, hang in there!
It's okay! That's enough!
Chopper, take care of him for me.
You're going?
We haven't lost yet, okay, Usopp?
So instead of being sorry, hold out for a victory.
Time to go!
With your power versus mine,
this fight will go on forever!
Then you'll just have to give up so I can do my job!
Coming through! Watch out!
Thank you for leading the way.
Now, can you two tell me where to find Luffy?
Another Warlord?
And another one!
Do you wanna tell me what you three are planning?
First of all, calm down.
And second, we're not planning anything...
or at least not planning anything together.
Huh?
I've got business with Festa, assuming we survive.
Everyone shut up!
We're gonna get blown up if we don't book it!
You can work out your stupid problems later!
No one cares!
There is only one thing that matters here!
I inquired about Luffy's whereabouts
and I demand an answer!
What is your damage, lady?! Get off of me!
Huh?
Time is up. Out of my way.
This conversation's over.
Not the most dependable alliance, I suppose.
Huh?
If you don't wanna die, listen to me.
I have a strategy that should
break Bullet out of that shell of his.
You tryin' to be flashy?
I already told you, the only
way to survive is to run away!
Oh, damn it. Sea Prism Stone.
I'm listening.
We'll only have one shot.
His punch can split an island in half.
You'll have to follow me closely.
Following a pirate on some suicide mission?
No thank you!
I'm telling you, there's no other way.
I'll just do this on my own.
Wait a sec.
It's Luffy!
Where are you, Bullet?!
So you survived after all, huh?
Now that's what I'm talking about!
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Were you trying to fly straight into his fist?
Luffy!
Oh, how I've longed to see you!
That was some punch!
Please, just look at me!
Hey, Hancock. Long time no see!
Have you been okay?
Ah! Even injured, he's still worried about me!
I can die without regret.
Oh, Traffy! Hey, pal. You're looking better!
I'll be better when this is done.
Let's team up.
I've got a plan to drag Bullet out.
Whoa, really? Sounds great!
Hey! I didn't even explain!
Sabo! And Smokey!
'Sup, Luffy?
All right, let's do it!
Let me warn you.
If we blow this, we're all as good as dead.
Why would we blow it? We got an awesome team here.
And there's no use worrying, anyway.
Huh?
You work out the complicated stuff, Traffy.
You're good at that.
As long as I get to punch him.
All right. Guess I'll help you.
I'll follow you anywhere, my love, just name the place.
There's no time to discuss it, anyway.
Let's go!
Well, that's a sight!
A pirate, a Marine, Warlords, and a Revolutionary.
Quite the ragtag group you've got.
Well, it ain't gonna change a thing!
Straw Hat, not yet!
Luffy!
I'm coming for you!
Dammit, if you're gonna agree to
my plan, at least hear me out first!
Well, you can tell me, at least.
Bullet's Haki is our biggest obstacle here.
But all we have to do is make a crack.
I'll take care of that with my power.
Then I need you guys to attack the
opening and whittle down his outer shell.
You really think that's gonna be enough?
The fewer things he controls, the weaker he is.
It won't be easy, but I think we can finish him
off before he can build his armor a second time.
I can only make that crack once, though.
Doesn't sound like much of a plan, but what can I say?
Now, Gum-Gum!
I like your pluck, kid, but come on,
that's not gonna cut it!
Oh, no!
Could someone stop him?
Moron. He'll never learn.
He really is strong.
Guess I can't beat him like that, after all!
Okay, then.
You're nothing but a bunch of insects.
But that's fine, I'm happy crushing you all!
The Navy, pirates, or anyone
who dares to stand against me.
I'll eradicate every last one of you!
Strong as he was, even Roger
wasn't able to accomplish that!
Then everyone will know I'm the strongest!
Spread out!
Follow Straw Hat!
When I use my power, that's the sign!
If you're Luffy's friends, then I can trust you!
Friend might be a strong word.
And this is gonna play out, just like you said?
Are we doin' this or not?
Quit your yapping and hurry up.
Fine. As planned,
I'll provoke his transformation, and you... Hey!
Not once, but twice you struck him!
A crime that you shall pay for a thousand-fold!
Even death is too great a mercy for one such as you!
Tch! Can't rely on anyone!
I'll strike you down!
Perfume Femur.
Magna!
He's harder than I thought!
I hope you've enjoyed yourselves,
because it's all about to come crashing down!
Actually, this might work out just fine!
Pathetic.
Ground Death!
And Sables!
Crocodile?
After all this time, you're still just a pile of junk!
This is a surprise!
Well, if you came here to die, too, then be my guest!
All right, Room!
Huh?
And Shambles!
Seems you're all brawn and no brains.
Now time for the real fight.
If I wanna beat his power, this is all I've got!
Clever, but a petty trick like
this will barely even slow me down!
You think I can't absorb the debris again?
My Armament Haki is coming back already!
That's our cue!
All right, Marine. Let's go!
I don't take orders from you!
White Blow!
Burning Dragon Claw Fist!
Flame Dragon King!
What?
Nice, Smokey!
You little!
I thought we made a good team!
Still not enough!
Ow. Ow. Damn it!
Ya buncha little punks.
Agh! It's always you!
I woulda been off this island already if you
and your stupid friends hadn't found me, Straw Hat!
And how dare you disrespect a Warlord?
I am gonna sock you one good.
Huh?
And now I got crap falling on me?
Gimme a damn break!
The legend of Buggy is just getting started!
I didn't claw my way to the top
just to get crushed under some junk!
I'm not gonna die in some wasteland buried
under trash where no one will ever find me!
Although I guess it was a good life.
Thank you, Mother, for bringing me into this world.
Don't bury yourself yet, Buggy!
You got flashy tales of fancy yet to tell!
Wait a sec. Speaking of flashy, I
still have my famous weapon to use!
Special attack!
C'mon, Muggy Ball!
What?
Cipher Pol showed up, too? Buncha Government dogs!
Oh, yeah, I'm totally that strong!
I knew that would happen!
How is this happening?
This guy's the heir to Roger's strength.
He's s'posed to be invincible, right?
Amazing. But the real battle's
just getting started, isn't it?
Probably.
But it's nothing that Luffy can't handle.
We just need to get back to the Sunny.
Robin, sorry! I'll catch up in a second!
Huh?
That's not even going to slow me down!
Everyone, get back!
I don't need two arms to crush you!
I'm sorry!
Anything else you wanna try before you're dead?
We're finished. Damn it!
Not yet!
If we trim him down one more time Luffy can win!
Come on! Hurry!
What're you, crazy?
Well, damn.
Luffy!
All right! Let's follow him!
What's that?
Bleh! That was close!
I think that's enough for today, thanks!
Again?
I'll swat you away like flies!
How 'bout this, then?
Huh?
Not gonna die! Not gonna die!
Oh, you think you're pretty clever, don't you?
I'll destroy this whole island and you along with it!
What now, genius?
I didn't think that he'd still able to move!
Bullet!
This time, I won't lose!
You think you can beat me, just because you won't give up?
Looks like I'll have to put you in your place!
Now, Gum-Gum...
...King-King...
Ultimate Faust!
...King Kong Gun!
No!
That wasn't bad!
But still not enough!
What's he doing?
I'm not sure!
If only you were a bit stronger!
But there's only room for one at the top!
Huh? What the hell?
He's falling apart!
Special... Green Star... Snake Fireworks.
They're set off by a strong impact.
Snipers are here for support, after all.
Bullet! No!
All my hard work undone by some
moron with a giant rubber fist.
This can't be the end of me!
Took long enough.
That treasure's mine!
Huh?
Outta the way.
That belongs to Luffy!
I'm going to crush you!
Now, finally, it's one on one!
Awfully cocky!
You think I can't win in a fist fight?
I hope you've got something to show!
You don't have to keep reminding me that you're strong!
It doesn't matter anyway,
'cause I'm still gonna surpass you!
All my friends are here!
And they're counting on me!
Your friends?
There's no room for friends on a battlefield!
Only conviction, and faith in
yourself alone can save you out here!
And that's why you'll never defeat me!
I wield the greatest power on these seas!
I am the world's strongest man!
And that's why...
...I am the King of the Pirates!
Even if you're strong, you don't get it at all!
I'll just have to show you!
I'm gonna bury you, boy!
Gum-Gum King Kong...
Der Starkste...
...Gatling!
...Strike!
The only reason I've been able to grow this
strong is because I learned to rely on myself!
On these seas, that's all you can do!
Shut up!
You never would've made it
this far if you were really alone!
You forgot who helped you!
You're strong.
But mark my words.
Someday, I'll become even stronger.
Then we'll see who's the King of these seas,
Roger.
Challenge me any time. I love a good fight.
Same as you, Bullet.
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
Do you hear me?!
Luffy!
Please tell me you're all right!
Well, I got the treasure.
So, uh...
...I guess we won the game!
This can't be happening.
Luffy, what is this box?
It's the Pirate King's treasure.
No idea what's inside, though.
Oh, it's one of these things.
I can't believe my eyes!
That's an Eternal Pose to Laugh Tale!
Wait, to Laugh Tale?
This is it! You've found the way.
What is it?
Hand it over, Straw Hat!
That's mine!
You bastard.
Do you realize what you've done?
I'll make it on my own.
Not this way.
No surprise coming from you.
Hey! Luffy!
Good luck surviving the Buster Call, you dimwits!
How's that for a finale? Everyone gets roasted alive!
We've had our eyes on you this whole time.
It hasn't been pretty.
You call yourself Festival Master,
but you're really nothing but a warmonger, aren't you?
Right, Buena Festa?
A Revolutionary, huh?
I should've known.
Huh. So this little operation
with Straw Hat and his friends,
was that your doing?
No, we just got lucky, actually.
Or rather, Luffy inspired us to work as a team.
Fire Fist!
So that's Straw Hat's power.
Inspiring his friends and enemies, too.
Then he makes the impossible possible.
He could bring a new era.
A man like that could become King of the Pirates.
A pity.
I guess I bet on the wrong guy, didn't I?
I wouldn't beat yourself up.
It's not like he would team up with you, anyway.
Robin found a way out, but this is a real mess.
Do we break through?
They're gonna start the Buster Call any second now.
We gotta figure out something!
Uh! We're like rats in a trap.
I call dibs on the whole fleet, you hear me?
I'm sinking every last one! All you, stay outta my way!
Well, that'll work!
Franky! Let's go for it!
Y'ready, Sunny?!
Quick favor.
Use your power on this.
We're stuck! They're blockin'
us! We'll tear through! Keep going!
Oh, no!
Kizaru!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel.
Here comes the pain!
Fire fist!
Message from Vice Admiral Smoker!
"The Pirate King's treasure has
been destroyed by Straw Hat Luffy.
Many Marines are still trapped on the island!"
I request that you cancel the Buster Call immediately."
Repeat: I request that you
cancel the Buster Call immediately.
It's blocking the enemy.
We can escape now.
Waiting for the order, Luffy! Ready?
Until next time, brother.
No complaints from me! Let's go!
Yeah!
You made an Eternal Pose?
If that's a joke, then I'm not laughing!
We did it just in case!
I mean, what if we wanna come back?
There is no coming back.
Don't you get it?
We've reached the end of our journey.
And the treasure we've left?
Well, it's far beyond the reach
of someone who would use this.
Aw, Captain, now you've done it!
Perhaps, we were a bit before our time.
I do wonder who will find One Piece in the end.
Why, my son, obviously!
You don't have a son!
Not yet, but I got one on the way!
What?
You broke Roger's treasure?!
So you didn't want the Eternal Pose?
Nuh-uh!
Are you even trying to get to One Piece
anymore, or is this just a big game to you?!
What good does destroying it
do? You could have asked us first!
Well, that's no surprise!
Like Luffy would have it any other way!
Seems crazy, but whatever.
If we took a short cut, who knows what we'd miss out on!
There's all sorts of amazing stuff out
there and I wanna share it all with you guys!
What are we waiting for?
One party's over, so let's look for the next one!
Set sail for adventure!
Yeah!