[RED]
It's been three years since
the Demon Lord Taraxon
invaded Avalon.
Four nations have fallen,
and the Demon Lord now
holds half the continent.
But we know the god of
our world has not forsaken us.
[roars]
[TARAXON groans]
[RED] For Ruti Ragnason,
a maiden with
the Divine Blessing
of the Hero, is here.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
[RED] Henbane staunches bleeding
and disinfects wounds.
Koku leaves make antidotes.
You Are (Not) a True Comrade
Yujin mushrooms
function as a tonic.
[RED] Well, guess that's
enough for today.
[RED] This is the borderland
region of Zoltan.
To the north and
the east stands a vast,
unexplored mountain range called
the Wall at the World's End.
Zoltan
The rest is ringed by marshland.
This makes Zoltan
both difficult to reach
and of no strategic value,
so development has
proceeded at a snail's pace.
Even brigands have
forsaken this land.
There's just not
much worth taking.
The only travelers
we see tend to be
fugitives, hermits,
or eccentrics.
Adventurers' Guild
But I couldn't think of a better
place for me to be right now.
[MEGRIA]
Seven pounds of henbane,
four pounds of koku leaves,
and a bag of white berries.
Excellent work once again, Red.
That comes out to a
hundred and thirty perills.
[RED]
Great, thanks, Megria.
Don't mention it!
I hope you'll come back in soon!
[MAYA] Red, been out gathering
medicinal herbs again?
Yeah, so what?
Happens to be
something I do best.
That may be so, but that
bronze sword of yours
is just really sad.
At the very least,
you should have a steel one.
Hold on now, you're one to talk.
I mean, the one you
carry around is for show.
Put a cork in it!
My dream is to open
my own apothecary.
I'm not looking for adventure.
Just a quiet life
for me, thanks.
[RED]
There's only one problem.
I don't have the money
to open a shop.
Well, not enough,
anyway. Not yet.
[TANTA]
Hey, Red!
Oh! Hey, what's up?
Helping out at home?
Yeah! I've got the important job
of bringing Dad and Gonz lunch!
Really? Proud of you, Tanta.
And guess what?
Gonz said he thinks I'll make
a fine carpenter someday!
I still haven't figured out
what kind of Blessing I have,
but don't worry,
I'm gonna become a carpenter
and build a shop for you
no matter what!
[RED]
Good. I'm counting on it.
Hey, what's your
Blessing, anyway?
I've never asked.
Well, I guess there's
no tellin', huh?
Go on, your dad and
Gonz must be starving.
Aw, you're really not gonna say?
Fine, whatever.
But come by and
visit again soon.
I'll give you some advice about
opening a shop and all that.
Done.
See ya!
[RED] All living things
have a Blessing.
Every one.
Bestowed by the All-Mighty
to guide people's lives
and grant them the strength
they'll need on their journey.
That's why they're called
Divine Blessings.
Blessings grant powers,
known as "skills,"
Warrior
Hunter
according to their type,
such as Warrior or Mage.
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Warrior
Hunter
Martial Artist
Mage
Blessing
Warrior
Skills
-----------
Enhanced Strength
Enhanced Agility
Enhanced Stamina
Blessing
Warrior
Skills
-----------
Enhanced Strength
Enhanced Agility
Enhanced Stamina
Blessing
Warrior
Skills
-----------
Enhanced Strength
Enhanced Agility
Enhanced Stamina
-----------
So, fighters have
great combat skills.
And mages have the ability to
Blessing
Mage
Skills
-----------
Enhanced Magic Power
Enhanced Magic Resistance
Enhanced Memory
Blessing
Mage
Skills
-----------
Enhanced Magic Power
Enhanced Magic Resistance
Enhanced Memory
Blessing
Mage
Skills
-----------
Enhanced Magic Power
Enhanced Magic Resistance
Enhanced Memory
-----------
both utilize and
defend against magic.
[RED]
As for me...
You're not a true
comrade, Gideon.
If you would excuse me, please.
All right, you wanted to
see me, Ares? What's up?
I want you to
strike me with that.
[gasps]
What's the problem?
Could it be you're
actually afraid
to have to prove
your strength, Gideon?
There are many ways,
both physical and magical,
to pierce a ward such as this.
And yet, you are
totally unable to do so.
[GIDEON] If I used Thunderwaker
instead of this bronze sword.
Even if you did, that would
be Thunderwaker's power
rather than your own,
so what would that prove?
We both know that it's
a powerful weapon
no matter who wields it.
You're not a true
comrade, Gideon.
A true comrade fulfills
their allotted role
and is one you can trust to
the death and fight alongside.
Are you're saying that I'm not?
[ARES]
Even you must have noticed.
You couldn't pull
your own weight,
even in the recent
battle with Desmond.
Not only that, but having
you along on a quest
meant Ruti had to protect you,
and that gave our enemy
a very real advantage.
Frankly, you're a liability,
but what might be even worse is,
you're a dead weight
hanging around Ruti's neck.
You have the Divine
Blessing of the Guide.
You instinctively
lead and protect
the first leg of
the Hero's journey.
From the day you were born,
your Blessing made you as
formidable as a veteran knight,
a wonder to behold.
And make no mistake,
you've fulfilled
that role admirably.
Even I can admit and respect
that undeniable truth.
But now, we no longer
need you in our party.
[gasps]
You must know Ruti and
the rest of the members
have exceeded your level.
To put it bluntly,
there's no longer anything
you can do better than us.
But I'm...
I'm trying really hard
to do anything I can.
You're trying? What are you,
a complete idiot?
[GIDEON]
I...
Listen, making an effort,
even a successful one,
is no excuse for
being a liability.
It's the epitome of
selfishness to expect us
to forgive you because
you're "trying hard."
You simply aren't a comrade
and that's all there is to it.
[gasps]
[ARES] The Hero wouldn't
abandon a comrade,
and I doubt she'll ever
ask you to leave.
You should consider
quitting on your own,
so you'll no longer be
a burden to your sister.
[GIDEON] I'm second-in-command
of the Bahamut Knights.
Returning to the order
after being named a liability
would forever stain their honor.
Tell them I was out
keeping tabs on the enemy
and just never came back.
Will you please do that for me?
Don't tell them the truth.
Okay, very well.
I suppose we can
go with your story.
I'm grateful.
[ARES]
And one more thing.
Make sure to leave
your equipment here.
Since we earned it,
not you, it's only fitting.
[RED]
And that was it.
That's when I changed
my name to Red
and moved here to Zoltan.
The truth is, Ares was right.
[RED] I'm worried about my kid
sister, Ruti, but that's silly.
She's so much more
formidable than I'll ever be.
[RED]
There's no glory to be had here,
but I also don't have to
risk getting killed in battle
or deal with
nerve-wracking intrigue.
That's the path Zoltan offers.
[RED] This is the
second phase of my life.
[RED] My Blessing doesn't
have any innate skills,
but it has many common skills
that anyone could obtain.
The Survival skill is one.
It keeps me from getting lost in
all but the deepest
mountain reaches,
and it allows me to identify
most medicinal herbs.
[roars]
[RED]
Oh, an owlbear.
Just let it be.
You're not in the
Hero's party anymore.
Hey! Red! I'm so glad
you're alive and well!
Did something happen here?
How are you acting so casual?
An owlbear was spotted
in the mountains.
You're Albert.
I think that's "sir"
to you, D rank.
Right, fine, B-rank
adventurer Albert, sir.
So, what do you want?
[ALBERT] Well, I've heard
about you, believe it or not.
Your specialty is
gathering herbs,
and you're
a mountain expert, right?
[RED]
Yeah, I do what I can.
I'm about to head out
with this party
to put down the owlbear.
But we haven't done
much in the way of
herb gathering and all that,
so we don't know
the mountains very well.
I see. So you're
needing a guide?
We just don't want to
waste too much time.
Not on a lowly little owlbear.
Sorry, but I think I'll pass.
What is your problem?
This is your big chance
and you're missing it!
It'll look great on your resume.
Think about it, you might even
make C rank because of this!
I've got no interest in C rank.
If you must know, my dream
is to open an apothecary
and lead a simple life.
Fine, then!
We'll look elsewhere!
I wish you'd accept, Red.
It would put our minds
at ease having
someone who knows
the woods in the party.
I can even guarantee
your promotion
to C rank if that helps!
I'm sorry, but I'm really
not interested in that.
Huh? All right then,
if you're sure!
I'll be returning to the
guild shortly, so maybe,
you could come
drop off your herbs there.
[RED]
Got it. See you there, then.
Right! Now, excuse me.
[RED] I'd rather keep my past
a secret and avoid standing out.
Big Brother.
[RED] I only made
ninety perills this time.
At this rate, it'll take over
half a year to open a shop.
But it'll be fine.
It's not like I'm in some
big rush or anything.
[footsteps]
[GONZ]
Red! It's me, Gonz!
[sighs]
[knocking]
Stop knocking so hard
on that door.
You're gonna break it down.
What's wrong?
Tanta has a really high fever.
The doctor told us he thinks
he's contracted white-eye!
[gasps]
Nao!
What do we do?
There isn't any medicine.
Don't worry, we'll have
Red get us some.
After all, there's
no one in Zoltan who's
more skillful at
gathering herbs than he is.
Doctor.
I'm glad you're here, Red.
Thanks for coming.
[RED]
Let me have a look.
Irises turning white,
a mouth full of sores,
and swollen lymph
nodes on his neck.
Yeah, he has all
the usual symptoms.
Indeed.
[RED] How long since
he developed a fever?
He collapsed right around
three o'clock in the afternoon.
There's a very high
risk of blindness
after the first 24 hours.
So, he'll need the right
medicine well before then.
Yes, I know.
But with goblin fever
and the white-eye
epidemic this month,
we don't have nearly
enough medicine left.
We have koku leaves,
but not the blood needles.
They should be
starting to sprout
in the mountains
by now, I think.
[GONZ]
Please, Red!
You gotta get
the herbs he needs!
I know the mountains
are dangerous right now.
But I don't have anybody else
I can to turn to for help!
I'll pay any price!
Whatever you want! I mean it!
You've gotta save him!
[RED] The mountains are
currently off-limits,
so the Adventurer's Guild
might expel me
if they find out I was there.
I'd like to avoid that.
Red? Can you?
I'm happy to take
this on as a friend
instead of formal
adventuring work.
So, just don't tell the guild.
You're the best, Red!
Be back soon.
Please keep an eye on Tanta
for me, will ya, Doc?
[RED] Okay, looks like
the coast is clear.
[RED] Endurance Mastery:
Fatigue Immunity.
High-Speed Mastery:
Lightning Speed.
[RED]
I don't want to waste any time,
but it's pretty likely
I'll run into Albert's party
if I take the shortest route.
The long way, then.
That smell!
[RED]
Great, they used fire magic!
Why did it have to
be right here?
[RED]
This is the only good patch of
blood needles in
the whole region.
But how can I
extinguish this fire?
If only Ruti and Ares were here
to deal with this instead of me.
[footsteps]
There you are.
Guess you dodged Albert.
[roars]
[grunts]
[OWLBEAR 1A groans]
[CAMPBELL]
Albert! Over here!
[DIR]
B ranks are somethin'.
But I did help guide you,
so I'm looking forward
to a fine reward.
Look at the wound.
What, something wrong?
Never mind.
Let's get out of here before
the resistance magic wears off.
[NEWMAN]
He'll be fine now.
The medicine seems
to be working,
and it was administered early,
so no there's
no permanent damage.
What a relief.
I don't know how to thank you!
Well, we're very lucky
we got the medicine in time.
And that's all thanks to Red.
Thank you, Red, I'm so grateful.
I'm so sorry that helping
us put you in danger.
[RED]
Oh, no worries at all.
I can't believe him.
Only a total idiot would burn
the main blood needle
supply like that.
[NEWMAN] You know, Red,
doctors around here
would be delighted to have
an adventurer like you
open an apothecary.
Please be sure to let me know
whenever you set up shop.
I'll have plenty of
orders for you.
I'd welcome the business.
Where ya goin?
Join us for dinner!
Maybe next time.
Keep a close eye
on Tanta tonight.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
[RED] I can't believe that
after an all-out effort,
I only managed to gather
one bag of blood needles.
It's my limited Blessing.
I've improved my common skills
as much as possible,
but I've hit my limit.
If this really is
the best I can do,
then I definitely won't be
saving the world anytime soon.
No wonder they kicked me out.
[GONZ]
Red!
I couldn't let you leave
without thanking you again!
My friend! In saving Tanta,
you've saved my family!
Come on, I didn't really
do all that much.
Stop being stupid!
Who knows what would've
happened without you?
I'm so grateful that you
came to live here in Zoltan!
Thanks. Maybe we should
talk about the reward now,
before we forget.
Oh, right!
Well, go ahead and ask away,
then, don't be shy!
[RED]
I won't be.
I'm finally gonna ask for the
thing I want most in the world.
[inaudible]
Four months later...
[KEITH]
Yeah, and that's when...
Hey, it's the Champion Rit.
[OLIVER] I wonder if
she'd let me join her.
Rit does the majority
of her work solo.
She wouldn't give you
the time of day.
Hi, Rit!
[RIT]
Interesting.
I've never seen you
dressed like that.
Probably not. I've been invited
to a friend's celebration, so.
[RIT] Oh, this is probably
a bad time, then.
Stop! You know I'll always
help with whatever you need!
So, don't even think
twice about it, okay?
[RIT]
Well, thanks.
I need to file
a job completion report.
Sure!
I'll just go ahead
and prepare the form.
[RIT]
So, what's the occasion?
Red really wanted to celebrate
his shop's completion.
He's an adventurer
who specializes
in gathering medicinal
herbs and such,
but today he's opening
his brand-new apothecary.
He's an herb-gathering
specialist?
That sounds interesting.
What's this guy like?
Well, let's see, he's kind.
And pretty charming, too.
The townspeople all adored him
right from the start.
But... I think there might be
more to him than meets the eye.
He gets this really
pensive look at times.
[RIT]
So, there's more to him.
That's nothing unusual
in Zoltan, though.
I suspect Red is actually
far more formidable
than he's letting on!
I just have a feeling!
[RIT]
Oh yeah?
Now you've definitely
piqued my interest.
Gimme the details.
No problem.
Here's the first thing.
[RIT] So, you're saying
this Red fellow gathered
endangered herbs in a wildfire
and brought them back to town?
Yep, and here's
the interesting thing.
He keeps claiming that
he gathered them up
before the guild put
those mountains off-limits
and I don't buy it.
But the guild has no proof,
and he got the
much-needed blood needles,
so I guess they just
decided to leave it at that.
I was blown away
that he was willing to
risk his life to gather herbs
for someone else.
I mean, it's rare for an
adventurer to do that, right?
Come to think of it,
Red has quite a chivalrous side.
Maybe he was a knight
before he came here!
[RIT]
A knight?
[MEGRIA]
Is something the matter?
Huh? It's nothing.
I finally have my shop.
[GONZ]
What do you think, Red?
Thank you so much, Gonz.
You really are
Zoltan's top carpenter.
Well, don't forget
Tanta lent a hand.
Heh-heh, a man always
keeps his promise.
That's right. He should.
And it matches exactly
with the design you drew.
Thanks so much.
[RED] This is the reward
I requested from Gonz.
He agreed to build it
for me for free.
As it turned out,
I had just enough saved up
for the building materials.
[NEWMAN] Red. Just wanted
to make sure you received
that order I placed
with the apothecary.
Yes, I definitely did.
I'll have it delivered
to you tomorrow evening.
Great! Thank you.
[OLIVER] Guess what I heard
down at the port?
The Hero's party
actually managed to
defeat Gandor's forces,
not just once, but twice.
Really? Then it's
only a matter of time
before they defeat
the Demon Lord, too.
The world is safe and sound
as long as we have
the Hero Ruti! [laughs]
[RED]
It was all for the best.
And for Ruti, too.
[GONZ]
Hey, Red!
Give us a speech
about your big dreams!
[RED gasps]
Uh... Well, the truth is...
[RED] There's no need
to be pretentious.
After all, I'm not a knight
in the Hero's party anymore.
You've already made
my dream come true.
Thank you.
Now, all that I want
is to take it easy.
On hot days like this,
for instance,
I just want to share
some food and drink
and chat with everyone here.
So, please, come by
whenever you like.
[RED] And that's how my brand
new, much slower life, began.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku