Where are all the customers?
These medicinal herbs
and concoctions
are gonna expire
if nobody buys them.
But with all this rain,
who could blame the people
for staying warm
and cozy at home?
[door opens]
Welcome!
[RIT]
Gideon.
I can't believe it,
it really is you.
Hi, Rit.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
[RIT] It's been forever
since I've seen you, Gideon.
Uh... Actually, I've been
going by "Red" these days.
The Princess Who Did (Not) Join the Hero’s Party
Yeah, so it seems.
I heard about it
down at the guild.
I certainly never
would have expected
to see you here in Zoltan.
[RED] Rit is a B-rank
adventurer in town.
Her full name is
Rizlet of Loggervia,
the second princess of
the Duchy of Loggervia,
a major military power.
[RED]
What about you?
After all, you're a princess.
Why's a princess working as
a B-rank adventurer
in the boonies?
Some people back home
favor me for the throne
over my younger brother,
the crown prince.
So I decided to leave before
it tore our family apart.
Just enjoying my freedom
till things settle down.
[RED]
I see.
Hey, by the way,
what's with the name?
Rit and Red. So close!
You must have wanted
to be like me?
Uh... Truth is, I couldn't
think of anything,
so I riffed off Rit.
[RIT]
I'm flattered.
I can't believe you
actually remembered me.
Well, yeah, of course
I remember you,
I mean, we were comrades,
brief though it was.
[RIT]
Comrades, huh?
You still insist on
calling it that?
So, Gideon... or Red, sorry.
What are you doing here?
Oh, uh...
[RIT]
Unbelievable! That's not fair!
You two adventured
together for so long!
Yeah, well, the fact is,
I was a liability.
That's not true!
You did your best to ensure
the party always succeeded!
You totally worked
your butt off!
[RED]
You don't have to get mad.
As long as I was there,
I endangered my comrades.
Retiring before any harm
was done was for the best.
But do you really
think that Ruti and
the rest of the party
are okay without you?
They beat Gandor,
a Celestial King
in the Demon Lord's army.
They're doing just fine.
Your tea's gone cold.
I'll go make some more.
[RIT]
No, this is fine.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Least I could do is serve you
a good cup of tea.
[RED] I was banished
from the Hero's party.
There was nothing more
I could do. Not for Ruti.
It's so good.
I think it might even be better
than the tea back at court.
Oh, wow, that's
laying it on thick!
I only have novice-level
cooking skills.
I sure can't compete with
the Chef's Divine Blessing.
Well, then, maybe
the real reason why
it tastes as good as it does
is that you made it for me.
[RED]
We met several years ago.
Several years ago
Duchy of Loggervia
Alonor
Several years ago
Duchy of Loggervia
Alonor
Several years ago
Duchy of Loggervia
Alonor
It was in the
border town of Alonor
in the south of Loggervia.
The orc sightings seem
to be appearing out west.
Well, the vast majority
of them are, anyway.
All right, so we go defeat them.
But they might be scouts.
That's the most likely.
[DIR] Hey, sweet maid.
C'mon, let's have a drink.
Don't you ignore me.
The name's Dir, little darlin!
You must've heard of me.
[DIR screams]
[DIR]
Ow, that hurt!
Hey, what do you think
you're doing, you wench?
[grunts]
Rethinking that tone now?
You've picked the
wrong one to mess with.
[gasping]
[DIR]
My bad! I'll be on my way!
[PROPRIETRESS 2A]
You haven't paid yet!
So, were you disappointed
that I didn't need your help?
[RIT]
Then understand this.
The Duchy of Loggervia
doesn't need the Hero
to crush the Demon Lord's army!
Smug
[RIT]
Hmph.
Smug
Just ignore her, okay?
Yeah, I know that.
Well she certainly
has some spunk.
Who do you suppose she is?
That was the Champion, Rit!
The most formidable
adventurer of all!
She's never been
defeated in the arena!
[PATRONS] She's our
beautiful pride and joy!
[PATRONS laugh]
You weren't very honest
with your feelings back then.
You seemed to be really prickly.
[RIT]
Oh wow, was I really?
Yeah, we fought
side by side a few times,
but you always complained.
But I could be honest
about my feelings sometimes.
[RED]
Like when?
You know, like that time
at the mountain village.
[RIT]
So! Made any progress?
Nope, nothing to speak of.
Y'know, I'm starting to realize,
the Hero's party isn't
too great at collecting info.
You're probably right.
There's never been
anyone in our group
that had a Blessing
to help us with that.
[RIT chuckles]
Well, our investigation
has been making
terrific progress.
Wanna hear about it?
Yeah, let's have it.
All right, then.
If you say, "Please,
Princess Rit, I beseech you,
tell a fool such as me,"
then I would be more than happy
to tell you all about it.
[gasps]
[GIDEON]
All right. Please, Princess Rit,
won't you tell
a fool such as me?
[gasps]
It's quite a small price to pay
to save Loggervia,
don't you think?
Now I feel bad.
Really?
[RIT] What's that mean?
Nothing. I'm just
surprised you'd admit
feeling guilty about anything.
Wha... Seriously?
Fine then, now I'm not
even gonna tell you!
Aw, forgive me.
Okay. So what did your
investigation uncover?
[sighs] I found some strange
tracks around the village.
They seem to be fresh
and indicate travelers
moving regularly
back-and-forth from the north.
From the north,
that's interesting.
There's a mountain cabin used
by loggers up there, you know.
Right, but here's the thing,
the only logging
being done is happening
toward the northeast.
It's strange how even though
no wood's being delivered,
the logging continues on,
just like normal,
but then also, there are
those strange tracks.
The question is, where did
the missing wood go?
I dunno. There's no sign
of it having been moved.
[GIDEON]
Must've been magic.
[RIT]
Most likely.
I don't understand
why the villagers
aren't all up in arms
about this.
Hostages, I bet.
There are almost no children
or old folks left around here.
Huh. So, you think
it's a group that's
organized enough
to hold hostages?
Yeah. And that would eliminate
both brigands and goblins.
So it must be...
[GIDEON, RIT]
The Demon Lord's army.
Hey, Rit, don't you
think we should be
working together on this one?
Huh? With that party?
Please, don't make me laugh.
After all, I've already
soundly defeated
the Demon Lord's army twice!
Loggervia has no need
for the stupid Hero!
It wasn't the
main force, though,
when you beat them back.
What's your point?
Loggervia has never one time
lost land to invaders.
We win battles and
it's as simple as that!
We don't lose!
When that enormous
force of goblins attacked,
your ancestors requested
help from Central.
I doubt Loggervia's too proud
to do what it takes,
no matter what it is,
if it will give them
a real shot at victory.
[gasps] No, they just can't.
I can see that I'm gonna need
to take care of this myself.
Then Father won't have to cede
command of any of our forces.
And the royal guard
will remain his,
so he won't have to
depend on the Hero's party
or anyone else to do it.
Okay. I'm not gonna
twist your arm. Here.
[gasps] For what?
Well, food has been
pretty scarce around here.
Uh... Okay but this
better not taste gross!
[gasps]
Whatcha think?
It's not too bad.
Where'd you buy these, anyway?
[GIDEON]
I made them.
Really? You did? Why?
I've gotten so sick of eating
all these salt-cured foods.
So, I decided that
I would learn to
cook some recipes
on these long trips.
Well, at least you
did one thing okay.
See? That was an honest feeling.
Oh, was it really?
What about when
we joined forces,
you couldn't have
forgotten that.
Look, you're not half bad,
but don't dare let that
go to your head.
Because all I'm admitting is
that you're barely capable.
[gasps] Okay, okay,
he gets it, enough already!
[chuckles]
[RED] Rit wasn't truly honest
with her feelings
till our big showdown
with Shisandan.
But sadly, the outcome of that
battle was nothing to celebrate.
The Duchy of Loggervia
Fortunately, for the time being,
the enemy offensive
has come to a halt.
But there's no doubt in my mind
the Demon Lord's army will
resume its invasion before long.
[SOLDIER 2A]
We must do something now!
Food and fuel are
both running low!
We'll be annihilated if the war
continues on much longer!
[RIT] Don't forget,
the enemy's in the same boat.
I found a mountain fortress
where they've been storing food.
Instead of wasting more time,
we should strike there.
I think that's
the smartest thing to do.
[RIT] So, while our main force
distracts the enemy,
I can lead a party
of adventurers
in a raid on the fortress.
No way!
We can't risk having
a princess in enemy territory!
[SOLDIER 2C] If they're also
wearing thin, we can take cover
and defend against the siege.
Well, Lord Gaius?
I actually like
the princess's plan.
Master!
[GAIUS] The royal guard and I
will serve as a decoy.
We'd like to aid
the effort, as well.
[GAIUS]
That is most welcome.
I hereby entrust the castle's
defense to the Hero's party.
[RED] But unfortunately,
the plan failed.
[RIT]
Master? What are you doing here?
[GAIUS]
Hmm.
[gasps] Who are you?
And where is my master?
Well now! I am Shisandan, child.
I devoured your master.
You see, I needed his memories,
oh dear student of mine.
[yells]
It's obvious that
your people love you
and consider you
a hero amongst them.
I used that fact to
infiltrate your country
with great efficiency.
What do you think
about my strategy?
[gasps]
What are you doing here?
I dunno, something
didn't feel right
about being left at the castle.
Don't cry, Rit.
For the Hero's comrades,
vengeance doesn't come through
tears, only by cold steel!
[gasps]
Ruti will be here shortly.
We've just gotta
hold out till then!
Right!
[yells]
[gasps]
The Hero!
[SHISANDAN screams]
[GIDEON] You didn't attend
the war council again today.
They decided to keep holing up.
[GIDEON]
May I sit?
[RIT]
Mm-hm.
Listen, if you really
don't want to fight,
I won't make you,
'cause that wouldn't
do any good, anyway.
But I happen to think
that you do want to.
It's just this deep sorrow
is weighing heavily.
[RIT] That's probably true,
but it's no use.
I'm too freaked out.
Just the thought of
losing someone else.
I'm scared, really scared.
My master, the royal guard,
and all those adventurers.
I know them. Each and every
one of the fallen, I knew.
I know what they're like,
how they lived their lives,
and why each of them were there,
fighting alongside me!
But, they're gone.
All of them are dead
because of me.
I will never see them again.
First thing we need to do is
break through those siege lines.
Then, we can
summon reinforcements
and head straight into
the Bewitching Woods.
[RIT gasps]
It's usually pretty
much impassable,
but a former comrade
of mine lives there.
Her name is Yarandrala,
and with her Blessing,
I think we'd have a good chance.
That sounds good.
I'll leave it in your hands.
[GIDEON]
Rit.
I'll fight if the reinforcements
arrive. Don't worry.
Doesn't matter.
You know what does?
Whether Loggervia
has the will to fight.
The will and pride
to keep going.
You must join our quest
for reinforcements
and help us out with
battling the Demon Lord.
Because without you,
all the people of Loggervia
will remember is
the fateful day they lost
their beloved captain
of the royal guard.
Even if the Demon Lord
is vanquished,
that bitter memory will remain
a thorn in the duchy's side.
You are my comrade and
a comrade of the Hero. However.
I think you know this
war isn't hers to win.
It needs to be won through
Loggervia's will to go on.
[gasps]
[GIDEON] Otherwise,
if the Demon Lord returns
after the Hero has gone,
you will never prevail.
[RIT] You're saying we have to
claim victory ourselves.
[GIDEON]
That's right.
[RED]
Rit regained her will to fight,
and the Demon Lord's
army was vanquished.
Hey, are you hungry or anything?
Starving!
I haven't gone
shopping yet today,
but I can throw
something together.
Red, listen.
How would you feel about
letting me work here with you?
[gasps]
Red and Rit's Apothecary.
It has a nice ring to it,
don't you think?
Whoa, slow down.
You're one of only two
B-rank adventurers
in this entire area.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna retire.
No, no, wait.
I just opened shop,
and business is slow.
I can't afford
to hire anyone now.
Okay, but think about it,
who's gonna look after the shop
when you're out gathering
all those herbs?
It would be a total
waste to have to
close up shop every time, right?
I don't have many customers,
though I do see your point.
Well, it's early,
your business will grow.
Do you have any
special concoctions
that can only be found here?
Oh, well, yeah.
I have two original creations.
This is my Multiply Potion.
The way it works is you
mix it with a magic potion.
When you do that, it increases
its volume by a factor of five.
I'm thinking that's a bad idea.
Uh... But why?
Listen, I'm just sayin',
if you start selling this stuff,
potion prices will crash.
It will never get
approved at the guild.
What was that just now?
We're talking potions here,
not some kind of
trendy, newfangled,
What was that just now?
super-pricey magical device.
Affordable potions are vital.
Making sure that
they're available to all
supports the economy.
I mean, just imagine
all the damage
you could do if you
made prices crash.
I... You're right.
[RIT giggling]
[coughs] So sorry about that.
But I won't lie, I'm relieved.
You are?
[RIT]
It's just...
I've always thought
you were this amazing guy.
You're multitalented
and always so chill,
so I felt this vast
distance between us.
Oh, come on, I'm not
that big of a deal.
You are.
And there's no use
trying to deny it.
But I never imagined
that there would still be
things you didn't know,
or that you'd have a birdbrained
side, like everyone.
So are you disappointed?
Honestly, I think it's
made me like you even more.
So, this is the other
creation I made.
It's a new pain killer
as effective as
existing compounds,
but thankfully,
it's proven to be
far less addictive.
I like the sound of that one.
But pain killers still require
the Council's approval,
even if it is less addictive
than the alternatives
that are on the market.
Oh, that's right.
Um...
[sighs] Well. I, uh,
whenever you have
some extra time,
that'll be fine.
And I can't pay you much,
but it'd be great
if you would help out.
I'm sure there are lots of
things you could do.
[gasps] Sure!
But don't say it like
"whenever you have time,"
or then we'll never
be apart again!
Looks so good!
It is good!
[RED]
Glad you like it.
Oh my gosh, and now
I can look forward to
enjoying your cooking every day!
[RED]
You will?
[RED] Sounds like cooking
will be more fun now.
So tell me,
what time is breakfast?
Uh, around seven
o'clock, I'd say.
Then I guess I probably
should get up early. I'll try!
Oh.
[RED]
She's coming for breakfast, too?
I know! Why don't we
build a bathtub
and I'll cover the cost.
A tub? I can't have you
spending that much.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, I'll be using it, too.
What?
[RED] She's even
planning to bathe here?
You have one single-bed,
isn't that right?
[RED]
Uh, yeah...
Then I'll buy another tomorrow.
My belongings are
all in my item box,
so I won't need
new furniture or anything.
It's funny to hear you talk,
I would think
you were moving in!
Well, yeah, that's because I am.
I thought I made that clear?
[RED gasps]
[ARES]
Please forgive the wait.
This is Tisse.
I've asked her to join
our party in Gideon's stead,
since he's out now.
She has the Divine
Blessing of the Assassin
and is a rare talent,
even among the
Assassins' Guild elite.
She'll be far more useful
than Gideon ever was.
Thanks for this opportunity.
This is my pet,
Mr. Crawly Wawly.
I had to scour
the various guilds
before I could find
one of her caliber.
Thanks to Gideon, I've had to
work my fingers to the bone!
Danan. Martial Artist's
Blessing. Pleasure.
Theodora, and my Blessing
is the Crusader.
Is anyone listening to me?
[DANAN]
It's the Hero.
Hello, my name is Ruti.
Hi, I'm Tisse Garland.
I want you to understand,
you're going to be under
my command, not Ares'.
Is that clear?
Yes, it is, and I will
swear right now
to obey your every command.
That's good.
We're going to hunt for a weapon
the previous Demon Lord
left behind.
We leave tomorrow.
I'll be ready.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku