Why am I on the floor?
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
Let's Start Our Quiet Life Together
[RIT yawns]
G'morning.
Morning. You sleep okay?
[sighs] Not really.
Guess I'm just
not used to that bed.
I got it for next to nothing,
so I can't say I'm
all that surprised.
Oh, it wasn't that bad.
That's not really why I had
trouble sleeping, though.
[RIT]
This looks so good!
It is!
Great, 'cause you better eat up.
We have a busy day ahead, so
we'll both need lots of energy.
[RIT]
On it!
First, I'm gonna go
buy myself a bed,
then, I'll run home and
grab some paintings
that'll look good in the shop.
[gasps] Paintings?
The impact of good artwork is
nothing to sneeze at, you know.
Displaying a compelling
piece of art
is always a sure way
to boost sales.
Really? I've never
heard of that before.
[RIT] Oh! We also need to
go ask the Zoltan Council
to review and approve the new
pain killer you created.
It's probably going to take
some smooth negotiating.
Well, I've got that part
under control.
[RIT]
Oh. So, hey, about my salary.
How about one point five,
which will total up to
around 30 perills a month?
[RED] That's a reasonable salary
for live-in help.
For Rit, though, it seems like
less than she deserves.
What if she ends up saying
she'd rather not be paid at all?
I'd probably just insist on it
and offer her even more,
if I'm honest.
Okay, I'm fine settling on that.
[RED]
Wait a second.
Did she only say she
wanted to live here
so I wouldn't worry as much
about paying her a real salary?
Don't tell me she had it all
planned out from the beginning.
I appreciate it.
Oh, sure! Totally my pleasure!
[BOTH chuckle]
[RED] One nice thing is,
Zoltan's far removed
from the threat of
the Demon Lord's army.
It feels like it's
in another world.
It's a land without any
urgent need for the Hero.
A land without any
urgent need for the Hero?
I mean I'm glad of that,
but sometimes I feel like
something's missing.
You do?
Doesn't matter.
After all, I didn't join Ruti
and the rest of you
even when I could've.
I have no doubt that I
would have found a life
spent adventuring with you
and the Hero's party
to be satisfying, but...
I know being here is
the right answer for me.
[RED] We have left
the blood-soaked path
of the Hero on our own accord.
Now, we travel the land of
Zoltan simply as Red and Rit.
Stormthunder, you there?
[STORMTHUNDER]
My, if it isn't Lady Rit!
Thank you for choosing to
shop at my humble little...
Hold on just a minute,
what's Red doing here?
Well, it's kind of a long story.
I've just decided I'm
going to move into his place.
So, now I'm shopping to
buy a brand-new bed.
Congratulations!
Isn't that wonderful news!
Red, you're killin' me here,
you lucky dog, you!
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink!
Ugh. Hey, come on.
You've got the wrong idea.
[STORMTHUNDER chuckles]
Hey, Storm, what's the deal?
You weren't nearly this nice
to me when I was in here.
You know why? Because customers
who haggle 30 minutes
over a cheapo bed don't get
treated the same as those
who pay full price
for a quality product!
Okay, that's fair.
This walnut double bed's
gonna be perfect for me!
[RED] I really think
you should make it a single!
Tsk!
Sheesh, what a wimp.
Come again?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Such a wimp.
Unfortunately, the bed
won't fit in my item box.
Would you please deliver it
to Red's shop instead?
Of course, you got it, Rit.
Thanks for your business!
There sure is
a lot of good stuff
at Stormthunder's shop,
don't you think?
Well, yeah, Stormthunder has
the Craftsman Blessing,
and he's leveled it way up.
Wow, you know how high
a Blessing's level is?
Oh, I just happened
to learn about his.
I was helping him by hunting
to barter for some goods.
Ah, I get it.
[RED] The Almighty Demis
grants a Divine Blessing
to all living things at
the time of their birth.
Lineage and education have no
impact on the Blessing granted.
Strategist
Orphans who come from
the slums have been
Strategist
Thief
granted the Strategist
and General Blessings.
Thief
General
And at the same time,
even some of royal birth
General
Thief
have been granted
the Thief Blessing.
General
Thief
At the end of the day,
their success depends
completely on whether or not
they can level up
their Blessing.
So, then, the question is,
how does one level up?
[RED]
There's but one way.
You must battle
and slay someone.
Someone who has a Blessing.
It's the same
with all Blessings,
whether they're
battle-related or not.
People are willing to kill
each other just to level up.
[RED] This world,
it's rife with violence.
[TANTA groans]
[AL]
Tanta, no!
Are you okay?
You son of a...!
[RED]
Is that a skill?
Hey, stop it! That's enough!
Butt out!
[BULLIES gasp]
Wow. You know, at your level,
you should be fighting monsters
along with the adults.
Yeah, you talk tough,
but all you got is that
crappy bronze sword!
Tanta, you okay?
And what about you? You good?
Uh, yeah, but I...
[TANTA]
His name's Red. He's my friend.
He's also an apothecary
and an adventurer.
Wow, really?
That's why he's so strong.
This is my friend, Al.
Al, it looks like
you hurt your knee.
Huh?
[TANTA] We gotta patch
you up. It's Miss Rit!
Wait, hold on! What are you
doing here with Red?
Do you live here now?
I'm here with Red because
we're good friends.
And yes, I just moved in
with him yesterday.
What? I had no idea you
even had it in you, Red!
Good grief, people are weird.
[RED chuckles]
[RED] That should do it.
It'll feel better in a few days.
Uh, thank you.
Why were you two
fighting earlier?
It was that guy's fault.
We were just playing,
but he told us
we needed to scram
'cause we were in his way.
That kid is already
developing his Blessing.
That was a pretty strong
attack for a minor.
[AL]
Yeah, I know.
Thing is, Ademi hasn't
always been this violent.
But he's been an
annoying hothead lately.
[RED] He must've
discovered his Blessing.
Oh wow, is that really
what happens?
[RED]
It has an impact, for sure.
Divine Blessings do affect
a person's personality.
Why's that?
For example, with the
Craftsman Blessing,
you'll crave building things,
and you'll love it.
And with the Mage Blessing,
your thirst for knowledge
will start to grow.
So, what's Ademi's Blessing?
I'm not sure,
but probably Bar Brawler.
[TANTA]
That's a Blessing?
It's a Blessing
focused on fighting
with whatever might be at hand.
They'll use anything
they have as a weapon,
like rocks or jugs of booze.
They're good at
knocking people over
or flinging them
through the air.
That kind of thing.
The problem is, Ademi has
a really high affinity
for his Blessing.
Affinity?
Right. Your skills
can grow stronger
when you have a natural
affinity for your Blessing.
Ademi is a natural-born brawler.
[TANTA]
So, he's good in a brawl?
Whoa, what a crappy Blessing.
I agree. Really couldn't
have said it better.
It would make life
a lot easier for everyone
if Blessings were
all socially acceptable.
But some definitely aren't,
and that can end up
steering people toward evil.
[RED] Now, when Ademi encounters
any kind of obstacle,
his Blessing makes him
resort to violence.
Oh, now I see.
[RED] You don't need to
worry about it, though.
His Blessing had
a very powerful...
No. I don't want a Blessing.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't say that out loud...
The Church elders
would never understand!
So have you discovered
what your Blessing is yet, Al?
Yes, I've been gifted with
the Weapon Master Blessing.
Wow! That's a very
impressive one!
It's a Blessing
which enables you
to specialize in
one type of weapon.
Although, if it means I'm gonna
be like Ademi, I don't know.
Al, I know exactly
how you're feeling.
Coming to terms with your
Blessing can be scary.
After all, it can determine
the life you'll lead.
[RED] Rit has the
Spirit Scout Blessing.
That means she is a scout
for forest dwellers.
Spirit Scout
[RED] That probably
explains why she couldn't
Spirit Scout
live peacefully in the castle.
Because her Blessing
craves freedom.
Spirit Scout
Remember, no matter
what Blessing
you might have,
you'll always be you.
Huh?
[RED]
Blessings are but a part of you.
Think about it, even a mother
who's usually gentle
may sometimes lose her temper
when she gets angry.
[AL]
I see.
You're a sum of
all the parts that
make you who you are,
Blessing included.
But you're not a slave to it.
It's a big part of you
that you can still control.
Do that, and you'll
see how useful
it can be throughout your life.
Really?
Yeah. Your Blessing gives you
lots of skills for
overcoming fear.
As long you have
your mastered weapon,
you'll always be okay.
[AL] Um, I'm kinda
afraid of the dark.
Will it help me get over that?
Sure! Even if it's super dark,
you won't be scared.
That's a relief!
Thanks so much, Mister Red!
Al, we better get going.
[AL]
All right.
Listen, come by
our shop any time
you're feeling anxious
about something.
As long as you don't mind advice
from a D-rank adventurer.
[AL] Um... Thanks! Can I maybe
come over to play, too?
Even if I don't need advice?
Sure. I might even feed you.
Sounds great!
[BOTH]
Bye-bye!
[RED]
Well, we should be off, too.
Now it's time to go get
Red and Rit's Apothecary's
future hit product approved!
Uh, are you sure about this?
Once we've changed the name,
I won't let you off so easy
if you want to quit the shop.
So, I guess you're saying you
want me to stay here forever?
I...
[DAN groans]
Still no! No, no, no!
But, uh...
My concoction is a lot
less addictive than...
I'm a busy man!
Get that out of
my face and scram!
Well, now it looks like
we've got no choice
but to go over his head!
[RED]
It's worth a shot.
[RIT]
Let's go!
Miss Rit, I'm surprised to see
you've teamed up with someone,
you've always worked solo.
Should be interesting.
What can I do for you?
Well, uh...
[RUDOLF sighs]
I see. I apologize for that,
but your timing couldn't
have been much worse.
[RED]
Has something happened?
There's a remedy we approved
only a month ago.
Now, as we come to find out,
it's being misused as
an illegal narcotic.
It's spreading fast
on the black market
to everyone from
townsfolk to nobles.
And the remedy was approved
only a month ago?
[RUDOLF]
That's right.
The new remedy was
mass-produced outside of town,
and once it was approved,
it flooded the
market so quickly,
we were completely taken aback.
It seems clear that the maker
was targeting illicit use
from the start.
So now, our reputation
has taken a big hit.
This fiasco has done great harm.
Dan, who is in charge
of the new remedy,
has been dealing with
angry townsfolk non-stop.
I see.
All that being said,
seeing as how this request
is coming from you, Miss Rit,
I'll go ahead and
personally approve it for you.
Wow! You'd really do that?
We appreciate it a lot!
Sorry for making you do
all the heavy lifting in there.
Oh, there's no need
to apologize.
[RED] But I did say,
"Leave the negotiating to me,"
like some kind of idiot.
Who cares about any of that?
I'm just happy that
I could help you with this.
And I wanna keep doing so.
Don't you understand, Red?
I would do anything for you!
Aw, Rit, thanks
for that. I, uh...
I think we're great.
Yep!
My new pain killer was approved.
So, that's a good start.
But it will take a while before
its effectiveness
is known in Zoltan.
Yeah, the shop is in dire
need of a hit remedy,
and one that's fast-acting
in the sales department.
A hit remedy, huh.
Do you happen to have
any revolutionary ideas
for something customers
will want to buy at all costs?
[RED] Let's eat
while we think it over.
I love that idea!
You know, you really
are a good cook, Red!
How about serving food
along with your concoctions?
C'mon, don't be silly.
I mean, my Cooking skill
is actually really low.
I can't compete with
a professional chef.
Plus, I'm certain I've
never even heard of
an apothecary that serves.
[gasps] An apothecary
that serves food?
[RIT]
What is it?
I think we should give it a try.
What's that?
This is a nutritional
supplement.
It's good for colds, exhaustion,
and preventing sicknesses.
[RED] The thing is,
it's difficult to take
because it's so bitter.
Is that apple jam?
[RED]
It sure is.
I'm attempting to use
my Cooking skill
to make the bitterness
accentuate the jam's sweetness.
[RED] And thankfully,
my Prep skill lets me bake
without destroying any of
the nutritional value.
I get it!
So, it's like medicine
in cookie form.
[RED]
Now for the final test.
[BOTH]
So yummy!
This just might work!
Yeah!
Free samples!
Everyone, come get
your free samples
from Red and Rit's
Apothecary right here!
It helps prevent colds
and other illness!
It's medicine without
the bitterness!
Would you like to try one?
They're also effective for
post-battle exhaustion.
Get your free
samples right here!
[RED]
Free sample of the day.
So would you like to try one?
Cookies? [chuckles] No thanks.
Welcome, ma'am.
[CUSTOMER 3A] Hello.
Our daughter caught a cold
last night and now
she has a fever,
and someone told me you were
selling medicinal cookies,
is that true?
Yes, we sure are.
Would you like to try one?
[CUSTOMER 3A] They have that
bitter medicine inside, right?
Delicious!
My daughter would actually
love the taste of this!
Hey, I'd like one, too!
Great!
We sold every one.
[BOTH]
Yay!
[RIT gasps]
It's all thanks to you, Rit!
You really think so?
'Cause you just made my day.
[RED]
Are you kidding me?
Without you, I'd probably
still be twiddling my thumbs
without a single
customer in sight!
Rit! Thank you for
being there for me!
Well, sure!
I'm so happy I can be here
with you, Red. Seriously!
I'll never forget each and
every word you just said to me!
I'm sick of this!
[DANAN] Do you even
realize how much time
we have wasted in this desert?
The desert dwellers
are completely useless,
and we have no leads
for the weapon we're after.
Now you wanna go back
and resupply again?
It can't be helped, can it?
It's the previous
Demon Lord's weapon.
So it was never
going to be easy to find.
I did my best
trying to negotiate
with the desert dwellers,
but they are a lowly,
salt-of-the-earth people
who won't even obey
the king of this land.
The state of supplies
and negotiations
were never this bad
when Gideon was here.
[gasps] Are you saying that
I'm less useful than he is?
I'm a Sage, so I have no need
for his common skills.
[DANAN] Whatever!
I'm gonna go find Gideon!
[gasps] You can't do that!
Please, hold on just a minute!
I joined this party
because it was
a shortcut to defeating
the Demon Lord.
That's the whole
reason I'm here.
But if that's no longer true,
then there's
nothing left for me.
You made a fatal
tactical mistake
when you unnecessarily banished
Gideon from the party.
I couldn't have stopped him,
he left of his own free will.
[RUTI] Danan, you're going
to look for my brother?
[DANAN]
Oh! Milady!
Yes, I believe that we
need Gideon in our party.
Surely even you must...
Even I what?
What I mean is...
I'll allow it. Now go.
Danan!
[RUTI] Danan. I want you to
go and find my brother.
[ARES gasps]
The rest of us will
continue our journey.
Ruti.
[THEODORA]
So, what now?
I have no choice but to go.
Hey, I've been wondering,
do you think Ares
could've killed Gideon
simply because
he was in his way?
Well, Yarandrala suspected
that he might have.
That hurt.
She was beyond upset.
She knew Gideon's abilities,
and she appreciated them.
He was always a strong
and skilled fighter.
I was impressed
he could fight that well
using only common skills,
'cause it's not easy.
He was a tactician
worthy of my respect.
And yet, somehow,
you never failed
to criticize his
combat blunders, either.
Well, because that's
just the kind of man I am.
Mistakes are bound to repeat
unless they're
expressly called out.
But I swear to you
on my Blessing,
I never once thought Gideon
was a liability to our party.
Not at all.
I'm glad. And I suppose
you'll tell him so
when you see him, right?
We both know Sir Gideon's
a worthy fighter,
and that means a lot
coming from us,
the greatest martial
artist of our times
and the master of the Temple
Knight's spear fighting.
It doesn't even matter
how skilled a mage Ares is,
he'd be hard-pressed to slay
a knight who's so revered,
especially right next
to you and me.
That's a very good point.
So, then, Gideon yet lives.
[DANAN]
I'm off to find him!
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku