Red & Rit's Apothecary
Oh, g'morning, Red.
Uh, morning.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
Of Mead and Motives
Life can be so unexpected.
[RED] If anyone asked
if I'd ever thought
this would be my future,
I'd tell them I had no clue.
I could've guessed
battling the Demon Lord
with the Champion Ruti.
Or defending the capital as
second-in-command
of the Bahamut Knights.
Or even receiving a small domain
and living as a noble.
But living way out in Zoltan,
running an apothecary with
a princess, not so much.
[RIT] Red. I'm all
finished up over here.
Great, thanks.
Does an omelet and herb salad
sound good for lunch?
[gasps] Oh, heck yeah!
[RED]
Yep. This isn't so bad.
[RIT]
Welcome!
What? That's Champion Rit!
What the heck are you
doing in Red's store?
Red, tell us
what's going on here!
I don't know, one thing
led to another, and then.
I decided to retire
from adventuring
and start working here!
Red and I are living together
now and so far I'm loving it!
[ALL gasp]
[KEITH] What the devil
is going on here?
Like I said, one thing...
[KEITH]
But what was the thing?
I don't know,
all kinds of things.
[KEITH]
What the hell?
[RIT]
Anyway.
Can I interest you in
a potion while you're here?
Of course, why wouldn't I?
[MAYA] I can't. I just cannot
believe the Champion Rit
is actually living with Red!
[KEITH gasps] Hey, Maya!
We better go after her!
I'll be back, Miss Rit!
Wait for me!
[RED] Zoltan's most
formidable adventurer
now works at an apothecary.
I guess that would be a shock.
But then again.
People can become an
adventurer when they want to,
and stop adventuring
when they like.
Freedom's kind of
built into the job.
Know what? I'm in the mood
to drink some mead!
Some mead?
Y'know, Honey-based liquor.
[RED] I know what it is,
but where's this coming from?
[gasps] Well, nothing
in particular, I guess.
I, uh, just had
a sudden craving for it.
Yeah, I know exactly
what you mean.
Unfortunately, we don't
have any, but there's wine.
No, it's gotta be
mead or nothing.
Would you be okay
if I go buy some?
[RED] Sure! Why don't
you run over there
before the store closes?
Okay, I'll be back in a sec!
See you in a bit.
[RED] A dinner that
goes well with mead.
Something like bread and
cheese stew sounds good.
[door opens]
[RED]
Welcome in... Huh?
Albert, sir.
What a hole-in-the-wall.
Thanks for that.
Now, then, what do you need?
Medicine or something?
Heh. No, I'm not here
to buy medicine.
You're happy working
in a place like this?
[RED]
I am. It's my own shop,
filled to the brim with
my very own concoctions.
I'm earning enough now to live
in a way that's
quite comfortable,
and I have a cute
roommate. [gasps]
Anyway! I'm totally satisfied.
[chuckles] Those who know
nothing of the good life
have such low expectations.
But whatever. Hey, D rank?
Oh great, now what?
All I want from you
is the truth.
Did you kill
the owlbear? Tell me.
What are you talking about?
Everyone knows you killed
the owlbear, right?
No, it wasn't my sword
that delivered the fatal blow.
I know that beyond
a shadow of a doubt.
The wound was obviously
made with a blade
that's far less sharp than mine.
You know, like maybe
that bronze stick of yours.
Oh, I'm just
a D-rank adventurer.
I couldn't take down an owlbear.
[ALBERT]
I'll ask you one more time!
Tell the truth! Did you
kill that owlbear, Red?
I already told you,
it wasn't me.
[gasps]
[ALBERT] I thought I'd
ask you to join our party,
but it seems that's
not in the cards.
Rit! Back off!
Rit? But you're...?
What are you doing here?
What are you doing?
Red is someone I happen to
hold very dear, Albert.
So, think carefully,
or you're dead.
[RED] He came to ask me
to join his party.
[sighs]
That was just Albert's
way of testing me.
Wait, how are you
standing there right now?
You were just
behind the counter!
I mean, I waited till
it was safe to come out.
Get the hell outta here.
[RIT] Red, are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
Nah, why would I be?
[RIT]
That's a relief.
I mean, what is
his problem, anyway?
Maybe I should've gone ahead
and cut him down, huh?
We could've totally
claimed self-defense.
[RED] Unfortunately,
Albert's the only B-rank
adventurer in Zoltan right now.
I'm afraid killing him is out.
The town still needs him,
even if he is a big jerk.
Does it really, though?
And you didn't even
fight back, Red.
I don't understand that.
[RED] 'Cause I was sure
it wouldn't escalate.
I knew he'd stop.
What would you have done
if he hadn't stopped, though?
I guess I would've
had to fight back.
But how would you
have managed that,
considering he already had
a blade to your neck?
You're capable of
something like that?
I dunno. In any case,
you really didn't have to
drop the mead that you'd
just laid out good money for.
Right, sorry! I just...
Though I'll admit.
I'm happy you could get
so upset for my sake.
Sure.
[RED, RIT]
Cheers.
[RIT] Well, we have
all the furniture we need,
and now that we've
got our new sign,
it feels like our new life
has actually begun.
Is that what you
wanted to toast to?
Maybe.
Oh! We could also really use
a big bathtub in there.
Yeah, actually I already talked
to Gonz about it. I agree.
I would love if it was a tub
large enough for two.
At the same time?
I meant one that size.
Oh, of course.
A big tub would be nice.
Wouldn't it?
After a day's work, there's
nothing like a long, hot bath.
[RED] I meant to ask,
would you like to try out
my favorite sauna sometime?
[gasps] Yes, please!
Okay, good, let's go there
on a day off soon.
Great!
Ahh! That's so yummy!
[RIT] Come on, Red.
You drink up, too!
[RED]
All right.
[RED] How did this happen?
This is insane.
Why did it devolve into
an endurance contest?
[RED]
There it is. You done, Storm?
I've got lots more
sweating to do today, boys.
Yeah.
[RED]
What are we even competing over?
Aren't we s'posed to be
here to relax?
Who'd have thought, right?
Never would've
guessed you'd end up
hiring the Champion Rit
as an employee at your shop.
Y'know, come to think of it,
shouldn't you have
gotten a double bed
rather than a single
the other day?
[RED]
Mind your own business.
Oh, now I see,
but if your relationship
hasn't progressed to that
point yet, you'd better be
more courageous or you're
gonna miss your chance.
[RED]
Mind your own business.
Yeah, he's right.
Bet you wish you'd
got that double bed.
Mind your own business.
[RED]
Oops. I said that one out loud.
It sure is hot.
The summers in Zoltan, I mean.
The people of Zoltan
get lazier than usual
when summer comes around.
They don't work or
even leave the house.
They do nothing but
lay around and sleep.
Where do you get off,
spouting an opinion on that?
You weren't born and
raised here in Zoltan.
Don't make things up.
We're lazy in winter, too.
[RED]
Good. He's hit a wall.
I think it's finally
warm enough, don't you?
Yeah, thankfully.
The stove isn't exactly
doing its best work today.
[RED]
Why are they staring at me?
What do they want?
Jeez. I guess it's up to me.
What do you think?
All warmed up now?
[BOTH]
Yeah.
[STORMTHUNDER, RED]
Gonz!
I wondered what the heck
was taking so long.
What is wrong with you?
Oh, it's nothing!
I forgot I felt a cold
coming on earlier.
Well, that not true,
you're just overly competitive.
Good grief.
Hey, this whole place
is practically empty.
You okay? Hangin'
in there, pops?
Have you heard?
There's a new public bathhouse
that just opened
a little while back.
Do you mean that big place
the nobles built?
Yeah. A state-of-the-art sauna,
a restaurant,
and even a masseuse.
It seems like everyone
prefers to go there now.
How could I ever compete
with something that fancy?
Zeff, stop! You never know
till you try!
So don't quit before
the battle's over!
But this ramshackle old sauna
couldn't possibly compete.
Huh? What's wrong with you?
I'll keep coming here for
as long as it's still standing!
Assuming you'll
still serve drinks!
Now, gimme a beer!
Coming right up.
One for me, too!
Gimme a beer, pops!
Gimme one, too! I'm loyal!
I'll join in, too,
'cause I love coming
for a nice hot sauna with Red!
Oh, but I'll pass on
the beer, thanks.
While you're at it,
one for me, too.
You certainly are
a strange bunch, you know,
but I appreciate it.
[BOTH]
Gimme another!
Coming right up.
I love this sort of
thing, don't you?
I sure do.
[NAO] What will we do if
Zeff really closes up shop?
That would be sad.
I like his sauna, too.
Yeah, I wonder if
there's anything
to be done at this point.
We could easily promote
his place if it had
something that the
big bathhouse lacked.
A price low enough for
commoners to use it!
He can't afford to
compete on price though.
Maybe the best beer around?
Well, the competition
has a restaurant.
So, sadly, beverages won't help.
[RED]
Tea's ready.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
[TANTA]
This looks good!
Hey, Red, do you happen to
have any thoughts about
how Zeff could
attract more customers?
I'll have to think.
This smells so incredible!
It's some kinda herb, isn't it?
Yeah, I infused it with an herb
that helps one
recover from fatigue.
Well, it tastes delicious,
which is the important part,
if you ask me!
Oh, thank you, Tanta.
Oh, wow. I know.
[RED]
Hey, pops.
[RIT]
We've come back for more.
Ah! Welcome back.
Something smells exquisite!
Well done!
You don't miss a thing.
Here, I brought you
a potpourri sack.
A potpourri sack?
Yeah. We've been trying to
think up different ways
for you to attract
more customers.
And I had this idea.
Steam therapy.
I can't say I'm familiar.
There's a race in a hidden vale.
They're known to lead
a very primitive existence.
And they're more commonly
known as the wild elves.
Whenever they fall ill,
they enter a cave
and prepare an herbal soup.
They let the steam warm
and heal their bodies.
So I had an idea.
I made this to try their steam
therapy here in the sauna.
This sack is full of herbs.
We can hang it over the stove,
so the herbs' aroma
mingles with the steam,
just like in those caves.
It's both relaxing
and good for the throat.
Ohh.
Like it?
If it works, I can
offer you a steady supply.
It sounds very
interesting, for sure,
but do you really think
it'll be enough?
Well, we'll never know
unless we try.
[ZEFF]
Ohh. This isn't half bad, huh?
Yeah. We've tried it out
back at our place,
but the aroma really
shines in the sauna.
[ZEFF] Wow. It seems
I still have much to learn.
So? Don't you think
it's possible
this could help you
stay in business?
Maybe. It might be
just what I need
to keep customers
coming back for more.
'Cause I'll have something here
that the big bathhouse doesn't.
Here I was acting like
I knew everything about saunas.
But it seems I was wrong.
I gave up so fast.
I was far too hasty thinking it
was time to throw in the towel.
I haven't been humbled
like this in a very long time.
It's one for
the books, this day.
All three of you have my thanks.
I'll buy some potpourri sacks.
I'd be thrilled to use them.
You tossed us a lifeline
here today, Red.
[NAO, RIT]
We did it!
Any time!
Since you're here,
get warm, on the house.
[sighs]
[RED]
Yep, it was a great idea.
A new sauna experience.
[door opens]
[RIT]
What a wonderful smell.
[NAO]
Oh, for sure.
That should attract
more customers.
[gasps]
What are you guys doing?
I was in here first, you know?
Not fair. You don't get
the sauna to yourself.
Yes, I would agree.
[RED] Okay, but then
why are you half-naked?
What's with that?
Sheesh, what's the
big deal? It's just you.
[RED]
No, this isn't right!
Plus, Nao is a married woman.
Huh?
Uh... What was that reaction?
[laughs] I've got a towel on.
It's perfectly fine!
I give up. Guess I'll
just leave, then.
[RIT gasps]
Wh-What's the problem?
Come enjoy the sauna with us.
Are you really gonna stand here
and make a lady beg like that?
[NAO] If you're a real man,
you should just do it.
Do it. Do it!
[laughing] It's not as if you're
a couple of teenagers.
There's no need to blush like
that, just relax and have fun!
Anyway, whatever.
I must say, I'm impressed, Rit.
Impressed with what?
You have a keen eye,
choosing Red as your partner,
seeing as he's about
a million times better
than those noblemen one finds
in the center of town.
Red saved my son's life
and I'm so grateful,
though it's true,
some people make fun of him
for being an eternal D rank.
But he's a total pro
at herb gathering,
his work is absolutely flawless.
[RIT] Mm-hm! Yeah, when I
first met him, years ago,
his work was
tried-and-true perfection,
and that's still the case.
This time it just happens
to be in a shop in Zoltan.
[RIT]
Listen, Red.
[gasps]
We should all
come back here again!
[RIT, NAO]
Red!
[RIT, TANTA]
Hit me again!
Coming right up.
A potpourri sack, huh?
Not a bad call.
Yeah, it could have been worse.
I know, right?
Wow! It's warmed up
nicely in here.
[STORMTHUNDER chuckles]
Not even.
[RED]
This again?
Hey, that's enough already!
[ALL]
Stormy!
It makes me so happy to see
his customers are coming back.
Never in a million years
would I have imagined
that I would end up finding
Zoltan as fulfilling as I do.
I was thinking
that same thing earlier.
[GONZ] Well! We'll see
you two later. Take care.
Yeah, see you later!
Till next time!
Such a nice family.
Yeah, they are.
Um, the other day...
The other day,
when I said I wanted to
drink some mead,
there was a reason.
The truth is, when someone
gets married in Loggervia,
the couple takes a month off
from work together,
and they drink mead, and spend
the entire time with each other.
And so when I remembered that...
[RIT] I suddenly felt like
all I wanted was mead.
[gasps]
Let's go home.
Yeah.
[ARES]
Unbelievable!
Just when we could
actually use their help,
they leave the party.
At this rate, we're never
gonna find anything!
Let alone the weapon the
previous Demon Lord left behind!
[TISSE]
Uh, excuse me.
I've finished setting up
the tent, like you asked.
How's your new party?
Are you disappointed?
It's fine. No, I don't
feel disappointed.
It wasn't always
like this, y'know.
We never had these kinds of
non-combat problems before.
And in combat, we were
like a natural-born team.
It started after
Sir Gideon was gone.
Then the party
fell completely apart.
And the trust that was
once there vanished.
[THEODORA] The party desperately
needed Sir Gideon.
[THEODORA]
So then, why did milady...?
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku