[RIT]
We're good on potions.
And we have enough
medicine cookies, so...
Oh sorry, folks,
we are not quite open yet.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
I am Galatine, a senior official
at the Adventurers' Guild.
The Amber Bracelet
Welcome, sir.
I've come to find out
if the rumor
that Rit's living here is true.
It is.
Then we would like to
speak with her, please.
You're welcome to do that
as soon as we're
finished getting
ready to open up.
Shouldn't she be allowed
to answer for herself?
You should at least
speak with her
before you give us an answer.
You'd prefer to make us wait?
I answered because
I knew what she'd say.
[GALATINE] You seem quite
confident, Master Red.
I'm kinda surprised
you know so much
about a D-rank adventurer.
I have memorized the faces
and personal histories
of every adventurer who's ever
been a member of this guild.
Very well then.
We'll wait as long as we must.
[RED]
I appreciate your patience.
I can take over re-stocking.
Those bigwigs are here,
aren't they?
I say we make 'em wait.
[RIT] Finished.
I'll go tell them "no" now.
Be right back.
Sure. But please don't
take too long, okay?
I really do need your help here.
[RIT]
Welcome!
[RED] Aren't you
the Thieves' Guild's...
You know who I am?
That's impressive
for a D-ranker.
What is it that you want?
[RED]
An elven coin.
Oh, you know what it is?
Then I'll just cut to the chase.
If you sever ties with Rit,
the coin is yours.
[THIEVES GUILD 5A] It's worth
ten thousand perills.
I think you'll agree,
that's enough for you
to live quite comfortably.
I can get you women, too.
Not the cheap ones, I'm talking
the 50-perill-a-night kind.
[RED]
Too low.
Wha...
Your problem is,
Rit's priceless.
Not even a thousand elven coins
would be close to enough.
I can't tell if you're
a big shot or just an idiot.
[RED] Sorry, but I know she's
far more valuable than that.
Why else would the
Thieves' Guild try this?
Buying me off with elven coins?
Oh, I'm afraid
you've got me there.
Well, let me know
if you ever change your mind.
We'd be more than happy
to bargain with you.
You can forget it.
It's not gonna happen.
[THIEVES GUILD 5A]
Peh.
What do you want, more money?
[RIT]
No!
Perhaps you'd like
a better title?
[RIT]
Not interested!
How about an honorary peerage?
[RIT]
No means no!
I'll give you my son's
hand in marriage!
[OFFICIALS]
Are you completely insane?
Enough already!
I signed a lifetime employment
contract with Red's shop
because I retired
from adventuring!
You got that? Done!
And another thing, if you end
up hounding Red so much
that he moves out of town,
I will be going with him!
Do not test me on this!
[gasps]
[RIT sighs]
Huh? You heard that? Oh gosh.
A lifetime contract?
To work here with me
at my shop? Huh.
It's just, those guys,
they refused to shut up
and they wouldn't take no
for an answer. Sorry.
[RED]
Rit. Come over here.
[RIT]
What for?
Well, I was thinking that...
Give me your hand.
Okay...
[gasps] Wait, what're you doing?
It's a gift.
[RIT gasps]
A down payment on your
lifetime of employment.
A bracelet with an amber stone!
Wow. A down payment?
I should warn you,
if you keep giving me
gifts like this,
I might get the wrong idea.
You know, come to think of it,
there is something else
I'd like to go pick up.
Do you have a favorite gemstone?
Just wondering.
I think I'd like anything
that you picked out,
as long as it was from you.
[RED]
Oh, okay.
[BIGHAWK] Come here.
I have a job for you.
And it concerns Rit.
Of course.
You know I'd be more than
happy to help with that.
The Adventurers' Guild
has got a big mess.
They're desperate to get Rit
back out and adventuring again,
as you're no doubt
already aware.
[DIR]
Indeed.
The Thieves' Guild
feels the same way.
They're just as hell-bent on
convincing Rit not to retire.
As if we needed anything
else to worry about.
[DIR]
What does that mean?
Rit is the wild card
around here.
You know what that means.
Any group she ends up
on the wrong side of
will always pay a hefty price.
It's remarkable.
Even the Thieves' Guild
tends to back off
whenever it looks like
she's getting involved.
[DIR]
Isn't her retirement
something to be
celebrated, then?
[BIGHAWK]
Not even a little bit!
The situation is manageable
as long as she's in the guild,
but not when she's on her own.
What if she suddenly
saw us as a threat?
Uncertainty is bad for business.
[DIR]
I see.
And that's where
you come in, Dir.
What I've heard is that you
know what her weakness is.
Yes, you could say that.
I'd ask what that was,
but I know better.
Keep your secrets, then.
Anyway, the Thieves'
Guild isn't gonna
pick a fight with her,
and that's certain.
Uh, okay.
[BIGHAWK]
So you know what I want?
I'd like nothing better for
this problem to
take care of itself,
do you understand
what I'm saying?
[DIR gasps] If the problem
were to be taken care of,
what would be in
the deal for me?
Well, nothing, officially,
'cause the Thieves' Guild
has nothing to do with this.
But, maybe I could
throw an easy job
hauling cargo your way,
how would that be?
And said cargo
might contain money.
Say no more. Leave it to me,
I'll get it done.
[RIT] I am so happy right now
I can hardly stand it!
[RIT] To think I'd be
living with Gideon!
Or should I say "Red"?
[RIT] I never dreamed
this would happen
when we parted ways
in Loggervia.
[RIT] With the Demon Lord's
army on all sides
and the Captain of
the Guard fallen,
Loggervia was in dire straits.
As the crisis unfolded,
we set off for
the neighboring Duchy of Sunland
to seek some kind of assistance.
But first, we had to find
a way to slip through
the Demon Lord's
heavily guarded lines.
Loggervia
Bewitching Woods
Sunland
Gideon came up with a plan.
He proposed that we head
through the Bewitching Woods,
which was considered
impassable to humans,
as well as the Demon Lord
and his army.
Our first stop along
the way was a village
that sat right at
the edge of the woods.
[YARANDRALA] Gideon!
You finally made it, after all!
Hey, Yarandrala.
It's, uh, good to see you again.
Sorry for the delayed
reinforcements.
No worries at all.
Hey, Rit, this is Yarandrala,
the elf I told you about.
It's a pleasure!
Uh, yeah, same.
[GIDEON] Her Blessing
is Singer of the Trees.
She can converse with plants and
have them come to
her aid when necessary.
For those of us who are born
in the Bewitching Woods,
the magic cast upon it
thankfully has no effect.
Which means, I can
find my way through
just by listening to
what the plants say.
Huh?
Yarandrala is the key
to our current strategy.
To be honest, I doubt
that even the Demon Lord
knows the way through
the Bewitching Woods.
You're willing to place the fate
of our entire party
in her hands?
I guess that means
you must trust her a lot.
Yeah, I do. She's a
true and trusty friend.
Now, let's get to work.
Theodora and Danan,
protect the villagers
and get them to safety.
The rest of us will go through
the Bewitching Woods.
That means Ruti, myself, Rit,
Yarandrala, and Ares
will go together.
By the way, where is Ares?
[GIDEON]
Ah, yes.
Those are the
mercenaries he hired.
[RIT] I wonder
where we are right now.
Is this north or south?
I don't hear any spirits.
Huh?
[YARANDRALA giggling]
[sighs]
[RIT] Gideon is a member
of the Hero's party.
Why would he bother
wasting his time
cheering up a
depressed princess?
I knew that and I
still got my hopes up.
What's wrong with me? So dumb.
You okay back there, Rit?
I hope you're not under
the impression that
I need you to worry
about me, 'cause I don't!
I guess you're right.
Apologies. My bad.
[RIT gasps]
Know what?
No, what?
The white birch just
gave me the low-down.
Told me there's a river
right up ahead.
Would you want to bathe
if we get to take a break?
Oh, wow. Like, take a bath?
You'll feel so refreshed.
The high elves have a saying.
"Cleanliness is
next to holiness.
Evil and grime go together."
You ready?
Take care of things, Gideon.
We're off for a bit. Bye, now!
[RIT]
But, I...
I never actually
said I wanted to go.
Ruti, care to join us?
That's what I thought.
All right,
let's all take a break.
[ARES] Are you nuts?
We don't have time for that!
[GIDEON] We promised
we'd follow Yarandrala's lead
while she got us through
the Bewitching Woods.
Yes, I know! Because you're
nothing but a pushover!
Wait, that's not true.
Try to relax. Gideon can
handle things, okay?
No, but...
[ARES]
I mean, don't you get it?
No, of course, you don't!
It's so obvious
you have no clue!
[YARANDRALA] Come join me, Rit!
It's so cool and refreshing.
[RIT gasps]
It's freezing!
[YARANDRALA giggles]
[YARANDRALA]
So, Rit. You like him.
You like Gideon, right?
[RIT] Huh? What?
What're you talking about?
Well, it has been
pretty obvious.
[RIT gasps]
And you're such a lovely person.
I'm positive Gideon
likes you, too.
I wonder.
[YARANDRALA] You get angry when
you're embarrassed, though.
You need to work on that.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe instead of
trying to hide it,
you could show your
affection playfully?
Find an outlet for
all of that good energy?
That sounds like a good idea,
but it's a lot easier
said than done.
[RIT]
What about you, Yarandrala?
Do you feel the same
for him as I do?
Who, me? Oh, no.
Really?
Well, it's tricky.
High elves live a little bit
longer than humans do.
That being the case,
I make it a point
not to fall in love
with them if I can help it.
I learned my lesson, there.
[YARANDRALA]
So, don't worry.
I see Gideon as a close friend,
a comrade in arms,
and the human I can most trust
in this world of ours, you know?
But that's not the same
as true love.
All I want is for Gideon
to be truly happy.
He's always assumed
a greater share
of the burden for his comrades.
That will never change.
He is who he is.
What I hope for him
is that he'll learn
how to live life
for his own sake.
I want him to enjoy
a simple kind of existence
with someone he truly loves
by his side for the whole thing.
Do you really?
[YARANDRALA] But I can't
carry Gideon's burdens.
No one else can do that for him.
People don't seem to
understand that his abilities
go far beyond his obvious
Blessing and skills.
Yeah. I agree.
Gideon is definitely formidable,
but he's not invincible.
It's as if everyone
in his life depends on him,
and they take it for granted.
I think that has to change.
It isn't right for him.
But I think you could be
a really good fit for him.
[RIT]
Huh?
[YARANDRALA] Just be sure
not to lean on him and
accept his care without
giving anything in return.
I think you two could
help support each other.
I could?
But ever since I've known him,
Gideon's been the one
who carries all the weight.
You'll figure it out.
I mean, after all,
you truly love him,
and in the end that's
what matters the most.
Yes, I do. I definitely do.
See, it'll be fine.
And when he's feeling down,
Gideon will always
be able to lean on you
to help him through it.
[ARES] How much longer now?
Yarandrala?
[YARANDRALA]
Stop!
[GIDEON] Scouts from
the Demon Lord's army?
[ARES]
It can't be!
[GIDEON]
It's that mercenary.
They did warn us.
We knew the Demon Lord
still had informers
among the conquered nobles.
Look, I was convinced
that we lacked information.
Well, what's done is done now.
The question is,
what can we do about it?
[GIDEON]
I'll distract the enemy.
Ruti and Rit, I want you
to break through their line.
That's risky!
She's right.
Even you can't think...
Trust in my brother.
But it's...!
Yarandrala, I think it best
that you accompany him, too.
Count on me!
Wait, Ruti! I don't think
this is the best...
I don't need your consent
to give orders.
Not to my own party, Rit.
[gasps]
[GIDEON]
Don't worry.
I wouldn't do this
if I thought I couldn't.
[RIT] The Demon Lord's
army was waiting
by the Bewitching Wood's exit.
Fearing their presence,
Sunland had deployed
troops at the border.
[RIT] This allowed us to
request reinforcements
faster than expected. However...
[RIT] I beseech you,
Almighty Demis,
and you, Larael,
Guardian of Hope.
Please watch over Gideon.
And Victy, Guardian of Martyrs,
please, I beg you,
don't claim Gideon
as one of your own today.
Rit.
[RIT gasps] What? No, I'm not
too scared to keep on going!
Fall back, now.
No, wait! You're not
charging in alone!
So this... is the power
of the Hero.
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[RIT]
This is the Hero Ruti's war.
[GIDEON]
Hey there.
[gasping]
[RUTI]
Brother.
[RUTI] Forgive me,
there was no other way.
I won't do it again.
Hey, it's all right.
Yarandrala and I are fine now.
Never again.
Ruti.
[RIT] I didn't end up
re-joining the Hero's party
after the battle.
I had to help rebuild Loggervia,
but that wasn't all.
Mainly, I felt I shouldn't
put myself back in the position
to risk coming between
Ruti and Gideon again.
[RIT] So I decided to
continue my journey alone.
To think I'd run into
Gideon here in Zoltan.
It's nothing short of a miracle!
Hey, just remembered.
Don't you have a delivery?
Oh my gosh, I forgot
all about that!
[DIR]
Young lady.
[RIT] I've seen you before,
in Loggervia.
My goodness, I'm so honored
that you recognized me.
I've never known
your name, though.
Good grief. I'm the
adventurer Dir, Miss Rit.
It's very important
I speak with you.
Not interested. Good day.
Well, I know who you
really are, Princess.
What do you think of that?
[RIT] So? It's not like I'm
trying to hide it or anything.
[DIR] Oh boy, let's not
get bent outta shape.
I can be a sweetheart
just like Red, you know...
[groans] I... I'm gonna
tell Loggervia
that you're living
here with Red!
That's right, Princess.
You've played with fire
for long enough.
Return to adventuring,
or go back to Loggervia,
either one will do.
That whole royal
succession thing
should be settled by now, right?
I don't care about that.
Eh?
I couldn't care less about
losing my social status
in Loggervia.
I don't need fame and fortune
as long as I can
live like this with Red.
And Red and Rit's Apothecary.
That's all I need.
How could you wanna live
such a boring little life
when you've got
a Blessing like yours?
Who knows?
You may have it right.
But still. This is
exactly what I want.
[RIT]
I'm back!
Welcome home!
[gasps]
What's wrong?
Nothing, it's just,
hearing you say "welcome home"
makes me happy,
even after all the
time we've spent.
Boy, am I hungry.
So let's eat, huh?
Mm-hm!
I don't need to sleep,
and yet, the nights
are long and boring.
It was so much better when
my brother was still around.
[ARES] Ruti, don't be shocked
by what I'm about to say.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but your brother
has left the party.
Why's that?
[ARES] Gideon said he'll keep
an eye on the Demon Lord's army.
Said he feels more useful
as a scout at this point.
I tried to stop him, but he'd
already made up his mind.
There was no changing it.
So, I finally gave up
and let him go.
Why did he tell you?
Why wouldn't he
tell me to my face?
Uh, well, if I had to guess,
I'd say it was probably
a matter of pride.
I can certainly understand that.
It makes perfect sense.
I know you feel uneasy
without your brother around.
After all, you were just
a normal little girl
before you became the Hero.
Plus, compared to Gideon,
you've still only spent
a relatively short
amount of time with me.
But I hope you know
I'll always be here for you.
[RUTI]
He did something to my brother.
[yells]
[RUTI]
Sorry about that, but you see,
my journey must continue.
After all...
I'm the Hero.
But... now there's a hole...
where my brother once was.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku