Dr. Newman's Clinic
You filled my order to a T.
Except, is it safe
to assume that
you still can't get
any blood needles?
[RED sighs] They've been
hard to come by this year.
[NEWMAN]
No luck, huh?
The merchants don't have much
in stock, either, unfortunately.
[JACKSON screams]
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
[clattering]
The Rampage Begins
Hey! You okay in there?
Jackson!
[gasps]
[NEWMAN] This is not good.
He has an irregular heartbeat.
[RED]
Try this.
It's an antidote we made
from gray starfish grass.
How do you know an antidote
is what he needs right now?
Well, it's a First Aid
common skill,
and I've taken it
to the Mastery level.
Much like a doctor,
I usually know how
to relieve symptoms,
even if I may not know
what caused them.
[NEWMAN]
Jackson, drink this.
Doctor Newman.
Isn't that? Come on, Red.
Help me carry him
to my clinic. Hurry.
[RED]
Of course.
Well, he's out of the
woods now, thankfully.
What do you think might've
caused this, Doctor?
[NEWMAN]
A narcotic.
It was that recently
approved medicine.
I'm absolutely certain.
So what you're saying is,
this was an overdose.
That's right. The exact
symptoms and treatments
are as yet unknown to us,
but I'd never have thought
to use gray starfish grass.
You saved the day, Red,
and I'm so thankful.
But I fear, we'll be seeing more
and more patients like this.
I'd like you to go
ahead and stock up
on the medicine we'll need.
Got it, sir.
[RIT] What took so long?
I'm about to starve over here!
[RED] Sorry about that.
Ran into some trouble.
Oh, really? What happened?
I'll tell you later.
So, what're you
feeling for lunch?
I think an omelet
would hit the spot!
I have some leftover
tomatoes that I can use.
It won't take long.
Sounds great!
That's so beyond yummy!
[RED]
Glad you like it, ha.
[RIT] It's so good
I'll even forgive you
for coming home late.
Sorry. I had to stop at
Dr. Newman's for a few minutes.
Hey, Rit, do you remember
that narcotic we heard about
when we went to get
my new compound approved?
A neighbor overdosed and I
had to help save his life.
Needless to say,
it was kind of intense.
Wow! There's already
been an overdose?
I guess it is a dangerous drug.
The doctor says there's
bound to be more.
Gotta stock up on supplies.
That's just awful.
Who would want to sell
something so unsafe?
I have no idea, but it's not
our job to track them down.
'Cause we're just
an apothecary, right?
Yep, we sure are!
[RED]
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's go hang out
by the riverside.
The weather is nice
for a barbecue,
and we could swim!
Just the two of us?
Yep, just us. Sound good?
I mean, yeah, sounds great!
I'm so ready to go have fun!
This is awesome!
I love drake-riding
so very much!
Seriously, this is so fun
it's worth the price!
It's amazing!
Hold on! Whee!
Come on, I'll race ya
to the river!
[RIT] Well, I'm here
and I wore my swimsuit.
So let's go swimming!
[gasps]
Take that!
[gasps] Oh, now you've done it!
Here, back atcha!
Take this!
[BOTH laughing]
[RED]
It's times like these.
I never know
exactly what to say.
[BOTH laugh]
You know, I thought
you'd be a lot more
used to this sort of thing.
Did you really?
Why, do I look like
a girl who dates a lot?
Well, I didn't mean that.
It's just, when you
showed up at my shop,
you were pretty forward
about us, remember?
I kept thinking,
what if he were to reject me?
Or, worse, what if he's
forgotten me altogether?
I was beside myself.
And honestly, I always
assumed you would be
the one more used to
this sort of thing.
Oh, why would you think that?
[RIT] I don't know,
maybe because I try my hardest
to get your attention
on a near-constant basis,
but you never batted an eye.
I feel kind of
invisible sometimes,
like you see me as some little
girl who's in over her head.
[RIT gasps]
[RED] I just didn't want to come
off as lovesick or desperate.
What do you think?
Should we open up
another bottle of wine?
Or would you like to swim?
Well, I think for right now,
let's just enjoy this.
Okay, that sounds good.
And maybe...
Do you see now?
That's how close
I want us to be.
[ARES] The remaining ruins
from the time of
the previous Demon Lord
lie up ahead.
The weapon we seek
has to be there.
It's the only place
that makes sense.
It's fortunate that we
happen to have the Hero
and the Sage with the
greatest Blessings ever.
Which means the chance that our
quest will fail is near zero.
You see? We don't need
worthless fools in our party.
Now, let's prove how easily
we can do this without them.
All right.
Let's set off as soon as
we manage to resupply.
Right, good plan.
I'll go get the water!
Something wrong?
Mr. Crawly Wawly?
[TISSE gasps]
Um, pardon me.
But may I please
ask you something?
Go on.
I was just wondering,
when is it you sleep, milady?
Because I know you're
always wide awake
when I peer into your
tent late at night.
Yeah, I don't sleep.
[gasps]
[RUTI] The Hero's Blessing
includes a resistance
to many things.
Sleep is one of them.
I don't need to sleep,
and I never feel tired.
Not ever.
The same with food.
I no longer need
to eat to survive.
And I'm impervious to heat.
To any kind of environment.
So I'm never uncomfortable
but never refreshed.
This is who I am because
the Divine Blessing demands it.
Emotions are useless.
Therefore, they have
been eliminated.
I'm the Hero.
That means I can't bring
my brother back to us.
[RED] Okay! That was
a very nice diversion,
but let's get to work!
I do love your enthusiasm,
but there's really
not much to do.
Yeah, I suppose you're
right about that.
Oh, hey, what about
that antidote
you mentioned for the narcotic?
Ah, nothing much happening
on that front.
Yes, but based on what I'm
hearing from the adventurers,
the use of that drug
is really spreading.
They said that it
makes you feel like
you're an entirely new person.
Really? A "new person"?
Yeah, not quite sure
what that means,
but apparently it's
the only thing the users
of the drug have been
able to talk about.
[thud]
Please! Help me!
Are you okay?
Oh, this wound looks serious.
Hey, Rit, would you go outside
and see what's happening?
That doesn't just
look like an accident.
I'll go check it out.
[gasps]
[RIT] I know you, you're a
member of Albert's party.
It's Rit. It's Rit.
It's Rit. It's Rit!
It's Rit!
[RIT] He's quick and agile,
no doubt about that.
But... Is this how those with
the Thief's Blessing fight?
What's the matter
with all of you?
[BOTH yell]
[RIT gasps]
[RIT]
Albert!
Greetings, Rit.
I'm sorry to see a member of my
party causing so much trouble.
Would you care to tell me
what's going on?
I swear, I have no idea.
But I never would've imagined
he could be as
vicious as all this.
Who would have?
Well, even so, did you really
have to kill all of them?
One of those guys is
still breathing over there.
Shouldn't you go provide
first aid before it's too late?
It sure would be a big help if
your fiancé were around, huh.
Go ahead and send the apothecary
bill to me, all right?
[RIT]
What a jerk.
[RIT gasps]
[RIT]
Don't mind me.
It's just this habit
I've gotten into
to keep from
killing people like you.
So whenever my Blessing
gives me an urge like this,
I can barely keep it
under control.
They're still investigating
the motive of the crime.
There's been no
progress as of yet.
Do you know who
performed the autopsy?
I've no idea.
The article doesn't
make mention of that.
Do you think it's possible the
drug somehow drove them insane?
All I know is that I've
seen Campbell fight before,
and I never would've
classified him as being strong.
But this time
he wasn't the same.
I think the drug must've
enhanced his strength.
[RED]
You're right.
It seems really off that
Campbell would use an axe.
The Thief's Blessing makes
them prefer light weapons.
So, what now?
Are you going to look into it?
I'm not quite sure.
You want to do that?
All I want is to
sleep just like this.
[gasps]
Hi, what's up, Red?
[RED]
Hey!
Hey, Tanta! Hey, Al!
[AL]
Hello.
I was just about to
go make lunch.
You'll join us, right?
Sure!
Thanks. Only if it's no trouble.
I don't think kids should have
to worry about stuff like that.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, I guess everyone's
hungry, then?
[TANTA]
Yeah!
[RIT, AL, TANTA]
Thank you for the lunch!
There's lots more if you like.
If you're still hungry, I mean.
Chomp
Yeah! More, please, thanks!
You got it.
[RED] She must be
doing this so Al and Tanta
won't be shy about
asking for more.
An extra-large helping!
[RED]
Or not.
[AL]
Guess what, Mr. Red.
I was touched by my
Divine Blessing yesterday.
Really? How was that?
Well, it hasn't
given me any urges yet,
so I guess it's hard to say.
I'm just feeling a little
more anxious than usual.
Tell me something, Al,
your Divine Blessing is
Weapon Master, right?
Yeah.
That's it.
I bet you'll feel that way
until you choose a weapon.
So instead of a powerful urge,
you feel an absence,
which gives you
a sense of anxiety.
But, what does that mean for me?
Can I keep being the
same person I always was?
Al. I know life is hard
when these anxieties press in.
But without the skills
your Blessing grants you,
everything is more difficult.
I know that, but couldn't
I live my life
with just common skills
and still be okay?
Well, it's not like it
can't be done at all,
but it's definitely challenging.
I wish I had the
Warrior's Blessing.
That's the one that my dad has,
so I'm used to that.
[RED] Seriously?
The Warrior is the most
mundane Blessing of all.
It seems Al wants to
keep leading a simple life
rather than being the more
formidable Weapon Master
his Blessing made him to be.
Al, what would you like to
be most when you grow up?
I don't know, that's hard.
I mean, my dad unloads
cargo at the docks,
but I'm not sure if I...
[RED] Well, you know, with that
in mind, how about a knife?
If you master the knife,
then you could easily
slice through the ropes
that lash the cargo down.
Even the thick,
sturdy ropes that others
have trouble cutting
will be nothing for you.
You should take
your time, though,
deciding which weapon's for you.
Right. Thank you, Mr. Red.
Welcome in today,
how can I help you?
Oh wait, you're?
My name's Ria.
As you probably know,
I'm a member of Albert's party.
[RIT]
Yes, what do you want?
What I want first
is to apologize, Rit.
I'm sorry a fellow party member
caused so much trouble.
I regret their actions.
Well honestly it's not
like it was your doing.
So what is Albert up to now?
He's accepted some
guild requests.
More work than he
ever used to take on,
as a matter of fact.
He says he wants to make up for
the lazy summer
months in Zoltan.
Looking back, he must have
nerves of steel.
Extraordinary, really.
Some of our party members
aren't happy about that.
Albert doesn't play
too well with others.
Mundane Blessings frustrate him.
Blessings like the ones
held by you and me.
He seems endlessly
irritated that
we can't live up to
his expectations.
[RED] Albert has the
Blessing of the Champion,
which allows him to
overcome obstacles
and perform great feats.
It also drives him to
show his power to the world
and leave his own
mark upon history.
It pushes him onward.
But he failed to fully harness
this powerful Blessing,
so he ended up out here
in the countryside.
[RIA]
Albert must be fed up with us.
He must've hit his limit.
I'm just scared.
I'm afraid he'll decide to
leave Zoltan altogether.
[RED]
No, I don't think he will.
He may act like a jerk,
but believe me,
he's just trying to be the best
Champion that he can be.
Not to mention.
The guild can't do without him.
He won't be leaving
anytime soon.
[BUI] Hello. Are you
looking for Gideon?
[DANAN]
What did you say?
You seem formidable.
So who are you?
[BUI]
My name is Bui.
I'm looking for Gideon,
the same as you, I'd bet.
What?
So why not search together?
That would be
far more efficient than
looking around by
ourselves, you know?
[RIT] Okay, I've closed
the bedroom shutters.
[RED]
Thanks, the brunt of the storm
will strike around
dawn tomorrow,
according to The
Ancient Mineral Dragon
Weather Observatory's forecast.
[RIT] Yeah, the dragonlings
are flying around
to spread the word.
It's too bad they don't
come here to Zoltan.
I'd love to see them
in person again!
[RED]
Yeah, too bad. Here you go.
Oh, thank you, Red.
[gasps] It's so good!
Warm milk and honey
are just so delicious!
Yeah, it was Ruti's favorite.
So I made it a lot
when she was little.
Is that so?
I wonder what they're all up to.
Ruti and the others.
Last I heard, they were
doing just fine.
They're apparently in
the Bloodsand Desert now.
[RIT]
I see.
[CHILD 6A crying]
It's all right, love.
Ruti, aren't you feeling scared?
You mean about the storm?
Or about this building we're in?
It could fall. It could collapse
and then we'd all be
smooshed like bugs,
dead and twitching
on the ground.
[GIDEON] Any or all of those.
Does anything frighten you?
[RUTI] No. There's
nothing I'm afraid of.
You know that. I don't
get those feelings.
[GIDEON]
Yeah. But I'm scared.
So I'd like to hold hands.
As long as it's all right
with you, of course.
You want my hand?
Yeah, for comfort.
Here, then.
You still feeling scared?
Nope! Not anymore, I guess.
I'm so glad.
I lied. Sorry,
I wasn't scared, really.
I just wanted an excuse
to hold my sister's hand.
How come?
[GIDEON]
No reason.
But people do plenty of things
for no reason, every day.
[RUTI]
Really? They do?
[GIDEON]
You bet.
So if you ever
feel like you want to
hold my hand for no reason,
you can feel free
to let me know.
I wouldn't mind it at all.
[RUTI]
'Kay.
Big Bro, I hope you know
that I love you.
Aw, thanks! You made my day.
Wait, I don't get it, I'm the
one who loves you, right?
So then, what was it that
made you want to thank me?
Why do you think?
'Cause I love
my little sister, too.
That made you smile.
And when you smile,
it means you're happy.
It feels good to see you
feeling happy and showing it.
I'm sure you're right.
Same here.
I'm happy when you
say you love me.
You see that? I'm smiling.
Yeah.
See? That's why I thanked you.
[RUTI] Big Brother, is it okay
if I do something for no reason?
[GIDEON]
Sure, go ahead.
I like this way much better.
Okay, then.
Brother?
What is it?
Thank you.
You promise to
stay with me forever?
Sorry, I wish I could
promise that.
I'm gonna leave to
become a knight.
I need to get stronger so I can
adventure with you someday.
I have to make sure
I'm ready for that.
Oh.
But look, if there's ever
anything you don't want to do,
then you just let me know, okay?
And I will take care
of it for you.
Also, I'm planning to
come visit you on my days off.
Can I bring you anything?
Warm milk with honey.
[knocking]
[gasps]
[RED]
Al!
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku