[NEWMAN] There were
a large number of
stone fragments
embedded in his wound.
Maybe he was struck by a rock
kicked up by the wind.
It's hard to say.
[RED] What was he doing
outside on a night like this?
Al! Are you okay?
[AL screams]
What's wrong?
[AL] Ademi came to our house and
my mom and dad were attacked!
He had an axe!
You've gotta help me!
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
The Chaos After the Storm
[RED]
Are you okay?
How's it look?
[RED]
They're both alive.
[NEWMAN] Good. When Al
said Ademi had an axe,
I'm afraid I feared the worst.
[RED] Yes. It looks like
blunt-force trauma.
What happened tonight?
[RED] It could've been
much worse, but unfortunately,
this attack is bound to
lead to a lot more trouble.
Ademi is the son of Moen,
the captain of the guard.
After the attack,
Ademi vanished.
The people of Southmarsh
were outraged.
They insisted that
the town guard
must have been sheltering him.
But the guards wouldn't
respond to the allegation.
The smoldering
discontent was ready
to burst into flames
at any moment.
Al's parents are being
used as a rallying point
by the people,
a symbol of protest.
So now, they're recovering
in a mansion that
belongs to a Thieves' Guild
official named Bighawk.
And for the time being,
they've entrusted us with Al.
Doesn't Red make a yummy
plate of scrambled eggs?
[AL]
Uh, yeah.
[AL] Thanks for the food.
Um, Miss Rit?
[RIT]
Yes? What is it?
Will you... Will you teach me
how to wield a sword?
[RIT]
Okay, now try and strike me!
[yells]
[gasps] Can we try that again?
Al appears to be
feeling better now.
All thanks to you, Rit.
Actually, it's not me,
it's his Blessing.
He wielded that
weapon with strength
just like he hoped he would
and had the time of his life.
Yeah.
[RIT sighs]
I've never done this before.
It's my first time teaching
another person how to fight.
Hope he doesn't pick up
any of my bad habits.
I think you're
doing a great job.
Thank you, but my master
said there was a lot more to it
than just learning
how to swing a sword.
"There's always a philosophy
behind a blade," he said.
And he made it very clear that
it cannot be taught
by one's Blessing.
I just wonder if I'll be
able to teach Al the same
kinds of things
my master taught me.
[RED]
Sure you can.
Think so?
You are Rit, after all.
What does that mean?
I'm not sure how to respond!
Seriously.
[RED gasps]
Thank you.
[GONZ]
Red!
[RED]
Gonz. Nao.
The town guard just showed up
and took Tanta away!
Huh?
They what?
[NAO] He was out playing
in the neighborhood
when some of
the guards showed up
and took him away without
giving any kind of explanation.
So, of course, my husband
went to the guardhouse,
but they won't allow a visit.
[AL] Hold on! What do you mean,
Tanta's been taken away?
I get the situation.
But what do you want me to do?
If you're willing,
I want the guild to request
a joint inquiry
with the town guard.
[GALATINE] I see.
Then you can be present
for Tanta's questioning,
very clever, indeed.
Can I assume it's
Champion Rit who will be
working to resolve this matter
for everyone involved?
[GALATINE]
Very well.
It's a small price to pay
in order to have
such a capable ally in my debt.
So I'll take it.
[GALATINE]
Mido and Nao.
I don't like to see youngsters
looking so sad.
It's such a waste.
I'm owed a small favor,
which should
come in handy for us.
This kind of thing
goes with the territory.
Give it to the captain.
Leave it all to me.
What do you want?
[RIT chuckles]
[gasps] Go inform
the captain immediately!
[MOEN]
That won't be necessary.
Moen, Captain of the Guard
State your business here.
[MIDO]
Tanta!
Daddy!
They didn't mistreat you,
did they?
I'm so relieved
to see you in one piece!
No, they didn't do
anything to hurt me.
[AL]
Tanta! What a relief!
Oh, Al! You came, too?
Well, yeah, 'cause.
I was worried.
It's true, I gave
the order for him
to be brought in
for questioning.
But I had no idea
they'd tie him up.
I'm sorry about that.
And I never received any word
that his father had
requested a visit.
My apologies there, too.
Tanta's fine, so let's
just forget about it.
Why did you do this
to the kid, though?
[MOEN]
In order to question him.
My men think there's
a possibility Ademi's
actually been killed by
a Southmarsh resident.
Well, that's far from
the way we see it, Sir.
The guards always doted over
him, that's just the way it was.
Then, of course,
there was the terrible attack
that cost us the life
of one of my men.
You see, Campbell and
the other perpetrators
all hail from Southmarsh.
And now,
with this latest attack,
my men have mistaken
the victims for perpetrators.
They don't trust anything,
especially not
second-hand reports.
Believe it or not,
some of them even doubt
it was Ademi that
Al saw in his house.
What?
I saw him myself!
It was definitely Ademi!
Understand, I can't
rule out that you're lying,
which is a reasonable assumption
under these circumstances.
There's too much about the
latest attack that puzzles me.
For instance, how is it that
your parents survived?
And why would Ademi
allegedly use an axe?
That's why my men
hold to the belief that
the attacker wasn't Ademi,
but someone from Southmarsh.
Also, they're convinced your
parents' injuries were staged!
I mean. I don't really believe
Ademi would do something
like that, either.
[AL]
Tanta!
Please don't misunderstand!
I didn't mean I thought you
were lying or anything, Al!
It's just, Ademi
apologized to me.
He said he was
sorry for hitting me.
He was having a tough time.
He said the Bar Brawler Blessing
was making him
resort to violence.
But deep down, his dream
is to join the town guard.
He knows the town guard's job
is to protect people,
not hurt them.
That's what he'd rather do.
But he...
"You don't have to worry.
I won't hit anyone again
for no reason." That's what
he said to me.
Interesting. What do you
think he meant by that?
I don't know.
Your name is Red, correct?
I'd like a word
with you, if I might.
Of course. Sorry, Mido,
but would you mind
seeing Al safely home?
Sure.
[MOEN]
The Champion Rit.
Word out in the field is that
you've retired from adventuring.
But if I'm going to seek
your help with this issue,
then there are definitely
quite a few things
that you'll need to know.
Of course, you will
be compensated.
All right, I'm listening.
I appreciate it.
I hope you won't
take this the wrong way,
but I have a question.
[MOEN]
Go ahead.
Were there any signs that Ademi
might've used that new drug?
[gasps] I taught my son that
anyone who involves himself
in things like that
is worse than the scum
on the bottom of his shoe!
Surely you see it,
though, right?
The very real similarities
with the attack by Campbell.
There's no evidence
for that yet,
because no one in Zoltan
has the Appraisal skill.
What do you know about it?
We believe it is possible
it's creating another
Divine Blessing.
[gasps] Hi, welcome, sir.
I assume you must be Al.
[AL]
Hey, welcome back, Mr. Red!
Hello there.
Where's Miss Rit?
She probably won't
be back for a while.
[AL]
Really?
But, what do you say
I help you train?
[AL]
You really mean it?
Right. Prepare yourself.
[AL gasps]
Where's your weapon, though?
I think a broom should be
sufficient against you.
[AL yells]
What just happened?
You lost your temper
at my comment
and blindly charged me,
so I knocked you off your feet.
Weapon Master protects you
against fear and confusion,
but makes you vulnerable
to angry reactions.
Which means you must learn
to control yourself.
Well done. I think you'll
be levelling up in no time.
[RED] Now be careful here.
Your flank's exposed!
Oh gosh. I'm totally beat.
[RED] Well, then we
should call it a day.
Um. I was wondering,
why are you a D-rank adventurer
if you're so good?
Just because you're
good at something
doesn't mean that's
what you have to do.
I enjoy my life here a lot.
I'm running a shop with Rit,
and I get to meet
good people like you.
All while providing a vital
service to the community.
And if anyone close to me is
ever in need, I can lend a hand.
I really do enjoy
all that stuff.
Hold on. What about
living up to your Blessing?
And becoming a great hero
that goes down in history?
Wouldn't that sort of life
be even better than this?
[RED chuckles] You used to be
anxious about your Blessing.
Once, you even said you wished
you had the
Warrior Blessing instead.
But now, you've completely
grown into it.
Well, I guess so.
[RED] Hey, that's great
if it's what you want.
Live or die by the sword,
and you'll make
a name for yourself.
That's not a bad life.
But it just wasn't for me.
[AL gasps]
It's that simple.
I was just given a sword by
someone I've never met before.
[RED]
A sword?
[AL] I think it was someone
connected to Bighawk.
Heard the news
from your old man.
You've awakened to
your Blessing, huh?
[AL]
What's that?
It's a boon for a future
Weapon Master, that's what.
May the Almighty's
blessing be upon you.
[AL] It's a famous blade
of great worth,
and I thought maybe I could
become a champion
like Rit if I had it,
that was the idea.
But now, I'm not sure
if it was my own idea
or my Blessing that was
making me think that.
Good question.
You could ask your sword
if you're uncertain.
Does it want to cut down
mountains of foes?
Or does its focus seem to be
protecting those dear to you?
All you need to do is ask
your sword what it wants, Al.
Then again, I'm just
repeating what I once heard
from a skilled spear fighter.
[RUFFIAN 7A screams]
Gimme a break, will ya?
I really didn't anticipate it
taking days to hunt you down.
You've made me waste
precious time, y'know.
[gasps]
[RIT] Who would plant a bomb
on one of their own men?
Is it really possible there's
someone that cruel in Zoltan?
Ugh.
[RIT]
I let my guard down.
It's not like me to end up
in a position like this.
[RUFFIAN 7B yells]
[RUFFIANS cackle]
[DANAN] Oh my.
That's no way to treat a lady.
Hello there, Rit.
What a surprise.
I can't say I expected
to find you here.
[RIT]
Danan.
[RIT] O spirits of water,
cleanse this body of mine.
Now, then, tell me what
you're doing here.
I'm here on the orders
of the Hero.
She requested I go find Gideon.
[RIT gasps] Does that mean
you plan on taking him back?
Well, yes, that was
definitely the plan,
but Gideon's found somewhere
to call home, hasn't he?
I'll leave it at that.
I don't see any need to
drag him back. However.
A stalker demon?
It would certainly seem that
all's not well here, either.
What's an intermediate
demon doing in Zoltan?
No clue. Who was that
ruffian who exploded?
[RIT]
Some drug dealer.
They were most likely
a member of the Thieves' Guild.
[DANAN] I'd sure like some help
from both of you on this.
But it's better for all involved
if Gideon doesn't know I'm here.
Which means,
we should exchange info.
I'm close by.
All set up at a little inn
in Southmarsh.
All right, thanks.
I guess I'd better
get going now.
Till then.
Well, this world is
certainly full of surprises.
Hi, I'm finally home.
Welcome back.
You sure had a long day, huh?
Yeah, wow, I'm exhausted.
[RIT sighs]
That's better.
You sound like you're sinking
into a hot bath or something.
A bath would be nice.
I forgot we talked
about building one.
[RED] Don't worry,
I've already talked to Gonz.
He said he'd build it for us.
Hooray!
[RED]
Oh, yeah.
Al received a sword from
one of Bighawk's men
just recently.
[RED] He was hoping you'd be
able to take a look at it.
Detect magic.
[RIT]
The blade is crimson steel.
The hilt is ebony.
It was made by a swordsmith
in the Island Kingdom of Igos.
It's not half bad.
So, is it magic?
Well, it does have a basic
magic enhancement.
Oh, wait. Yes, I'm right.
This sword has
a Locate spell cast on it.
The location of
the sword's bearer
is constantly being
conveyed to the caster.
So the question becomes,
why would Bighawk
want to know where Al is?
Could it be he plans on
using him in some way?
[RED] What is it?
Is there something wrong?
No, it's just...
I wonder how long we'll be able
to live together like this.
But what do you mean?
Forever, of course.
I want that, too.
To be with you forever.
[AL gasps]
Are you sure it's okay?
I had my first sword made
especially for me
and I think you should, too!
You can't go wrong
with Mogrim. He's excellent.
Even if he is irresponsible.
I'm irresponsible, huh?
Now, is this the little lad
who's wanting a shotel?
[AL]
Yes, sir!
Don't worry, I'll help you
pick one out.
I just so happen to know
a thing or two about shotels.
[TOWNSMAN 7A]
At last, the time is here!
What the?
[TOWNSMAN 7A]
Come! Fight alongside us!
Strange things are
afoot here in Zoltan.
Every one of you
knows it to be true!
[TOWNSMAN 7B]
The town guard is definitely
harboring that brat, Ademi!
Maya, Keith.
Hi, Red.
This looks like a protest.
Yes, people have been
gathering like this
all over Southmarsh
as well, lately.
I heard that Bighawk has been
paying people to show up.
[MAYA] And the town guard's
so busy with the protests,
they can't even
investigate the attacks.
It's getting absurd.
Hold on, isn't that Oliver?
What a moron!
[MAYA] He looks so
out of place, doesn't he?
I just want my party member back
so we can get back to
our adventuring again.
Can you speak with him?
Sure. I'll talk to him
when he comes by the shop.
[CROWD cheers]
[MAYA]
Thank you.
[THEODORA]
That's...
[ARES]
A gargantuan demon?
Tisse, I want you to go look for
the previous
Demon Lord's weapon.
Yes, understood.
[RUTI] What's a gargantuan demon
doing down here, anyway?
Aren't the former Demon Lord
and the Demon Lord Taraxon
part of the same
group of monsters?
[roars]
[RUTI] All of demonkind
have certain blessings
that share the same role.
The Almighty expects
them to be evil.
At least, that's how
my brother sees it.
It's quite fascinating.
[yells]
Ares, look out!
[ARES gasps]
[MR CRAWLY WALLY]
Kyu, kyu!
What? What is it?
Oh, let's have a look.
[gasps] Is this it?
[GIANT DEMON 7A roars]
[RUTI] Ares, watch where
you're standing.
[ARES]
Uh... Oh, right.
I used to provide cover for
my brother before he left.
But Theodora and I,
we won't be doing that for you.
You must protect yourself.
[gasps] Please forgive me.
[ARES] It would be so much
easier to cast spells
if Gideon were here.
No, wait! This is all
Danan and Yarandrala's fault.
[TISSE]
I'm back.
What happened?
Did you find a weapon that could
eradicate the Demon Lord's army?
[TISSE]
Mm-hm.
[ARES gasps] Anyone know
what that thing is?
It's an airship.
It's extraordinary, milady.
Yes.
So, is there anywhere
in particular
you think you'd like to go?
There is, but I mustn't.
Not as long as I'm the Hero.
So, these wings.
It would seem they've
been wasted on me.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku