[RED] It's time.
The double bed finally arrived.
Let's try out the bed.
Yeah. I'm coming.
Over here.
Hey, your face matches
your name. [giggles]
And your heart is beating
a million miles a minute.
Don't act like yours isn't.
[RED gasps]
Red. I just...
[RED]
Rit.
I'm sorry. Because of
my training,
my hands have always
been really calloused.
[RED]
Don't worry, I like your hands.
[creaking]
It's probably just Al getting
a snack or a glass of water.
He must be tiptoeing around
so that he won't disturb us.
Rit, I was thinking.
Maybe not tonight.
It was never my intention
to take it this far right now,
but I guess I got
a little caught up
in the heat of the moment.
[RED]
Yeah, same here.
Goodnight, Rit.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
The Man Who Would Be a Hero
[DIR laughs]
Master Al!
Bighawk wants to
see you, little man.
Do you mind coming
with us for a while?
[DIR] Aw, there's
no need to be scared.
[RIT chuckles]
[DIR] Hm? Wait, that laugh
sounded a lot like...
Rit?!
So you thought I was Al?
Well, I'm certainly
sorry to disappoint you.
I realized something about
the Locate Spell on this sword.
It might reveal
where the bearer is,
but not who they actually are.
I guess you fell
for my trap, huh?
Nobody makes a fool of me! Go!
I wasn't expecting to see
the Champion Rit here.
This is sure to be
a thrilling battle.
My instincts are telling me
you're not human.
[RIT]
An axe demon!
[roars]
[knocking]
Who goes there?
[GODWIN]
It's me.
I know that voice. It must be
one of Bighawk's men!
[AL]
What are you...?
[GODWIN] The Champion Rit thinks
she pulled a fast one on us.
But no matter, it's best we
let her think
whatever she likes.
Because in reality,
we're one step ahead of her.
[gasps] So, what do you
creeps want with me?
We want you to become
Southmarsh's greatest new hero.
A hero?
[BIGHAWK]
So you're the famous Al.
Don't you look like
a feisty little one.
[AL gasps]
[BIGHAWK]
My comrades.
Every single one of us
is an outsider in Zoltan.
So, let's try to get along.
Unlike the weaklings
who were raised here,
I was brought up
in the cruel slums
of the Duchy of Daikan.
Whether friend or foe,
I slaughtered whoever
got in my way.
And now I've grown
so powerful that
none of those fools
in the council
would ever dare
lay a finger on me.
[BIGHAWK]
But I'm not stopping there.
I have what it takes to
climb this ladder far higher,
and if I become the
top dog here in Zoltan,
I'll make some serious changes.
And that's where the
new drug comes in, my friends.
I call it the Devil's Blessing.
It's made from the hearts
of 50 axe demons.
I've been flooding
the market with it.
But the devil can't
give a Blessing.
Up until this point,
each of us was
granted one Blessing
by the Almighty Demis.
So we go through our measly
little lives
fulfilling that role.
Isn't that right, Master Al?
But for the unlucky majority,
their Blessings and their
desires don't line up.
Thousands are forced to
pursue a life they don't want.
They have no choice
but to die in despair.
My godforsaken Blessing
is Master Torturer.
Demis has condemned me
to a violent life
in a dark hole filled
with the stench of
blood, sweat, and piss.
How could anyone
call that a blessing?
I won't accept it!
No kid wants to be a monster
when they grow up!
That's why the Devil's
Blessing is our savior.
Whoever takes it
gets a new Blessing.
They aren't trapped
by fate and can finally
take life into their own hands!
[AL] People can
change their Blessing?
Yes, and the groundwork's
already been laid.
The last part of
our plan is to find
the final spark to
get this fire started.
Based on what we've heard,
that spark might be you.
Hey, bring the kid in!
[AL]
Ademi!
Sorry, it's all my fault.
I just wanted to be a good
guardsman like my dad is.
So, I tried that new drug.
[AL gasps]
I know. It's bad.
Huh, I wonder where
Oliver ran off to.
[ADVENTURER 8A]
Ouch!
Watch it, what's the
hell's your problem?
[ALBERT]
Hey.
Huh?
Are you giving
that lady trouble?
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheering]
[TOWNSMAN 8B]
Look, it's Bighawk!
[TOWNSMAN 8C]
He's our real leader!
[gasps]
Good people!
Just yesterday, my men and I
protested before
the Zoltan Council.
It's horrible, the way
that Zoltan officials
allow the criminal who attacked
poor Al's family
to walk the streets.
So, we told them
that we demand justice!
They have the town guard
canvasing the entire city,
but they still can't find the
one responsible for the crime?
The reason is obvious!
The attacker was
the young Ademi.
This boy is the captain of the
guard's own flesh and blood!
The anger you feel?
It is righteous!
There is no justice in Zoltan!
How many of us have to die
before they take notice?
They do nothing but mock us.
And tell us that we'd
all be better off dead!
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheer]
Here is my irrefutable evidence.
[BIGHAWK]
These two guardsmen have bravely
decided to come forward.
We are here today to
denounce the town guard!
We both confess that we
took part in hiding Ademi!
You all should know,
there was a conscious effort
within our ranks to write off
your accusations as nonsense.
[TOWNSPEOPLE yelling]
[BIGHAWK] Unfortunately,
the time of forgiveness
has long been over!
[BIGHAWK]
So I declare to you, my people.
Today marks the
beginning of a revolution
in the name of justice!
Claim your vengeance, Master Al!
Restore balance
and execute the villain
who tried to slaughter
your parents.
With one fatal blow,
you can spark our revolution.
Help us light the fire that will
one day forge
a bright, new Zoltan!
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheering]
Is this real?
Do you... Do you
want me to kill him?
[gasps]
[BIGHAWK] That's right.
The fact of the situation
is that Ademi tried
to kill your parents.
It simply doesn't
matter why or how.
But... But you.
Wasn't it you who
made him do it at all?
Of course not.
We gave Ademi a drug that could
greatly benefit his future
and let him borrow an axe.
I even kept the boy safe after
he ran away, but that's it.
Just think about it.
Because he took my drug,
Ademi currently has
two different Blessings.
If you were to cut him down,
your Blessing would
grow so strong.
[gasps] He's right,
Ademi is my enemy.
Why would I
hesitate to kill him?
[yells]
My sword is telling me that it
doesn't want to spill his blood.
Starting now, I decide who
I should or shouldn't kill.
[BIGHAWK]
You're such a pain in my ass.
[gasps]
Ademi!
It's the Devil's Blessing.
It causes a murderous
impulse whenever
the holder lays eyes on an axe.
I thought you would have
put it together by now,
but that's the
reason he attacked.
Stop, you have to
snap out of it!
Hey, kid.
You better kill him before
he kills you! Hurry up.
[AL gasps]
Earlier, you said
it was wise to let Rit
think she pulled
a fast one on you,
you also mentioned that she can
believe whatever she likes.
Well, I agree.
It's best to let your foes think
they have the upper hand.
C'mon, Al!
Let's get out of here!
It's Red!
Acrobatics Mastery. Slow Fall.
Hey! Don't let them get away!
[ADEMI]
That's gross.
It's a tonic that the wild
elves make to temporarily
suppress any urges
caused by your Blessing.
Keep that to yourselves because
the Church doesn't
support its use.
Hello there. I take it
that you're Red.
I guess you're the one
helping Rit. Bui, was it?
Yes.
[RED] Great. Then let's
proceed as planned.
I don't understand.
Just wait, I'll need
both of your help, too.
[AL, ADEMI gasp]
Need back up?
I should be okay.
I'll take your word for it.
Oh. Hey, Albert.
That's "sir" to
a D rank like you.
Martial Art. Swallow's Approach!
What the hell?
You parried my magic sword
with that hunk of metal?
[ALBERT]
Was last time all an act?
You can try to hide it,
but this means
you and I are champions
of the same level.
That's some kind of demon blade.
Hey, what's Bighawk doing here?
He's nothing but
an empty shell, now,
but his body works nicely.
I make wishes come true for
those who agree to my contracts.
Bighawk's greatest wish was to
become King of Zoltan,
so we made a deal.
I was working hard on turning
that dream into a reality,
but I decided that I'd like
to be the king instead.
Now I understand, you're just
a lowly contract demon.
You want power.
I have to imagine you've
had a tough time so far.
After all, Zoltan is nothing
but a sleepy, little town.
All of our leaders are
determined by seniority.
Talent and ambition
don't matter here.
Even in groups like
the Thieves Guild,
it could take you 20 years
to reach the top.
Yeah, I've picked up
on that myself.
I don't think this town
will ever learn.
And the people here,
they're so lazy.
I've never met a group of
capable individuals
so complacent.
That explains Albert.
He can't enjoy the
quiet life, just like you.
We can only forge
contracts with those
who have darkness
in their hearts.
A strong will is also required,
a trait that is remarkably
rare in this town.
I'm sick and tired of wasting
my time in this damn place!
I hate these spineless people.
They'll go into
a complete conniption
over a stupid owlbear!
I was an utter idiot to ever
step foot here
in the first place!
If I somehow die
in Zoltan, every second
I've walked this planet
will be for nothing!
There's no need to
worry about me, D rank.
For I can finally
become a great hero!
Making deals with demons
might not seem heroic,
but I'll never take part
in any evil schemes.
Can't you understand
that you already have?
This mess is hurting people.
A necessary sacrifice.
My dream is noble.
I want to unite Zoltan to defeat
the Demon Lord's
army once and for all.
The contract we forged
does nothing more than
dedicate my life
to this valiant effort.
That's the truth.
It's certainly not based on
malice or anything like that.
You see?
I'll turn Zoltan
into a military power!
We'll all fight under
the Hero's banner!
For I am the Champion Albert!
And I am worthy of
the Champion's Blessing!
I will finally become
my true self!
So, Red, join me in my quest!
It's like the two of us are
cut from the same cloth.
You could be a hero!
Really, a hero?
That's right.
The future of Zoltan depends
entirely on your next few words!
Or should I say,
the future of the world!
How exhilarating.
This lazy place,
with some help from us both,
could become mighty!
Tell me, what will
it be, D rank?
Will you join me, battle the
Demon Lord, and become a hero?
Or will you defeat me and be the
savior of a quiet little town?
I don't want to be
a hero or a savior.
[gasps]
Looks to me like
you've drastically
underestimated
our town's abilities.
What are you...?
Well, I'm just an
apothecary, but I imagine
that these men are
here to arrest you.
[gasps] You have everything
it takes to be a hero!
You're strong and too smart
to be living here.
Why waste your power?
It isn't a waste at all.
Running the shop with Rit
is the only thing that I want.
I can't go down in
history as a filthy criminal.
Let me be defeated by
a hero at the very least!
I'll do anything to
give my life meaning!
For I am the Champion Albert!
Stop! Don't do it!
Do you even realize
how strong you are?
You could've put
an end to my plan
with your hands tied
behind your back.
I can't believe
that it came to this.
Listen to me.
Being a hero is about so much
more than physical strength.
Sure I might be strong,
but I'm still not a hero.
I was hoping someday
that role would go to you.
You wanted to be a hero
more than anyone,
and you suffered because of it.
Your determination alone
made you worthy
of that title, Albert.
Despite all of your flaws,
you were still
the hero of Zoltan.
They should be headed back
any minute now.
It's them!
Look, Al is home!
And that punk, Ademi!
Hover.
What's going on?
Did the town guard
put you up to this?
No, they didn't.
I decided to come here
out of my own free will.
The same goes for Ademi.
That's true. I just want to be
up here right next to Al.
Everyone. Let's go home!
Before something bad happens
or somebody gets hurt.
We should all go home!
Ademi and I are friends now.
Tomorrow we can play together!
Don't worry about the past!
Have you lost your mind?
The boy you call "friend"
nearly killed your family!
You're wrong,
that wasn't him at all,
an evil demon took his form.
That could happen to anyone
taking those new drugs.
You could turn into
a demon, too,
and hurt the people
you really care about!
That's why we need to
get home while its safe!
Al! Are you saying
you can forgive Ademi?
Yes, I am.
If the victim can forgive him,
there's no reason
for us to fight.
5 days later
[RED, RIT sigh]
Installing a tub
sure was an amazing idea.
Agreed. Gonz did great.
I didn't realize
a bath could be so nice.
Y'know, we haven't spent
our entire reward
for getting to the bottom
of those attacks.
Is there anything else
this place needs?
Woah, did you just use
your Stealth skill on me?
I didn't even hear
a little splashing.
[giggles]
[gasps]
Hey, I was wondering.
What's on your mind?
Is this what you want?
If you would've
gone with Albert,
maybe you could've
rejoined the Hero's party.
You never know, it might've
made Ares reconsider.
I honestly don't know
what I would've done
a few months back, but now?
I only want this.
That's sweet, but Ruti
and the rest of the party
might need your help
somewhere down the line.
If for some reason
they did, I wouldn't go.
There are hundreds of people
who can aid the Hero.
But there's only one person
who can be with you.
I'm sorry.
That came out all wrong.
Well, then, here I go.
[RED]
I love you, Rit.
You may think you know
how much I love you,
but it's at least hundred times
more than that.
You've become
the center of my world
and I would do anything for you.
[RED]
So I'll be staying right here.
I couldn't care less
what people say.
I'd rather be by your side
than be a hero any day.
And, who are you?
Hey, Belial.
Huh? Wait, how do you
know my real name?
Oh. You're Shisandan...
It's pretty lucky that Red
sent me with those boys,
or we would've ran
into each other earlier.
Things would have
been bad for you
if you had revealed
my true identity.
I never expected you would
start peddling
the Devil's Blessing.
What would you have done
if the humans found out
you don't need demon
hearts to make the drug?
Tell me, did you have
some sort of grand plan?
You know as well as I do
that the Devil's Blessing
has the potential to unleash
humankind's true power,
and that's why the
Almighty forbids its use.
It was an attempt to put
an end to you lousy heretics!
I am Belial!
I hereby revoke
my contract with Bighawk!
Listen up, Albert!
I can make your wish come true!
You can escape this place
now and join the Hero!
That doesn't matter
to me anymore.
Too bad!
Remember you forged
a pact devoting your life
to the battle against
the Demon Lord!
That contract doesn't allow you
to rot away in a cell!
Now make your wish!
Okay, then. Do as you please.
[AL]
Thanks for everything.
I'm excited for
my first adventure.
Your time has come.
I'd say that you certainly
look the part, Al!
We're only starting out
as a D-rank party.
I'm just glad to have a party!
All of us have similar
goals and priorities.
The words Al spoke on that day,
they prevented
a lot of violence.
Now we'll work together
to keep the peace.
I think that's
the role of a hero.
[RED]
Good luck out there, Al.
Thanks!
[RED] Weird, I kind of
feel like I have a son now.
[RIT] I was just thinking
the same thing!
[RED]
Kids aren't so bad, huh?
[RIT]
No, they aren't.