The airship's
really been stolen?
I think it's time to face facts.
The Hero and Tisse
are long gone.
They've gone and
they've left us behind.
[ARES] That can't be true!
It's just impossible!
How do they plan on
fighting without my magic?
[sighs] I don't know,
but the Hero will manage.
[gasps] What? It can't be.
It's the Hero's Badge.
But why would she
leave it behind?
[TISSE] Hard to starboard!
Steady as she goes!
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
Days of Peace and Ease
[MEGRIA] Really? You hunted
down the bladesharks?
[BUI] Yes. Eliminated
every one of them.
Well, then, congratulations!
You're B rank now.
That qualified you!
If you would,
please sign right here...
[OLIVER]
Wow, he's B rank already?
He literally just signed up as
an adventurer the other day.
Well, there haven't been
any B-rank adventurers
at all around here
since Albert left, you know.
I heard he played
a part in resolving
that Devil's Blessing incident.
He's well suited to being
a hero, it would seem.
Whatever.
Look, these bladesharks
are boring to me.
I've got better things to do.
Pardon me, but who was it
that fled in fear
instead of defeating those
tiny bladesharks in the harbor?
[OLIVER] I wasn't feeling
very good, that's all!
It was an off day!
[TISSE]
It is I, Tisse Garland,
assassin and member of
the Assassins' Guild.
But I guess I'm an airship
pilot now? I dunno.
S'cuse me. Why're we
going to Zoltan?
Because there's
a medicine maker there.
[TISSE]
Medicine?
[RUTI] Yes. I have
all my hopes pinned on it.
[BELIAL] Believe me.
The last thing in the world
we would ever want is go to war
with the humans of this land.
We're no different than you.
We even worship the same god,
the Almighty Demis.
And we seek to destroy
the Demon Lord!
That heretic who
defies the Almighty!
[RUTI]
How interesting.
It's too bad
my brother isn't here.
I'd like to talk
it over with him.
[RUTI] So. This is the
Devil's Blessing, then?
Yes! It's a drug made
from axe demon hearts.
And as such, it gives rise
to the Axe Demon Blessing.
It also allows
its user to transfer
Blessing levels,
which can be useful.
The way it works is,
one dose transfers
one level of an innate blessing
to the Devil's Blessing.
And?
[BELIAL] And as you know,
your Blessing won't level up
until you slay a foe
with a Blessing
rated as high as yours.
Monster Grave
But by using the drug to
temporarily weaken
your Blessing,
Monster Grave
you can quickly level it up
by slaying lower-level foes.
Furthermore, the Devil's
Blessing prevents
your combat ability
from weakening,
which, as I'm sure
you can imagine,
is a priceless gift
when it really counts!
Monster
Grave
No doubt about it,
this drug will definitely
help defeat the Demon Lord!
[RUTI]
So, it weakens one's Blessing?
I'll give it a try.
Poisons and curses
don't affect me, anyway.
[BELIAL]
This is bad!
The drug transforms the slain
axe demon's malice into a curse,
and then it binds
the demon's Blessing to it.
If the curse doesn't manifest,
then I'm afraid
the Axe Demon Blessing
may be lost!
And after that...
[RUTI] I'm going to
want a steady supply
for what I have to do next.
In Zoltan, I want to
hide that I'm the Hero.
To do that, I will need you to
treat me as a fellow traveler.
[TISSE]
What? I can't do that!
How can the Hero
pretend to be a commoner?
I break into a sweat
just standing next to her!
My back is sopping wet,
and I have to do
my laundry every night!
No disrespect, milady,
but do you know
anything at all about
being a traveler?
No, I don't.
Therefore, if my little act
ends up being unconvincing,
I'll need you to lend your help.
Oh dear. I fear
I may disappoint you.
I know I can count on you.
You can stay calm, even with me.
[TISSE]
Wow! I trained to maintain an
inscrutable expression,
but my heart is in overdrive.
[sighs] Not a customer in sight.
I'm not surprised.
Folks tend to stay inside
when it gets this cold. Here.
[RED]
Thanks.
This lack of customers
in the winter is a problem.
If only we sold something people
would want on a really cold day.
Any suggestions?
Well, in Loggervia,
we have hand warmers.
Hand warmers.
Problem is, making them
would actually
require Intermediate Alchemy.
Oh, no, I discovered a new way
to make them in my travels.
A "new way"?
Yeah, but I wonder.
About what?
Know what you said about
that Multiply Potion?
Well, maybe this is
a bad idea, too.
It's not. This one
is a great idea.
[RED]
That's a relief.
[GONZ] We don't see you
onsite all that often.
[RED] I came to bring you
a product sample.
[GONZ]
Huh? How is it so warm?
This is a hand warmer.
It's designed to provide warmth
for about 15 hours.
Well, it's amazing!
I'd definitely buy it.
[WORKER 9A]
This is great!
[RED]
It's freezing out here.
[RIT]
Red.
[RED]
Hey, Rit.
How'd it go?
I'd say it was
a marketing marvel.
That's great. Here!
Huh?
[RIT]
Just grab the end of my mittens.
[gasps]
[RIT]
Yay! Well? Nice and warm?
[RED]
Feels good.
Snow!
[RED] Huh. It doesn't
usually snow in Zoltan.
I wish I'd kept some of
those hand-warmer samples.
[chuckles] Ta-da! I decided
to keep one just for us!
You're the best, Rit.
[RIT]
Here. Warm yourself up.
You're colder than me, I bet.
I was born in the north,
so I'll be fine.
[RED]
All right.
[gasps]
[RED] Why don't we
take a little stroll?
[RED]
No one will bother us here.
So, I hate to ask,
but what's going on, Red?
What're you about to do?
[RED]
If you don't mind.
This should keep
both of us plenty warm.
You know, you're missing
the main event.
You see me all the time...
Look at the snow.
I've never seen you
like this, though.
Amid the falling snow, at night.
[RED] Sorry! Did I
say something weird?
[giggles] Wait,
why are you blushing?
I was the one caught off guard!
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to embarrass you.
[RIT] Hey, Red?
No one's here. We're alone.
[TISSE] These clothes should
help you blend in a bit more.
I think we should use aliases.
Milady is "Ruhr,"
and I'll be "Tifa."
[RUTI]
Hang on a second.
[GOBLINS scream]
I noticed a goblin hamlet
from the airship,
so I just borrowed this.
So, you defeated the goblins?
[RUTI] Uh-uh. There was a
sickness spreading among them,
so I used Healing Hands.
This is my reward.
They weren't bad goblins.
[TISSE]
Wow, you're amazing, milady.
No, I'm just a simple
traveler named Ruhr.
[TISSE] There's a knight
barring the bridge ahead.
We'll have to
take a little detour.
No, we cross here.
Uh, okay.
I am the great Otto!
And this'll cost ya!
For you to pass, you must
give me a hundred perills!
Why though?
Simply because I said so!
[RUTI]
Then I see no reason to pay.
Goodbye, now.
[TRAVELER 9B]
That was weird.
Yeah, you wanna get out of here?
[TISSE] Everyone's looking.
Everyone's looking.
Everyone looking at milady.
[OTTO]
Hey! You! Halt right there!
I am Otto! Call me
Otto the Drakerider!
What?
Just hold it right there.
I'm seeking a trusty partner
to fight by my side,
so I'm challenging to battle
all who attempt to cross.
[RED]
Ah. So you're the one
causing the trouble
on the bridge.
I'm "trouble," am I?
Men of ambition
are misunderstood
by little men like you.
It's fine. I met my match
in the form of
a woman warrior
and it was glorious,
so I can forgive you
for being rude.
[RED]
Lucky me.
And guess what else
I've decided?
I'm going to propose to my sweet
little soldier as soon as I can.
[OTTO] Unfortunately,
my arms and armor
and all the rest of
my possessions
were swept away in the river.
[RED]
Yeah, so?
Forgive me, but you're
gonna gimme all your money!
[OTTO screams]
That was bad.
I got so mad that I punched him
as hard as I could.
Well, what's done is done.
It would've caused
trouble next spring,
so I just took it out.
[GUARD 9A]
Wait right there.
I'll go fetch the butcher
and a wagon.
Hey, Ruhr, I think we should
go and find an inn.
After we're settled,
I'll scout the area.
Sounds good to me.
[RED]
Hey.
[GUARD 9A]
Oh, it's you, Red.
You've got last-minute arrivals
down to a science, huh?
I take work seriously.
[GUARD 9A] Then maybe you could
try arriving ahead of time.
Anyway, feel like
having a drink?
[GUARD 9A] Daikon, beef tendon,
egg, and hanpen fishcake!
And I'll splurge with
hot mustard and a beer!
[RED] I'll have daikon, a
sausage, and a chikuwa fishcake.
And beer in a glass, please.
Hope you enjoy.
By the way, Red,
tell me it isn't true.
You're not selling your
hot mustard anymore?
Yeah, I only have
enough ingredients
to make it for personal use now.
That's too bad.
The supply in town's
never been very stable.
[GUARD 9A]
Another, Oparara!
You bet! Welcome!
Daikon, tendon, egg,
four chikuwa fishcakes,
and hot mustard.
[OPARARA]
Coming right up!
Oparara, didn't you have
a booster seat for kids?
[OPARARA]
Oh, sure thing.
[TISSE]
Thank you very much.
[RED]
You're welcome.
You okay?
Oh, sorry.
New faces always
make me curious.
Plus, you didn't even
hesitate to order hot mustard.
Yeah, 'cause you can't
have oden with it.
[RED] She's pretty small,
but she's in good shape.
And her gear looks
smart and practical.
It's obvious she's a real pro.
And yet, she's keeping
a low profile.
Her work must require her
to avoid attention.
Maybe she's a thief or a spy.
She could even be an assassin.
[TISSE] Shoot. Don't tell me
he noticed my concealed weapons.
He's been around.
He looks strong and
has wounds that have
been treated and
healed all over his body.
And drinking a beer
in a small glass
instead of a mug
indicates caution.
He's definitely got an
adventuring background.
[TISSE] This guy...
[RED] This kid...
[BOTH]
is a pro.
[GUARD 9A]
Ouch! Hot mustard!
[RED]
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah. Hey, it's you again.
Friend of yours?
I'd like to take the rest home
with me if that's all right.
Yes, of course.
[TISSE]
Please add four fishcakes, too.
Will do.
[RED] And I'll have chikuwa,
daikon, and chicken.
Make it to-go for Rit.
Coming up!
[GUARD 9A]
Leaving already? You're no fun.
You'd choose a woman over me?
Of course I would.
[GUARD 9A]
Right. Got it.
[TISSE]
Please be careful.
I think I just met someone
who could be trouble.
[RUTI]
Trouble? Who?
It was a young man.
The thing is,
we only spoke briefly,
but he noticed my concealed
knife and armor.
Ah.
A man of that caliber doesn't
seek obscurity for no reason.
He could be the top
adventurer in Zoltan.
No, not from what I hear.
That title belongs
to one called Bui.
Looks can be deceiving, I guess.
Interesting.
I wonder who he was.
His bearing would
seem to suggest
he was trained as a knight.
We must make a decision
on what to do.
Do we choose to work
with him or against him.
We can't work with him.
The alchemist I seek's
being held in prison.
More specifically,
in the infirmary.
[TISSE] You're saying
we must plan a prison break?
Right.
Well, the town is going to
view us as outlaws, then.
No doubt. So will that man.
We'll need to
come up with a plan.
[KURUKURURU]
Hello!
It's a fairy dragon.
Little fay.
Hello, there. I'm Red.
[KURUKURURU] I know who you are.
I'm Kurukururu.
Please, I need your help.
[RUTI]
How do you plan a prison break?
What would you do, Gideon?
[GIDEON]
Me? Let me think.
First I'd look at
the prison's schedule
and find out where
the infirmary is.
It would also be helpful to know
how many people work there.
[RUTI]
I'll keep my ears open
around the prison
until nightfall.
And with your keen perception,
you can tell by their footsteps.
[GIDEON]
That's good thinking, Ruti.
[SISTER 9A]
Wait up, big brother!
[RUTI]
I miss him.
There's so much
I want to talk about.
I can communicate
so much better now.
He'd be proud.
[RUTI]
It's not a wish.
I will see him again!
[RIT] I had no idea
there was a fairy hamlet
on the outskirts of Zoltan.
So, where's the patient?
[KURUKURURU]
Right this way.
[RED]
An undine, a water archfay.
That's right. Welcome to
my humble pond, friends.
[BOTH gasp]
[RIT] Red! Miss Undine,
please put on some clothes!
Oh dear! Pardon me.
[RED] Rit, I can't
think straight when you
press up against me like that.
What you need is a heart remedy.
I'd say something to
heal spiritual damage
should do the trick.
You think I've been
damaged spiritually?
Would that explain why I have
these bags under my eyes?
This is no illness.
It's a spell targeting
those with power.
I'd guess, this is
some type of curse.
A curse?
[RED] Yes, one that
saps spiritual energy.
[gasps] Have I really been
under such a terrible spell?
I had no idea.
This curse is obviously
more powerful than I am.
There's someone in Zoltan who's
more powerful than an archfay?
[gasps]
[RED] The curse has the same
effect as the spell Nightmare.
Take this, it'll help.
It'll stop you from dreaming
and halt your loss
of spiritual energy.
Really?
[RED]
Yeah. Try it before bed tonight.
Thank you so much, Red.
What about that cold-like
illness spreading across town?
Do you think it could be
due to the same curse?
Yeah, the symptoms
do seem similar.
[PRISON GUARD 9A]
Huh? What was that?
[GODWIN]
What the hell?
Someone tell me
what's happening!
[PRISON GUARD 9A]
Call for backup!
What the hell is this?
[RUTI]
You're Godwin, I take it?
[gasps]
Who're you people?
I want you to make
some Devil's Blessing.
Devil's Blessing? But... But why?
[RUTI]
So I can take it.
Fine! I give up!
I'll do whatever you want!
Just stop looking
at me like that!
Good morning to you...
What's wrong?
You didn't sleep, milady?
Not really.
[TISSE]
What shall we do today?
I want to heal Godwin's wounds.
But I won't use Healing Hands.
I don't want him
to know I'm the Hero.
Yes, understood.
[RUTI]
Where's the apothecary?
Let's see, I know
there's one in Central.
Oh, yeah, there's also
a highly rated one
that makes those
Loggervian hand warmers.
Hand warmers. How nice.
[GONZ]
Another freezing day.
Hey there, Gonz.
[GONZ]
I need five hand warmers.
[RED]
Sure. I'll be just a moment.
I heard there was a jailbreak.
I did, too.
[TISSE]
Pardon me, sir.
Welcome.
It's you.
[gasps]
[RED gasps]
Ruti!
[RUTI]
Gideon.
Big brother!
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku