[RUTI]
Big brother!
Did you just call him
"big brother"?
So, you're Red's
kid sister, huh?
I can hardly believe it.
That must mean, you're milady's
long-lost Sir Gideon.
Who's Gideon?
Who's Red?
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
Saving the Hero
[TISSE]
I don't know.
Was it a good idea
to let him leave
after what just happened?
[RED]
Yeah, Gonz won't be a problem.
He's not the type to pry.
I can't imagine him
meddling in our affairs.
All right then.
My name is Tisse.
We didn't do
introductions earlier.
I joined the Hero's party
after you left,
so we just missed meeting.
I see. You're my replacement.
[RUTI]
Do you live with anybody?
Uh... I do. There's someone
I live with here.
[RUTI]
Oh.
[RED] Yeah. Remember when
we were in Loggervia?
There was that princess
by the name of Rizlet?
You're talking about Rit.
I assume Ares must have
told you that I left
to keep tabs on
the Demon Lord's army.
No, he said that you had fled.
I should've known.
[RED] I should've known
that 'no-good Ares'
wouldn't keep his promise.
[RED]
Ruti, the truth is...
[RUTI]
Okay, I understand now.
[RED] I'm sorry for suddenly
disappearing like that.
[RUTI]
It's Ares's fault.
But I'll make sure
he keeps his mouth shut.
Then it'll be fine.
You can rejoin the party.
It's wrong without you.
Totally incomplete.
We could kick Ares out.
No big loss.
You, we can't do without.
Ares failed to
take on the burden that
you once shouldered
for the group.
Danan took off to go find you,
and Yarandrala left
the party because she was
actually convinced that
Ares had killed you.
[gasps] All this time,
I just assumed
your adventures were going well.
So, then?
I'm sorry, Ruti,
but the thing is,
I've found a reason
to stay here.
Well, then I suppose I'll
be moving here, too.
[RED, TISSE]
Huh?!
[RIT] I'm home!
It's Rit.
[RIT] You there, Red?
The closed sign is up.
[gasps]
[RUTI]
It's been a while.
[TISSE]
Thank you very much.
So, tell us,
what brings you to Zoltan?
Well, first.
I wanted to find you.
You did?
Yes. We need you to come back
to defeat the Demon Lord.
[RUTI] And I'm also
looking for someone else.
Someone who knows how
we can defeat the Demon Lord.
Although, I think I've
already found them.
I see.
[RIT] So. What now, Red?
What will you do?
I'm staying right here with you,
and we'll run
this shop together.
Really? You're sure?
No need to worry, Rit.
Like I said,
I'll move here, too.
[RIT]
Wha?!
I'll be going now.
You're leaving?
I've something important to do.
We'll stay at the inn.
Uh... All right, then.
Don't be a stranger.
I'm almost always here.
[RUTI]
Goodbye.
[TISSE]
Thank you for the tea.
[RUTI groans]
[TISSE]
Milady! Are you all right?
[RUTI] I shouldn't've
said I would stay.
I'll have to weaken again now.
Listen, are you sure about this?
[RED]
About what?
I know it's not really
my place to say this now,
but it seems as though Ruti
might actually need you.
And if that's true, then I think
you should go with her.
[RED]
For the sake of the world.
Some might say she's selfish.
But if that's true,
or if there's something
terribly wrong with that,
then it's on me.
It's certainly not Ruti's fault.
I mean, how could it be?
[gasps] Why not?
She may bear the very fate
of our world on her shoulders,
but at the end of the day,
she's still a 17-year-old.
[RED sighs]
We need some time to think.
Why don't we talk about this
when we can include Ruti?
[RIT]
Okay.
[TISSE]
How are your wounds healing up?
[GODWIN]
They're healing quite nicely.
So, when will we
be leaving Zoltan?
[TISSE]
We've had a change of plans.
It seems we'll be here
a little bit longer
than expected.
Hold on, what did you just say?
No, I can't be here,
because if anyone
from Zoltan finds me
and I'm sent back to prison,
I'm sure to be executed.
And you know you can't
make that drug without me!
Please, you really must
calm yourself.
Honestly, I was
just as shocked as you.
[knocking]
[TISSE] Milady, I don't
think we'll be able to
keep Godwin locked up
for much longer.
Also, he says he'll need
a fully equipped workshop
in order to make the drug.
[RUTI]
Did he?
There's somewhere
I wish to search.
If I find nothing in a week,
then I'm willing to give up.
You're wanting to search
a certain area?
I heard there's an elven
ruin on the mountain
where our airship landed.
An ancient elven ruin would be
an excellent place for
a hideout, that's certain.
But why are you so convinced...
[TISSE]
Did I say something wrong?
What is it?
[MR CRAWLY WALY squeaking]
Please don't hurt
Mr. Crawly Wawly!
Sorry. You misunderstand me.
I know that little guy
is your friend.
I wasn't trying to strike him.
"Really look"?
Is that what you said?
You have it wrong.
I meant no harm at all to
your friend. Please forgive me.
[TISSE gasps]
[TISSE] Who is this person
standing before me?
It's the Hero. She has
the greatest Blessing of all,
and the fate of the
world is in her hands.
And though she lives
only for what is right,
even her comrades fear her.
But in this moment,
all I see is a puzzled girl
who accidentally upset a friend,
and now she can't
seem to figure out
why or how she even
managed to do it.
We failed to communicate
to the point
that I ended up
drawing my sword.
But to the Hero,
she assumes that's
a normal response
if you upset a friend.
Her lack of communication skills
has left her isolated
her whole life.
[TISSE] I'm sorry I
misunderstood your intent.
I hope you'll forgive me.
So then, you're not angry?
I'm not. Tell me,
how do you feel, Lady Ruti?
I'm not angry.
I'm so glad.
But if you wish to
pet my friend,
I ask that you
warn me a bit first.
Understood.
[RUTI]
His name?
[TISSE]
Mr. Crawly Wawly.
[RUTI]
Crawly Wawly.
[TISSE] Mister.
Mister is part of his name.
Hello, my name is Ruti.
It's a pleasure.
[TISSE] I am Tisse, assassin,
part-time airship pilot,
and now, friend to the
Hero Ruti. Imagine that!
[BUI] Try as I might,
I can't find any
wood-elf-age structures
that are still standing.
Were they hidden the usual way,
using nature as a defense?
No, I seek that
which the wood elves
would do anything to protect.
There's a slight chance
it's on the ocean floor
or perhaps underground,
but more likely,
it's someplace where
no one can enter.
The ancient elven ruins.
[BUI] Huh? Is this all the
magic power it's accumulated?
It makes no sense.
How could anyone have become
aware of the curse so soon?
[TISSE]
Greetings.
[gasps]
I bid you welcome.
[ADVENTURERS scream]
[TISSE] The customers
keep running away.
[RED] Well, Ruti has
quite the formidable vibe.
Just a thought, but have
you considered smiling?
No.
It helps.
A warm smile can go
a long way with a customer.
So, hey. Care to join me
for a trip into town?
I'll show you around.
[TISSE] I think I'll stay here
and mind the store
with Mistress Rit
if that's all right.
Please enjoy yourself,
Lady Ruti.
[RED]
This is the sauna we frequent.
Our store actually supplies
the potpourri sacks they use.
Sauna?
Want to give it a try?
[ZEFF]
Welcome. Oh, Red, it's you.
Business is booming.
Yes, it's thanks to you.
Oh, I've never seen you around
these parts, young lady.
[RED]
Kid sister.
Oh, yeah? I had no idea
you had a little sister.
[ZEFF gasps]
What's wrong?
Sorry. I'll be just fine.
A customer's past is not
any of my business.
Neither is the Blessing
they possess. Period.
So please forgive me if I
offended you, little lady.
There's nothing like a little
fruit-flavored milk
after the sauna!
It's been ages since we've been
together hanging out like this.
You're right.
[DWARF GIRL 10A gasps]
Look, it's the shaking girl!
What?
It was amazing!
She dumped water over her head
and her entire body,
and then she started
shaking so fast,
she completely dried off and
it was the neatest thing ever!
[SAUNA PATRONS gasp]
[RED]
Oh gosh.
Must've been one of her
superhuman abilities.
She's great, right?
I'm proud of my kid sister.
[DWARF GIRL 10A]
Yeah, she's something else!
She really is! I've never
seen anything like it.
[SAUNA PATRON 10G] I never knew
you had such a talented sister.
Yeah, she looks more
formidable than you.
[SAUNA PATRONS laughing]
Forgive me. I never
meant to stand out.
It's all right.
No one around here's going
to pry into our affairs.
There's no harm in sticking out.
So don't worry.
Are you really sure
it's all right?
[RED]
Yeah.
I'm glad I got to
introduce you to everyone.
My pride and joy.
You mean it?
I'm your pride and joy?
Sweet Ruti, you're adorable,
kind, and trustworthy.
I'm so proud of you.
[RED]
Okay, let's go visit the market.
[RUTI]
If I could be granted one wish,
I know what it would be:
that this day
would last forever.
But the Almighty has bestowed
the Hero's Blessing upon me.
So, who could ever
make my wish come true?
[ARES]
I'm sure of it!
Ruti has to be at or near
the Wall at the World's End.
Tell me, have I been
of any help at all?
[THEODORA]
Well, thanks to you,
we are closer to
tracking down the Hero.
That much is true.
All right, then.
We'll buy you a prosthetic hand
at our next stop.
Allow us to do at least that.
[ALBERT]
That man who severed my hand.
He was a strange one.
[ALBERT] How could he possibly
be so powerful and yet
leave aside fulfilling
his full potential?
[THEODORA] We must all
live lives that are suited
to our specific Blessing,
it's true.
[ALBERT] It's one of
the Church's teachings.
[THEODORA] Yes, but people are
more than their Blessing.
They also have free will.
And they still have their own
lives, and dreams. Futures.
If someone happens to
have a Blessing
that could make them a champion,
does that mean they
must follow that path?
Are they not allowed to
choose another if they wish?
[ALBERT]
But, wait.
Is that really what the
Almighty wants from us?
[THEODORA] If not,
then why give us free will?
What's the point?
If fulfilling the role allotted
by one's Blessing is everything,
we have no need
for free will, do we?
I guess I don't know.
[THEODORA] I, too,
am seeking an answer to that.
That's good.
[RED] It's warm milk and honey.
Your favorite, right, Ruti?
Here. This is sugar water.
I thought your pet spider
might like it.
Thanks, that's so thoughtful!
This fella is
Mister Crawly Wawly.
Crawly Wawly.
Mister is actually
a part of his name, though.
[MR CRAWLY WALY squeaks]
We also have a bathtub.
Care to bathe
before you head back?
Sounds good.
Can I take a bath with you?
Uh... Well, I think we
might've grown past the age
where we can bathe together.
Okay. I'll take one
with Rit, then.
Huh?
That a "no"?
It's fine. Let's do it.
May I join you?
It sounds like fun!
I love baths in
different places,
and I make it a point to keep
an accurate record of each one.
My fellow guild members have
taken to calling me
the Bath Critic.
[BOTH]
Ohh.
[TISSE]
Four stars.
Unfortunately, it's filled up
a little too high,
which means the water reaches
all the way up to my mouth.
[TISSE] The real issue now
is right next to me.
As a member of
the Assassins' Guild,
I've come across
lots of people who've
wanted another person dead.
Love can turn into
a motive for murder.
So, I must remain
watchful and vigilant
to ensure there are
no misunderstandings.
[RUTI]
Rit?
Uh-huh?
I wondered. Have you taken
a bath with my brother yet?
[TISSE]
Yikes! She really went there!
[RIT]
Yes, I have.
[TISSE] Double yikes!
She actually answered?!
Yeah, I have, too,
but it was long ago.
Tell me. What was Red like as
a kid, or should I say "Gideon"?
He was the same as now.
[RIT]
You don't think he's grown up?
I don't. My brother was
always an amazing person.
But me. I used to be weak.
I have to admit, that's kind of
hard to believe, seeing you now.
[RUTI]
But it's true.
I remember my first battle,
so long ago.
It happened while searching for
a lost child in the mountains.
[RUTI] I was five.
So, I myself was but a child.
But I was the Hero,
so I had to act.
Ruti!
[RUTI]
I had no hope of victory,
but I couldn't
possibly abandon her.
Part of the Hero's Blessing
is that it prioritizes
being the Hero over
preserving one's own life.
[gasps]
[RUTI]
Healing Hands.
[RUTI] Even if I survive this,
I'll just go on to
suffer more pain
for the sake of others.
But even so, they all call me
a creepy kid behind my back.
And after they do,
they still ask for my help
when they're in need.
[RUTI]
I've had enough.
[RUTI] But never seeing
my brother again.
That I can't abide!
[RUTI]
Big brother, help!
Big brother.
Ruti! I hate that it
took me so long to get here.
I'm really sorry, sister.
Whenever I was in
any kind of anguish,
he stayed right by my side.
He even shed tears
for his little sister.
It made me so happy.
I really don't enjoy baths
as much as I used to.
Huh?
It's my body.
It resists all manner of things.
My temperature doesn't vary,
no matter how hot or cold it is.
The only reason I still
think baths feel good,
is that I remember
how it used to feel,
and it makes me so happy.
Some things are different.
Milk doesn't taste
as good as it used to.
I remember my brother's
warm milk and honey
always used to taste
so good to me.
[TISSE] It sounds like
Lady Ruti's feelings aren't
as intense as they used to be
due to her Blessing.
So all she can do is
hang onto the past.
Sir Gideon is all Lady Ruti
has in the world.
[RUTI] I admit.
I didn't like you very much
when we were adventuring
together back in Loggervia.
Yeah, I had a chip
on my shoulder,
so I wasn't about to
let the Hero handle
everything without my help.
[RUTI]
No. I envied you, that's all.
You were free to laugh,
or get angry, or break down.
[RUTI] I also envied
the fact that you were
growing closer and
closer with my brother.
I did. I really envied you.
You see, Rit, Tisse,
this is who I am.
This is the real Ruti.
Oh, Rit, I never wanted
to be the Hero.
I wanted to be you.
[gasps]
[TISSE]
I guess I can't help, then.
Only Sir Gideon
can save Lady Ruti
the way she needs to be saved.
[MR CRAWLY WALY squeaks]
Disagree?
You're right.
Nothing is really impossible.
Princess Rit was fixated
on the Hero's Blessing,
but the champion who saved her
turned out to be Sir Gideon.
Well, then, maybe I
could be the champion
who saves the Hero!
[TISSE]
And so, the story begins.
This is the tale of
how I save the Hero.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku