[RED] Thanks, Tisse. Rit told me
all about last night.
Milady is a very dear friend
of mine, who I care about.
There's no need to
thank me, honestly.
[RED]
That's reason enough.
[gasps]
My little sister has you
as her friend. So, thanks.
Milady should be the one
telling you this, Sir Gideon,
no, Master Red would be
more appropriate, I guess.
Either way, this must be
difficult for her, so...
I get it. She's going through
some pretty tough changes
right now, that much we know.
I'll place my trust in you.
If you'll let me,
I'd like to share what
I've learned up till now.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
Banished from the
Hero's Party,
I Decided to
Live a Quiet Life
in the Countryside
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
So, a contract demon
approached Ruti?
A Gathering of Champions
I had no idea about that.
If she keeps relying on
the Devil's Blessing drug,
then there's no telling how soon
she'll become addicted to it.
She should be fine while the
Blessing's full immunity lasts.
At least that's what I think.
What worries me though, is that
the drug weakens Blessings.
Once her Blessing weakens enough
to lose her full resistance,
will milady start showing
signs of addiction?
Can't say for sure, but perhaps.
In any case, let's see
what Godwin has to say.
He's at the ancient elven ruins?
Um. Are you...
Are you angry at milady
for breaking him out of jail?
Even just a little bit?
Well, I can't say I'm exactly
pleased about it, but no.
Nobody there was injured.
And anyway, it's not
my place to judge her.
What a relief.
Please do reassure her
of that, Master Red.
You see, Milady's likely worried
what you might say
if you found out.
I will.
Also. I'd like to stop
by the port to buy
the alchemical tools that Godwin
needs to do his work.
[RED] Our port is the end of
the line for trading vessels.
They may not have exactly
what you want, but I'll go.
Okay, We'll go rent a couple
riding drakes and head out.
Go on ahead.
I'll catch up later.
[ARES]
What a miserable-looking port.
I don't know about this.
You really think we can
accomplish our goal
without anyone noticing me?
The bandages have been
infused with magic
that diverts people's attention.
Stop grumbling and follow.
You go look for an inn.
We can gather intel there.
Fine. I refuse to spend
a moment longer
than I must in this grubby port.
The center of town
can't be this wretched.
I'll look for an inn there.
Jackpot!
[DANAN]
Gideon!
[RED]
Danan! What're you?
My friend,
it's been ages! C'mere!
[BOTH gasp]
Now that's some good stuff!
[RED] You always say that
whenever you eat.
Not lately! I swallow
slop day after day!
Ares' god-awful cooking
is the only thing
I've eaten since you left.
So? Why the hell did you leave?
[RED]
Ares told you everything.
I had reached my limit,
as far as combat ability goes.
[DANAN] No! It became crystal
clear when you left the party.
Gideon, you're a
formidable force.
Even when you fight
a much stronger foe,
you've got grit,
and you maintain your cool.
In combat, you lack magic
and martial arts skills,
but you make up for it
as a strategist.
You're the real deal.
Our party needs someone
as strong as you.
You're too kind.
But I belong right here
and not on the battlefield.
I'm staying here.
[sighs] I see now.
So, leaving the party was
your decision, after all.
Yes.
In that case,
I'm going to set up camp
in Zoltan to see what
exactly you're up to,
and I'll plan my next move
while I'm here.
[RED] Fine by me.
But there's just one problem.
What?
Ruti's in Zoltan, too.
[gasps]
[DANAN]
She suffers due to her Blessing?
I didn't know
anything about that.
Well, anyway. Truth is,
I don't really understand
much of anything.
Unless it concerns fighting.
I'm an expert there!
All brawn and no brains.
[DANAN] Whatever cause
the Hero takes up is
the objective that I,
too, shall fight for!
So, if milady says she
wants to quit being the Hero,
then I've gotta
start thinking pronto!
Now that that's decided,
we can't sit around
here gabbing all day!
Up and at 'em!
Let's get moving, play our part,
and save the Hero!
[RED]
Wait!
I haven't even heard
what happened to you!
We can catch up plenty
on the way there.
Besides, there's really
not that much to tell!
[RED] Right, like losing your
hand isn't worth a good story?
[ALBERT]
Shouldn't we pursue?
[DANAN]
It's me.
Danan?
[ARES] And what, pray tell,
are you doing here?
[DANAN]
Looking for Gideon, of course.
Gideon's in Zoltan?
[DANAN] Yeah. Appears the guy's
running an apothecary.
So. Where is the Hero?
Clearly not here.
Wasn't she with you?
Give me one reason why
I should explain anything.
[DANAN] Because Gideon
plans on settling down here.
[DANAN] Does Princess Rizlet
of Loggervia sound familiar?
It seems the two of them
are living together in town.
Ha! So, here I am,
risking life and limb.
Meanwhile Gideon frolics off
to live a peaceful existence
and tries to marry
into the royal family?
That filthy cur!
Well, our Hero is
wasting precious time
if she thinks she has
what it takes.
She can't win Gideon back.
Wait, do you think she knew of
Gideon's whereabouts
this entire time?
[ARES] Now I see.
Ruti realized Gideon was here
after she spoke to that demon.
You will take me to
Gideon's shop at once.
[DANAN] And just what do you
plan to do when you get there?
Well, I suppose.
I'll tell him to disappear from
Ruti's life permanently!
Oh? Good luck
getting him to do that.
I'll force him into
submission if I have to!
So where is he?
Tell me where the shop is, now!
Come, right this way.
[ARES cackles] You have
thwarted me at every turn,
but this is the
last time, Gideon!
[crashing]
[ARES]
Unforgiveable!
You dare drag the Hero into
such a crummy little shop?
What are you trying
to pull, Gideon?
Curses!
[DANAN] Now that you've got
that out of your system,
have you figured out that this
was a big waste of your time?
[ARES]
Shut your trap! Just shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shisandan still lives?
[DANAN]
Sure does.
I was attacked aboard
the ship I took here,
and had my right
hand bitten off.
I plunged into the sea
but was saved
when I washed up in a port town.
Though he took the form
of an adventurer,
I'm sure it was him,
the Asura demon
whom we battled back
in Loggervia, Shisandan.
But how? Ruti defeated him!
[RED]
She struck him down,
plunged her blade
through his heart!
Get a hold of yourself.
It's no big deal, Gideon.
No matter how many
times he revives,
I'll keep kicking his ass
back to the grave!
[DADAN laughs]
Well, that's strange.
Who in Zoltan could have
summoned a drake?
The magic needed is immense.
They're flying towards
the mountains,
which is where the Hero went.
Get moving.
Charge ahead without me.
I'll follow behind
as fast as I can.
Right!
[RED]
Rit! Tisse!
[RIT]
Red!
[RED]
Danan's on the way, too.
You mean you saw him?
Yes. He was at the port.
Looking for me, in fact.
The truth is, Red.
I knew he was here, sorry.
[RED]
You did?
Yeah. He just thought it
would be better if you
didn't know that he
was here in Zoltan,
since you're trying to
lead a quiet life now.
[RED] Was there anything
different about him
that you noticed?
Anything different?
No, nothing that I remember
stands out to me.
[RED]
I see.
Danan's right hand,
it's cut clean off the wrist
from what I saw.
[gasps]
How did that happen? Did he say?
[RED] Shisandan tore it off.
Apparently, he's back.
[BOTH gasp]
That can't be!
We all bore witness to
his death by Ruti's hand!
[RED]
That's true.
But Danan isn't one to forget
an adversary he's faced.
He's telling the truth.
I have no reason to doubt it.
So, then, who did I see
if not Danan?
Shisandan, most likely.
After devouring his hand, he was
able to take Danan's form.
This is my fault for not
telling you sooner.
You would've known he was an
imposter if I had been honest.
And then. And then
I could have cut him...
Cut him down, right?
Yeah, I didn't plan on
taking up my sword again,
but he's an exception.
Let's face him together, Rit.
We'll defeat him.
And avenge Gaius's
death once and for all.
You don't have to.
[RED] I do. Destroying
Shisandan for good
is worth taking up
my sword again.
There's no point
in avoiding this,
it's something
we must set right.
Yeah! I'll be
"Champion Rit" again
if it means we can
finish Shisandan.
You go on ahead, Red.
I'll be fine.
Roger that.
[RED]
She could've used the mechanism
that opens this place up.
My kid sister can be
so reckless sometimes.
[RED]
All right.
Acrobatics Mastery: Slow Fall.
[RED] It's supposed to be
southwest of here.
[RED]
This is wood-elf script.
But what's it doing
in an ancient elven ruin?
"Heroes' Administration
Authority"?
[RED]
Is it here?
Wait! You're that
apothecary, right?
The girl who dragged
you here, where is she?
How should I know that?
She's probably
somewhere in these ruins.
Okay, give a shout,
let's see if she comes.
What? You want me
to risk my life?
Call her yourself,
that girl scares me to death!
Right. By force it is, then.
[GODWIN screams]
Big brother? What?
Tisse told me what's
been going on.
I'm sorry. I haven't really
been much help to you.
[RUTI gasps]
[RED] Truthfully, I've been
looking for a solution
to suppress your Blessing.
[RED] This cocktail curbs
Blessing impulses.
If you're not careful,
it can be toxic.
Still too weak
for your Blessing.
[RUTI]
But why?
Saving the world is your
number one priority, is it not?
Back when we were kids,
all you ever dreamed of
was getting stronger.
You became a knight,
saved countless lives,
and joined me on the quest
to defeat the Demon Lord.
You didn't have to help
people the way I did,
and yet, you never hesitated to.
I've always wondered why.
Maybe I never
told you this, Ruti,
but I just wanted
to protect you.
Why's that? I am
the Hero, after all.
My sister. Reckless and silly.
Because you are
precious to me, Ruti.
[gasps]
[RED] I knew you'd embark on
your own journey someday.
I've actually been
hoping for it.
So, I don't mind that you
want to quit being the Hero.
I'll support you.
You really mean that?
After I abandoned my comrades,
and broke Godwin out of jail.
Even if I quit being the Hero.
You'll still forgive me?
Of course.
I can just do what I want?
Despite what's expected of me
by the whole world
and my Blessing.
I can really make
my own choices?
Just as my life
is my own to live,
yours is your own
to live, as well.
[RUTI gasps]
Gideon.
You know that I'm
truly selfish, yes?
I'm too selfish
to be called a Hero.
You won't hate your sister
for being this way, will you?
Hey now, I'll always love
my kid sister, Ruti.
Thank you.
Big brother?
You're the best, and I love you.
[ARES] It has to be around here!
Why can't we find it?
Hey, actually, there is
an ancient elven ruin
this side of the mountain.
And even if there is, who cares?
Quite your mindless blabbering
and help me find her!
Word is, part of the ruins lies
right here below our feet.
[ARES] Why are you
telling me this now?
What can I say,
it slipped my mind.
Well then? Where are
these ruins you speak of?
[DANAN grunting]
Huh?
Theodora?
[RIT]
Red!
That was quick.
[RIT]
We didn't waste any time.
I must confess, milady.
[RUTI] Tisse. You brought
my brother and Rit to me.
Thank you.
We must speak with Godwin
as soon as possible.
He needs demon hearts. They're
key to the Devil's Blessing,
we have to know what he's
planning to do about those.
The demon who visited me also
said it requires demon hearts.
And, yet, since the
curse of demon hearts
won't manifest within me,
the Devil's Blessing
can't take effect as usual.
Then how is it you're able
to weaken the Hero's Blessing?
A nameless Blessing
emerged within me.
A nameless Blessing?
Yes. It's just there.
Without any skills,
and without any impulses.
[GODWIN] Huh? I don't know
of anything like that!
A blessing without a name
shouldn't even exist.
[RED]
Tell us what you do know.
Are these murderous
rages a symptom of it?
Yes, that is one
widely known effect
of the Axe Demon's Blessing.
But if the Blessing
doesn't manifest,
then the murderous rages
shouldn't appear, either.
If this so-called nameless
Blessing has no impulses,
it's safe to assume
nothing bad will happen.
Fine but, good or bad,
what should we expect to happen?
Point is, it doesn't seem
all that dangerous.
Something's here!
Those are plague eyes.
They multiply so long as
their spell is cast.
If we attack them, the caster
will know where we are.
Convenient.
Lightning of Judgment!
Hey! Don't run off alone!
Red, wait!
Keep Godwin safe!
Catch up to us after!
Will do!
[RED]
I have no idea how Ruti has been
fighting her battles
since I left.
How far?
Just around that bend!
[RUTI, RED]
Ares!
At last, I've finally found you.
Now come with me and
defeat the Demon Lord.
Ruti, our Hero, you are
destined to save the world.
I will be by your side
every step of the way.
We don't need anyone else!
Surely you know that?
Every last one of them is
worthless and pathetic and weak.
You and I can do this!
The two of us can defeat
the Demon Lord alone.
A bright and beautiful
future awaits us, Ruti!
Here, take my hand and join me.
I refuse to join you any longer.
Pardon?
[RUTI]
Our journey together is over.
I will live my life as "Ruti,"
and not as the Hero you desire.
A thoughtful speech,
oh kind Hero.
You cannot rid
yourself of Gideon
even though he weighs you down.
You reject me for
a worthless Blessing holder.
You've got it all wrong!
Ruti isn't re...
Shut up!
[ARES] Look, Ruti!
You're finally free!
Now let us defeat
the Demon Lord!
[groans]
[RUTI] You never did understand
a single thing about me.
I missed your vitals.
Heal yourself now,
and you'll live.
Ares. I want you to
remember this:
Had you seriously
wounded my brother,
I would have killed you
on the spot.
[RUTI]
Gideon, are you okay?
Wait. Hero.
[RUTI]
I'm no longer the Hero.
There's nothing more
I can do for you.
[ARES] Why? Why won't you
fulfill your role as Hero?
It's preposterous.
Why am I, the Sage, sitting here
bloodied and all alone?
Fools! Why are the
lot of them so idiotic?
Ah! Damn them!
[BUI]
Need a hand?
[BUI] Call me Bui, a humble
adventurer. You'll need this.
Or perhaps you
don't need it, then.
Please excuse
my presumptuous offer.
[ARES] My eyes of Appraisal say
you're an Asura demon, yes?
How peculiar.
Asura Demons are
the only beings in this world
that exist without a Blessing.
Most impressive, Sage.
I've no wish to fight you.
Rather, I come with an offer.
Shall we form a party together?
[ARES]
Huh? Are you insane?
[BUI]
Allow me to finish:
A relic of the first Hero
lies hidden in these ruins.
We work together to find it, and
then if we must, fight for it.
The relic is truly here?
That's right.
If you give it to her,
then the Hero will no doubt
return to your side.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku