[ARES] My heart raced the first
time I laid eyes on her.
A beacon of hope,
shining so effortlessly
in this dark, dull world.
How could no one else
but me see that?
Who she truly was?
[ARES]
The Hero.
The only Blessing besides
the Sage I ever bow to.
I worshipped her.
I had finally found
my purpose in life:
To serve the Hero,
in accordance with
the Almighty's will.
[ARES] I was born to
right the wrongs of
this sinful world and
fight alongside her!
[BUI] The relic of the
first Hero lies just ahead.
Lead me there.
I will have Ruti
at my side again.
Ares is here, too?
A Parting of Ways
Yeah. Not only that,
he's after Ruti.
The spirit drake.
He probably summoned
that creature to get here.
Back in the corridor, the plague
eyes were his doing, too.
Ares has proceeded
to the lower level.
And he's not alone,
there's someone else.
Can you tell who it is?
I can't. Whoever it is
working alongside Ares
conceals their
presence with magic.
Is it Shisandan?
The only one it could be.
But, what are they
planning to do?
No point in standing around.
If Shisandan is deceiving Ares,
then we'll just have to
find out why.
[RIT]
Right.
Wait, hold on.
I'm lost, what exactly are the
four of you going on about?
Sorry, but there's no time
to explain. Let's go.
[gasps] Go where exactly?
I am staying right here!
Wait, don't leave me!
[DANAN]
I'm going ahead!
[THEODORA] Danan! I brought you
along for a reason.
No matter how things
turn out from here on,
I wanted us to face it together.
So I'd prefer if you didn't
charge on ahead without me.
What's that supposed to mean?
You truly are all brawn
and no brain.
You stick to your
fighting thing as usual
and I'll be the wits
of the operation.
Ah, not sure I follow,
but all right.
You do things your way,
and I'll do things mine,
that sound good?
[DANAN grunts]
[ARES gasps]
D-Danan?
Well, fancy seeing you alive.
Ares. If you know what's good
for you, stay out of my way.
[BUI] For a brute, that strike
was impressively calculated.
I can't even move my fingers.
However, he's still one-handed.
[DANAN] I almost forgot... and
don't take this the wrong way,
I'm still gonna kick your ass
where you stand,
but I oughta thank you.
The loss of my right hand
made me realize
just how worthless and weak
my left hand had become.
Now, it's as strong
as my right hand was.
Dragontail Fist!
[grunts]
[BUI]
Ares! Help me! Ares!
[gasps] Me? Against a martial
artist like Danan?
Seriously? I would not
stand a chance!
[BUI]
Ares!
[ARES]
No, I have to act.
There must be something
I can do, yes?
I'm smart.
I always make the right
choice when it counts.
[ARES]
After all, I'm the Sage!
Gargantuan Storm Javelin!
Go to hell.
[DANAN groans]
You've been wounded by
a blast through the body,
and yet you stand
ready for more.
Even I've never observed a
martial artist such as yourself.
Your strength surpasses the role
allotted by your Blessing.
[SHISANDAN grunts]
You're not the only
skilled fighter here, brute.
Though my martial arts style is
often mistaken for
mere acrobatics.
Well what d'ya know.
It looks like you got me, huh?
[ARES]
Am I really all right with this?
Yes, of course I am, what's one
more eliminated comrade?
[ARES] I, more than anyone,
knew how formidable Gideon was.
[ARES] And that's why I had
no choice but to get rid of him.
I couldn't be the Sage I was
meant to with him in the way.
[SHISANDAN]
Sage, I'm in your debt.
Oh, spare me, let's go.
Right.
Be on your guard for traps here.
[SHISANDAN]
We should have access now.
How did you unlock
this contraption?
Its origins date all the way
back to an extinct civilization.
[ARES]
The Holy Demon Slayer?
Only one should be in existence!
So why are there more?
You're wrong.
None of these blades
is the Holy Demon Slayer.
[ARES gasps]
[SHISANDAN] The sword
the current Hero yields,
what you call
the Holy Demon Slayer,
is a replica of
the swords before you.
The blades bestowed
by the Almighty
and wielded by the first Hero.
[ARES]
The true holy swords.
[SHISANDAN]
Aptly named, too.
They will be known as
the True Avengers,
no, the Sacred Avengers,
to distinguish them
from the replica.
[SHISANDAN]
Like the sword she carries,
the Hero, too, is but a copy.
The soul of the first Hero,
replicated by the Almighty.
A replicated soul?
Returning Ruti
to the Hero's path
requires precisely two steps.
First, you must pair the Hero
with one of the Sacred Avengers.
When wielded by her,
its power will
enhance the Hero's Blessing
and restore the innate impulses
that have been weakened
by the Devil's Blessing.
Simple enough if it means
having Ruti back!
The next step is most difficult.
Whatever it takes, I can do it.
You must strike him
from her heart.
Her brother is the reason
she's strayed from her path
and wishes to live
an ordinary life.
What's so difficult about that?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Stay on guard, everyone.
Here, Big Brother.
Thunderwaker!
So, you kept it.
[RUTI]
Yes, it's yours, after all.
Thank you.
My dearest disciple.
What a surprise.
[yells]
Paralyzing Flame!
Just die already, Gideon!
[RED]
Ares!
Sacred Magic Shield, rise!
Ares, there's still time.
Surrender now.
I'll surrender once you're
at my side again!
Gargantuan Storm Javelin!
Most Sacred Punisher!
Get me the hell outta here!
[roars]
You mustn't be so quick
to go running off like that.
Stay within sight
for now, please.
Yeah.
[ALBERT]
Are you all right?
[DANAN]
What, this? It's nothing.
Don't be absurd, it's fatal.
Drink this, quickly!
[ARES]
Ruti need only wield this sword.
Martial Art. Great Whirlwind!
[gasps]
[SPIRIT DRAKE 12A roars]
[SHISANDAN]
So, her power already exceeds
that of the former Hero.
Something's coming below!
What?
Move, Rit! Hurry!
[THEODORA]
Holy Chains!
Theodora?
[gasps]
But why?
Curse me if you wish.
I'll atone with my life after.
But your life must be sacrificed
to preserve this world's peace.
And why my life?
Because you are the Hero.
I never wanted to be!
Not once have I ever
asked for this.
There's plenty out there who
desire and earn that title.
So, why give it to me?
Countless lives will be lost
in the name of your ego.
Faceless lives you mean.
Why must I sacrifice
my own life to save strangers?
Because it is the
Almighty's will.
[gasps]
[RED]
Rit!
[laughs] A heart-
wrenching dilemma:
Will you save your beloved
or dear sister? Your choice.
[THEODORA]
Face the facts.
Gideon may wield a sword
better than anyone else,
but he can't save those
dear to him without your aid.
Humanity needs you
to be the Hero!
[RIT]
That's nonsense!
Don't place my life
in her hands!
You don't have the right!
Don't I?
Was it not the Hero
who saved your kingdom?
As living proof, you should
know more than anyone
that the world needs the Hero.
You're wrong!
[THEODORA]
How am I wrong?
[RIT] It wasn't simply the Hero,
the Guide, or the Crusader
that saved me and my country.
The ones I have to thank
for that, for saving us,
are Ruti, Red, and you yourself!
So you understand.
Listen to me!
The Hero is much more
than a Blessing!
She's a person,
who has the Blessing!
[RIT] It took much more than
the Hero to save Loggervia.
My country is here today because
you three inspired us
to rise up.
You made us fight for ourselves!
The will of the Almighty
is what I preserve.
Without question.
I will not rebel!
If His will involves placing
the fate of the world
on unwilling shoulders,
then I'll show Him
just how wrong He is.
That's just wrong,
and I don't care whether
He's an almighty god or not!
[THEODORA gasps]
[SHISANDAN]
It seems we agree on one thing:
The Hero does not simply exist.
Only those who strive to be the
Hero are worthy of that name.
And yet the Almighty is
too foolish to understand
a simple fact that
you all grasp easily.
Unfortunate.
[gasps]
No, Rit!
Rise, Iron Wall!
This is the end, Gideon!
No, Gideon!
[RUTI screams]
A measly replica
managing to shatter
the Sacred Avenger is
a most impressive feat!
[ARES chuckling]
Poof! Gone!
The Guide and his little
beloved are both gone!
I'm better!
You're dead, yet I still live!
Victor and vanquished!
The Sage and the foolish one!
[ARES cackling]
Tornado Cutter!
[TISSE screams]
[ARES]
You conniving little assassin.
I don't understand.
How could you ever
betray your own party?
My loyalty is to Ruti only.
And it's the Hero's
duty to sacrifice all
in the name of her Blessing.
That sacrifice is for
the Hero's greater good,
for her own happiness.
How would you know
anything about that?
It's true, my lady is
formidable in a fight.
Even when home, she's shy
and can't read the room.
But her heart's full of love!
She's just as normal and
ordinary as everyone else!
I won't let you take
my precious friend when you
can't even understand
that simple fact about her!
[cackling]
Huh?
[GODWIN yells]
Forget about me?
I'm not teaming up
with these fools,
I just hate looking at
cocky bastards like you
who act all high
and mighty because
they don't know
they're the bad guy!
The hell do you think you are?
What are you driveling on about?
[gasps]
As if a paltry little spider
could outwit a Sage.
[DADAN] I won't act like
I follow what's going on.
Or what the Hero
is going through.
[DANAN] What is right,
and what is wrong.
But, there's one thing
even I understand!
Gideon! Rit!
The two of you are my comrades!
I'll help you!
I'll get you out of this mess!
You're not dying on my watch!
No one's gonna
tell me otherwise!
Martial Art:
Rising Dragon's Roar!
What the hell?
Why won't you just die already?
You and your worthless Blessing!
Ares!
Die, Gideon!
Go, Red!
[RIT screams]
Now the killing blow!
[gasps]
Don't underestimate
Mr. Crawly Waly.
You should see the look on your
face now, you uppity bastard.
How did that
stupid spider get me?
[ARES]
Help me, Shisandan.
Heal me, bring me my hands.
Somebody. Anybody.
[ARES]
How can this be?
Why is it always you?
I'm more powerful! Far wiser.
Ruti. O My Lady.
It was foretold, that I was born
to serve only the Hero, and yet.
I want to live my own peaceful
life alongside my brother.
Regardless, you are
still a threat.
In the name of the Asura,
I will end your life
once and for all.
Is me living my own life
really so wrong?
Indeed.
You must fulfill your duty
as the world's Hero.
The Almighty and
all humanity won't allow
the Hero to lead
a peaceful life.
Something's burning in my heart.
The fire of rage!
[SHISANDAN]
Such power!
Even if the Devil's
Blessing sparked this,
I can't believe it
manifested so clearly.
Give it back.
The life my brother
and I shared! Now!
[RUTI yelling]
[gasps]
[grunts] This time
I will finish you!
[RUTI yelling]
[SHISANDAN] At last!
She wields the Sacred Avengers!
In the end, I was
at least able to do that!
[RED]
She'll heal fine with this.
Why are you saving her?
[RED]
Because she's my friend.
How'd I get mixed up
with a bunch of do-gooders?
[RED]
It's not like that.
I mean, yeah,
Theodora turned against us.
[RED]
And, yet.
Even though she
became our enemy,
the last thing I want
for my sister
is to lose a comrade
because of me.
Ruti! I was getting worried!
Are you hurt?
[gasps]
Tisse!
Please come to your
senses, my Lady Ruti.
The man standing before you
is someone very
precious in your life.
Please do not harm him.
Please, don't.