The Guide
She's completely lost it!
Godwin. Rit. Look after her.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
You idiot!
Are you trying to get yourself
killed with that thing?
[RUTI gasps]
You all right?
[RUTI]
Big brother!
[gasps]
Looks like we missed
all the fun here.
[ALBERT gasps]
Theodora!
No good. The wound's too deep,
my power isn't enough.
Let me help.
Oh no. Why won't it answer?
Huh?
[gasps]
Why now? When I fight,
my blessing, it...
It always comes to my aid,
in senseless battles
I want no part in.
Yet it abandons me
when I need to
save someone precious
for once in my life?
Please, no!
Just when I finally found
an actual friend.
And now Tisse.
She's gone because of me.
[THEODORA]
Allow me.
[gasps]
[THEODORA]
Regenerate.
She's safe now.
I still believe I'd no choice.
Therefore, I will not ask you
for your forgiveness.
Even if your actions
had killed Gideon?
[THEODORA]
That's right.
[THEODORA] Once Sir Gideon
left the party,
each and every one of us
fell completely apart.
It made me wonder
why you, the Hero,
didn't immediately
go after our Guide.
Then again.
You never needed
a party, did you?
Me, Ares, Danan, even Gideon.
We were of no use to you.
You could forge ahead
without us.
You don't need to eat.
You don't need to drink.
You never tire or even sleep.
Not even weaknesses
like fear or despair.
It took me an embarrassingly
long time to realize.
The Hero's path.
The Hero's path
is one filled with
loneliness and a cruel fate.
But I carried on
as your Crusader,
so you fulfilled your role.
Weren't you born to save us?
I wasn't. I never
wished for this.
But now the Almighty Demis,
and all of humanity beneath
Him must judge me.
My betrayal cannot be forgiven.
Go ahead, kill me now.
Don't do it!
All my life,
I wanted to be a hero.
I looked up to
every single one of you.
However, I never could
have imagined that
the path would be so grim for
those fated to be our saviors.
And now I see that
Theodora, too,
was anguished over
what she should do.
What she did may
have been wrong.
Some might even call it foolish.
Despite that,
Theodora is still a hero.
She fought for the
sake of the world,
using what means she believed
were right until the very end.
Therefore, I beg everyone here,
please spare her life!
[TISSE] Lady Ruti.
Thank goodness you're okay.
[RUTI]
Tisse!
Please forgive me for
making you worry.
Forgive me for harming you.
[RUTI] Everything's
going to be okay now.
Because from here on...
I'm going to live as Ruti.
I see.
It's just who I am.
I don't see myself as
a hero the world needs.
If anyone is suited for that
role, it's only you, Theodora.
[THEODORA]
Me?
It's true that you fought
for the sake of the world.
And here you are,
wounded and anguished.
As Albert said, is that not
the very definition of a Hero?
[RED]
I think any real hero
would never feel
that loneliness.
[THEODORA]
A real hero?
One who really wants
to save the world
of their own free will.
Physical strength
doesn't make a hero.
It's a hero's strength
of purpose that
inspires in others
the courage to fight.
Gideon. No, Red.
Do I have what it takes to
become a worthy Guide like you?
If that's what you truly want.
Sure you do.
I do.
[THEODORA] After all, it's far
better than fighting comrades,
for the sake of
the Almighty's laws.
[RED] Ares just had to
leave behind one more mess
for the rest of us to clean up.
[RED]
Snow.
[RUTI]
Gideon.
Hey there.
[RUTI sneezes]
You should really
bundle up, Lady Ruti.
[RUTI giggles]
I like it.
It's been so long since I've
felt the cold against my skin.
[RIT]
Pretty, isn't it?
Be careful not to
catch a cold, now!
I've never had one before.
I'm kind of looking
forward to it. [sneezes]
[RED]
Let's not.
How about you two join us
for a warm breakfast?
[RUTI, TISSE]
Thank you for the meal.
So good.
[RED] Ruti's Blessing
in its current form
is called the "New Truth."
Its skill, known as the Ruler,
is powerful enough
to dominate over
other Blessings.
But she mostly uses it
to suppress her own.
Are you and Tisse going out
and about after this?
Yes. With any luck, we'll find
a farm that's for sale.
So, you're really committed to
growing medicinal
herbs. Excited?
Sure am!
It's the first goal
I've made for myself.
And I want to help
Lady Ruti in any way I can.
[RUTI] I'll be back in time
for tonight's funeral service.
See you there.
I'll stay behind
to look after the shop.
Gonz is planning to
stop by a little later.
Right. Shop's yours.
[PRIEST 12A]
O Great, Almighty Demis,
today, we commend
unto Thee this,
Thy faithful child of
Thy faithful teachings,
to complete his first
and final pilgrimage.
The life he led is inscribed
upon his Divine Blessing,
and we now return it
to Thy keeping.
Along with his sins.
If his Divine Blessing
be full of virtue...
[RED]
According to the Holy Church,
we're given
a new Divine Blessing
and reincarnated after death.
If so, I hope that means
Ares is no longer
at the mercy of
the Sage's Blessing.
[PRIEST 12A]
Step forward.
[RUTI]
Gideon. Listen.
I'm sorry you got
involved in this.
I have to look after you.
It's my job.
Well, I'm headed back
to the inn now.
[RED] How long are you
staying in Zoltan?
Heh. Two or three-days'
rest is all I need
for this little flesh wound!
Then I'm on my way.
So soon. Visit anytime.
Fighting's more my speed,
forget the slow life!
But there's still
one thing I don't get.
What's a demon doing
wielding holy swords?
[RED]
Confused me, too.
I have no clue, honestly.
The sword was created
to slay the Demon Lord.
Theodora said that
the holy sword
was an ancient relic
of the first Hero,
and yet, Shisandan had five.
They're not just
spares, are they?
[RED] This is just a theory, but
I think one of them is missing.
[DANAN]
Who took it?
[RED] I'm thinking
one of the past Heroes.
If they did,
then the numbers add up.
[BOTH gasp]
You mean the number of
arms on an Asura.
So, that must mean
the first Hero was...
Asura demons
don't have Blessings.
So, the creator of
Divine Blessings
must've changed
the Hero's meaning.
Almighty Demis?
I'm positive the
first Hero would've
respected your choice, Ruti.
You took back what it means
to be the Hero, after all.
Thanks, you two,
for helping with repairs.
Everything looks exactly
the way we left it!
Come over to eat anytime.
It's really the least we can do.
I almost forgot, is your
little sister holding up okay?
Yeah, everything's fine now.
Well, that's a relief.
You'll have to introduce me
to her some time!
Of course!
[GONZ]
Later!
[RIT sighs]
He even slashed the bed.
The bed you and I
shared together.
You know, I never told you,
but lately I start freaking out
when I go to sleep.
Huh?
Guess I'm worried that
one morning I'll wake up
and you won't be
sleeping there beside me.
That won't happen.
We all need you, Red.
Everyone relies on you
for your guidance.
You truly are the Guide.
Everyone here counts on your
inner strength to save us.
There are plenty of Blessings
out there more capable.
[RIT] Mm-mm. No, it's not the
Blessing that we all depend on.
Everyone just trusts you, and
your experience through the life
you've lived that's been
shaped by your Blessing.
Do you think so?
[RIT] But I'm scared.
What if you leave?
What if you decide to go away
and guide someone else?
This shop and that bed
were somewhere
we could always return to.
But after Ares, I was afraid
you didn't want to
come back home with me.
[RED]
You're wrong.
I wanted to come back.
You really did?
I came back because
I need you, Rit.
This shop and our bed, without
those, I'm not fully myself.
I'm me because I'm with you.
[gasps]
Do you remember, Rit?
When we met again,
you called me "birdbrain,"
and you were surprised to find
there were things I didn't know.
You knew.
Even though I was far
from perfect back then,
you still stuck around to
run this little shop with me.
It made my heart leap.
[gasps]
[RED]
I am a Guide.
I guide someone until
they can go it alone,
and then, sure, I move on.
But you're different.
You stayed.
You never left my side.
Despite all of my flaws.
[RIT]
Red.
This shop marks the happiest
end to my journey.
I just love you so much, Rit.
More than I can even
describe or put into words.
[RIT]
You'll be with me forever?
Right now, that's all
my heart yearns for.
[gasps]
How pathetic,
we're already so fragile
that we can't make it
without one another.
[RED]
Is that so bad?
We're living
a peaceful life now.
We don't have to
be strong anymore.
[RIT]
Right.
[gasps]
[RED gasps]
I'm sorry!
Why you. I'll get you for that!
[RED laughing]
Cut it out, Rit!
How do you like it, huh?
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH gasp]
[RIT]
Did you see that?
[RED]
Mm-hm. You're beautiful.
[RIT] So cheesy. But being like
this, with you, feels right.
Exactly. You and I are complete.
Not yet.
I think there's one little thing
that we're still missing.
[gasps]
Don't keep staring.
So awkward, but okay,
Red! Here goes!
[gasps] Watch your hand!
[RED] Sorry, it's just... I've
been holding back all this time.
I don't think I can much longer.
[RIT] You don't think I've felt
the same exact way, too?
I love you, Red.
[RIT] Amazing.
Living together with you
has been nothing
short of amazing.
I'm pretty sure
this is true bliss.
You and I will share
plenty of years here.
[RED] I said before that this
was the end of my journey,
but it's also the
start of a new one.
[RIT]
What kind of journey?
One that's wonderful
but also peaceful.
We'll run our shop together,
and on days off, we'll go out.
We'll have a couple
of kids, too.
Mess up a lot trying
to raise them,
but laugh about it
when they're older.
And then we'll
grow old together.
We'll have to babysit
the grandkids, of course.
Things will get hectic again,
and though it may seem hard,
it'll be a lot of fun.
Lovely. I can't wait to
share it all with you.
I asked you before,
but a gemstone.
What is your favorite?
[RIT] Whichever you pick
is my favorite. You decide.
The one you choose for me
will be my favorite gemstone!
As you wish.
My heart's pounding so hard.
I just can't wait to see!
[yawns]
[RUTI]
Finally!
[RED]
Ruti.
Good morning, big brother.
Morning. Did Rit
take off already?
[RUTI] Mm-hm. She said there's
no rush to hurry over.
Then let's swing by
the port first.
Afterwards I'll take you
out for breakfast,
since we have time to ourselves.
The local cuisine
does sound delicious,
but nothing even comes close to
beating my
big brother's cooking.
[VENDOR 12A]
Hi, Red!
Oh, hey! New lady?
It's not like that.
This is Ruti, my little sister.
So, Red's got a sis!
She's a cutie!
She's also a brand-new
B-rank adventurer.
So don't get any funny ideas
if you want to live.
Say what?
Champion Rit and
your little sister?
Maybe I should get into
the apothecary business
for a leveled-up Blessing!
[RED]
That's not how it works.
Like it?
[RUTI] Mm-hm. It's unassuming,
but that gives it character.
If you like it that much,
it's yours. My treat.
Thanks, I'll take it, then.
I had fun today.
I had almost lost hope
that we'd ever be able to
spend time together
like this again.
And my friends.
Tisse, Mr. Crawly Wawly,
and Rit are all so amazing.
Thank you, big brother.
[gasps]
Can we stay together
like this forever?
Yeah, I mean,
I don't see why not.
I'll always be
by your side, Ruti.
iki wo suu koko de suu sugiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my time
It's a beautiful day.
And feel that breeze?
ku
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
And you're always there in my memories
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
kirei na koucha nonde
I see your face reflected
kappu no naka utsusu yokogao
in the fine black tea you're drinking
jibun ruuru no aru
Your cozy warmth,
anata no gokochiyoi ondo
so unique and unpredictable
suki no su no moji wa
I wonder when I'll be able
itsu ieru no ka na
to even try to express my feelings
taisetsu na no wa tsuzuku hibi dake
I just want these days I treasure to never end
shigoto owari nara tsutaerareru ka na
Would I be able to say it after work?
ashita wa haretara iin da
I hope the clouds clear up from the sky tomorrow
iki wo suu koko de suu ikiteku
This is where I can breathe and spend my life
manazashi no saki ni nagareru
And you're always there in my memories
omoide no naka ni itsumo anata ga ite
That I keep recalling throughout my days
soshite hajimaru
And so begins another
Beautiful day
Beau
ti
ful
day
[RED]
Thanks for dropping by!
We're done looking
over the herbs.
Thanks for the help!
I'm going to check
on them later,
you two should go
and take a break.
[RUTI]
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
At least take a seat.
Well, my feet could use a break,
but only because you asked,
big brother.
[gasps]
[RED chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
Seriously, what's happening?
I never know just what
to say during times like this.
[MEGRIA gasps]
Ms. Ruti!
What's going on?
An urgent job just came in!
A gang of ogres seized a village
and captured the adventurers
that were sent to
take care of them!
All up to you,
it's your life now.
I was saved when I couldn't go on
saikousou de sukuwareta
This is what I want to do.
wa
re
ta
Birthed into a vast, different world
owari no nai hoshi ni umareta
I'll be back soon, big brother.
ma
re
ta
Yeah. Be careful, okay?
In the end, she truly is
the Hero the world needs.
Lady Ruti doesn't
just fulfill a role.
With a hazy scenery behind me
kasumu keshiki wo se ni
ka
su
mu
She fights of her own free will.
I tried to start a new life
seikatsu wo tameshihajimeta
You said it.
I gather them, I lose them,
atsumete ushinatte
a
tsu
[RED]
Ruti!
And I move on to the opening the next window
tonari no nado wo akete iku
to
na
When you come back home,
I'll make whatever you want.
Any requests?
ke
te
i
ku
Do I have more things to think about?
kaisou fueta?
Just milk and honey.
Don't be prejudiced, stop hiding
shinjikondenaide deteoide yo
You're the one creating this
anata wa tsukutte iku no sa
a
na
ta
Aha! Drinking with
such a lovely lady?
My luck's finally
turning around!
Tell me, what is
Zoltan really like?
Let's try to turn this
saigo fureta?
sa
i
go
fu
A dreary backwater.
re
ta?
It's difficult to reach
and has no strategic value.
Into a story with a miracle
kiseki ga aru hanashi wo shite miru yo
ki
se
ga
a
Nothing much going on
in that place.
Oh? Sounds like you hate it.
ru
yo
A world I didn't know existed
omotte inai you na
o
mo
t
Not at all.
te
i
na
It may be a backwater,
but it's a fine town.
yo
u
na
Is opening up before me
sekai wa michite iku
se
I could never hate it.
Couldn't think of a better place
to settle down for a slow life.
te
i
ku
[YARANDRALA]
Gideon. Rit.
I very much look forward to
seeing the two of you again.