Who's the next target?
Frank Clard.
It took some work
but I was finally
able to catch his scent.
You gonna use those guys again?
You know, the weird ones.
Yes.
I believe we've already
decided to send them in.
It's gonna be a big
production, isn't it?
I think it's a necessity
if we truly want to raise
awareness of our existence.
Their power rages,
becoming hellfire,
burning even hell
to the ground.
And so we shall build
our world from the ashes.
[Music]
You're injured.
It's just a scratch.
Me, I kill.
In order to live.
I kill!
[Music]
They're gonna kill me.
I have to get out of here
or they're gonna kill me!
I have to run
or I'm dead.
Those eyes...
I can't escape
from those cold black eyes.
What am I gonna do?
If I can't get away,
I'll have to kill them.
It's kill or be killed.
Where? Where am I?
What is this place?
Why am I here?
What happened?
Who am I?
Why can't I remember...
my name.
Kanji?
A backpack.
That's me.
I guess.
Maybe.
Maybe I'm
a Japanese traveler who's lost.
What's going on?
Why can't
I remember anything?
Whoever attacked me
might still be lurking
around here someplace.
You shouldn't just be going
running off by yourself
all the time, Clo.
You do that,
and what the hell's the point
of having a bodyguard?
Well, would you like
to take a ride with me?
No way.
Relax, Lizzie,
I'm just going to
check up on them.
I can't very well
leave all the decisions
to that man alone,
now can I?
That snake in the grass.
Ten to one says
he's busy playing
with that fine
new toy of his by now.
What a disgusting pig!
He contributes a lot
to the organization, Lizzie.
Well,
he is the favorite puppet
of McGuire and the others.
So we're gonna
have to deal with him.
We use whatever means
we have at our disposal
to achieve our goal.
That's always been
the style of Inferno.
I know that, but...
Listen up, Clo.
You're treading
on dangerous ground.
Maybe too much of it.
You ever need my help,
just let me know.
I'm counting on it.
Thank you.
Now if the girl could just
learn to be a better driver.
His ability to assess is 074.
Awakening rate is 087.
That he's reached these values
after a only few minutes awake
is simply staggering.
As I told you before...
the young man is a gem.
I'm gonna burn in Hell
for all of this.
That is, of course,
unless I'm already there.
Sensory awareness very sharp.
That is the true nature
of animals.
It's the wild instinct
that is lying dormant
beneath the evolution
of his reasoning.
He will hone in on it,
I'm sure.
Although it will take some time
to reach the awareness
that I seek.
I'd say it's about time
for you to appear, Phantom.
But, show some restraint.
Yes, Master.
If you don't want to die.
Those eyes!
Then come at me
with everything you've got.
In a moment of crisis,
a danger to one's life,
a threat to one's
very existence,
when one is faced
with sudden misfortune,
one must be in touch with
his or her animal instincts
in order to survive.
If one relies on things
like morals and kindness,
if one believes in his heart
that his safety is guaranteed
based on those
transparent ideals,
then they are a weak human
who has abandoned
the "living" of this life.
The unfortunate truth
is this kind of reliance
on the intangible
has become the norm.
It sickens me.
Well, well.
If it isn't Ms. McCunnen.
To what do I owe
the pleasure of your company?
How are things going?
A work in progress.
Would you like to see
where we stand?
Yes.
Then by all means.
Who is that girl?
Why is she after me?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Not where I am,
not how I got here.
I don't even know my name.
There's no escape.
There is no escape.
If I can't get away.
It's this way for both of us.
Then it's kill...
or be killed!
It's about to begin.
What's that?
Why, the show, of course.
What is this?
You have to come at me
with all you've got,
if you don't want to die.
I have nothing.
No past...
no future...
I don't even have a name.
But still...
I don't want to die!
[Music]
Where should I go...
when I don't even know
where I came from?
When I don't even
have memories?
What do I have to do
to become free?
What is freedom
when you have to
kill people for it?
Tell me...
please.
What the hell!
What is this?
Where is this place?
Who am I?
Zwei.
W...wait.
Who are you?
My name is Ein.
And your name is Zwei.
Zwei?
You will answer
to that name.
From this moment on,
it is how you will be known.
What's happening?
What'd...
What did you do?
Zwei!
This is how it is for us now.
I am you,
you're me.
What do you think?
Is he not a wonderful find?
All things considered,
the result turned out
quite splendidly.
No prior training,
no knowledge of tactics.
A blank canvas.
He operated solely
on natural instinct.
But above all of that,
although
it may have been temporary,
he surpassed even Ein.
Phantom.
How shameful.
Forgive me for failing you.
He's a prodigy.
But his talent hides,
lurking beneath the surface
until he finds himself
faced with the stress
of a life or death situation.
He is certainly
the kind of person
who was born
to join Inferno.
Even if that's true,
are you sure
he would want that?
There is neither an egg
that refuses to hatch
nor a seed that evades
its eventual sprouting.
This has nothing to do
with his will.
Ah, more brainwashing.
It's the best method
for achieving our goals.
Using hypnosis and medication,
I sealed tight all memories
dealing with his identity.
Please understand,
Ms. McCunnen,
this is mercy.
It could've been
much worse for him.
A stroke of bad luck
led him in into
an unfortunate situation.
Under normal circumstances
he'd have been a witness,
and thus, eliminated.
I thought I'd give him
one more chance
to live a fruitful life.
A Japanese tourist
that's traveling by himself...
there's no search party?
No one will be able to
track his path any longer,
so our secret
is perfectly safe.
Okay, then.
Scythe Master,
I'll leave this boy to you.
I appreciate your confidence.
Ein and Zwei.
Perhaps you should put
a little more thought
into the names
you give your subjects.
Such arrogance!
Just how much longer
do you think
you'll be giving me orders
like that, madam?
I am the first woman, Ein.
You are the second man, Zwei.
Together.
What're you doing?
That is all, Ein.
Go home.
Return to your post.
Yes, Master.
Together, we are ghosts
that have
no place to haunt.
Nonexistent phantoms.
Welcome back home, sir.
You have a nice flight?
Yeah, yeah.
Where's everyone else?
They're here.
They're all inside
taking a nap.
It's the damn middle
of the day.
What the hell's
going on here?
Wait!
Who are you people?
We're phantoms.
Phantom,
the strongest assassin
in all of Inferno.
And the title given to the top
sniper in the organization.
My greatest masterpiece.
And now,
he is another.
That's takin' it too far.
I see.
Lookin' good.
That's one more
outta the way.
By now, two out
of the five organizations in LA
have totally fallen apart.
This is a start, my friends.
We're going to create
a new era with our own hands.
We will create
the era of Inferno.
[Music]
Ghosts, that have
no place to haunt.
Nonexistent phantoms.
[Music]
You are now only
allowed to exist
for the purpose
of killing others.