[Music]
Could I be excused
from guard duty,
just for tonight?
I have some
important business.
And what if...
I had more important business?
What is it?
You're kidding.
Here.
I thought you might want
your passport.
Your identity,
your name,
and your past.
[Music]
Ein...
Be careful.
I didn't know.
How could I have known.
The fate that was
about to unfold.
The future that lay ahead.
It's okay to look.
Are you afraid of
getting your past back?
No, I dunno.
It's just that I've been
killing people
for the organization
for so long now.
Yes, and you've been
extraordinarily helpful.
The thing is,
I was able to do that
because I have no past
or memories to cloud my mind.
It allowed you
to follow orders
like a machine,
feeling no guilt or remorse
for your actions.
If you get back
to your true self,
that guilt could rise up
and eat you alive.
Which is precisely
what you're afraid of.
But, that's why I want you
to know yourself,
what exists inside you,
to know your own will.
My will.
Distance: 249 yards,
with low intensity gusts of wind
from the south.
Restore your true self.
Then, and only then, can you
accept yourself, as Zwei.
How goddamn selfish!
Your organization
erases my mind...
it forces me to do things
that make me a murderer...
and now you want me to--
It's a revolution.
Our organization
is going through changes.
Soon, it will be reborn.
And when that happens...
Zwei, I want you.
See? No matter
how capable you are,
I need someone who is
more than just a puppet
who can only do
what he's told.
I need you to be
something of a partner.
A subordinate still
of course,
but one I can trust.
One who'll follow me
of his own free will.
If I come to know who I was,
I don't know
if I can stay who I am.
I'm sure you can.
My job is to back up
the assault.
The people I see in front of me
are just targets.
Shit! Who are those guys?
The truck!
Damn! A sniper!
We did it!
It may be too early
to celebrate.
Just step on it.
Right.
So you think you can
trap us all down here.
You sure got some balls.
Read the name out loud.
Azuma.
Reiji.
You remember now?
That's right, I do.
I was traveling, and then...
I've killed...
so many...
with my own hands.
Because I just...
I just wanted to live.
Oh God, I wish I didn't know.
I told you,
I don't need someone
who's just a puppet.
Wake up from your dream.
You can become you again.
Your past, your guilt,
you have to accept it,
all of it,
and face your own will.
Reiji Azuma.
Phantom.
Goddamn Scythe!
What do you want from me?
I want you to come with me,
but, of your own free will.
There's someone right here
before you who needs your help.
Because this is where
you belong.
And if you're willing to have
more blood on your hands,
if you believe
your soul has the strength
to bear mortal sins with me,
I can promise to give you
a wonderful future.
Since you have free will,
that means the other choice
is available to you as well.
What choice?
The other one.
You know what it is.
Going back home?
If that's truly what you desire
above all things,
I can make
a special case for you.
You may doubt
what I'm saying to you,
but I'm serious.
I will let you go back, promise.
Listen Reiji, I want you
to think for yourself,
no matter where
it may lead you.
Are you crazy?
You're shooting
your own people!
I don't care if Scythe
ordered you to do this.
Stop being his goddamn puppet!
You can't escape from here!
Think about it!
You know that old man's
just using you
as his little pawn, don't you?
Going back,
back to Japan.
I know this has to be
a big decision.
So I'll give you some time,
time to think about it.
Hello,
this is the Azuma residence.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
I can never go back.
Never.
Find her!
I can't believe
that bastard Scythe.
His little zombie
just dropped some of our boys.
We'll give him a fitting sendoff
after the final curtain.
Not forgetting our Phantom.
Ein, what the hell?
Did you come out here
to kill me?
What do you mean?
You don't know anything?
Good.
Then go back
to the organization.
If you show up alone...
Ein!
Ein?
It's me.
We've had a change of plans.
Scythe has betrayed
the organization.
He used Phantom
to attack Inferno's shipment.
Of course,
he vanished immediately.
Phantom's on the run, too.
Lizzie managed to get
a shot in, thankfully.
The organization is pouring
all its resources
into hunting
both of them down.
As of now,
we don't have a lead on either.
Inferno suspects
that you've betrayed them too,
but I can prove
where you were.
So listen carefully.
You don't have
the luxury of time,
make your decision now.
You're either going to
come to me, or not.
So as it stands now:
Scythe and Phantom
are the enemy.
If you choose
to take their side,
you're dead, that's it.
It won't stop bleeding,
the bullet is still inside.
I gotta get her
to a doctor now.
I can't.
They're probably checking
all the hospitals.
Okay.
Hang in there, please.
All the escape routes
are blocked.
They're birds in a cage.
No one escapes
the organization,
not even
the illustrious Phantom.
Yeah, that's true,
but now that we don't
have Phantom,
who's gonna
hunt down the prey?
Please, Ein.
Don't die.
You got all these people
at your disposal,
and you still can't find them?
The freeway?
Then block it!
Dammit!
I knew I should
just finished that bitch.
Clo, where is he now?
You mean Zwei?
Yeah.
A.k.a. Scythe's other lapdog.
He might just take
their side, you know.
If that happens, Lizzie,
I think
you should take care of him.
Ein...
you know something?
Tonight,
when I saw Ms. McCunnen,
she gave me a passport.
It was my passport.
It brought back
all my memories.
My family.
My home.
I finally had a place
I could go back to.
I also learned
what my real name is.
It's Reiji.
My name is Reiji Azuma.
It's a whole lot
better sounding
than that stupid Zwei,
don't you think?
But what's weird is...
it didn't make me happy.
Now,
I'm a different person.
I don't know
if I belong there anymore.
Does that make
going back to the organization
my only choice?
Maybe you and I could
go back together, Ein.
So as it stands now:
Scythe and Phantom
are the enemy.
If you choose
to take their side,
you're dead, that's it.
I won't be able to save you.
No.
If Ein goes back,
she's dead.
Then,
I'll just leave her here.
And I'll go back by myself.
What's up?
It's nothing, I guess.
Don't worry about it.
There's wind.
And there's blue, white,
and green.
But that's all there is
in that place.
Nothing else.
All I can ever remember
is the bright lights,
the colors,
and the blustery wind,
the strongest wind I've known.
Ein...
be careful.
You be careful, too.
Neither one of us had a name.
All we were given
were numbers,
then we were both used
like pawns, like trash.
To hell with it,
with all of it.
To hell with such a meaningless
way of life.
You're awake.
Ein, I will protect you now.
I promise.
I will.
And I'll never
let the organization take you.
Let's go together.
Leave here, leave Inferno.
Reiji.
Ein, let's go, okay?
[Music]
I'll give you a new name.
It won't be like Phantom.
It won't be some number.
It'll be your real name.