[Music]
Quit daydreaming, Reiji!
You should be cleaning!
Reiji's kinda weird.
I don't know
what's he's thinking.
But it seems like he's always
just staring off into space.
He is a bit of a space cadet,
doncha think?
Alright,
it finally stopped raining!
It's beautiful.
I almost didn't see it.
It's a natural work of art.
Most people
wouldn't even notice it.
The boat leaves
late Monday night.
We need to be sure
to meet our contact in Otaru
in the evening.
Monday, huh?
That means we've still got
five days here.
I hope Inferno will let us
leave without a fight.
I'm not sure of that...
so we should not
let our guard down.
I want us to get out smoothly.
Leaving no trace,
just quickly and quietly
roll out of town...
like fog.
Yo, Scythe!
Is there some kind of trouble,
Ms. Garland?
Where the hell's Phantom?
I swear, the two of you
better not be planning
on pulling
something stupid.
She's missing?
I was under the impression
she was going to be
in your charge
this afternoon.
Well, she's not.
Damn.
I took my eye
off her for a second.
Not to worry...
she'll return
when night falls.
Weapons are missing,
a lot of them.
Oh dear!
That could be dangerous.
I wonder what is her plan.
Ya know, I think
I have a pretty good idea
where she ran off to.
You need to go ahead
and get ahold of
Mr. McGuire and Shiga.
I'm gonna go
and look around for Phantom.
It seems the die is cast,
well...
Are you serious about this?
Come on, she's... a kid.
Zwei began this process,
I am only completing it.
Yeah, but...
Drei?
Yeah.
That's the name
Scythe says I should use.
Lizzie... listen.
I'm counting on you
to help me out.
Hey!
You're gonna be there
for me, right?
Ah, man!
This babysitting crap
is getting on my last nerve.
Hey!
Sorry you had to see that, Mio.
It's okay.
I'll be honest with you.
Listen...
I... I had...
a little problem
when I went to America.
I never expected
it'd end up like that.
It's funny...
ya know, I'm actually glad
I got to see her one more time.
I mean, she hit me.
But I think
it's resolved now.
Alright. So that's enough
about that, okay?
Yeah.
I promise we'll have
a real date sometime.
It can't always
be like this.
Anyway...
See ya.
Bye.
Why's it so quiet?
Oh, yeah.
Mom's not gonna be home tonight.
Hey! You remember me, doncha?
Don't look so scared, okay?
Well, what're you doing here?
Tell me, you're
Godo's little princess, right?
What? Godo?
Are you talking about
my - uncle?
You think he's your uncle.
Whatever.
I'll let you in on the whole
story in a little while.
Hold on!
I know you people don't see
a lot of guns in your country,
but trust me, it's real.
Hop on.
I'll tell you a story.
It gets a little twisted
and seedy though.
It's about Reiji after all.
[Music]
I've been waiting on you
to show up.
'Bout time.
Wait there.
Hey, Lizzie!
I was thinking about this game
that we're playing now.
Yeah?
The rules are pretty simple.
As long as she's alive,
we can't touch those two.
So we need to change things up
a little bit.
Killing the princess
should do the trick just fine.
Everyone better stay
the hell outta my way.
And no one better touch
my target.
How long are you gonna
carry on like this?
What?
Do you really
hate that boy that much?
Are you seriously
asking me that question?
There's two kinds of people
I can't tolerate.
Back stabbers and people
that'll hurt a civilian.
I can't abide
by this behavior!
There's a line
that you just can't cross.
Be careful, girl.
You're walking
right on the edge.
And you're
about to fall over it.
Hey! There's something
I've always wondered about you.
Why?
Why have you always thought
you could treat me
like I'm your little sister?
We didn't ever want you
to walk down this road.
To become the next Phantom.
Me and Zwei both.
Everyone had their own plans
for me, that it?
Too bad.
I'm Phantom now,
and if you don't like it,
you can make it stop
right here, tonight.
I'll pull out my gun
when the song's over.
If you can't pull
the trigger by then,
I guess,
you're just too soft.
It's gotta be kill or be killed
in this business, right?
Cal!
What?
Listen to me,
I don't wanna shoot you.
Cal!
I gave you a chance
but you just couldn't do it.
Sorry.
I just didn't
have the strength.
Are you sure
you want one so heavy?
Yeah.
I don't want it to be
too easy to pull it out.
This gun...
it got...
heavy...
so...
so goddamn heavy
for me to lift.
I can't raise it anymore.
Clo...
We're gonna be here
for a couple of days at least,
so don't eat too fast.
Why?
Please!
Why are you
doing all of this?
Why'd you -
why'd you kill her?
My phone!
Okay, so let's just see
who was the last person
you talked to.
These little squiggles...
they say Reiji, don't they?
Tell me, how do you know him?
I was his student,
and... his lover.
Liar.
How the hell
would you know?
What makes you think
you know anything
about that lying snake?
Wanna know a secret?
I learned to use this,
from your sweet prince.
I guess you don't know
what he was doing in America?
Killing people!
Oh yeah, he was real good.
That guy killed
shitloads of people
without thinking twice
about it.
No way.
You've been lied to
your whole life.
Two years ago,
this guy named Daisuke Godo
died while he was in L.A.
Wasn't he supposed to be your...
uncle or something?
How in the world
do you know that?
I know a lot
about the whole situation.
And I know that this Godo guy
was some kinda gangster.
And...
get this...
He wasn't your uncle either.
In fact, he was your brother.
That's a lie!
What's wrong?
You think you're too good
to be the daughter
of a big-time mafia boss?
Then you are gonna crap
when you hear this news.
Daisuke Godo's death
was not an accident,
if you know what I mean.
Your dear Reiji
actually had a big part
in the whole thing.
I don't believe
a single word you're saying!
I don't give a damn
if you believe me.
But, listen up, princess.
There's gonna be a war -
and you're
right in the middle.
Like it or not,
that's what's gonna go down.
When that happens...
everything I told you
here tonight,
is gonna make
a whole lot more sense.
What are you trying to do
with all this?
Start a fight...
with Reiji -
a fight to the death.
No way.
Sun's coming up.
We should get this started.
Hi, Mio.
Sorry! This ain't Mio.
What have you done to her?
Aw! Don't worry,
I don't wanna hurt her.
But since you got
your hands full trying to run,
I thought you might be
a little too busy
to take care of a hostage.
So I'm doing that for you.
I thought I was
the only one you were after.
She's got nothing to do
with this, you hear?
You just wanted a normal life,
isn't that right?
Okay, I'll let you have
your boring existence.
And I won't let
Inferno or the Godos
harm a single hair
on your head.
Just be a good boy
and go to school everyday
and you'll be fine.
But, don't even think
about vanishing on me.
If you try to run somewhere
that I can't keep track of you,
there's gonna be
a little reunion going on.
I'll reunite Mio
and her brother in hell.
So I'll be watching you
very closely, Reiji.
You hear me?
There's nowhere to run.
Nowhere.
So Cal...
decided to go against Inferno?
She hates me enough
to risk it, I guess.
We should act independently.
What d'ya mean?
How do you do, sir?
I thought I made it clear
Mio Fujieda wasn't
to be harmed in any way!
I wanna know why you let
Phantom take her like that!
Huh?
I see, news travels quickly.
God damn you!
I know that you're behind
all this, you smug bastard!
That's absurd.
I swore on my life
I would look out for her!
She isn't some pawn
you can just throw away!
I assure you this is a matter
that I take very seriously.
I will do everything
in my power
to see she is
returned to you safely.
I'm gonna go out and see
if I can locate them.
Do exactly as she said.
Do not raise suspicion.
I'm sure
that I can take out Drei,
and rescue Mio.
But, Cal is watching us now.
If we do anything
to make her angry,
she'll snap.
No. If I leave,
she still won't hurt Mio.
I promise.
How can you be so sure?
She doesn't care about me.
You are her only target.
Yeah, but...
She doesn't have us
cornered just yet.
We have to stay in control.
Whoever loses their focus...
will die.
There's no need to worry,
Mr. Shiga.
My new assistants will be
arriving very shortly to help.
Soldiers, meticulously
trained by me personally.
Each with a logical mind
that surpasses the bounds
of trivial emotion.
Very effective.
And I know, you will be
extremely satisfied
with the results.
There's absolutely
no chance of failure.
We are ghosts
that have no place to haunt -
non-existent phantoms.
[Music]
If you live on,
that's the proof -
that I lived.