[Music]
I kill people with this hand...
and I eat with this hand.
There isn't any difference...
I do both these things...
so I can live.
That's how life is...
we kill to eat.
Hey.
Sorry for your loss,
it's a real shame.
What the hell, Gant?
You have no right to be here!
Be careful, Tony.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you mean.
Yeah, you're innocent.
Try not to forget I've known
the lot of you boys
ever since you were
snotty little brats.
I know more than you think.
I can see it in your eyes.
You're looking
for a bloodbath.
Tony...
don't be stupid.
I've always got my eyes on you.
Are we gonna finish this?
Yes.
We will destroy Inferno.
This isn't just revenge.
We'll do it
to protect the family.
But with that asshole Gant
practically stalking us,
we need to be careful.
I have an idea.
There is a way to rid ourselves
of them forever.
And we won't even have to
dirty our hands in the process.
The way I understand it,
Inferno is made up of wiseguys
trying to buck their bosses
and join hands
with their enemies.
I put together a list of guys
who would seem
to benefit the most by cutting
their family affiliations
and joining up with
these other back stabbers.
Richard Harrington...
Carlo Mendoza...
These are made guys.
Are you saying they're goin'
against their own families?
And if we dig up evidence
that confirms my hunch,
they'll all be history.
Any mafia organization
would take exception
to that kind of disloyalty.
They're spitting
on the code of conduct.
So they'll be sent to hell
by their families.
Yeah.
Freakin' brilliant, Tony.
Anton, I'll leave
the arrangements to you.
Stay close to them
and reveal their true colors
to their families.
But, be cautious.
Good morning, Ms. McCunnen.
You're looking
just as beautiful as always.
Why are you here?
I asked him to come.
He has informative opinions
based on a unique insight.
I think we can learn quite a bit
from listening to him.
In fact, I plan on
having him participate
in future executive
meetings as a regular.
You don't have
any issues with that, do you?
No, sir.
Thank you all for coming
on such short notice.
The reason I called
this meeting today,
is to inform you of Tony Stone's
latest actions.
Stone?
Our message
didn't quite hit home enough?
I've obtained information
he's been spying on us.
I suspected
I had an annoying fly
buzzing around me recently.
So he was sent by
Tony the Stone of all people.
I guess that signal
we sent him the other day
did not have
the desired effect.
Seems like he's trying
to play it cool
and not just hitting us
right back.
He's trying to figure out
if we have a weak point.
Obviously he needs
to be taken care of.
However,
that was not the plan.
We originally
wanted to take over
the Stone family's territory
without turning it
into a battlefield.
So then what do you suggest
we do, Scythe?
The odds of a man like
Tony Stone behaving rashly,
well, they would have to be
a one in a million chance,
wouldn't they?
Yes, that's true.
Scythe, what do you
have in mind?
She's been gone awhile.
It's too dangerous.
We could never guarantee
something like that.
Oh, we could,
if we used the Phantom.
I would imagine
she's proven herself to you
many times over by now.
She has.
And although this is
a bigger "production"
than we've done before,
she has been able to pull off
some pretty impressive stuff
for us in the past.
We may have a shot at making
this thing work.
I'd like to hear your thoughts
on this, Mr. McGuire.
You certainly seem to possess
an innate ability to know
when you should promote
your talent, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Fine then.
Why don't we take a chance
on that confidence of yours,
Scythe Master.
Good, Ein.
Wonderful.
You really are
a brilliant subject.
This meaningless world
filled with confusion,
is going to be changed
by my will.
A new order,
a new balance.
I will orchestrate it all.
In this performance,
God Himself watches
from the balcony.
You are my lead, Ein,
my precious prima donna.
The meeting?
Did it go okay?
This is for
our next operation.
You can go over it thoroughly
later.
This time it's a series
of missions.
Many targets,
12 of them.
You serious?
All of them in one night?
Our individual missions
really aren't that difficult.
We just have to time things
carefully,
and focus on being
perfectly in sync.
So, these guys
are all senior members
of Inferno's rivals?
If this succeeds,
the power balance
on the West Coast is
gonna change significantly.
I dunno.
Doesn't it seem
kinda hasty to you?
Remember,
that is none of your concern.
But don't you think
it's natural
to wanna know why?
Did somebody tell you
that it was?
You shouldn't bother.
It doesn't have anything to do
with our way of existing.
What is our way of existing?
Do you know?
Be a tool,
be an instrument.
All we need to do
is just function.
Don't think about
unnecessary things.
How can you just say it
like that?
I'm only thinking.
That doesn't
hurt anything, does it?
We'll be destroyed...
destroyed.
Both of us.
I'm pleased to see
that everything's prepared
so promptly.
Don't give me that
silly smile, you son of a bitch.
This so-called plan of yours
is hardly an operation...
it's a joke.
You're putting me
and my whole team in danger.
Whatever do you mean?
I simply have confidence
in your team's abilities.
And another thing,
why are you insisting
on running this show
all by yourself
like you own the damn place?
Where's Clo, anyway?
Claudia had a matter
that required
her personal attention.
So...
I'll be acting in her stead.
Listen, Slimeball,
I'd do anything for Claudia,
no matter
how dangerous it was.
But I don't know why the hell
I should risk my life
for your sorry ass.
We will be having
more and more
of this type of operation,
you know.
I hate to tell you this,
but you may have to rethink
your future plans,
Miss Garland.
But such is life.
Lizzie, it's time!
We gotta get outta here.
Let's go.
We should go.
Right.
Great seeing you again,
have a good time.
Phase one, complete.
Roger, phase two, starting.
Now, hurry!
He's headed for the exit!
Search that way!
I got him!
Over here!
Who is this guy?
I know I've seen him
somewhere before.
I think he worked
as a bouncer
in one of Tony Stone's
strip clubs.
The Stone Family?
Why did they come
after the old man?
Those bastards!
Yeah, doesn't look like
Carlo's doing anything
special tonight.
Just stuffin' his face
at some high roller joint.
That guy's a real piece of work,
if you ask me.
Yes, sir, I understand.
Right. Okay.
I'll talk to you
on the next scheduled call then.
What's going on?
With regards to
the Ahlen Construction murder,
there's a rumor
that a local mafia family
was involved in the killing.
So, it remains highly likely
that this is a fight
between rival syndicates.
I see.
Oh, yes.
According to the information
we just received,
a gunfight has caused
a fatal accident.
We have someone on the PCH
now reporting to us live.
Perhaps they can
shed some light
on this terrible tragedy.
Typical media overreaction,
huh.
This night has just begun.
What are you trying to say,
Ms. McCunnen?
There's gonna be more?
Tonight's bloodshed
is just the beginning.
You see,
from this evening on,
it is truly going to be
a new era.
We should celebrate.
Let's toast
the survival of the fittest.
It's a world where
any dream is possible
if you have the power,
Mr. Godo.
Would that way of life
appeal to you?
Anton, what the hell
is going on?
Where's Abel and Bark?
Why the hell
aren't they responding!
Don't they know we're
in the middle of a goddamn war?
They're all dead by now, Tony.
Like a bullet, each one of them
left their mark.
I'm sure they're satisfied.
Wait.
What do you mean?
Are you saying
Bark and the others
are behind those bosses
getting whacked tonight?
Well, that's what everyone's
gonna believe.
After all, dead men can't
answer questions, can they?
A theory you can test.
Anton! Why?
Don't you get it?
No, I guess you wouldn't,
you never waver.
You're Tony the Stone.
You done good, kid,
real good.
Yeah, and finally,
I'll be able
to get out
of this filthy town.
I've been waiting 25 years
to break free
from this cesspool.
It's all over now.
Retiring already?
So young.
I received a pretty
substantial pay-off
from Inferno.
I can buy
a nice little cottage
or something on a beach
in the Caribbean.
What was your cut?
My first promotion
in 15 years.
I mean,
when you think about it,
I did single-handedly
end a mafia war.
You did.
Looks like we'll both have
a long life to look forward to.
An era came to a sad end
yesterday.
The six men
who had long controlled
the criminal underworld for
the entirety of the West Coast
were all tragically killed.
Tony Stone was considered to be
the mastermind of it all,
and the law ended up
bringing him to justice.
Having lost their leaders,
each organization
will be led to the new era
by our friends and brethren.
Under the banner of Inferno.
Splendid!
It's a miracle,
and we can attribute it all
to your Phantom.
Pleased to be of service.
Lieutenant Cyrus Gant,
received an award
from the Mayor earlier today
for his contribution
in resolving the mafia war,
a conflict that shook
the heart of this city.
Melanie Square entrepreneur
and gang leader, Tony Stone,
was behind...
So Ein, do people
actually believe
that's what happened
to those men?
You'll find people don't really
care about the truth.
They're not even interested.
...was brought to an end
by Lt. Gant's heroic actions.
I wonder
if anyone will pray
for the people
that died that day.
I wonder who'll
atone for that sin.
There is neither
prayer nor atonement.
Death is the end
of everything.
It doesn't matter
what you do after that.
There's no point.
[Music]
There is nothing...
dreams are just illusions.
All they do,
is get in your way.