[Music]
You shouldn't
drink yourself blind
just because you're not
getting any customers.
It like I'm having to come
get you every night lately.
Yeah, I know
you're probably right,
but I'm glad
I gotta good little sister.
Thanks.
Judy?
Judy!
Why her?
Judy?
I'm looking for where
Miss Judy Devens died.
Is this it?
Who are you?
I heard what they called you.
They called you Phantom.
I know who that is,
Judy's friends told me
he's someone that goes around
and kills gangsters.
Does that mean
you're a real assassin?
You really are,
aren't you?
You're the assassin Phantom.
Yeah, that's me.
Hey.
I'll give you
all of this damn money
if you kill them for me.
The guy in the alley,
the guy with the gun,
the guy who was supposed
to get the money.
Kill everybody that had anything
to do with Judy's murder.
Will you do it for me?
Judy...
So...
I was actually able
to get close to Phantom.
If I take the money I found
from the guys that killed you,
I think he can help me
avenge your death.
Hey, Cal.
I'll be straight with you,
five mill's not enough.
Okay.
But...
the difference isn't really
all that much.
I'm sure
you can earn the rest.
What do you mean by that?
It's easy,
you'll be my assistant.
That's so cool!
Hey!
So if I'm really gonna be
your assistant,
that means I can be there
when you do it,
when you get the guys
that murdered Judy, right?
Well, first off, we're gonna
have to pick up something.
Found anything?
Uh, hold on.
Just find the one
you want the most,
and we'll get you that one.
But it's hard,
I can't decide on which one
I like the most,
it's like I like them
all the same or something.
And if I do pick one,
that means I have to give up
on something else I like.
Don't worry,
it's not like this store
is gonna go anywhere.
If you really want something,
we can come back and get it.
Really?
Yep.
So all you gotta do today,
is pick out the one
you wanna wear today.
Cool! Well...
Hey, hey,
do I look cute in this?
Yeah.
You look really cute.
I've never had clothes
this nice before,
thank you!
If you can wait
for just a bit,
I'll get dinner
ready for you
when I'm done with
all of this stuff.
Okay.
But why are you cleaning?
'Cause this place is filthy.
I guess it makes sense though.
An assassin who made sure
his room was all neat and tidy,
probably
wouldn't seem that hardcore.
Now that I'm your assistant,
you can leave this stuff to me.
Cool! Well, thanks.
I'm gonna have to be
pretty useful
if I wanna earn what
that five million doesn't cover.
Hey, Reiji?
You got a family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
So you're like me.
Your folks too, huh?
I don't know for sure.
I ran away from my lying
sack of crap father.
A little while after that,
Judy took me in.
If it wasn't for her,
I think I'd probably
be dead by now.
That's tough.
Sorry, Cal.
The way I see it,
she's the only family I got,
but now, now she's dead.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Since I don't have her
anymore...
I don't know where to go,
I just feel so lost.
I really don't know
what the heck to do.
I know.
I've felt the same way.
It's a part of life,
everybody dies.
Hey, Cal.
All right,
give me your hand.
What for?
Your payment for today.
Oh, wow!
Oh my god, thank you!
I'll take good care of it.
I promise I will, always.
All of our main performers
have gathered.
Claudia, who betrayed me
and again devises
a nefarious plot.
Daisuke Godo,
who is being roped into Inferno
solely to provide her security.
Wisemel,
who saw the folds of this plot
and currently
tries to stop it with force.
And then there's this one,
our newest player.
A compelling ensemble indeed.
Now, we have quite a bit
of work to do, Ein.
Is he the one?
You think he's the one
who killed Judy?
I don't know, probably.
I'd at least
be willing to bet
he's one of the people
responsible.
I want to be with you
when it happens.
It's him!
He's behind the water tower!
Show yourself!
Reiji?
Show me your face!
I can't believe you bastards!
Mr. Godo,
don't do anything yet.
Why?
Wait, what just happened?
It was for you.
Ray, I got your back.
No!
Oh my god, Reiji,
are you okay?
Did he get you?
I'm fine,
it's just a scratch.
You're so stupid.
Why would you do
something so stupid?
Couldn't help it.
Chalk it up to some kinda
morbid curiosity.
You did a good job today.
I'm proud of you.
Come on, Cal,
you got revenge for Judy.
That's a big deal.
Yeah.
Mission accomplished.
Good job.
Leave your position
via route C,
wait for your next order.
Yes, Master.
Hey, when I went out
to pick up groceries,
I heard someone saying
Isaac from the Bloodies died.
Yeah.
So then, it's over, huh?
We got revenge.
That's it.
Well, how was
my assassin training?
Was I on my way
to getting any good?
If you wanted me to,
I suppose I could stick around
and help you on your missions.
You need to forget
about being a killer.
Why?
Just forget about it, okay?
Okay, I guess
you don't need me anymore.
Do you?
Now, I didn't say that.
I'd probably starve
if you weren't around to cook.
You can cook
and clean and stuff.
That's great!
Oh, I'll totally be your maid!
I always loved that outfit!
And I can wear it
around the house
while I'm doing
my cleaning and stuff!
Reiji...
What's up?
I, uh, I want you to know
that I still want to be
your assistant.
Come on, that's over.
Yeah, I know, but, I've been
thinking about it a lot
and there's a bunch of stuff
I wanted to say.
Maybe if I told you
more about myself,
you'd understand why.
Listen,
you're one of the smartest,
most capable people I know.
You could do
anything you want.
So why in the hell do you wanna
just throw it all away?
You don't like what you do?
No.
So, you don't like yourself,
do you?
No, I don't.
Do you think I wanted to spend
my life as a goddamn killer?
I hate myself.
I'm worthless.
No, you're not.
I'm too young
to be this broken.
And if you follow me,
you're gonna be fucked up, too!
I'm sorry, Reiji, sorry.
Cal, I was being a jerk.
I'm sorry.
I don't want this life
for you.
So many people've died
because of what I am now.
If it wasn't for me,
they'd still be alive.
They could've gone back home
to the people
who meant something to them.
It was never your fault.
It's your job, Reiji,
and if you didn't do it,
someone else would.
That's just an excuse.
Oh, fine.
Then tell me,
did you want to
kill those people?
Did you shoot them because
you thought it'd be a good time?
You like it?
Is it fun for you?
It's not, is it?
You gotta understand,
once you kill somebody,
the whole damn world changes,
right then.
It's hard to describe, but,
it's like
everything else dies, too.
The world starts to turn gray.
You still have a kind heart.
And you can accept people
for who they are,
it doesn't matter to you.
I just don't want you
to lose that.
This place I'm in now,
I can't bring you into it.
I care too much about you.
What am I supposed to do?
That world is where you're
always gonna be, isn't it?
I have to go there
if I want to be with you
forever, right?
You can't.
I don't want to ever
be apart from you.
I want to always
be by your side.
Forever.
I want to be...
with you.
I think I get it now, finally.
I want to be who I was
before this.
I thought somehow
I could be that person again
if I was with you.
Like you're the key.
I can be that for you,
I know I can.
I can learn
to live in your world.
No, let me do it.
I need to go back.
I need to get back
into the world you live in
and out of mine.
Reiji, you said
you would be by my side.
You made a promise.
You promised, remember?
I can't believe they're just
gonna call you in right now.
I'll probably be gone awhile.
You should go on to bed soon.
Naw, I'll stay up.
I found an old broken VCR
earlier this afternoon,
I think I'm gonna see
if I can get it working.
Just buy a new one.
That's a waste of money.
It might still work!
You think it'll work, huh?
Maybe you're right.
Hey, come back soon.
'Kay.
Promise?
Yeah, I promise.
That's right,
it's a promise.
...which leads
to the Peace Party...
Sweet!
It freakin' works!
That's right, Mary.
This, of course...
I wonder if the video store's
still open.
Reiji! Reiji!
You can't go in, kid!
It's dangerous!
Reiji's inside!
Help him! Help him!
Reiji!
What happened?
You'll be back.
Right?
You promised me you would.
Liar!
You said we'd never be apart!
You said you'd stay with me!
You promised!
Yes, he made a promise to you
and he broke it.
That man is
quite the con artist.
A liar.
Who are you... mister?
[Music]
It's okay to grieve.
You're leaving something behind,
it's human nature.
But now you have to go back
to who you were before.