[Music]
Eren...
What is it?
Nothing.
I just wanted to see
the look on your face
when I called you that.
I wanted to see
how you'd respond.
You found him, didn't you?
Where's Scythe?
Tell me.
Thank you,
I appreciate the favor,
Colonel Roshenko.
I am honored that you feel
you can call
on your old comrade
in your time of need,
Dr. Giuseppe.
That name
evokes many memories.
It brings to mind
my time in Moscow.
This is quite unexpected
from a person
with your intellect.
I never pictured you
as a man on the run.
I take it you found fieldwork
more challenging than lab work?
As the Bard has said,
there is a tide
in the affairs of men.
What?
A quote from Shakespeare.
Their tide is mine as well.
The seeds of perfection
which I've sown...
have ripened on the vine.
Listen up,
there's something funny going on
with some small-time
arms dealer named Roshenko.
Apparently, he's tight
with our man Scythe.
There's also a rumor
that's he's been hangin' around
the San Francisco Bay Area
as of late.
We've heard
that Scythe was spotted
headed this way as well.
That bastard is gonna try to
ship his ass outta the harbor,
and we're gonna stop him.
Clo's here?
What in the hell?
You have got to come
to your senses, girl!
That punk ass kid
is the reason Phantom escaped
in the first place!
And you expect me
to drag his two-timing ass
along on a job like this?
I do, and you will.
Damn!
You're a hard-headed bitch.
The same goes for you.
He can tag along with us
but I'm the one
calling the shots, you hear?
Scythe was spotted
in the area tonight.
He's heading toward
the Oakland Wharf
in the East Bay.
I also heard
that a bunch of Roshenko's men
have been hanging around there.
Check it out for me.
Got it.
Let's roll!
Make sure the bastard's dead.
Don't fail me.
Yes, Ein.
I too feel it's a shame
that Zwei could not
be secured as well.
Impossible,
given the current straits
in which we find ourselves.
I'll let that vixen
lay her claim to him.
Sorry, but I am
a little bit confused.
Master?
I don't recall telling you
that you were at liberty
to ask questions.
Sorry, Master, forgive me.
Colonel Roshenko,
is there a problem?
Oh!
They've learned our plans.
No, we'll be fine.
I'll have my assistant
aid in entertaining
whoever drops by
to wish us farewell.
Oh, and you will help as well.
My deepest gratitude, Colonel.
I will see you shortly.
I suspect my old comrade
is attempting
to buy my fealty
with a few men.
Ein...
I have to wonder,
can you still fulfill
my expectations?
Take this, please.
It should more than
serve as an adequate prop
for tonight's performance.
There are two additional
magazines as well.
I'm sure you recall
the delicate touch
that this weapon requires.
Avoid successive shots
as much as possible.
Yes, sir.
We must make this count,
as it will serve
as your final curtain call.
Yes.
Ms. Garland will be arriving
at the Wharf very soon.
She'll do fine, I'm sure.
I hear you've also sent in Zwei.
- Yes.
- That young man
has shown disloyalty
to Inferno in the past.
If he compromises the integrity
of our organization,
I'll accept full responsibility
for the results.
I see your faith
in our prodigal son
remains unwavering.
What I have faith in
is quite another thing entirely,
free will.
The free will to kill someone
on his own terms.
I imagine the novelty
of that control
after taking lives
at our behest,
would be irresistible.
Listen up, punk.
I think you being here
is a bad idea.
And you running around
with that toaster in your hand
is ten times worse.
Of course you do,
one bullet in the chamber,
15 more in the magazine.
I could kill everyone here
and still have a few left over
for target practice.
The hell?
Have you lost your damn mind?
The way I see it,
one bullet
may not be enough
for me to shoot my way
outta here.
But, that is definitely enough
to kill that bastard Scythe.
You talk a lotta smack, doncha?
At least
I don't have to worry
about being shot
in the back.
Look up!
That punk ass.
Now hold on!
Scythe!
Where are you?
Alright, you brainwashed,
back stabbing little
freak of nature.
I don't care if you're
number one or number two.
But because of this crap
you were trying to pull
with that other one,
my older brother ain't gonna see
his next birthday.
And unlike that bitch
that got you back in Inferno,
I don't forgive.
Now hold still.
Hey, Eren.
Let's go back.
It's not too late for that.
Please, Eren.
Let's go.
Scythe!
Now, Ein.
I understand.
Very nicely done, my boy.
I knew you would eventually
surpass Ein's level.
It's of little wonder
why Claudia so fixates on you.
Not only did your perfection
bloom at an amazing speed,
but you used Ein as a trellis
upon which to climb.
What do you mean?
Zwei, you know exactly
what I mean.
Stop.
Please, don't do it.
It's for your own good.
If you let me kill him,
Inferno will forgive you
for leaving, I'm sure of it.
Please, just come with me.
Eren.
Ein, dispose of him for me.
Do that, and show your true
allegiance to your Master.
Now run, Ein!
You dumb ass.
You run off like some kinda hero
and I find you here?
Thanks.
So how'd you guys do?
We took care of most of them.
Although we did take
a few hits,
but lucky for you, I'm fine.
Now get up.
He's still not dead.
So the plan is to meet up
with our crew
at Pier Number Five.
The northeastern edge.
Sir.
Hold it right there!
Oh yeah, you better run, bitch!
I'm coming for your ass!
Keep her at bay,
I'll go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my dear god.
Master.
Scythe!
Reiji.
What an interesting outcome.
A twist suitable
for the finale.
Eren.
What is it?
Nothing.
I just wanted to see
the look on your face
when I called you that.
I wanted to see
how you'd respond.
I guess a normal person
might smile
in this situation.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll make you smile someday.
I promise I will.
Someday you'll smile
when you're happy,
and you'll cry
when you get sad.
You'll be just
a regular girl someday.
You think so?
I do.
Just stay alive
until that day.
Okay?
I promise,
I'll protect you until then.
Eren.
I won't forget
the promise I made you.
I promise,
you'll smile again.
[Music]
I lost everything.
The only comfort I have now
is the name of a killer,
Phantom.