[Music]
I've never had clothes
this nice before.
Thank you!
Cal!
I was an early victim
of Claudia's treason.
A plot deftly woven
with strands of deceit.
Not content with betraying me
and turning
the title of "Phantom"
into one synonymous
with sexual slave,
she seized power with
the bloody coup of your friend,
acts that would make
Machiavelli blush.
Lizzie Garland contacted me
earlier this evening,
rather alarmed
that Ms. McCunnen
was nowhere to be found.
Her disappearance is suspect,
she's usually very quick
with an alibi.
As much as I'd prefer
not to believe it...
the evidence you've presented
is certainly compelling.
As for the Godo Family,
you suggest we ignore
their previous alignment,
and allow them to operate under
our organizational structure?
I can imagine
Inferno's pride still stings
from the theft of product
that the Godos
were a party to last year.
However, profit potential
in the Far East
exceeds the loss
suffered in that robbery,
by a large degree, in fact.
Oh?
The man who worked in collusion
with Claudia has been disposed.
The direct result of a difficult
executive decision
reached by Mr. Shiga,
and one illustrative
of his desire
to make amends with Inferno.
We will honor
the intent of our partnership,
but the details will
require renegotiation.
Of course, as penalty for their
involvement in the incident,
we will insist that the family
take a smaller share
than in our initial arrangement,
do you agree?
Very well, Mr. Shiga.
It seems we now have a mutual
foe in our former ally,
Claudia McCunnen.
I assure you she will pay
a very steep price
for her treachery.
I appreciate your understanding,
Mr. McGuire.
We are currently investigating
Claudia's whereabouts.
But the real mystery
is Phantom.
How will he respond
to her absence?
If I may suggest, Mr. McGuire,
Ein would be
an appropriate agent
to solve that question
once and for all.
A battle between the current
and former Phantoms.
That's lovely.
Have you lost your damn mind?
You want to team up
with the Bloodies?
Clo, Isaac practically
put your brother
in the grave himself!
I know, but they have
the backing
of a new organization,
a very large and powerful
syndicate.
What in the hell
are you talking about?
This group is destined
to be a major player
on a global stage.
Oh, yeah?
And you wanna get
to the top so bad,
you'll sell your soul
to the highest bidder.
I'll reach the heights
that my brother never could
in his lifetime.
My success will serve
as a shrine to his memory.
Giving up now
would not honor him.
Please, Lizzie,
I need your help.
I can't do this all by myself.
I hope you can
understand this, Clo,
I've been in the game
for a long time now,
but I still have some morals.
There's a line
that I just won't cross.
Promise me that you won't
cross that line either.
I'm serious, Clo.
Promise me that,
and I'm still with ya.
I swear on my life.
You went too far,
too goddamn far.
You screwed it all up.
We tore up the place,
but didn't find anything.
Shit, call Lizzie,
and tell her it's clean,
there ain't a damn thing
worthwhile here.
Yo, dudes,
I found the car keys!
Sweet, come on, man,
let's open that bitch up.
I'd rather be driving
its hot piece of ass owner.
No shit.
Reiji! Thank God.
I'm so glad you're alright.
Well, I guess you know
the situation by now.
Claudia!
What've you done?
I'm not gonna waste your time
with bullshit excuses.
All this time, I've only
ever done what I had to
to keep myself
from getting pulled under.
And I've rewarded you
for your loyalty.
I have no intentions
of giving up now.
You have to listen to me.
Reiji, I need you with me.
I have contacts
on the East Coast
that can help us out.
Inferno will
send someone after us,
but I'm confident
you can handle that.
Meet me at the diner
on Route 39.
Please, Reiji,
my life depends on you.
It's your fault.
[Music]
You know, those scars
could be removed
with minor surgery.
So tell me, why have I not
allowed you such treatment?
Out of cruelty?
No, Master.
What do those imperfections
represent?
Corruption and disgrace.
Correct, Ein.
You were the crowning
achievement
of my life's ambition.
A work of art desecrated
by that fool Zwei.
You've fallen
so far from perfection
that it disgusts me
to even look at you.
Perhaps there's hope.
Although you are now
a miserable shell
of your former glory,
it's possible one day
you may redeem those qualities
which were tarnished by
betrayal, if you kill Zwei.
If you can eliminate the one
who corrupted your mind,
the one who sullied your body,
perhaps you can
restore your luster.
And we can remove
those bothersome reminders.
I'll once again have
the master's pride in his work.
I won't fail you, Master.
You believe it's likely
she'll defeat
the current Phantom?
What I believe is
Ein will no doubt take the fight
to its ultimate conclusion...
and pay the ultimate price
if needed.
So, you're willing to count her
as a collateral loss?
In a way, Ein represents
my crude, experimental phase.
But now I'm on the cusp
of achieving a higher level
of refined expression.
Although I look upon
my first work with fondness,
I can't hold on to her
for the sake of mere nostalgia.
But given that we are
at the final stage,
do you think it's wise
to rely on her to deliver?
An actor's performance
can transcend
the most tiresome of dialogue.
An errant brushstroke
can spawn a masterpiece,
bringing unexpected delight
to artist and patron,
mischief caused by the muses.
Will our finale be
tragedy, or comedy?
I actually find
entrusting the outcome to fate
quite thrilling.
My mind races to envision
the endless
possibilities to come.
This mission hits close to home
for you, Ms. Garland.
Are you positive you can
go through with it?
Come on, man.
Haven't I proven myself by now?
You and Claudia have been close
for a very long time.
My fear is
you might be too emotional
to pull the trigger.
Shut the hell up!
I'm on it!
Girls don't like boys
who aren't on time, Reiji.
This is it.
Where it all started.
That's it, Zwei.
I can't.
I'm not Zwei.
I can't be him.
Cal!
What the hell have I done?
Right now,
I'm doing exactly
as I always wanted,
running so fast
no one can catch up,
leaving everything
a blur in the distance.
Yeah, but...
you're gonna lose touch
with the ground that way.
That's real freedom.
Unbound and light as air.
How far were you trying to go
that made you take
such huge risks?
Honestly, I don't know.
As far as I could, I suppose.
Listen, Clo...
all this running,
this whole damn lifestyle,
just wears you out.
What happens
when you finally fall?
Aren't you gonna regret
leaving something behind?
Losing everything?
I have to accept that.
The things
I've seen at this height,
I could never have experienced
any other way.
It's worth any cost.
I've always wanted
to see them.
[Music]
I've run to the end.
Dammit, Clo...
I'm sorry.
Are you just going to accept
your death without a fight?
It's useless to fight you.
My orders are to fight you
and achieve victory.
I must fulfill them.
I must prove
that I am the strongest.
The rightful holder
of the title "Phantom."
Well, then you should
fulfill them.
I'll fight.
You're still strong...
and you're still
following that man's orders,
his reasons to risk
your life and fight.
Scythe still controls you.
Eren.
But why?
There's no way
I can beat you.
I don't even really want to.
No, I'm done.
If I did kill you
and left this place forever,
what the hell
would I do then?
What the hell
would that change?
Would I stop being lied to?
Could I save
the people I love?
There's no exit
from this goddamn way of life,
no relief from this cycle.
So do it.
Put me out of my misery.
End it for me.
Reiji, I don't blame you,
there's nothing
you could've done,
I know exactly how you feel.
But Eren, you're still
in that world.
You're still living for the one
who lies to you, for Scythe.
No.
What I'm living for now
is this.
I remember what you told me,
you told me to find
my own reason to live.
This scar
is a constant reminder
of what you did for me.
It reminds me
of your strength.
That day, you did things
you never thought
you could do, for my sake.
The proof of your devotion
will always be here,
it's carved on my body.
Because of that,
I could never give up on myself.
Eren...
You're my other self.
You took the path that I wasn't
strong enough to take.
I went back,
you kept fighting
for your own life.
Since then,
I've been dreaming of you.
I could always take comfort
in the thought
that my other self was living
somewhere in the world,
strong and free.
This scar binds us together,
my life to yours.
I couldn't accept it
any other way.
It would be too painful.
If you can't go on
living like this,
no one could ever blame you
for that, but still...
If you want to keep
your promise to protect me,
you have to
end my life first.
Save me from the pain
of losing you.
I can't do that,
there's no way.
With you gone,
I'm just my Master's
greatest failure.
A useless puppet
waiting to be thrown away.
Eren!
You're my only salvation
from this endless hell.
Your life
is the only comfort I have.
So please, Reiji,
kill me first.
Because I don't ever
want to live
in a world
that doesn't have you in it.
Until today, I felt like
I couldn't keep any promise.
I thought
that I had lost everything.
Reiji!
Eren...
I tried to keep the promise
I made to you that night.
But I failed you.
I'll risk my life,
to make things right.
I swear.
You'll never see him again.
I must say that this
is an extremely disappointing
turn of events.
I'm not so sure of that.
Perhaps this is just
a brief intermission
before the final act.
Daisuke.
[Music]
Oh, wow! Uh!
Oh my god, thank you!
I'll take good care of it,
always.
Cal, I'm sorry
I can't be with you.
I can't go to where
you're waiting for me,
not for a while.
There are things
I have to do here first.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
[Music]
Liar! You said
we'd always be together.
You said you'd never leave me,
you lie.