[Music]
Then it's kill
or be killed!
So you woke up.
You don't have to be
scared of me.
I won't attack you anymore.
Who are you?
I no longer have a name.
But you can call me Ein
if you need to.
That is what
I am now known as.
Tell me, Ein.
Why did you attack me?
I was told to
verify your talent.
What talent?
You possess certain abilities
you may not be aware of.
You have the talent to kill,
and the talent to survive.
These are both skills
of an assassin.
No way!
But this doesn't
make any sense!
What the hell
makes you think that anyway?
Because you tried very hard
to kill me.
In your situation,
an ordinary person
would have panicked.
They would have frozen up.
And they would have
been killed.
But you were different.
You acted on your instincts,
before you even fully
understood the situation.
And you survived.
Zwei.
Zwei?
That is your new name.
No, it's not.
You can't just call me
whatever you want.
Why don't you call me
by my real name?
It's...
My name is...
You're wasting your time.
You no longer have that name.
What do you mean?
All your memories
were erased.
By a group called Inferno.
Just wonderful.
After the shooting death...
Your little Phantom
is the best in the field,
Scythe Master.
I'm honored.
Thank you, Mr. McGuire.
I'll be damned!
Can't believe a kid
pulled a job like that.
Yet, it makes sense.
Why else would we bestow
the moniker of "Phantom"
on the little thing?
It is quite the feat.
The creation of a ghost
living among us
but not entirely
of this world.
We owe many thanks
to the backing of Ms. McCunnen.
You have
a good subordinate, Claudia.
By the way,
I heard there was a slight issue
getting rid
of that journalist.
Was he too much to handle?
No! No trouble at all.
I also heard
that the execution
was witnessed by a tourist.
Is that true?
I don't know where
you got that information,
but we took care
of all witnesses,
and the target's body.
The scene
was totally cleaned.
Good.
That makes me happy.
You used Phantom
for all of that?
Yes.
You were supposed
to be killed,
so all evidence
could be eliminated.
But, Master
noticed your talent,
and he thought it'd be
a waste if you died.
"Master"?
Scythe Master.
He's my boss.
He decided that it would be
best to erase your memory,
to use the talents
that he saw in you...
and prepare you
for another life.
One as a member
of Inferno.
In this new life,
you'll be an assassin.
An assassin?
But why?
We're bringing you on board
as my second.
We need your talent, Zwei.
That's crazy!
Why the hell would I do that?
I'm not a killer!
You are absolutely free
to refuse our offer.
But know that if you do...
things will continue
as we originally planned
right here, right now.
And I will kill you.
You have to be reborn
if you want to live.
From this point on,
you exist solely
for the purpose of
killing other people.
But I...
I don't wanna die.
A dream.
That's all.
Just a bad dream
I can wake up from.
Believe that
if it comforts you.
Just keep thinking
that everything is a dream.
But, it's going to be
a very long one.
Put those on.
From this point forward,
you'll be with me at all times.
Follow every direction
I give you.
You got that?
Let's get started.
Zwei is progressing
through training as planned.
He hasn't made
a single fuss.
The boy is obedient.
If one trains
that hard every day,
I would imagine
forming any kind of thought
would be difficult.
That's precisely
how you tame someone.
You won't be disappointed
in the results, Ms. McCunnen,
I promise you that.
Do I seem too eager?
My pawn is your pawn
is my pawn, madam.
But we both know that everything
is an offering to Inferno.
Don't put your finger
on the trigger
until you're ready to fire.
And don't focus on
your shoulders or your arms.
Focus on the fingers
that hold the gun.
This is the front sight.
You aim by looking
at the front sight
through the notch
in the rear sight.
When you have the gun ready,
stabilize like this...
stretch your right arm out...
and then pull
with your left arm.
And even then, focus on
your hands, not your arms.
When you fire the gun,
don't rush.
Stay calm
and squeeze the trigger.
Now, fire.
Fire
the remaining five continuously.
At this distance,
you shouldn't miss a shot.
Once you can do that,
we'll work on your speed.
Your goal is six shots
in four seconds.
Focus on hitting those targets
every time.
You're still too slow.
Even though you can
hit them all now,
you'll be dead before
you empty the chamber.
Do it again.
All I do...
is exactly
what I'm told to do.
As long as
I keep doing this,
as long as I stay focused,
I won't have to think
about anything.
As long as I do this...
I feel relief.
I even forget
all the questions I have.
And then the day...
...just disappears.
I'm going out.
Keep up with the same
training routine.
Where're you going?
I have work to do.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
That man...
he must be Scythe Master.
This is your first sniping
assignment in a while.
But I'm sure it will be
a piece of cake for you.
700 yards to the target.
I have a .308 caliber
Remington waiting for you.
The weather at the location
is cloudy with a slight breeze
and should remain that way
until tomorrow morning.
Details are in the envelope.
Do you have any questions?
No, sir.
Good.
By the way,
how is Zwei doing?
The initial training phase
has been completed.
He'll be starting
a new regimen tomorrow.
I'm thinking
it's almost time for me
to prepare
a skills test for him.
Don't mind me.
Continue what you're doing.
I should start off
with "hello."
My name is Claudia McCunnen.
Are you curious to know
more than just my name?
No.
You've got to have
some questions
about the organization
that took you in.
Inferno?
I'm taking your lack of reply
as an affirmative.
Inferno is...
Well...
In a world of no legal order,
it is a group
that aspires to the creation
of a different kind of order.
Try this.
If we were to compare gangs
and mafia families to countries,
then Inferno is somewhat like
the United Nations.
Its goal is to unify
the underground world.
Such an idealistic goal
would have been laughable
if not condemnable
just a few years ago.
But we now have something
that will make
all of this possible.
I mean Phantom.
Yes.
That's your instructor.
The power of Phantom is...
absolute.
She eliminates the target
without fail.
Her existence gives Inferno
every confidence.
It's the fear,
the tremendous fear
organizations have of her
that keeps them
from defying Inferno.
She is truly the most powerful
assassin in the world.
Hold on.
She's just someone like me
that's being used
by your people.
That means Phantom and I
have no other choice
but to live like slaves.
It's true that we're
forcing both of you
to live this way.
But, you are not slaves.
You have freedoms
of which you're not aware.
Like speed.
How so?
Though your path may be set,
you can gain as much speed
down that path
as you would like.
You just need
the desire to progress.
And if you're fast enough,
you may even be able
to reach the top.
How you choose
to get there, that's up to you.
Now, don't ever think of
yourself as a slave again, okay?
Remember that the way
you present yourself
colors how others view you.
Act like a slave,
and you'll be treated like one.
CLAUDIA: I'd love to stay
and chat longer,
but there's some business
that needs my attention.
Alright, Zwei.
Bye.
You know, cars are meant
to be driven by people.
They're not driven by puppets.
Though your path may be set,
you can gain as much speed
down that path
as you would like.
You just need the desire
to progress.
Desire...
Freedom...
I'd forgotten those words
this whole time.
Ein...
Yes?
On your job, did you...
kill someone?
Hmm.
How'd you get this way?
Why do you do it?
I don't know.
They never told me
about my life before this.
Like me.
That's right.
I'm just like you.
They erased
all of my memories.
Made me a killer.
But, who cares?
The most important thing
is surviving one moment
to the next.
Because a killer...
doesn't have a past
and doesn't have a future.
They have nothing.
But...
This woman named Claudia,
she said...
You met her?
She came by here
when you were gone.
She said you and I
aren't slaves for Inferno,
she said we're free.
If you want to believe that,
then go ahead.
But, eventually
you'll feel nothing,
just the same as me.
It's the only way
to bear the burden...
just turn off.
Some day,
you'll feel just like me.
You'll understand
once you start killing people.
Out here, alone,
it's easy
to pull the trigger...
the target
is just a brick.
But, if it's something else...
Fire.
Now, Zwei! Do it.
Zwei!
[Music]
This is the continuation
of the dream...
the dream from which
you will never awake...
until you die.