[Music]
Well?
Oh, it looks fine.
I mean, good.
Uh, it looks great, really.
Hm. Yeah, whatever.
Hey, come on, slowpoke,
we don't have forever, you know.
Yeah, I'm coming, alright.
It's this way, I think.
You looked at the map,
didn't you?
Yeah, of course I did.
I'm gonna look in there,
will you wait for me?
Of course.
Your wallet, please?
Hello, young man!
Nice to meet you.
He's cute.
Gonna carry him all day?
Yes, sir.
So, are you here alone?
Let's go sit down.
I'll buy you a new one.
Dummy.
This is very sweet of you.
Well, it was my fault, so...
It's the least we could do.
Ahh! It looks yummy.
So uh, you guys in school?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
But it's a weekday.
Playing hooky?
Well, there's more to it
than that.
It's the school's
founding anniversary
and they're having
a lame party for it.
It's cool.
I used to ditch sometimes.
Don't we all?
I'm sorry.
You have some ice cream
on your mouth.
Oh!
You're too careless...
Wallace.
Ready to go?
So did you memorize
the floor plan?
It's drilled into my head.
How many security cameras
do they have set up
on the main walkway?
Sixty eight.
There are a couple
of blind spots...
but not quite enough.
Be more careful
when you're talking to people.
I'm sorry.
We should go back home
and work up
our plan of attack.
Our supplies
should be arriving soon.
Yeah, right.
Hey, Zwei...
Your acting...
stinks.
With the addition of Zwei,
Phantom can now
carry out her missions
far more efficiently.
They are a cohesive unit.
Those kids kinda
give me the creeps,
but I appreciate you
helping us establish a presence
on the East Coast
so far ahead of schedule.
It's my pleasure.
Phantom...
has been used
quite a bit of late.
Such repeated use
won't draw attention, will it?
I feel the same way.
Perhaps we should be
more prudent.
Put Phantom on hold
for a little while.
With all due respect,
you shouldn't trouble yourself
with undue concern
for Phantom's exposure.
I implore you to allow us
to proceed with this mission
as originally planned.
As added insurance,
I will be traveling there myself
to oversee the assignment.
Oh, yeah?
Got a hard-on
for this one, huh?
Alright, I'll leave it
to your Phantom.
I appreciate your faith, sir.
Wallace Yang...
That's the alias
given to me by Inferno.
A student,
living in Los Angeles.
An ironic choice,
the name of the first man
I murdered.
Ever since that night...
I've been working
regularly for Inferno.
Killing,
on their behalf.
Together with Ein.
As a team.
Don Lucio...
High rolling
Dallas mafia boss.
He's a recluse.
Spends most of his time
in the protection
of his mansion.
But tomorrow
is an exception.
He's traveling to the mall
to get a birthday present
for his granddaughter.
That's when we strike.
A present for us.
We are expecting the target
to arrive
at approximately 3 p.m.
We should be in place
and ready to act
well before he arrives.
Where is the best place
to pull it off?
You tell me.
What's this, a test?
Master asked me to.
We should definitely
mingle a bit
before we approach the target.
It's important for us
to fit in.
But, we can't do the deed
inside the mall.
Why's that?
It's too public.
I'm sure it'll be crawling
with guards inside as well.
They may even have control
of the security cameras.
We should make our move
somewhere more unexpected,
a place with less security.
And where would that be?
There's only one place.
We gotta be
where the target and his men
feel like
they can relax a bit.
Then...
Alright.
You're right, Zwei.
Let's go back to the room.
Yeah.
[Music]
Yeah, what is it?
I've located the target,
but they may have spotted me.
I've got two tracers
on my tail.
I need you to help me
throw off the scent.
Meet me at the fountain
by Elevator 9.
Hurry!
How long am I supposed
to wait for you?
I've had to walk around
all by myself.
Sorry.
I don't wanna hear another
one of your lame excuses.
So, what are you gonna do
to make up for being
such an insensitive jerk!
Well, uh...
You better give me
a real good answer.
Tell you what.
I'll buy you anything
that you want today.
And dinner.
Yeah, okay.
While I was waiting,
I checked out a buncha stores.
This is gonna be painful.
It's your fault, silly.
I said I'm sorry, didn't I?
The target's
in an antique store
in the mall's
southern sector.
So his car should arrive
to collect him
at the south entrance.
So, should we leave now?
We appreciate your business.
This outfit
would look totally fabulous
with those shoes over there.
You ready to do this?
Yeah.
I'll go in for the attack.
So cover me.
Got it.
We gotta be where
the target and his men
feel like
they can relax a bit.
Now, we take our leave.
Outstanding work, you two.
Bravo.
What's up?
It's nothing, really.
And you?
Oh! I'm totally fine.
Everything's great.
To what bychance do I owe
the honor of your presence?
Just checking up.
It's common
to commend one's subordinate
for a job well done.
I'm impressed.
And I appreciate
your diligence.
I appreciate your praise
as well.
That young man...
has been transformed.
Does this please you?
Well, of course, yes.
Problem?
No. So where are they now?
They are returning
on a commercial flight,
after disposing
of the equipment.
You wanna go, someday?
Not particularly.
Oh.
The waiting tire her out?
Oh, hello again.
Getting away?
Going back, actually.
We were on a trip here.
Well, that's nice.
Did y'all have a good time?
We did.
It was great.
Good.
Well, maybe
we'll see you again.
Bye.
See ya.
Hey, Zwei...
Your acting
was much better.
Two dogs...
kept in a cage
until the next hunt.
That's all we are now.
Time for another.
What's up?
It's nothing, I guess.
Don't worry about it.
Master was right about him.
The same path...
the path that took me
two years to complete...
only took him three months.
He is who I used to be.
But...
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid that...
by watching him...
I might learn the truth
about myself.
Those eyes...
scare me.
[Music]
We toss aside our emotions,
and pull the trigger.
We take away
the happiness of others.