Ya think everything's okay
down there?
Now don't you mind her, Cal.
She probably
just ran outta booze.
I'm out.
And unless I meet Mr. Right,
I'll be back in the morning.
Bye.
See ya!
This way!
Holy shit!
That must be The Phantom.
[Music]
This is just the latest
in a series of 20 murders
of high-ranking Mafia figures
in this last year alone.
These killings have been dubbed
the "Phantom Assassinations,"
and have sent shockwaves
through the entire
American crime underground,
leaving not only bodies--
If there's one thing
that Claudia's crew
is good at,
it's getting their work
on the evening news.
It's no laughing matter,
Daisuke.
We may well be
the next headline.
It seems the Gambino Family's
number two,
Deluca Rezzo,
has taken in his last aria.
We've taken out
their biggest muscle, huh?
The East is now ours.
We have our beloved Phantom
to thank for this bounty.
I was quite impressed
by the previous holder
of that title,
but this young man has more
than cleared the bar she set.
The speed at which
he's advanced is...
Well, it's a bit unnerving.
Kudos on being able
to tame him so thoroughly.
My intuition
simply paid off.
I suspected were we
to give him the choice,
he would choose
to remain loyal.
Ohh, really?
'Cuz I thought
our man was breaking a sweat
just so he could suck on
those big ol' titties of yours.
By the way, Mr. McGuire...
Regarding the Godo Family,
I have some more info.
The Japanese organization
that is looking
to join forces.
They have been able
to cultivate quite a large
demand in Japan
and have turned
a considerable profit.
However,
their Southeast Asian supplier
was recently struck
a devastating blow
and the family
has not been able to re-up.
They currently have
no viable product in stock
and no functioning supplier
for more.
I'm certain that if
we were able to establish
a working relationship
with them now,
we could easily
put ourselves in position
to be the top supplier
for the entire country
of Japan in no time.
Oh?
To that end,
I've arranged the sale of
five million worth of product
to Daisuke Godo who oversees
the family's operations.
I'm sure it'll be a healthy
start to our friendship.
Now hold on!
You ain't got the kinda
clout to go around
making deals like that!
You gotta know
your goddamn place, woman!
Enough!
Listen...
If the negotiations go well
under Ms. McCunnen's
watchful eye,
I see no reason why she
couldn't handle the account.
Well then, I'll see to
the proper arrangements.
How'd it go?
Clo, have you been stepping on
those boys' toes?
Maybe a bit.
Well, I hope you know
what you're doing here.
But remember, if you push
too hard for something,
you're gonna have to deal
with what happens afterward.
It's fine,
I can handle it.
Well, well,
you're back early.
Yeah, I'm back in town.
It's good to see you.
Thanks.
Lizzie briefed me earlier
on your outstanding progress
in New York.
You performed well.
I always do.
I'll bring your car
around front.
You driving?
You can drive me.
You finally got yourself
some game, Phantom.
So, what did you think
of the "Big Apple?"
It was too cold.
Guess what?
Isaac actually
had the balls to say
the only reason you took
this job, was for my body.
It's definitely a nice perk.
So that is the reason after all?
Well...
honestly, I've forgot.
Yeah. Who cares?
It doesn't matter.
You're here solely
of your own free will.
Bullshit.
I have no free will.
Right now, I have nothing.
Eventually,
you'll feel nothing,
just the same as me.
A killer doesn't have
a past or a future.
They have nothing.
You were right all along...
Eren.
[Music]
Your steering's
a little rough there.
Well, I guess
this 25-kilo package
is a little distracting.
Is it just us?
We're trying
to establish a relationship
based on trust
with these guys.
If we show up with a gaggle
of goons to back us up,
it may not make
the right impression.
Understood.
So, who are they?
They're some of
your fellow countrymen.
That Yakuza guy.
So this is a real
back alley deal, is it?
Relax, this turf
has been under
the Bloodies' control
for quite a long time.
Isaac's gang runs it?
Yep.
I doubt anyone
would be stupid enough
to cause much trouble
and piss off the West Coast's
biggest gang.
Therefore,
this is the safest place
for Inferno
to carry out our business.
That them?
There's no signal.
That's weird.
What?
Stay here.
A lone attacker.
Looks like he used
a pistol with a silencer.
And a large knife.
Picked them off,
one by one,
while they were panicking
in the dark.
He's definitely got skills.
I told you
to wait in the car!
What's going on?
What happened?
There's no deal tonight.
Someone canceled it.
Who the hell was it?
I don't know.
But there's not much sense
in sticking around
trying to put together
the pieces.
You should get back home ASAP.
What'll you do?
Clean it up.
That stunt you pulled
caused a lotta grief
on my property.
My turf!
The cops are all
lookin' for collars.
And the ho's and my boys
slangin' on the corners
are too scared
to get out and earn.
It's a goddamn mess out there
because of you!
You hear me?
I thought everyone
was supposed
to tend their own garden.
Isn't that how it's done?
Say what?
The security of your turf
is your responsibility.
My guests lost five million
dollars cash,
and four men
in your backyard.
I want you to consider
that carefully,
before you start
assigning blame.
Bitch, who the hell
do you think you are?
Let's be civil.
The Godos.
What is their reaction?
They're furious, of course,
but staying calm for now.
Alright, I trust you can
keep them at bay.
Assure them
that we'll look into it.
Of course,
we'll have to deliver
not only the money that was
taken from our guests,
but the bodies
of those who stole it.
You can handle that, Isaac,
that's your job.
Hold on.
You're calling
those Japanese guys our guests?
I never made
any kinda deal with them.
It's called saving face.
Someone came knocking
on Inferno's door
and was attacked.
Whether they are
guest or beggar
has no bearing
on what transpired.
The question now is,
will you allow that sin
to go unpunished?
Right, I'm on it.
Well, any breaking news
from the bosses' office?
So your stiff,
I asked around.
Her name's Judy Devens.
Twenty-six years old.
Been walking those corners
for a while.
Couldn't find
any connections on her.
Seems she was
in business for herself.
No pimp, I mean.
And her place?
We tossed the apartment,
but it was pretty clean.
No weapons anyway.
Looks like she had
someone living with her,
but we haven't
tracked them down yet.
You don't look
too happy about it.
You mind watching things here
for a while?
Huh?
I don't remember saying
that I'd stick around.
Go on ahead.
The cops
and the ambulance chasers
should be
outta there by now.
[Music]
Can you tell me if this
is where Miss Judy Devens died?
Who are you?
What's wrong, you deaf?
Well, what about you?
Were you one of
Judy's friends?
Were the two of you
very close?
Sisters.
What, ya think
we can't be sisters
just because
we're not the same color?
Sorry.
Do you happen to know
who did this to her?
How in the hell
would I know who did it?
You don't have any idea?
Whatta you mean?
Like Judy was askin' for it
or somethin'?
Guess it was
a stupid question.
Hold on!
What happens if you find 'em?
Whatta you gonna do
to whoever did this?
When I find them,
I'll make sure they get
what's coming to them.
Can you really do that?
Seriously?
Yeah.
Well, then you should let me
go with you to find them!
I'll help you
with whatever you need.
Hell, no.
Hey, listen, I really do know
who killed Judy!
I was there
when she got killed.
I swear I saw it
with my own two eyes!
The whole thing happened
right in front of me!
She had gotten drunk,
I was helping her.
She needed me
to walk her home.
We heard some shots,
and one hit her.
Please, take me with you.
What's your name?
It's Cal, Cal Devens.
What's yours?
My name's Reiji Azuma.
Cool. So you're Japanese?
Alright, Reiji!
The two of us are gonna be
partners in justice
from here on out, okay?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You and I are gonna team up
and get back at the person
that killed Judy.
I swear, you won't be sorry.
Alright.
I don't mind being
your partner, little lady.
At least until
we finish this job.
We met by chance,
or possibly fate.
And even with
the best intentions,
I know I will continue
to commit my sins.
Once again, my life
is thrown into confusion.
And unfortunately...
I'll be bringing someone down
that dark road with me.
[Music]
I don't know what to do.
I don't know where to go.
I'm lost.
What should I do?