[Music]
Romero.
I wonder,
if you had his life,
would you have that same
calm expression he does?
I thought surely
you'd be gone by now.
Shouldn't you be
headed to Mexico?
Yes, but before I say adios,
I wanted to remind you
you better be
on your best behavior
while I'm not around
to look after you.
So, what's up
with this passport?
He's kind of a handsome
little guy, don't you think?
You're asking
the wrong girl about that.
I can't tell the difference
between any of
those Asian dudes.
All I can say is
he looks like
he doesn't have a single care
in the world to me.
Well, you think
he could be a killer?
Honey, he doesn't look like
he'd hurt a fly.
Good.
That's exactly what
we're looking for.
One thing you must remember.
A knife can be used as
both a weapon and as a shield.
Now then.
But you must also
remember this, Zwei.
While deflecting your enemy's
attacks with the knife,
you have one hand open
to attack with as well.
That first time,
you were goin' easy on me.
Don't rely on
submission holds,
never forget
there is a knife.
The body
of Special Agent Theodore Brice
was discovered in Tijuana
this afternoon.
When learning languages,
you must use
your ears and your eyes.
...with a suspected
terror group at the center.
Brice was allegedly looking
into the activities
of Noche de Songre--
- Sure.
- ...a drug gang with ties
to many terrorist attacks
in both Central
and South America.
Officials have declined
further comment,
but it is widely believed
that this group may have
had a hand in the murder.
She's gonna kill someone else.
[Music]
And how is our friend Zwei?
Skill-wise, he is very close
to being completed.
Excellent.
Impeccable timing.
Disrobe please, Ein.
Yes.
Absolute perfection!
Who would suspect
that beneath this
beautiful, flawless exterior,
beats the heart
of a hardened killer.
Take it.
My Ein.
Unadorned clay,
molded by the master's hand
into something truly divine.
Could this perfection
beget perfection?
Could what you sculpt with Zwei,
dare match what we've created?
Yes.
Your glory will be crowned
with what you engender
in your protege.
Plant the
seed of perfection within him.
Yes, Master.
So Ein, you were gone
for a while.
Come on.
You have to get ready.
So how long I gotta wait here?
I'm not just some kinda freakin'
everyday jerkoff, you know?
I've risked my ass
for you guys.
It's because of
my dedicated service
that I can get you people
all those beautiful guns.
Your dedication
has not gone
unnoticed, Lieutenant Wallace.
I assure you that.
But we were unprepared
for so sudden a visit.
It's my crappy luck, pal.
My only goddamn vacation,
and I walk into a crime scene.
Yes, quite unfortunate.
Compounded further by the
victim's position in the FBI.
You knew him perchance?
No, I didn't.
And I have no idea why
in the hell they fingered me.
Nor do I.
I'm sure they would
want to investigate
any unsavory associations
I may have.
It might be in Inferno's
best interest
to throw me a line here.
I understand.
I hear the Caribbean
is lovely
this time of year,
Lieutenant.
I'll send you a postcard.
Now take one.
Chose whatever firearm you feel
the most comfortable with.
So more training?
No, not exactly!
A test.
I see.
Come with me.
What the hell?
This doesn't look like
the goddamn airport to me!
What's the score here?
The esteemed Mr. McGuire,
meet one
of the U.S. Navy's elite seals,
Lieutenant Wallace.
Another Inferno member?
Semi automatic.
She a bodyguard?
So what the hell is goin' on?
Something's up.
You've
been a very bad boy, Lieutenant.
If only you'd been
a bit more...
monogamous.
However, your insatiable
appetite
has led you to the trough
of terrorists.
And now the FBI
is smelling a rat.
Discretion is paramount to
the existence of Inferno.
WALLACE:
So you gonna do me like that?
You agree?
Lieutenant Wallace,
Inferno
is prepared to offer you
somewhat of
a bailout measure.
You can run.
What?
We will delay our search
ten minutes.
After that time has passed,
we will send someone
to intercept.
Escape,
and you may live.
Do you find this bargain
acceptable?
Yes.
Inside this building,
you will find
a well-stocked armory.
Take whatever you wish.
What the hell is this?
An opportunity to win your
life by sheer force of will.
It will also serve
as a test of skills.
All things considered,
this offer
is more than fair, Lieutenant.
I stuck my goddamn neck
out for you people.
And I get this?
Your time is far too valuable
to waste.
Dammit!
The situation is just
as you've heard.
This is your test
as well, Zwei.
You will kill that man.
How does not concern me.
Just complete the task.
But, I'm not ready.
My training?
Your training is done.
You performed very well.
Amazingly well.
I believe you're ready
for an actual mission.
Quite impressive.
To garner such accolades from
the Phantom of Inferno herself.
Let her praise
bring you confidence.
Confidence?
You're talking about murder.
Time to begin.
Find him.
I can't.
I can't kill him.
You only have two options
to choose from, Zwei.
You can either accept
the terms of your new life,
or you can reject them
and die right here.
[Music]
You believe he will succeed?
A Navy Seal
would be difficult quarry.
I wholeheartedly believe
you were invited here
to bear witness firsthand
to his abilities.
I have the utmost confidence
that you will
not be disappointed.
Which weapon did he choose?
Anytime you are
pursuing a target,
try to think from the
perspective of the one running.
But, your enemy
can do this as well
and anticipate your moves.
Phantom, what are your thoughts?
Lieutenant Wallace
is a highly skilled
and well-trained adversary.
He also possesses much more
actual combat experience.
True.
But Zwei's instincts
are extremely sharp.
If he can maintain his focus,
they may be enough
to give him the advantage.
And his odds of survival?
Fifty-fifty chance.
But this exercise will
definitely enable us
to get a measure on his
true potential as an assassin.
You think Zwei can win?
It's difficult to say
without knowing the extent
of Wallace's skills.
Wait! Don't shoot!
So now I'm unarmed.
Please listen to me.
I don't know why
they're making a guy your age
do something like this.
But just think for a second.
There's absolutely no reason
for us to kill each other.
Hey, kid.
You got family, right?
You actually remind me
of my little brother,
he's about your age.
All I ever wanted to do
was make sure
he was taken care of.
If you see one rat,
there are 30 more.
Just as if
someone tells one lie,
they will tell others.
I know there are more
honest ways to make a living,
but I was finally able
to send him to college.
I wanna be there
when he graduates.
The craftsman has
more than one tool.
An assassin
should be no different.
They're using us, you know.
Inferno doesn't give
a rat's ass about us.
We should go after them,
doncha think?
Two shots have been fired.
Perhaps the final outcome
has been determined.
What if the result
is not to our favor?
What if Zwei fails?
I assure you we have
a contingency plan
in the unlikely event
of failure.
Nonetheless, I still think
we should exercise
some degree of caution
and wait in the car.
Agreed.
[Music]
Game over,
you little prick.
I can't tell you
how many assholes like you
I've seen in my lifetime,
too afraid to close the deal,
and pull the fucking trigger.
Now, pay close attention.
I'll show you
how you kill someone.
Get that, bitch?
Killing ain't something
anyone can do.
And it ain't something
you can take lightly.
Now keep watching.
This lesson
ain't quite over yet.
That's it.
You did very well
for your first time.
Why?
This is all
just a dream, right?
I told you
that this would be
a very long dream.
It may just be
the beginning.
And unless you either die
or lose your sanity...
you will never
wake up from it.
You can end it if you want.
It is your choice.
These things
that are yours,
your eyes,
your ears,
your heart,
cast them all aside.
Become only Zwei.
See through Zwei's eyes,
hear through his ears.
You will lose all your fear.
You will be free.
No.
I can't.
I'm not Zwei.
I can't be him.
Yes.
You are absolutely right.
I can help you do it.
End it for you.
Please!
I'm ready to wake up.
It's over now.
You don't exist anymore.
Alright, Zwei.
Stand up.
Zwei...
Tell me how you discovered
that boy, Claudia?
A source.
A contact in Japan
recommended him.
I see.
He has quite a bit of
that country's character.
He found power
in a hopeless situation.
Yes.
You passed the test.
From now on,
you are part of Inferno.
[Music]
You are now as I once was.
I know the despair you feel,
I know your pain.