[Music]
It's a pleasure
to meet you, really.
So you're her...
the very first person
to be called Phantom.
But...
you're not Phantom anymore.
That name
belongs to me now.
Actually,
Scythe calls me Drei.
Ein, Zwei, Drei...
Pretty predictable, huh?
You sure like to talk more
than we did.
Does Phantom kill by talking you
to death these days?
If all I wanted to do
was kill you,
you'd already be dead.
Come on, sounds like
pretty boring work to me.
Finding you,
cornering you,
and then finally
killing you.
It's been my dream
for what seems like forever.
It's even worth working
for those assholes at Inferno.
I think I should have
as much fun as possible.
Watching you run,
and watching you die.
Really!
Will that satisfy you?
Oh, yeah.
Ohmigod, you should have seen
the look on Reiji's face
when he saw me
roll up on 'im!
He turned all pale and white
like he saw a freakin' ghost.
What'll top that?
Let me think.
I guess I should kill you
in front of him.
That should definitely
do the trick.
That'd be awesome.
What do you think
he'll do then?
You'll never know.
Unfortunately you ran into me
here instead of him.
So you'll never know...
what he'd do,
you'll be dead.
Ooh! So you came strapped.
All this to protect
Prince Reiji.
Is he really that important?
Obviously he is,
at least you think so.
What?
Ever since
he abandoned you,
you can't seem to get him
out of your mind.
You can't stop wondering
how he feels.
You hope
it's tearing him apart.
It's not,
Reiji's changed.
He's learned a lot
since then.
The past is behind him,
where it should be.
So what?
It means, he's put you
behind him as well.
And if you stand
in his way...
I know.
...he will shoot you down.
What are you,
his goddamn shrink?
I just know him
better than you.
I know his true strength.
Well, speak of
the freakin' devil.
Please, stop this.
Nobody here
has gotta die today.
Awww!
Did you hear what I heard?
So, I guess that means
you don't know him
as well as you think you do.
The players
are not all assembled.
There are still some
waiting in the wings.
Keep moving.
Yes, sir.
Do it!
Shoot.
I said stop it.
Right now.
Reiji, in your mind,
I was already dead.
Just make it official,
you'll feel better.
No way.
Come on, man up.
Send me to hell
where you want me.
I'll just take her along
for some company.
What is this
kindergarten shit?
Dammit! I knew
this would happen.
Why you gotta
keep acting a fool?
This is none
of your business.
We are in Japan!
There is no way in hell
people are not gonna notice
you firin' off a gun
in the middle of the day!
Who gives a crap?
Alright.
Go on ahead, fire then.
But right after that,
I'm gonna start firin'
till I empty this whole clip
in all three of your asses.
Now...
Listen to me, girl,
calm down.
Put down your gun
and walk outta here.
I've got a clear shot
on both of them.
Pow!
This sucks.
You guys are no fun.
Go home.
Inferno made her
the next one, that child.
And, I guess
I'm her new babysitter.
I think that I'd rather be
deep in the ground somewhere.
I'm glad it's you.
Someone has to.
And I hate to break it to you,
but your little
back-to-school special is over.
Inferno knows where you are.
So you need to go ahead
and get the hell outta dodge.
And I mean right now.
Also, Blondie's gone
kinda nuts.
I can't promise that I can
rein her in for much longer.
Alright, we'll run.
Hold on.
Lizzie, listen...
Enjoy life
while you got it, okay.
Don't make the same mistake
that Clo did.
Would you have shot her?
How about you, could you?
Eren!
If it'd gone further,
what would you have done
if you really had to
make a decision?
That won't happen.
We don't have much time.
We need to look
for an escape route,
I can handle that.
Also we need to get Inferno
to put a leash on Drei
at least until we get out.
It's time to play
our trump card.
Hurry up, Mio!
We'll leave you here.
Oh, sorry!
What is it?
Excuse me, sir.
There's a call for you.
Who is it?
Well, sir,
he won't give his name,
but he says
he's Claudia's right hand man.
What's this about?
It's been awhile, Shiga.
Two years.
Who is this?
I told you who I was.
Claudia's right hand man.
That kid that was
always by her side.
He was an assassin.
Phantom.
So you remember.
Last I heard, Inferno
was asking for your head.
Are you looking for mercy?
You're familiar
with Shinokura Academy?
Oh, my god!
So you must know
that Kaiten Godo's
illegitimate daughter
goes to that high school.
But she goes by Mio Fujieda.
Let me make this
perfectly clear;
she is off limits!
She has nothing
to do with this!
Don't worry.
As long as we're safe,
she's safe.
So you better help us
stay safe.
What do you mean?
Inferno has sent an assassin
to take me down.
I need you to throw
your weight around a bit.
Put a collar
on Inferno's dog.
This is your turf, after all.
How dare you?
Do it, or not.
It's up to you.
This has nothing
to do with her!
Make sure
it stays that way.
Dammit.
Your acting's gotten better.
Nice work.
Still not as good as you.
Hopefully, this play will
buy us a little more time.
Shiga understands,
he's smart.
I'm sure he'll decide
to play along.
But what if he doesn't?
In that case, we'll think
of something else.
I don't want to put Mio
in any real danger.
Reiji, are you happy
that Cal's alive?
Yeah.
I thought that I was poisonous,
everything I touched,
all I cared about
withered and died.
But she's still alive,
broken but still living.
Tomorrow, I'll head north
at daybreak.
I know of a smuggler
that runs a cargo boat,
I'll go talk to him
in person.
All by yourself?
Yes.
You need to stay with Mio.
I guess we should head home!
It's gotten kinda late,
I still need to
make us dinner!
Hey, Phantom!
The higher ups
called me earlier.
This is bullshit!
Well, I guess
she already heard.
And isn't too happy.
Kaiten Godo's progeny,
whose existence
has been kept hidden.
Seems like Ein and Zwei knew
exactly what they were doing.
Their choice of disguise has
proven to be quite brilliant.
I don't give a crap about
the damn Japanese Mafia!
I know you don't,
but look,
the Godo Family is a major
player in Inferno,
so we gotta do what they say.
Correct.
Your hands are tied
until the Godos
confirm the girl's
lasting safety.
Zwei has outsmarted you.
I'm sure another chance
will come.
But we will have to wait
'til then.
Goddammit!
You want us to watch
a high school girl?
That's correct.
Who is she, sir?
All you need to know
is that she is of high value
to the Godo Family,
as well as me personally.
And, uh, you need all of us
to tail her?
Yes, I do.
Protect this girl
with your very lives.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
So you really hate Reiji,
don't ya?
Yes.
That's what's kept me going.
And it's the only reason
why I've been putting up
with all this crap from this
goddamn operation for so long.
I've been waiting for the chance
to kill him all this time.
And now, I am so close.
To be honest with you,
I think putting the brakes on
is a good thing.
Yeah?
I don't wanna see you two
kill each other, Cal.
It's just a waste of life,
so yeah.
So in your mind,
we'd both go down.
You don't think
that I could win?
It's not that.
Reiji did pull a bunch of crap
a few years ago
and told a lotta lies
to Inferno.
I even felt a little burned.
Because he's a damn
con artist.
But in your case,
he was only lying
to protect you.
It was really
for your own good.
Don't give me that crap!
He lied from the moment
he met me.
He kept me in the dark
and told me
whatever the hell he wanted.
He was scared
out of his mind.
He knew he couldn't
keep the act up forever.
I'd see right through it.
He wanted to keep you
outta all that violence,
He lied so you wouldn't
get dragged into it.
Oh, please!
The only person that bastard
ever cared about was himself.
He abandoned me.
And as soon as he got himself
in over his head with me,
he split with that girl.
Even if that was the case,
that's still no reason
to follow in his footsteps
and start killing too.
Is this really what you wanted
to do with your life?
It's exactly what I wanted.
I was pitiful and weak,
but now, I can scare
a crying child into silence.
All those big shots
that used to do
whatever the hell they wanted,
tremble at my name.
It's really
a dream come true.
Kicking those assholes around,
listening to them beg,
and putting them
outta their misery...
sounds like
a great life to me.
Reiji saw this in me,
and it terrified him.
He was afraid of me.
He knew I was gonna be
stronger than him.
So he tried to throw me away
before that happened.
Now he's gonna pay for that.
Cal...
all that rage...
It's gonna burn you out.
Did Eren really not come
to school today?
Yeah, she started
having a fever last night.
I'm sure it's just
a little cold.
I can totally
help out with that.
I'm sure I can figure out
some way to take it from her.
Hey! You know,
seeing you two chatting here
makes me think
that some villages
are missing their idiots.
Shut up.
So listen, we're gonna
see a movie later,
and if you want,
I'll let you guys tag along.
I guess that's an invitation?
Mio will be there.
Wow! I am in high demand today!
Can't do it though,
I already got plans.
You got a date or something?
That... could... be... it.
Well, I guess it's just
the two of us.
I guess so.
It's not like her.
Normally,
she just orders me around.
This is sneakier than usual.
Yeah.
Poor Eren.
I hope she starts
feeling better soon.
Well, let's go get our tickets.
I need to stay out
for a while anyway
so Eren can get some rest.
Cool!
This is perfect.
If I start hanging around Mio,
Shiga will think
I mean business.
I guess I got
a little carried away.
How embarrassing.
It's fine.
What did you think
of the movie?
I'm kinda glad
Sanae picked it out for us.
You know, Reiji,
I think you're
a really mysterious guy.
What?
It's not bad,
you're just different.
It's like you see the world
in your own special way.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
It's like most people
seem to take life for granted.
But not you.
You seem to really appreciate
things more than most folks.
Just being with you makes me
enjoy things a lot more...
it makes me happy.
It makes me remember
that even when things
aren't that exciting,
they still have meaning
if you look.
I think most people
have forgotten that these days.
Am I interrupting?
Who is that?
Okay.
So that chick
is the Yakuza princess.
First Ein,
then me,
then old man Godo's daughter,
You've got a real talent for
picking out the girls you use,
doncha?
I know you're not really
gonna do crap to her.
You don't have
the balls for it.
Listen.
Now, back to the game.
We gotta settle
who the real Phantom is,
who deserves that title.
Looks to me like it's you.
I'm, I'm just an average
ordinary person now.
Oh, please!
Don't give me that crap, Reiji.
I know you better than that.
If you want my head, Cal,
you got it.
Is that so?
You've been running
for way too long
to just give up.
I don't believe you.
You don't wanna die now.
You're just lying to me.
If you were to kill me,
it'd be what I deserve.
It'd just be karma
finally coming back
to bite me in the ass.
One thing,
you can kill me,
and Eren does not get hurt.
Right?
I'll trade my life for hers.
So you're willing
to sacrifice yourself
for that bitch?
She's not gonna
cause any problems
for Scythe or Inferno.
I know she won't.
You're too goddamned selfish
for me to believe you.
You abandoned me,
and left me for dead
just to save your ass.
Now you're telling me
you'd give up your own life
for hers?
You gotta understand,
I thought you were dead, Cal.
You'll get your wish.
I promise I'll kill you
eventually.
But first,
I'm gonna make you suffer.
You understand?
Then I'll kill you.
Reiji!
We are ghosts
that have no place to haunt.
Non-existent phantoms.
[Music]
If you can't pull
the trigger by then,
My guess,
you're just too soft.
It's gotta be kill or be killed
in this business, right?