Hey, what're you doing?
What's it look like?
Cooking.
Hope you're hungry!
What in the heck
is in there?
Those.
Come on,
don't be scared of it.
I cooked pretty
much all the meals
when I lived with Judy.
Man, that's good!
Yeah! Innit it?
Yeah, so I grabbed one of
the nice expensive pots
off the shelf.
And then I just
whipped out a $50 bill.
You should've seen the old guy
at the counter's face
when I flashed
that cash at him.
Oh, oh, and then,
I was like--
I see.
You'd like to
take this girl in
and train her
in the ways of an assassin?
Hey, Cal.
Yeah?
You don't...
happen to know
how to use a gun, do you?
Oh, yeah.
"You feel lucky, punk?
Well, do ya?"
Well, that's how
Clint Eastwood does it.
Ummmmm...
Then there's...
Look, I'm serious here.
Listen,
I'm trying to make a plan
to avenge Judy's death.
But I'll be straight with you,
five mill's not enough.
Okay.
But...
the difference
isn't really all that much,
I'm sure
you can earn the rest.
What do you mean by that?
It's easy,
you'll be my assistant.
You don't have
to say yes, but--
That's so cool!
So, I'm gonna be
the Phantom's assistant!
Yeah.
It's cool,
I can handle it.
Hey, so if I'm really
gonna be your assistant,
that means I can be there
when you do it,
when you get the guys
that murdered Judy, right?
Well, first off,
we're gonna have to
pick up something.
Like what?
You gonna get me a gun?
Some new clothes.
Yeah,
we'll go shopping tomorrow.
Okay, sure.
You goin' out?
Gotta job to do.
Well, what should I do?
You stay here
and guard the hideout, okay?
What? That's boring.
Well, work is
supposed to be boring.
That's why it's called work.
Just hang out here, will ya?
Yeah.
Five million dollars
and four of our men's lives
were taken.
What's more,
this all took place
on your turf.
But you refuse to offer
compensation or an apology?
I am sorry for those who died.
But we can't be held
responsible
for events that transpired
before our arrival.
You bitch!
Cool it.
Yes, sir.
Look, our business took a hit
with this
unforeseen event as well.
We are doing
everything in our power
to find out
exactly what happened.
Yeah?
Then maybe you'll be able
to get us back our money.
In the meantime,
I would like you
to remain stateside
until the matter
is completely resolved.
Of course, I'll see to it
your stay is comfortable.
Well, I'm not sure that--
We had our money stolen.
And we lost
some of our best guys.
I personally
don't wanna go home
completely empty-handed
with our tails between our legs.
Come on.
Let's stay
a little while longer.
How will we explain it
to the old man?
Tell him the food here
gave me the runs.
Isaac's behind all this,
I know it.
You sure about that?
There's no way our conversation
at Headquarters
was leaked outside the room.
It had to be an inside job.
But, what went down didn't
exactly work out for him either.
That's true.
At least it would appear
that losing five million dollars
and an untold amount
of street cred,
would be a bad thing.
But maybe it's not.
I suspect that he sees it
as the cost
of preventing the Godo Family
from becoming
a part of Inferno.
He's obviously afraid of me
getting such a strong backing
in the organization.
It just seems too aggressive.
You think he got
to the top of Inferno
with just tough talk?
He's the kind of guy
that'll do whatever he can
to get what he wants.
I'm almost positive
that he'll try to take out
the Godo's again.
Then why don't you just
let them all go back to Japan?
That would mean letting go
of our most tempting bait.
What?
We're shark fishing.
Using Godo as the bait.
And you as the hook.
Yes.
It seems we're staying here
a bit longer.
I would appreciate it
if you remained in town as well.
Yes, of course.
And as for our
contingency plan--
Give it a goddamn rest
already, Shiga.
You're gonna spoil the booze.
Well, we'll talk later.
I hope the rest of your stay
is pleasant.
I've got some good news.
I was finally able
to track down a coordinator
with no ties to Inferno.
Was that that Giuseppe guy?
If he's as knowledgeable
about the underworld scene here
as he says he is,
maybe you can stop worrying
and enjoy yourself for once.
Yes,
you could be right about that.
Have a drink and forget
about it for a while,
It's on Inferno.
We got some 30-year-old Scotch
right here.
Well, can't let this
go to waste now.
Bait, huh?
Hey! Reiji.
The hideout's totally secure!
Don't be so loud about it, okay?
Ohmigod, I'm sorry!
Damn, you weren't kidding
when you said we'd have
a comfortable stay.
I never kid.
You know, Claudia,
I meant it when I said
I wouldn't go back empty-handed.
Your subordinate
isn't too happy
with this turn of events.
Who? Shiga?
Not to worry.
He's my advisor,
so it's part of his job.
I never trust a yes man.
Right.
If I were you,
I'd definitely be
watching my step right now.
You're on the edge,
aren't you?
You can tell?
It's like they say
back in Japan,
the stake that sticks out
gets hammered down.
But, once this thing's
sorted out,
the strength of the Godo's
will carry you.
Wonderful.
[Music]
Found anything?
Uh, hold on.
Ya know, it's been two hours.
Yeah, but,
I'm kinda stuck.
Nothing you want?
Come on.
There's lot's of stuff!
Well?
There's just
too many of them.
This is all way harder
than I thought it'd be.
I don't even know if I could
narrow it down to one.
Just find the one
you want the most,
and we'll get you that one.
But it's hard.
I can't decide on which one
I like the most,
it's like I like them
all the same or something.
And if I do pick one,
that means I have to give up
on something else I like.
Don't worry.
It's not like this store
is gonna go anywhere.
If you really want something,
we can come back
and get it.
Really?
Yep.
So all you gotta do today,
is pick out the one
you wanna wear today.
Cool! Well...
But we're not gonna
come here everyday
to buy you new clothes, okay?
Yeah, I know!
I hope so.
Hey, hey,
do I look cute in this?
Yeah.
You look really cute.
I've never had clothes
this nice before.
Thank you!
Hey!
Come on, slowpoke!
Go on home,
I'll be right there.
SIG-Sauer, huh?
Seein' how you like
that Beretta so much,
I grabbed this one.
Nine millimeter, 15-shot.
But, since you said
she'd never used
a gun before,
I thought
I'd get something smaller.
It looks good to me.
Let's try it out.
Thank you.
So?
"So" what?
So what else is going on?
You didn't come
all the way here
to give me a gun
I didn't ask for.
Well, it's about
your little friend, Cal.
Her name came up
in the meeting today.
Isaac bring her up?
Worse than that.
It was McGuire.
He wants to know if
there's been any progress
in Cal's training.
So I just thought
it might be a good idea
if you at least taught her
how to use a gun.
That took a while.
What's up?
You already decided
to change?
Those are my special clothes.
I can just wear these
if I'm hanging out at home.
I guess you're right.
But you should
grab your jacket.
Huh?
You're gonna learn
how to use a gun today.
Really?
So, this is where
you practice?
It's been a long time
since I've been here.
It seems lonely.
Let's get started.
Hold the gun firmly.
Focus your strength
on your hands.
Stretch your right arm out
and pull with your left.
Good. Very good.
Now make sure
that you can see your target
right in the middle
of that notch in the back.
You see it?
My hands are shaking.
Don't focus your strength
on your arms,
focus on the fingers
holding the gun.
Now keep holding it like that,
and slowly pull the trigger.
Just slow down.
Try not to pull it.
Give it a steady squeeze.
'Kay.
Whoa! I hit it!
I really hit it!
Hey! You see that?
Aw, yeah!
You gotta change out the clip.
She seems pretty comfortable
handling the gun.
Okay.
Practice by yourself
for a while.
Okay!
So it's lonely, huh?
"You talkin' to me?
You talkin' to me?
Then who the hell else
are you talkin',
you talkin' to me?
Okay."
"You're dead."
Hm?
Oh, man.
I missed big time.
Cal.
Yeah, well, I...
I was just fooling around.
That was DeNiro.
Lemme see it again.
Huh?
Cal, I want you to do your
DeNiro thing one more time.
"You talkin' to me?
Not the words.
Listen.
Don't just shoot right away.
When you think you're ready,
count one
and then pull the trigger.
Alright.
Holy crap!
I did it! I did it!
Yeah?
You ready to go shark fishing?
Godo's starting to get
a little stir crazy.
He's looking to go out
and hit the casinos tonight.
Keep an eye on him,
and be on the lookout
for Isaac to make his move.
Hell, yeah.
I wasn't even close.
They seem pretty relaxed.
Yeah.
Argh!
It's not my lucky night.
Aww! Those are the breaks,
my friend.
Only those who believe
in the Goddess of Victory
can hope to win her heart.
She's already spread her legs
so wide for you,
I'd just be getting
your sloppy seconds.
What? You quitting?
Just going back
for a little taste,
at least I got that.
Don't get too wasted.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm kinda surprised
that he decided to break off
from the group like that.
Alright, bro,
looks like you're in.
Uh, sure.
Hey!
How much do you wanna bet
that this place is
totally run by the mafia?
This isn't some kinda
DeNiro movie, ya know.
She's probably a natural,
like me.
But does that mean
it's okay
to make her walk down
the same path that I took?
No, I need to set her free.
As soon as I can.
Wanna play poker?
'Scuse me.
Yes, sir?
I lost my friend,
I think he was just
sitting here a minute ago.
Oh, is your friend
a Japanese guy?
My guess is he went back
to his room.
He just left
with a young lady.
There goes the bait.
[Music]
Ah! Shit.
No.
It can't be.
Eren?
[Music]
No way.
It can't be her.
Eren is dead.
I killed her.