[Music]
There is one more thing.
I have another task for you
in LA.
I was under the impression
that the focus of our activities
would be shifting
to the East Coast after LA.
This particular operation isn't
from McGuire and the others.
No, this is to score points
on a personal level.
So your superiors
will owe you one,
you want to make
an unexpected contribution.
Yes.
So what do you think
about making this one
a bit more clandestine?
I must confess to you,
I enjoy doing things sub-rosa.
I'd expect no less.
And I promise you,
everything will commence
in profound secrecy.
This will show
the true greatness of Phantom,
won't it?
[Music]
Thank you.
That was your local weather
and now on to the news.
It's a topic that always gets
a lot of attention around here.
The construction
of the much talked about
large-scale shopping mall
in Santa Monica.
Although the West Coast
garners the attention
of thousands of tourists a year,
most of them frequent
the big recreational parks...
Who was it?
My part-time job.
Someone called in sick
so they want me
to come in and cover.
Okay.
I'll drop you off.
I was planning to go out
to practice my driving anyway.
You don't need to.
If we're supposed to be
a couple living together,
it seems like
the normal thing to do.
I guess.
Now for our next story.
It's an unfortunate
but well known fact
that the illegal drug market
on the West Coast
has been monopolized by
the Chinese Mafia for some time.
However, recently,
the Japanese Mafia
has been stepping in.
This greater presence
has led to various scuffles
in Chinatown
and the surrounding areas.
You should be careful.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not gonna get myself
dragged into that whole mess.
That's not what I meant.
We don't want anyone
to find this place
because you set off
the fire alarm.
Yeah, right.
Are you two going somewhere?
Hello, Ms. McCunnen.
Maybe you'd like to
come with me?
I'm sorry, but I was planning
on going out
to practice driving
for a while.
Why don't you try
using this piece of hardware?
I think I'll walk.
So? How's she handle?
You like the car?
Don't you feel like you could
just keep on driving forever?
Makes you feel like the goddamn
king of the world, doesn't it?
Not me.
I don't know if I'm ready
for a car like this,
it's too much.
I'm impressed
that you were able to stop.
For a second there,
it was all over.
All over?
I've learned that nothing
will ever be over,
not even if I die.
And all that'll mean,
is fewer murder victims.
You're wrong.
You're not going to die
for nothing.
It will matter.
And I will decide the place
for you to die.
As one of the few men
who've won my trust,
I'd say you've earned
that much.
Now, go.
Keep driving, Zwei.
I know this mission
might seem a bit unexpected,
but these things happen.
Consider it a part-time job.
Yes.
Claudia seems to be infatuated
with Zwei.
I want you to keep your eye out
that she doesn't steal him.
Even if that were
to take place,
it wouldn't be a problem.
Zwei's participation
is not necessarily required
for me to complete my missions.
That's true.
I mean, the two of you
working together as a team
was simply the effect
of mere coincidence.
And convenience.
Take her out for a spin.
Get to know her a little better.
Just be back within the hour.
Are you sure about that?
Of course.
I want you to get familiar
with this sort of thing.
Enjoy your drive.
See ya.
That's one hell of a car
you're stepping out of
in those heels.
Tell me,
you think it's cool,
meeting out in the open
like this?
Don't worry about it.
I understand
if you feel intimidated.
But I guarantee you,
you are safe
in speaking to me here today.
I'll take your word for it.
I thought a lot about
the plan you designed.
Basically, you ready
the weapons and logistics.
We're the soldiers,
we get in there
and make the grab.
Those are the terms
as I understand,
unless
I'm missing something.
No.
We do this
and then you pay up.
500 kilograms of cocaine,
uncut, no filler.
Ha! That's about 200 mil,
which'll keep our funding
problems at bay for a while, eh?
Yes.
Does something
not sit right with you?
I'm not sure I see the benefit,
Ms. McCunnen.
I'd like to know
what you're going to gain
by offering
such good terms to us,
if you don't mind.
I'm just trying to do
the Godo Family a favor.
And knowing your family's
reputation for loyalty,
I'm trying to get you
to owe me one.
Yeah.
So you're looking for backing,
huh?
Yes, I'll give you
200 million,
but in the end,
I'll gain something
that's worth so much more to me
than money.
I see.
Sounds like
a fair deal to me.
It doesn't matter, it's done.
We've already made our decision
either way.
It's too good to pass up.
You can count us in.
That's true.
I mean, the two of you
working together as a team
was simply the effect
of mere coincidence.
Look, I'm an INN reporter.
- Hey!
- Shut up and listen.
Just take this! Please!
But, why?
I want you to give it
to the police.
That's all you have to do.
Now hurry.
Wait! Hold on!
[Music]
Why is this happening?
I'm done with this.
I gotta eat something soon.
So tired.
Don't even know
what day it is.
I wanna go back,
back home.
It's quiet now,
so if I run, I might make it.
No way.
I go out now,
I know she'll find me,
and then,
she'll kill me.
After the tough time
he's given you, Phantom,
he still clings to life.
I must say I'm impressed.
Through suppression
of his hunger and even his fear,
he chose to remain
in this place.
He assessed this
as the only course of action
to his survival.
It was his instinct
that made him continue
to suppress his impulses.
Interesting!
A fascinating subject.
Zwei, Zwei,
wake up.
We're going out.
You need to get ready.
Sure, right.
New mission,
we'll do it tonight.
But before it gets dark,
we need to scout the location.
At 20:00 hours tonight,
500 kilograms of cocaine
will come through here.
And let me guess,
Inferno wants it.
The primary objective
of our mission
is to back up
the assault unit.
What do you know about
these assault unit guys?
Are they reliable?
Claudia seems to be somewhat
infatuated with Zwei.
I want you to keep your eye out
that she doesn't steal him.
They told me nothing.
I don't know.
So this is a mission
that only Phantom can carry out.
Let's go back, we have
to ready our weapons.
Hey, Ein, tell me,
are you able to remember
any of your dreams?
My dreams?
Like things
that you've never seen before,
or people you know
you've never met.
I guess I just wonder,
are they dreams?
Or, memories?
Dunno.
What do you dream about?
You have 'em, right?
Sometimes.
I have dreams
about colors.
Yeah? Is that all?
No, there's...
there's wind.
Strong wind.
And there's blue, white,
and green.
But that's all there is
in that place.
Nothing else.
All I can ever remember
is the bright lights,
the colors,
and the blustery wind,
the strongest wind I've known.
I wonder if that place
you dream of, if that's home.
I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
What would we do?
We find out where we're from.
Then what?
Wouldn't you at least
want to check it out?
Come on, the place holds a spot
in your memory, your past.
It's gotta be important.
It's not,
there's no place for us there.
There's no place
for killers anywhere.
There's nowhere.
Just right here
and right now.
There's nothing else for us.
Dreams are an illusion.
They just blur
your view of reality.
Yo, it's me.
Lizzie. What is it?
Well, Zwei.
I've got a message for you.
From Clo.
She wants you at her house,
eight o'clock.
That's pretty short notice.
Is something going on?
We're switching shifts.
I have this big hoopla
to attend tonight,
so it was decided that you'll be
guarding Clo in my place.
You can handle that, can't you?
I don't think so.
We already have
our orders for tonight.
What?
No one told me.
Who gave you those orders?
Scythe Master.
He must be acting
out on his own again.
Not like
that matters to you much,
Clo being your boss and all.
- But.
- Eight o'clock.
Don't forget.
It's alright, you should go.
Ein...
I'll carry out the mission
given by Master alone.
I've done it before.
You follow Ms. McCunnen's
instructions to the letter.
You sure?
It's not safe.
I'll be fine.
You'll be doing it alone.
It's not up to us.
We don't decide any of this.
Yes. It seems that he's been
doing quite a bit
without involving me.
Remember, Scythe Master
isn't a fool, no.
He's just trying to keep
his research secret.
Right.
Then humor his ambitious little
bones under your management.
I'm sure you can
make it work for you.
You can take the car
that we have hidden
on Fifth Avenue.
Okay.
I don't care if it's money
or drugs or whatever.
Just let him have his way.
But once he goes beyond
those things...
Once he crosses the line,
I will step in
and fulfill my duty.
I will bury Scythe.
Along with his little puppet.
Ein...
be careful.
You be careful, too.
[Music]
If I come to know my past...
If I come to know
about myself,
I'm not sure I can
continue to be myself.