[Music]
I kill.
In order to live,
You okay?
Let's go.
It's begun, Mr. Shiga.
It's playing out
exactly as I've dreamed.
I wouldn't start gloating
just yet.
This scenario you've created
seems very open-ended.
It could prove to be
disastrous.
Not in your favor.
No matter.
I always intended for chance
to play a major role.
Now!
It's time to sing and dance.
My dear players,
let us take our places...
our fated roles
in this bacchanal of blood
and madness and death!
So who are they?
More victims of
Scythe Master's experiments,
poor mindless killers.
Just like we were.
There's at least
two more of them,
I'm sure of it.
Bad odds for us.
That may not be the case.
I have a feeling
that Inferno isn't intending
to send any more after them.
Why not?
In his mind,
Scythe would see it
as having too many players
on stage.
So this is his big finale?
It is...
and our last battle as well.
It seems our veterans are
putting on quite the show, eh?
Neun and Funf
have taken their bows.
This is a beautiful scenario.
Yes.
A fitting twist
for my grand finale.
Keep moving.
I'll distract them.
While I'm doing that,
you go and track down Scythe.
If he's the one
giving the orders,
we have to take him out.
You were with him
for a long time,
you know how he thinks.
Be careful.
Yeah, you too.
Two on one.
Well, well.
You're here.
Welcome.
Finally!
You've come to take the stage.
No, Scythe, I didn't come
to perform in your play.
If there are only two here,
the rest...
are with Eren.
What now?
I know you don't plan
on surrendering.
You're right.
I plan on killing you
with my own hands, Master.
Kill me?
Is that so?
How fascinating.
That is not a part
of the narrative, my dear,
so I'm sorry to say,
the odds are not in your favor.
What's also not in your story,
is the kind of ending scene
where I am just simply
shot to death.
Surely you came up
with something
better than that, right?
I must say I'm pleased
by your appreciation
for a more satisfying
conclusion.
The reason I came here.
My entire motivation
for coming back
to this island nation,
was to see
my beloved daughter's
first and possibly
final performance.
These girls...
these lovely girls...
are Sechs and Sieben.
They are the little sisters
whom you never knew.
Ein.
Girls, meet Ein,
the prototype in whose image
you were created.
You should play with her
for a while,
and once you've exhausted her,
you are free
to cut her to ribbons.
What's wrong?
You don't seem
your old self, Ein.
They are holding back,
but still seem to have
the advantage over you.
Disappointing.
Their reactions,
their movements, their thoughts.
They are programmed
to behave exactly like me.
So, that means,
since the time you created me...
you're stuck.
You haven't grown.
I'm sorry
to use you like that.
It's all I could do.
Thank you.
Unbelievable!
This is quite unexpected,
indeed.
I had no idea that you still
could wield that kind of power.
I told you.
Didn't I?
I came here to kill you.
That is simply not possible.
Why?
Because
I'm going to surrender.
But why?
Because it means
that I no longer pose
an imminent threat
to your survival.
Yes, Ein,
you can't kill me
now that I'm unarmed.
Can you?
This illustrates the difference
between you and Zwei.
Whereas he possesses
a strong free will,
you can only act
out of mindless obedience
or self preservation.
Anything else would weigh
too heavy on your heart.
Your acts of cold-blooded murder
reverberating
through your fragile mind,
the guilt would be too much.
Your complete
lack of willpower
means your mind
is exceptionally weak,
much weaker
than your average person.
You have no original
thoughts,
no ego,
no discernable personality
of your own.
You have nothing.
That's why you need me.
This has been
a very delightful evening.
Eren.
You're a fool,
an old delusional fool.
You think you can see
into someone's mind?
You really believe
that's true?
As clear as day.
I will kill you
of my own will.
Because, I despise you.
Because, I will never forgive
what you've done,
how much you've hurt him.
But what will you
gain from this?
It won't bring you peace...
or your lost memory.
You'll continue
an endless pursuit
of something
you can't catch.
It may not change that fact,
but at least you won't be
in this world anymore,
you'll be dead.
Wonderful!
How wonderful!
My Ein!
Don't call me Ein.
My name is Eren.
I was given that name.
It's who I am.
Eren.
Mischief caused by the Muses.
I'm sure I'll see you
again in hell.
But now...
I'll stay.
I'll stay here with him.
Come on, Eren.
Let's go.
I see.
Scythe Master
and his familiar both.
How would you
like to handle it, sir?
New blood can restore
the ardor of an infirm body,
if only temporarily.
Flowers are certain to wilt.
The unborn will end
their lives as ghosts.
Time and tide
wait for no man,
but still, we press on.
What the heck is everybody
starin' at over here?
I heard it was some kinda
big shootout or something.
Ooh! Freaky.
See you later,
I promise.
Helmut Von Giuseppe,
supposedly
he came from Berlin.
Earned a PHD in both
psychology and neuroscience
at the University there,
and went on to work
in interrogations
and mind control.
He applied this knowledge
in the underworld,
and made a name for himself
as a kind of assassin broker.
It was then he took on
the name - Scythe Master.
Finding out more about him
was the key to discovering
Eren's past,
where she came from.
When Scythe discovered her
five years ago,
that's when
her life as Ein began.
They met in Asia -
in Hong Kong.
And you're positive,
the man in this picture
was here?
Yes, sir.
It was five years ago.
That man said that he was
interested in becoming
a foster parent
for the girl from Ulan Bator.
Really?
Mongolia?
She was such a beautiful child.
I'd say she's probably
about your age now
or maybe
just a little younger.
It's kind of strange,
but she looked a lot like
the young lady
you're with today.
Now, we've come
all the way to Ulan Bator,
but we still can't find out
anything about her past.
Stand on the wide plateau
and gaze at the sky...
and surely the answer
will come to you.
You can never forget...
that sky.
We're here.
Yes.
If you're truly
a child of Mongolia,
it would be impossible
to forget that sky.
It's part of your being...
your heart and soul.
Just look up
and you'll know.
We can stop searching,
this is it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
We don't have to go
any farther.
This is the sky
I always dreamed about,
it's part of my memory.
I know this is it.
I lived a life,
leaving nothing behind
but shattered dreams
and broken promises.
There was one promise
I could never break.
I found what I needed.
I have this feeling,
and the name I was given.
I promised...
to make you smile.
I have memories now.
The time I've spent with you.
You'll be truly happy.
I know you will.
[Music]
These things...
these are my own.
I can take them and live.
They're all I need.