I thought I made myself
clear to you, Sam.
I don't want any drugs
in Melanie Square.
Wait, please.
I didn't have a choice.
You gotta believe me, Tony.
Ben told me
that I had to sell them here,
no matter what.
I don't remember asking you
why you did it.
This here is my turf,
the Stone Family's turf.
And I'm not known
for showing compassion.
Everyone follows my rules.
I don't care
who they are, got it?
Okay, Tony, that's enough.
If it ain't old man Gant.
I can take over from here.
Thanks for the help though.
He's all yours.
Tony the Stone,
you're as stubborn as ever.
I don't know of any other
Mafia family around
who doesn't allow hard drugs,
at least not in LA.
All I want is for Melanie Square
to be a decent place to play.
We have plenty of ways
to make money
that won't force us
to "bend our principles."
What the hell do you know
about principles?
After all,
you don't even live
by the sweat
of your own brow, do ya?
It's called
chain of command, pal.
And that's why
he's Tony the Stone.
Daddy!
Hey, champ.
When'd you get here?
He couldn't wait another
second before seeing Daddy.
Darling.
We were out seeing a movie
in the Square,
so we thought we'd say hi.
Daddy, you didn't forget,
did you?
In two days, we're gonna go
to an amusement park!
Now, how could I have
forgotten that?
It's gonna be so much fun,
I can hardly think
about anything else.
Tony, got a sec?
The bastard's persistent.
I want this thing settled.
If he tries to say no again,
you may teach him a lesson.
Right.
Ms. McCunnen,
it's Richard Harrington.
I was hoping we could get
this matter solved this evening.
We're offering you
the best deal we can.
I know, and it's not
a bad deal.
However,
I think I'll pass on it.
Why's that?
My reason's the same.
Melanie Square
belongs to my family.
And everyone in the Square,
whether they live here
or work here,
is like a member
of that family.
I don't care
what the hell you offer,
I will not betray them.
All right,
you have your answer,
so why don't you
get out of here
and go report back
to your boss?
Otherwise,
I'm sure we can just
deliver the message to him
with your body.
Apparently, this family
has yet to fully comprehend
the true power of Inferno.
The hell?
We'll give you three more days.
This is your last chance,
Tony Stone.
I trust
you'll change your mind.
We'll be in touch soon.
Man, that guy's a real prick.
So what do you think?
It might've been a bluff.
but either way we're gonna
need to check it out.
Lutz, Rob...
I want you to find out
exactly who's behind Inferno.
Because, my gut's telling me
they've been around for awhile.
Yes, sir.
[Music]
Are you ready, Zwei?
Anytime.
Just because
you blocked me once,
doesn't mean
the fight will end.
Yeah.
Very nicely done!
When you got here,
you were barely able to survive.
But now you're
quite skilled at combat.
I've got a good teacher.
I have two important missions
I'd like for you
to handle, Zwei.
Will you accept them?
What are they?
Come with me to my place...
I'll explain there.
Yes, ma'am.
So, this house belongs to you,
Ms. McCunnen?
That's right.
Although it can feel
a little big
for a single person
with no family.
Lizzie's got her hands full
working on a different case
tonight.
So um, what were those
missions you were talking about?
About the missions.
First of all, I want you
to be my guard this evening.
I'd like for you
to keep me company.
Just for tonight.
I told you Lizzie's out.
And although the security here
is flawless,
I would still prefer someone
to stay and keep an eye on me.
But ma'am,
you're a senior member.
Why do you only have
one bodyguard?
Do I need anyone else?
All right.
For your second mission,
I want you to monitor
a mother and child.
Sure, if that's your order.
So obedient.
You're not a doll, you know.
You can ask why
you have to monitor them.
You can ask
what is so important.
That is allowed. Okay?
What do you mean, you
couldn't find any information?
We couldn't.
We went around and hit up
every reliable source in town
that we could think of,
but all of them told us
somethin' completely different.
One of 'em would say
that the Verrocchio Family's
involved,
and then we'd talk
to someone else
and they'd turn around
and say Cervantes.
Of course the Bloodies' name
came up a couple 'a times.
but we ended up with nothin'.
What the hell is your problem?
Now, I want an answer
and it better not be
"we got nuthin'".
I'm sorry, sir.
Let him go, Anton.
They did what I asked them
to do.
What do you mean?
The way they
extended their power
in such a short time.
Their various techniques.
Senior members who never show.
Add on the information
they just got.
And there we
have our answer about Inferno.
They're some kinda organization
that seems to have deep roots
in all the West Coast
Mafia families.
Think so?
Where else do you think that
schmuck's confidence comes from?
They've got us
over a barrel on this
and the only way we can survive
is by giving in to them.
The little bastard
knew it too.
Boss, if that happens,
what about Melanie Square?
It's not gonna happen.
No matter who we're facing,
I won't betray
the people of the Square.
Anton, set up a meeting
with Inferno immediately.
But tell them this.
I will meet with them
under one condition.
They have to bring
their boss this time.
Tony, don't tell me...
I can play ball with them,
at least I'll try.
My guess is the real boss
won't show.
That's not how
their organization is set up.
But, believe me,
I'm willing to bet
I'll still be able
to pick a fight.
If you do that,
there's no way
they won't retaliate against us!
Anton's right.
It's not just the Square,
your family will be in danger.
I'm well aware
of that possibility.
We'll keep them guarded.
We're
more than Inferno bargained for.
They've no idea.
Then, depending on
how they react,
the mother and child?
Yes, and if so...
can you?
Tell me.
I don't want you
to just take orders.
Tell me your answer, Zwei.
[Music]
C'mon already!
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Sure.
Looks like you're
getting used to it.
If you wanna blend in
with a flock of sheep,
you've gotta wear
their clothing.
What did the fifth person
we passed look like?
A Caucasian male
in his mid 20s.
He was wearing a
Dodgers' cap and a black shirt.
Based on his cell phone
conversation,
he got separated from his
friend and is trying to find out
where they're supposed
to meet up.
Correct. Yes.
Even when wearing sheepskin,
a wolf should not forget
his sense of smell.
That's also something
you taught me.
Hey now, hold on.
Can I have a balloon, please?
Sure, why not.
Now be a good boy, Duke, bye.
Bye, Daddy!
Thanks, Tony.
Bye. Love you.
I just heard from Anton.
He said everything is ready
when you are.
Let's go.
Well, looky here.
Where are you fine gentlemen
headed dressed up like that?
Old Man Gant,
it's not really
any of your business, is it?
Listen, just don't do anything
that will hurt good people,
you got that?
'Cause if you do...
Yeah, I know.
Abel and Bark are headin' up
the security detail
at your place tonight,
watchin' over the missus
and the kid.
So don't worry,
that place is practically
a damn fortress.
And Inferno?
They're gonna be here real soon.
You feel confident
in handling this matter?
Yes.
We have to think
about our future.
So I'll be happy
to serve as a liaison.
Again, I thank you.
Although,
as head of this district,
my feelings are mixed.
We'd like to make
Melanie Square ours
without turning it
into a battlefield.
So I'm counting on
your persuasive skills.
Oh, I wouldn't worry.
Don't forget
we're holding two trump cards.
Even Tony the Stone
wouldn't call our bluff.
[Music]
Uh, Ma'am,
I just now
got off the phone with Rob.
He said they've already
started the meeting.
I see.
Now things have been
pretty quiet outside,
and we've got the place covered.
So, there's no need
for you to worry.
As
long as nothing happens tonight,
the game should be ours.
I hope so.
To be perfectly honest,
I never expected
a senior member of Inferno
to be so lovely.
Most people make that mistake.
Yeah, I'm sure they do,
but we didn't ask to speak
with a hot piece of tail,
we wanted your boss.
Well, I certainly won't pretend
that I'm the number one, but,
I've been given full authority
with regard to this transaction.
And so, his attitude
is less than respectful.
Back off Melanie Square,
it's mine.
Do you honestly believe
we'll just leave it at that?
We'll pay the debt later on.
You realize that even the Mafia
has its code of ethics.
You don't have to
pay us the debt.
All we want,
is for you
to give us the Square.
These people here may live
on society's underbelly.
They may be part of the seedy
side of life.
But Melanie Square is their home
and their livelihood,
and they are very loyal to me.
So, you understand
that I will be loyal to them.
I view them as family.
And I will not betray them.
That would go against
everything I stand for.
Right, you're Tony the Stone.
Your tough reputation
proceeds you.
I wonder
if you'd be so stubborn
if your real family
was in danger.
What's the story there, Stone?
If you did what I assume
you're threatening,
you'd lose everything.
Is that what you really want?
I told you what we wanted.
Now, are you gonna play ball
and hand control
of Melanie Square
over to Inferno or not?
No.
Thanks, Phantom.
You're late.
What the hell?
Sniper!
Shoot him!
Kill the bastard!
We can't! He's too far away!
Zwei, it's your turn.
What? What about Tony?
He okay?
Rob and Lutz are dead.
The negotiations
didn't go well,
but your husband's fine.
Oh, God.
Ma'am, I think
it would be best
if you went and stayed
with Duke, okay?
Yeah.
My God! They're insane.
This is war.
Mommy!
Duke, why aren't you asleep yet?
The man
from the amusement park is here.
Eva! Eva!
[Music]
Wonderful.
You are wonderful.
[Music]
Be an instrument.
Be a tool.
The only thing
we need to do
is function.