[Music]
Hey!
Wake up, sleepyhead,
school's over, you know.
Sorry, but I don't
think I deserve
to get punched in the head
for taking a nap.
Whaddaya want?
A favor.
You need to come with me.
You know, that sounds
a lot like an order to me.
Because it is one.
And it's all gonna
work out in your favor
if you shut up
and do as I say.
Come on, what's with
the skepticism, Reiji?
What's with all the secrecy?
You'll understand everything
when you come
up to the roof with me.
[Music]
You gonna tell me
why you're draggin' me
all the way up here?
Well, what's this about?
You'll see.
I know you, don't I?
Aren't you from the class
next door?
Well, thanks a lot, Sanae,
do you mind if we...
Yeah! Go on, girl,
I can't hear a thing!
Well, have fun!
So, you're friends
with my sister, aren't you?
Your name's Fujiwara,
isn't it?
No, it's Fujieda,
actually it's Mio Fujieda.
And I guess you're friends
with Sanae, too.
Oh yes, we were...
I was in the same class
as her our first year.
Cool, so...
is there something
that you wanted?
Um, well, I want to
ask you a question.
Lemme guess, you wanna know
something about Eren.
No, but you're close,
um, it's more about...
Actually, it's about you.
I wanna know, do you...
Is there someone you like?
But, you probably
don't wanna go out with me.
No, I mean, uh...
yeah, I guess if uh--
Mio?
Eren!
Brother, what's going on?
Why're you on the roof?
I thought I heard you
talking to someone up here.
How do you know each other?
We, uh...
Well, what're you
doing up here?
I was looking for Mio.
I got a wicked craving
for Kanekoya's Waffles.
Thought maybe
she'd like tag along.
So, do you wanna go?
I can't, I have
a lot of errands to run.
See ya.
Later.
Did I interrupt?
Oh, yeah.
What'd she tell you?
That she likes me.
What?
Fujiwara likes me.
Fujieda,
but I'm messin' with ya.
Seriously,
she said she likes you?
She did, kinda.
She does have
pretty weird tastes.
Whattaya mean by that?
Nothing.
So what did you say to her?
You busted in before
I had a chance to say anything.
Well, go get her!
What?
That girl just put her heart
on the line
and got nothin' back from you.
I mean, sure, I know I'm the one
who interrupted you two,
but it's cruel to just
leave her hangin' like that!
'Kay, fine.
What the heck do you
want me to say to her?
Whatever you want to, dummy!
Great advice.
Just go!
And after all the trouble
I went through
to arrange this thing?
Could you be any more clueless
when it comes to guys?
Sorry.
Why couldn't you have done it
the way that I told you to?
You just say,
"Reiji, I like you,
you're my boyfriend now."
Then you gotta get him
to nod his head
even if it means
you have to choke him.
It'll take like five seconds.
Trust me, shock and awe
is the only way to go.
Why are you dragging
your heels on this?
I don't know, it's hard.
I'm just so nervous.
Come on and grow a pair!
This is the last spring
of your high school existence!
Don't let it pass you by.
Sanae?
Good timing!
I thought I was gonna
have to hunt you down
so we could start over again.
I'll spare you the trouble,
I was hoping
I could talk to Mio alone.
So why don't you get outta here?
Oh, sure, I see how it is.
Well, Romeo, I'll let
you two little lovebirds
have some quality time alone.
Good luck!
Where are you going, Sanae?
Same place as you.
Come on.
Fujieda, uh...
Yeah?
About what you were
asking me earlier,
I never got to answer.
Listen, I...
Do you mind?
Like I was saying...
Right.
So...
Yeah?
What did you end up
telling Mio?
That I just wanted to be
friends right now.
Typical teenage male response.
I totally expected
that from you.
It's not your problem.
Well, have you and your "friend"
made any kinda plans?
Yeah, we did.
We're going into town
tomorrow.
Hold on a sec.
What now?
Mio's a good friend of mine,
you know.
You better treat her nicely
when you're out.
You do something stupid,
you're gonna have to
deal with me.
Bang!
You're being kinda creepy.
I'm being serious,
she's a really nice girl.
Yeah.
I got a good feeling
from her when we talked.
Good.
Now fork over
my emergency allowance.
I believe I already gave you
this month's allowance.
What?
Oh, that's exciting news!
He might not be
your boyfriend yet,
but he's promising
to take you out.
That's a pretty big deal
for a late bloomer like you.
Yeah, totally!
What're you ladies
gabbing about?
Oh. Just a little good news,
Ms. Fujieda.
Nice to see you again.
Likewise.
You won't believe what
happened to your daughter,
It's the neatest thing ever!
What is it?
How should I put this.
Mio...
Shut up, Sanae!
I know, it's a date!
How'd you figure that out?
You remember the food?
Yep, well...
See you later.
Just one more thing.
Now you look presentable.
"Presentable"?
Repeat everything
I told you last night,
and you'll be fine.
I like you, Mio!
I love you, Mio.
Money means nothing to me.
You sound like such a stud.
[Music]
Thanks, Reiji.
The picnic was really nice.
Yeah, it's such a nice day,
it seemed like the thing to do.
So, do you and Eren
really live by yourselves?
Our parents died
in a car accident, so...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please, don't apologize.
It happened
when we were really young.
I've gotten over it now.
You're strong, Reiji.
And I know what it takes.
I live alone with my mom,
but you know,
seeing her tied up
with work constantly,
starts to wear on me
after a while.
Makes me wish that my father
could still be around,
help take some of the burden
off her.
Just be sure
you can give your mom
all the support you can,
And when you need
a guy's help,
just pick up the phone
and call me.
That's sweet,
I appreciate it.
What's next on the game plan?
What are you looking at?
That's Sanae's handwriting.
"The place
you don't talk about."
Uh, Reiji,
so, what exactly is
"the place you don't
talk about?"
Just think of me
as the fairy godmother
to your Cinderella.
I'm a dude.
Follow the list
exactly as it's written
and the date'll be perfect.
Even you couldn't
screw it up, Reiji.
She is so dead.
Check out the lady
on that bike.
It's kinda funny,
it's so big compared to her.
I guess 'cause I grew up poor,
I've always had a thing
for expensive bikes.
That's weird.
How'd that happen?
Is something wrong?
The sound of
a .9 millimeter Parabellum
fired through a silencer.
That's the sound
that woke me up from this dream.
We traveled
from Mexico to Peru,
and then to the Philippines
through Palau.
It's been six months
since we came to Japan.
We were trying to make
this town our home.
Leave our past behind.
This is the country
that you're from.
And ever since we came here,
you've been different.
You've changed so much.
It's like your heart opened.
For someone who has
a place to call home,
that must be
a normal thing.
I thought that's what
it'd be like if I had one,
a real home.
But it's over now,
someone's found us.
It's Inferno.
Probably.
It was a silent warning.
I see, it's finally time
to wake up.
I was afraid of this.
I had hoped that you could
stay in this dream
for the rest of your life,
letting the past drift away.
And you?
Penance, I have to be
forgiven for my sins.
Seriously? Who are you
asking for forgiveness?
God, I know
I'll see him someday.
Eren...
I didn't expect them this soon,
but Inferno's here.
And now everything has changed.
I was hoping to
not have to take advantage
of Mio's feelings.
What the heck
are you talking about?
What are you planning, Eren?
Tell me!
Mio's parents, they separated
right after she was born.
Yeah, she mentioned
something about that to me.
Her father vanished
and he's still M.I.A.
That's what Mio was fed
growing up,
and that's the lie
she still believes.
The lie?
Her father's still around
and has quite a reputation.
You've probably heard of him.
Who is he?
The head of a very large
and powerful crime syndicate,
Kaiten Godo.
You gotta be kidding!
No, "Fujieda"
is her mother's maiden name.
Insane, she's a Godo!
Does she even
have a clue about it?
Not at all.
Even to those inside
the Godo Family,
only a handful
have been told.
It's a very well-kept secret.
Kaiten wanted to keep them safe
from the power struggles
that tend to shake
the family tree,
so they took on a new identity.
Then Mio's actually
related to Daisuke Godo?
Yes, she's his half sister.
Kaiten Godo is in a difficult
situation with Mio.
Although he wants to keep her
away from the violence
of the family business,
he can't openly protect her.
So that means
she's his biggest weakness.
So how did you find out
about all this?
Scythe Master
told me the whole story.
You mean, Scythe knows too?
He learned all of this
quite a long time ago.
After Master was forced
to turn his back on Inferno,
he came to Japan and
went into hiding for a while,
I told you about
this before, right?
Yeah.
It was then that Master
made a thorough investigation
of the Godo Family.
He wanted to be able to take
advantage of their weaknesses
if he found his back
against a wall.
Weaknesses?
Hold on, Eren!
You're telling me that you're
gonna use Mio like a pawn?
She could be a powerful
trump card if we need one.
The senior member who's got
the most pull in the family
is Toru Shiga,
he's in Inferno.
So he can call off their dogs.
So now you know
the whole situation.
It doesn't matter if
the person on the motorcycle
was from Inferno.
We've got Mio,
so our deck is stacked.
Eren, why didn't you tell me?
I dunno.
I probably should've
told you earlier.
I guess I just didn't think
that the two of you
would start dating.
Maybe I was being naive,
but I hoped that we'd finally
gotten away.
I wanted this life
to last longer,
I had lots of plans.
I know you did, Reiji,
but we have to run now.
You're right,
we have to run.
we're out of options.
It's okay to grieve,
you're leaving something behind.
It's human nature.
But now you have to go back
to who you were
before we came here.
I can't do that,
I gotta face facts.
They're after us, I know
I have to be ready for that.
But I can't go back
to the way I was.
That's good. You were able
to forget what that was like.
You changed, you were happy.
I was proud of you,
you'd overcome so much.
Eren...
These last six months,
your smile,
even the way you looked
when you slept,
you finally looked
like a happy person.
Seeing that was so good.
It made me very happy.
If being home can do this,
then maybe
it's not so much a dream.
That's how I thought of it
for a long time,
but now it could be
real for me.
Maybe I could find my home.
Remember, it wasn't long ago
that you promised me.
You said you'd help me
find my real home.
I don't want your happiness
here to be a waste.
There's no reason
that it has to be.
This isn't forever,
we can come back.
Everything
will still be here.
I know the day will come.
I know we'll make it
back here someday.
We'll find ourselves
back in normal life.
I'm sorry, Reiji,
but that time just isn't now.
What?
Reiji bailed and left you
in the middle of your date?
What a jerk!
Look, it wasn't a date.
We were just hanging out.
Anyway, he said it was
some kind of urgent thingy.
I couldn't really stop him.
There is nothing
in this world more urgent
to a high school girl than love,
why can't he understand that?
Geez, you're being
pretty dramatic.
Yeah, I worked my butt off
to schedule out
that whole date of yours.
Why doesn't she mind
her own business?
'Cause she doesn't have much.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Speak of the devil.
He thinks he can just
leave you hangin', huh?
Take this!
Hey!
Ow! Let go of me!
Uh-huh, sorry about that.
Calm down, Sanae.
Geez! Hey, Reiji.
I had a really nice time
yesterday.
Cool, sorry I bailed.
Did you get your thing
taken care of?
Yeah, it's all good.
You may have gotten
the upper hand this time,
but don't let your guard down,
I'll be watching you.
Right.
Look, I gotta go see Eren,
so I gotta run.
Later.
Hey, lover boy, you're leaving
your girlfriend behind.
Oh, am I getting
on your nerves?
Something's different
about him.
I don't really know exactly how,
but he's different.
[Music]
Why is she here?
Of all places in the world,
what the hell is she doing here?
No, the real question is:
Is that really her?
I can't believe
she's still alive!
Cal!
We are Ghosts,
that have no place to haunt.
Non-existent phantoms.
[Music]
How's it going, Ein?
Or, should I call you
ex-Phantom?