[Music]
You're finally awake.
Let me out.
Why should I?
Master, I have to find him.
Scythe betrayed Inferno
and ran like a coward.
And he also left you behind,
remember?
I know what happened.
I will try to find
Master regardless,
and if I cannot go with him,
I will still help him escape.
I can stir things up.
I can dispose of whoever
is following him.
Stop the car.
No way.
If you wanna continue
your mission,
you'd be better off
staying with me.
Although you may not be
with Scythe right now,
you're still protecting him.
Phantom's powerful reputation
and the way he controls it
is always
hanging over him, guarding him.
I guarantee the organization
will be very careful.
So if you were
to get picked up now,
he would lose
that kind of protection.
You're a different
person now, you've changed.
Have I?
You have.
Everything about you
has changed.
Because, you are no longer
just a number.
You're Reiji Azuma.
So you were listening.
You have a home
to go back to now,
you have your own identity.
Not me, I have no home,
and no name.
All I have is the number
Master gave me, Ein.
And the only place I can go
is back to my Master's side.
That's not true.
Nothing belongs to me.
I belong to Master.
I am his possession.
Ein!
I am not a person,
I am a shadow,
just Phantom.
You're more than that.
Thanks a lot, sir.
My pleasure.
That should help a little.
Did you know I'd still
be here when you came back?
You may be reckless,
but not stupid.
They've recovered
the hijacked truck.
Empty as a scoundrel's promise.
Bastard took our product
and got the hell away clean.
Your dog done pissed
on the wrong leg,
time to take him
to the woodshed.
I'll see that it's done.
[Music]
You know this song?
Oh, sorry, is it too loud?
You know what it's called?
Uh, I can't remember the name.
But I heard it a lot
back home.
It was pretty popular
for awhile.
It was popular?
So everyone there
likes songs like this?
Japan's just the same
as anywhere else in the world.
Everybody has
different tastes in music.
Tell me something else
about Japan.
You got your memories back,
right?
So you remember things
about your life
back home in Japan,
don't you?
Yeah, I do.
[Music]
Hey, it's me.
We got your present.
I hope it's to your liking.
Are you kidding me?
Everything's perfect.
I couldn't ask for more.
I must say
it's been a real pleasure
doing business with you,
Ms. McCunnen.
I'll contact you
as soon as we've settled in.
I look forward
to hearing from you.
Bye.
I wouldn't put much stock
in that woman.
For the sake of the Family,
we should view her as a fox
in well-tailored clothes.
I'm well aware of that.
She's in a unique position
to extend our
influence overseas, that's all.
It's risky still.
Come on, don't get cold feet
on me now, Shiga.
It's all good.
I'll come out ahead,
always do.
Please, leave me behind, Reiji.
You should go back home.
Go home?
That's right.
How the hell
can I go back home now?
You know all the horrible
things I've done
these past six months,
don't you?
I can never go back
to a normal life.
You can, you have a past
and a real name,
you're Reiji Azuma,
and you really exist
in this world.
You really exist too.
You can find out who you are.
It's not the same.
You have something
that I will never have,
you have something
that will prove who you are.
Is this thing here what makes
you and I so damn different?
It is.
That passport gives you
proof of your identity.
I don't have that proof.
Why are you doing that?
But why?
Do you have any idea
what you've thrown away?
That proves who you are!
That was just paper.
And that does not contain
all that I am.
I have memories.
So do you,
somewhere inside you.
You told me before
about your dreams,
those are memories,
memories of somewhere.
A place full of sunlight
and strong winds.
Maybe they're memories of home.
Those are just illusions.
There's no reason to think
they're memories from home.
They didn't just come
from nowhere.
The fact is,
you have a real past.
And you have
your own real name.
Not just some number like Ein.
Reiji...
You shouldn't concern yourself
with me.
You have nothing
to gain from it.
I don't wanna gain from it.
I just don't wanna
see you die.
I have to try and help you.
It's part of what makes me
who I am.
This is my true identity.
I have to stay faithful to it.
It's a lot more real to me
than some damn piece of paper.
It is me.
License, please.
Where ya comin' from?
From L.A.
Driving out to see
an old friend.
Mr. Wallace Yang, age 20.
You sure don't look 20.
Tell me about it.
Who's she?
That's my kid sister.
Is she alright?
Cars make her a little
queasy, but she'll be okay.
Alright.
You're free to go.
You've gotten much better.
You mean my acting?
Well, I had a good coach.
You taught me
everything I know.
So what are you planning
to do next?
We need to keep moving,
stopping to let you rest
along the way.
And when you're all healed up,
we'll go somewhere far away.
Far away?
Like where?
As far as we can.
Impossible.
We have to.
I've already made up my mind
about it.
I'm gonna go grab us
something to eat.
Hey! Open up!
Yesterday was the first time
I really felt afraid.
I'm scared.
But I can't pull the trigger.
Reiji, please help me.
End this nightmare.
I can never do that, Ein.
I can't give up on you.
You've changed.
You've always been
so much stronger
than I ever was.
No, that's not true.
I was just living for Master.
It was all for him.
Even if it went
against Inferno,
I followed Master's orders.
But now, I have no purpose.
I have no reason to live.
Inferno is chasing me,
but I just run.
I'm not even strong enough
to pull the trigger.
It's like,
if I'd died yesterday,
at least
I would have died as Ein,
not as nobody at all.
Stop it.
Please don't say that.
Did we live this long
just to give up now?
Listen, we did what we did
in order to live.
I don't want you to give up,
after we've made it this far.
I want you to live.
It's really just that simple.
I know Inferno is after me.
When they finally
catch up to us...
will you take a stand
against them,
or will you
point your gun at me?
No way.
I'm on your side.
And I'll kill
whoever they send here
of my own free will.
I don't understand.
I don't have the same
kind of will to survive
that you do, Reiji.
I can't live like that.
I guess I just
don't have it in me.
You just gotta keep living.
I don't.
I have nothing to offer.
I'm nobody.
I have no reason to live,
no function.
Ein, I...
No, not Ein anymore.
Ein is just a goddamn number.
It's not a name.
We need to give you
a real name.
Real name?
Not some number, not Phantom.
Your name...
A new name for your life
ahead of you.
Eren.
It's Eren.
That's your name.
You're Eren from now on.
But why, why is it Eren?
It doesn't matter,
it's just what it is now.
It's a name that you'll start
your new life with.
A life where you're
not a killer or a puppet.
Eren...
Eren.
It feels so strange.
That'll change.
Eren, come on.
Let's find your past together.
Eren.
Take that name as your own,
and find your reason
to live again.
You're strong.
You'll do whatever you can
to keep going .
It may still be tough
right now,
but
I know we can do it, together.
This little boy toy of yours,
what'cha gonna do
if he hooks back up
with that creep
in the white coat?
Spank him?
Kill him.
I'm gonna go get us
some money and a different car.
I should be back in an hour.
You okay?
I'll be fine
as long as I don't push myself.
Stay safe, Eren.
I will, Reiji.
Eren, the new name
that Reiji gave me.
And with this name,
I'll start over.
You
don't seem yourself today, Ein.
Come on, overcome the pain
with your inner strength.
You came for me.
This is it, lover boy.
Your little teenage honeymoon
is over now.
Lizzie...
So you were taken in
by Scythe's toy.
This has nothing to do with him.
Bullshit!
We'll talk about all that
at a later time.
I just got
some interesting news.
The gentleman I had
trailing Phantom
was just found murdered.
And your little girlfriend
went back to her daddy.
No. You're lying.
Eren.
Just make it easy
on yourself, kid.
Tell me where they went!
I don't know.
We were just...
Alright,
I guess he's just as ignorant
as we thought he was.
You can go ahead
and leave now.
I'll handle it from here.
You're definitely
a stubborn son of a bitch,
I'll give you that.
There's no one
listening to us.
You can tell me
whatever you want to now.
Taking Ein and trying
to run away together,
was that entirely
your own decision?
You're such an idiot.
Don't you realize
you were helping a traitor?
That doesn't
look good for you.
Not getting back to Japan
should be the very least
of your worries.
But still...
there is one way you could
get out of this predicament
if you really wanted to.
You could prove your innocence,
and maybe get Ein back.
How?
Tell me.
[Music]
You still remember
how to use this, don't you?
Of course I do,
and I will kill him with it.
[Music]
Eren, I promise someday...
Someday I'll make you smile...
A real smile.