[Music]
No, it can't be.
Eren is dead.
I killed her.
For the longest time,
I tried to hang on,
I tried to convince myself
that she was still alive.
That was my only hope
to gain her forgiveness.
But I can't
believe that anymore.
She's gone.
This is really starting
to wear on my patience.
I lost four goddamn men
on your coke deal,
and another one today.
This last one
hits too close to home.
Muroto's been
a good friend of mine
since we were kids
coming up in the family.
I want you to tell me
what's going on,
and if I don't like
what I hear, Shiga,
feel free
to kill them both.
Yes, sir.
Lizzie...
Mr. Godo, I'll ask you
to be rational.
Shooting each other here,
it would certainly thrill
Muroto's killer.
But would do nothing
to bring your friend back,
or help you get a seat
at Inferno's table.
I was under the impression
that you ordered the killing.
If you want to be
suspicious of me,
that's your prerogative.
However, if you choose to
fire your weapon,
you should be prepared
for the fallout.
C'mon, Claudia, I know
you're better than that.
I'm sure you have a plan
that'll save us the trouble
of blowing
each other's brains out.
Yes, of course I do,
and I'd like you to stand by
while I put it into action.
In three days,
I'll have the ringleader
smoked out.
Then you can do
what you will with them.
This'll be interesting.
Let's see how Inferno takes
responsibility for this mess.
You wanna try
a counter snipe?
That's right.
I don't know.
Day after tomorrow,
the Godos will be invited
to a meeting
of Inferno's senior members.
Once there,
they will be officially approved
to join the organization.
Once that happens,
even Wisemel with
all of his underhanded dealings,
can't touch them.
So this will be
his last opportunity.
I suspect he'll take it.
Isaac...
You're still suspicious
of that guy?
All of those shootings
that happened the other day,
and Muroto's murder.
Wisemel's the only one
who would stand to benefit.
So we need to watch him
carefully.
The meeting will be held
in a conference room
with a large window
on the fifth floor
of the Atrium Hotel.
So we're putting
the prey on display.
It shouldn't be difficult
to find a spot
with a clear view
of the meeting.
You really think it's smart
to keep using
the Godo family as bait?
If it works, then yes.
However, I haven't
forgotten what a gamble it is
without my one and only...
my Phantom.
Oh, good!
He's home!
I hope you had a good day.
Like any other.
Wait just a sec,
I'll run into the kitchen
and reheat you some soup.
Hey, Cal!
I found this when I was
cleaning up the place.
Did you disassemble it?
Yeah.
Sorry.
I'll fix it.
So tell me...
you good with machines
and stuff?
I've always kinda liked
taking stuff apart
and putting it back together.
I guess I just want to know
how everything works
or somethin'.
Okay.
It's ready.
Good.
Now put it back
where you found it.
Got it.
Is that work?
It is.
Do you wanna sit down
and help me figure out
what I should do?
Oh yeah, totally!
What is it?
Look here.
The target'll be on the fifth
floor of this building.
So I gotta assume
the sniper will be shooting
from this side.
Are you the sniper?
No, I'm not.
Someone else.
And I don't know who yet.
Our job is to try and figure
out where this guy is gonna be.
Gotcha.
But he can't do it
from just anywhere.
He'll choose the place
that best meets
the criteria of the hit.
Whaddaya mean?
Well, the place will need to be
high enough to see the target,
but still keep the shooter
out of the line of sight.
Like maybe a roof top
or somethin'?
I don't see why not.
Well then, what about here?
I don't know,
it seems too close.
If the target can
catch a glimpse of the shooter,
then the jig's up.
The guy's gonna
have to settle down
at least 400 yards away.
Four hundred yards!
He can still hit the target
from there?
Depending on equipment
and skills,
he could get a good shot off
from up to 800 yards away.
Whoa!
So like, he could
basically be anywhere.
How are we gonna
narrow it down?
I don't know,
but there are a whole
lotta places to choose from.
It's your homework
before bedtime.
Now let's eat dinner.
You figure out the situation?
I did.
It's all good.
Don't you worry.
Don't screw this up.
You do, I'll cut off your balls
and feed 'em to my dogs.
I understand, sir.
What's the matter?
I was wondering...
Is it hard to aim
from a really high place?
Or like uncomfortable?
What makes you say that?
The way you hold the gun,
when you point it so far down,
it seems hard,
a little unnatural.
What is it?
Does that sound stupid?
Not at all.
You gotta good point.
It is pretty hard to shoot
with your body posed that way.
It seems like it to me.
So maybe we can forget about
looking for him
in really high places.
He'll probably wanna be
on the same level as the target.
Somewhere that's gonna be
easy for him to see it.
So if we think of it that way,
we cut down the number
of places he could be.
I think you're
on to something.
So I'm right?
You're doing pretty good so far.
That's awesome!
We'll do the rest of the work
when we get to the site.
Hope you don't mind
coming with me.
Omigod, really?
I'm going somewhere with you!
Don't forget,
this is still work.
Yes!
Sorry to bother you.
I thought you should know
Muroto's body
went back to Japan
earlier today.
Kakinuma and Tsuzuki
are flying in
on the redeye tonight,
and are bringing
all of their men with them.
Any word on guns?
I had Giuseppe get them.
They'll be in hand
by tomorrow afternoon.
Well, he'd better
come through for us.
Goodbye drink to Muroto?
Yeah.
You should really join me
on this one.
May he rest in peace.
Sonofabitch Muroto.
Died without
finishing the bottle.
He's not the only one.
Homura and Shinjou
got taken outta the game too.
I've gotten
five of my men killed
in this foreign shithole
since we got here.
Millions of dollars
are at stake.
It's natural
for it to turn into a war.
I'm sure that every one of them
understood that.
Yes, it's war.
That's why
I'm pissed at myself
for letting Muroto
go out without a gun.
What the hell
was I thinking?
I should've known better.
Goddammit, I know
Inferno's behind all this,
and they're gonna pay for it.
They owe us bodies.
Speaking of Inferno...
listen.
I've got some
fairly deep suspicions
of that Claudia woman.
Well, let me hear 'em.
Our involvement
in her little caper last year
puts the two of us
directly in the crosshairs.
If push comes to shove
on this matter,
I suspect she'll find a way
to take us out of the equation.
Listen, Shiga.
In this case,
I gotta tell ya,
Claudia's an innocent woman.
You have any proof to that?
Proof?
Shiga...
You know
what the tattoo on my back is.
Five colored spheres
and a rising dragon.
The dragon on my back,
he feels it.
That woman...
she carries
the same dragon on her back.
The two of us share
the same kind of spirit,
a dragon,
that gains control of heaven
by first conquering
the spheres.
So, I think I should leave
the matter in her hands for now.
It's hard to explain.
This probably
sounds crazy to you.
You've always been
the rational one.
That said,
I'm counting on your wisdom
to pull me through this.
You need to trust me.
But more importantly,
you need to trust my spirit.
If you insist that much of me,
I suppose.
But I can't help
but to keep one eye open.
Thanks for coming.
Wonder what Inferno's
gonna think about this.
Can't wait to find out.
Come on, Cal!
Yeah, I'll be right there!
Since we're going out,
I wanted to look cute.
Shall we?
Let's!
Okay,
that's the target building.
First we need to
narrow down the places
that meet the criteria
we talked about,
then we walk the streets
and identify
the most viable location.
How do we do that?
Look for a weather vane.
How come?
Part of the preparation.
Without it,
even the most skilled pros
couldn't pull off
a difficult sniping.
Look around,
there are tall buildings
everywhere.
It's windy.
That's right.
A strong wind can screw up
what should be a clear shot.
You don't wanna miss.
So you have to make sure
that you can see the wind.
Yeah, but you can't
see the wind.
So, you use that.
Yeah, like a lotta snipers
will put up something like this
that'll catch the wind
and tell us what it's doing.
Cool, we gonna walk around
and look for something
hanging like that?
Maybe in a place
where it sticks out?
That's how we roll.
Hey, Cal.
Hey!
Oh, sorry.
I didn't find anything yet.
Yeah, me, neither.
Well, on we go.
Alright,
that's it for today.
Hey, hold on.
Look!
This place seems
a little weird.
How so?
Check it out.
Good catch!
Nice one.
I got it?
You did.
Yeah, this is it alright.
Our sniper's gonna be
right there.
Okay.
So I guess you're gonna
wanna be here
to get a good shot at him.
Yeah.
Is he the one?
You think he's the one
who killed Judy?
I don't know.
Probably.
I'd at least
be willing to bet
he's
one of the people responsible.
I wanna be with you
when it happens.
Please let me see it.
I want to see you shoot
this guy in the head!
You shouldn't
want to see that, Cal,
no one should.
I saw Judy.
It happened
right in front of me.
Nobody asked me
if I wanted to see it,
but I had to watch her die.
Sometimes, a sniping mission
will be assigned to two people
that are working together.
Like a team.
Some say a sniper
needs an assistant.
The assistant will spot,
their job is to keep an eye
on the target
and the surroundings.
It helps the sniper
stay focused.
They're like an observer.
They watch,
but they don't shoot.
Can you do that?
Yes!
All right,
give me your hand.
What for?
Your payment for today.
Oh, wow!
Ohmigod, thank you!
I'll take good care of it.
I promise I will, always.
That's where he's gonna be,
the sun'll be behind us.
So he shouldn't
be able to see us.
That's the plan at least.
It's time.
Isaac and his guys
just got here.
Good.
Funny thing is,
Randy Weber's M.I.A.
Seems a little
suspicious to me.
This is a pretty big deal,
so why wouldn't he bring
his right hand man
along with him?
You think they're gonna
try to pull something?
Today's the big day.
I can't wait to see
what that woman
is gonna pull out of her ass.
How do I look, boys?
A stunning white suit
and a loaded gun.
Seems appropriate
for jumping into hell.
Let's go, Shiga.
Yes, sir.
Wherever you go, you can
count on me to follow you there.
I don't see anyone
over there, Reiji.
Do you think he could maybe
be hiding someplace else?
Just relax, it's early.
Welcome, sirs, to Inferno.
It's him!
He's behind the water tower!
I see him.
What about a face?
Can you see his face?
All I see is the gun.
I can't even tell
if it's a man or a woman.
This is bad, Reiji!
He's about to fire!
Hurry!
No way!
It can't be her.
What's wrong?
I know what I did.
She's dead!
I killed her!
Eren!
Come on! Shoot him!
Show yourself!
Reiji?
Show me your face!
Get him!
No!
Ohmigod, Reiji,
are you okay?
Did he get you?
I'm fine!
It's just a scratch.
You're so stupid.
Why would you
do something so stupid?
Couldn't help it.
Chalk it up to some kinda
morbid curiosity.
You did a good job today.
I'm proud of you.
Come on, Cal,
you got revenge for Judy.
That's a big deal.
Yeah.
Listen...
we know who's been pulling
the strings this whole time.
It's over.
I can't believe
you bastards!
What the heck just happened?
The one we got wasn't alone.
What?
Can't be!
No way.
Mission accomplished.
No way!
Yes...
Master.
[Music]
I can't live without him.
I wanna be with him forever.
I'll try so hard.
I'll do whatever I have to
to make him feel
the same way about me.