[Music]
I can't believe
she's still alive!
It was her.
I know it.
You okay?
What happened?
I saw her, a ghost.
I swore I wouldn't leave her...
that I would protect her.
The fact that I wasn't there
when she died
has haunted me
all this time.
And now I find out
I was wrong.
She's still alive?
That shot yesterday...
she fired it.
I see.
Dammit,
they made Cal join them.
She's their Phantom.
Master Huang,
it is a great honor
to be here with you tonight.
To be accepted
as one of your own
at this special occasion,
your birthday dinner,
I feel very fortunate.
Xu, now don't be so modest.
Honestly,
I've been much too slow
to offer you praise
for your achievements
in Western Japan.
You've done quite well.
Thank you.
And I assure you, the East
will be under our control
in the very near future.
Very good!
All the more reason
to celebrate!
Let's have a toast,
to our future!
The Godo Family
is having us put the hit
on this Chinese Mafia guy, Xu.
That's the main target,
isn't it.
Do you have an issue?
Do we really have to rub out
old man Huang along with him?
Given he's in league with
one of Inferno's enemies,
I'd consider it a bonus.
That man took you in
when Inferno had enough
of your underhanded crap,
he saved your ass.
That's true...
but the worm has turned.
Not a lick of honor.
You and I simply
view the world differently.
It's Darwinism,
survival of the fittest.
Gregor here, you copy?
Yeah. I'm here.
We're all set,
awaiting your order...
we can go anytime.
Sit tight for a sec.
Where's Phantom at?
Dunno.
She didn't seem too excited
about this gig
from the get-go...
we'll do it without her.
Okay?
Go on, this task does not seem
suited to her tastes.
She can be quite finicky.
Alright, Gregor,
let's get this thing started.
Parker Unit, I want you
to go through the back
and meet the welcome wagon,
got it?
Got it.
If you were to guess,
what would you say
their execution time
in this operation will run?
Three minutes?
Yeah, what's up?
Nothing.
I suppose that's acceptable.
But Phantom could get in
in less than ten seconds.
Oh yeah?
Damn it!
No way!
Hey! What the hell was that?
No way.
Look out!
Dammit!
What the hell is she doing?
It looks to me like she's
getting the task accomplished
in the most efficient way
possible.
Are you out of your mind?
We are not back home!
Are you saying their lives
have a higher value?
Life is cheap worldwide.
I think it should be safe
up here for now, sir.
I'm right behind you.
Who in the hell would have
the balls to hit us like that?
Someone I was foolish enough
to trust.
It's you...
Scythe's pet!
I helped that man
when everyone else
treated him like a leper.
This is how
he repays my compassion?
Sorry, pop.
That word ain't
in my vocabulary.
Master Huang!
You think you've got a pair?
Alright then, let's party!
Seriously,
I admire that.
Okay.
How 'bout a game?
The "shoot
when the song's done" game.
How dare you!
If you had any idea who
you were talking to right now,
you wouldn't
insult me like this...
you'd be pissing your panties.
I think
you got that backwards.
I'm Phantom.
Everybody who's anybody
knows my name.
I'm actually kinda
like a celebrity.
But, you're lucky.
You get to meet me.
If you win this game,
think of how famous you'll be.
It'll be sick.
If you believe
in reincarnation,
try to pick a better life
next time.
Adios, Gringo.
It's my fault.
I brought her down.
I dragged her
right off the streets...
straight into hell,
into murder.
I taught her how to kill
and live with a wounded soul,
and then, I left.
I'm working on our arrangements
for leaving the country.
Keep up the act till then.
Yeah, I know.
You were away
for a while yesterday.
I was just checking up
on an old flame.
Did you two catch up?
How sweet.
Aw, put a sock in it.
I got plans for him.
Yes, of course.
I have some great plans
for you, Reiji.
[Music]
Reiji.
Hey.
Good morning.
So I guess you went home
kinda early yesterday?
Huh?
Ah, well...
I went to find Sanae
right after school let out...
and you were
already gone by then.
Yeah. I had...
some stuff to do.
I hope I'm not being
too nosy or anything.
I didn't take it
that way at all.
Good.
It's snow.
That's weird.
I didn't hear anything
about it snowing today.
It's beautiful,
doncha think?
Yeah.
Last night's spectacle
did not go unnoticed
by the police.
I may be stating the obvious,
but anyone who was directly
involved in the attack,
should be out of the country
by tomorrow at the latest.
I apologize
for making a scene.
And most of those involved,
already left.
I accept your apology.
Actually, I'm quite pleased
you eliminated Xu
without leaving any trace
of our involvement.
It was certainly not our style
of conducting business.
But, in the future,
if you have plans
to operate in our country again,
I'd like to go over
the details with you.
Have a good day.
It shouldn't have gone down
like it did.
If we'd stuck to the plan...
none of our boys
would be in a bag.
I shoulda known better.
Right then.
Right, when Phantom didn't show
up when she was supposed to,
I shoulda known she was
gonna do something stupid.
You don't have to martyr
yourself like this, Lizzie.
And although it's true
that Drei has her quirks,
you have to be
more understanding.
She just gets impatient.
Eager.
In her mind, she has not
fully taken on the title
of Phantom quite yet,
as she's never
had the chance to contest it
with the previous Phantom.
I believe when that issue
is addressed once and for all,
her behavior
will likely conform
to something
more suited to her role.
So now, we should let her
resolve this matter promptly,
and decisively.
Yo, man.
You didn't bring
your lunch today, huh?
No, I didn't.
You worried about me starving?
Nah. But you wanna
hit the cafeteria?
Alright.
Guess you didn't
bring yours either?
Yeah, but I ate it already.
In recognition for your
bringing a welcome guest,
I will allow you
to sit here today.
Thanks.
I aim to please.
Hey, do you remember me?
Of course.
You're that unpopular kid,
Motegi.
My brother told me
all about you.
What'd you tell her, man?
I didn't tell her
anything that wasn't true.
Aw, come on.
I don't see why you should
get all the happiness
all the time,
it's not fair!
You're that desperate?
Take it easy on him, Reiji,
he doesn't seem
like such a bad guy.
Really?
Wow, I have the exact same
opinion on that very thing.
Maybe we can find
more stuff we agree on, huh?
I'm sure we'll be safe
as long as we stay
in public places like this.
At least I hope so.
Hey, Mio.
Can you save this seat for me?
I'm gonna grab some lunch.
Oh, sure.
Get me something, will ya?
Get it yourself!
Wait.
So he left poor Mio
all by herself
because you called him away?
Something came up at home
all of a sudden
that I really needed him
to help me with.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt
you two's date, Mio.
Uh. It wasn't really a date.
Oh, yeah?
So all that work
I did for you guys
was just so
you could hang out?
Well, it's just...
it's a little embarrassing.
You don't know the first thing
about girls, do you?
He should lose some food
as punishment.
You wanna tell me
why you should eat it instead?
You don't deserve to have
all the happiness, man!
Say what?
Oh, my god!
You really don't
get it, do you?
There are so many people
out there
starving for happiness!
That's right!
Like Motegi here.
Hey, what?
Hey Eren, I'm supposed to
give this to you.
Alright, thanks.
Hey, guys, I gotta run.
Why?
Yeah, why?
What's up?
Gotta do someone
a quick favor.
There goes my only shot
at happiness.
Don't be so dramatic, man.
Excuse me.
Wait, you're leaving too?
I just gotta keep an eye
on my kid sister.
Relax, just because
she's a hit with the guys
doesn't mean
she's doing anything wrong.
Don't get weird!
Yeah.
You should go on, Reiji.
It's okay to be
a little protective
of your only sister.
Sorry.
I swear
we'll get to hang out soon.
But what about my needs?
Shut up.
[Music]
Eren.
Looking for someone?
You'd love to kill me
here and now.
You're certainly capable
of killing me
with your bare hands.
Not because you were trapped
or mindlessly following orders.
But because you want to.
That personality trait
makes you a very special
boy indeed, Zwei.
That intent to kill
set you apart from Ein.
She was simply
a brainwashed agent
carrying out
whatever order she was given.
But to me,
you represent a failure,
although our experience
has led me in a new direction
on future projects.
New themes.
Hatred was my muse
on my next endeavor.
You've seen her, right?
My third work in the series.
My Drei.
Tell me.
What'd you do?
In artistic terms,
it was minimalism.
Very clean, very pure.
I even let her keep
her childhood memories.
For her, I refined her hatred.
She had quite a surprising
abundance of... hate.
I have nothing but
the deepest gratitude for you
for leaving me
such an intriguing subject.
She was quite a gift.
Bastard.
I can't wait.
Can't wait to kill me?
Yes, I know.
But you can't
do it here, my boy.
People would see what you are.
Such marvelous restraint.
You still can counter
the murderous rage
welling up inside you with
discipline and self control.
A beautiful balance.
That is my one true
complaint with Drei.
She lacks that control.
But...
she does at least
have the good sense
to avoid large crowds.
No way.
If you'd like to help,
you should hurry.
You can just come out
and face me.
We won't be disturbed here.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, really.
So you're her.
The very first person
to be called Phantom.
We are ghosts,
that have no place to haunt.
Non-existent phantoms.
[Music]
My only goal in life,
has been to hunt down
and kill that man.
Make him suffer,
and I am gonna enjoy it.