[Music]
Five million dollars.
Disrespecting my yard,
and taking five goddamn
million of my dollars?
There's got to be some penalties
for that type of shit.
Find who's responsible
and drag his sorry ass to me.
I wanna deal with him
personally.
But if there's
gonna be some commotion,
drop him.
Oh my god, thanks, Reiji.
It's silly,
but it's always been
a fantasy of mine to do this.
I've always wanted to order
a mountain of burgers
to pile up on the table,
and pig out, ya know?
Yeah.
So, Cal, the thing we were
talking about earlier.
The guy that killed Judy,
you see him?
So I've been thinking about it.
How are we gonna
take care of these guys?
Huh?
I mean, if you're really
gonna take revenge
for Judy's murder for me,
how you gonna do it?
These are the kinda guys
that probably carry
Uzis and stuff.
Don't think I can handle it?
You don't look
like the hero type to me.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm used to that by now.
But you won't have to worry.
I'm not gonna be the one
who's gonna do the job anyway,
I'll ask a friend of mine
to handle it.
Oh, really?
Yep.
You really have a friend
like that?
I'm actually a pretty
well-connected guy.
And as soon as
you spill the beans
and tell us
who we're after,
my friend's
gonna hunt him down,
and make sure his heart
stops its beating problem.
So tell me,
what does this guy look like?
When it's done,
I wanna be there.
What?
I wanna see it happen myself.
It'd mean a lot to me.
Please, Reiji, please
let me be there when it happens.
No way.
Aw, come on.
I'll ask
your friend myself
if you're nervous
about it or something.
Pretty please?
Little girls don't need
to get involved with that stuff.
But...
There's no way in hell.
Hey, listen, I'm sorry,
but I can't.
Okay, you win.
I'll do it.
I promise I'll ask my friend
if that'll be cool with them.
You will?
Yeah, but...
So once the meeting
with your friend is set up,
I'll tell ya
what they look like.
Just to let you know,
it may take me
a little bit of time
to get in touch
with the right person.
But I'll see if
I can track 'em down tonight.
I'll talk to you
again tomorrow.
Uhh, tomorrow, huh?
Yeah, you busy or something?
Well, we were
a few months behind
on our rent
at the apartment,
and the landlord kinda
kicked me out this morning.
But maybe I can stay
at your place?
So what's up, Lizzie?
How is the detective work going?
Any leads?
Phantom's busy checking out
the roommate's story.
And I'm seeing
if I can find some eyeballs.
But, it may take a little while.
I'm looking forward
to getting this figured out.
Who in the hell screwed this up?
I have to get
the Godos behind me
to get more leverage
in Inferno.
I can't let this bullshit
get in the way.
Ahhh, so this is your place,
huh?
It's kinda depressing.
It does me just fine
for what I need out of it.
It's totally empty!
Yeah.
What are you doing?
We don't want these burgers
to go to waste, do we?
I guess not.
But are you threatening
to stay here
until they're all gone?
Say what?
Nothing.
The bedroom's over there.
I'm fine with you
getting this bed.
Did someone else
used to live with you?
Why?
Oh, just a hunch.
Yeah, a long time ago.
Girlfriend?
No.
Hey, Reiji?
Hmm?
Can I... use your shower?
So uh...
You want me to pretend to be
this gangsta friend of yours?
Yeah, do you mind?
Well, I certainly wouldn't mind
you owing me a favor.
You think this girl
really knows anything
about what happened?
I dunno.
Well then, what in the hell
are you doing with her?
Hey, Reiji!
Sorry!
I forgot to get a stupid towel.
Yeah, hold on.
What now?
I just think it's funny
that the notorious Phantom
is getting house trained
by a little girl!
Now, just because
y'all are having a sleepover--
He hung up on me.
So there must be
some kinda reason
why you've been diggin' around
in my backyard.
Right? Is there?
Wow, really?
Yep. My friend said
they'd do it for us.
We should hear from them
some time tomorrow.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, Reiji?
You got a family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
So you're like me.
Your folks too, huh?
I don't know for sure.
I ran away from
my lyin' sack a crap father.
A little while after that,
Judy took me in.
If It wasn't for her, I think
I'd probably be dead by now.
That's tough, sorry, Cal.
The way I see it,
she's the only family I got.
But now...
now she's dead.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Since I don't have her anymore,
I don't know where to go.
I just feel so lost.
I really don't know
what the heck to do.
I know.
I felt the same way.
It's a part of life,
everybody dies.
Some people suffer
for a long, long time.
And some people go
with no one to remember them.
But no matter what happened,
Judy has you to remember her.
She's lucky in that way.
You think so?
Yeah.
You really think so?
I don't know where to go.
I just feel so lost.
I really don't know
what the heck to do.
I believe
you have a house guest.
My witness.
I gotta say, man,
this place could really use
some jazzin' up,
some pictures and shit.
What the hell do you want?
Now don't be
such a wet blanket.
I just ran into
this fine sister
diggin' around
on my property,
looking for some kinda dirt
or story or something.
And I'll be damned
if she didn't have
some really interesting things
to talk about.
Now let me talk to my witness.
I gotta feeling
she'll tell me what she knows.
She in there?
The girl doesn't know anything.
Move it.
There's no way in hell
she could make the shooter
in that dark of a place.
If she says she saw him,
she's lying.
Move.
You deaf?
Hold on.
Shit!
Don't tell me that Phantom
is actually gonna go
toe to toe with me
over some triflin' little girl?
I must say you got me
even more intrigued now.
You know, I had a funny feeling
about this whole thing.
You and Claudia are playing
some kinda backroom game, huh.
No, sir.
Ten A.M. tomorrow.
Come to the base.
You can tell your whole little
story to me and McGuire.
And if you're
blowin' smoke then,
we're gonna have to
find the truth the hard way.
Sorry about that.
I just couldn't act
like I didn't know anything.
It's cool.
But doesn't this
screw things up?
What the hell are you gonna
tell the bosses tomorrow?
Don't worry, I'll think
of something to tell them.
So you think
she doesn't know, huh?
No, I'm sure she doesn't.
Alright then.
You don't know anything,
nothing at all,
right, Cal?
But you'll tell me
your story, won't ya?
That night...
Judy?
Judy!
That's what happened.
I figured as much.
You figured what?
That I didn't see anything?
That guy that was here...
That's Isaac Wisemel,
isn't it?
That's the guy who runs
the Bloodies gang, right?
Yeah.
Reiji...
why did you wanna
protect me from him?
I heard what they called you.
They called you Phantom.
I know who that is.
Judy's friends told me
he's someone that goes around
and kills gangsters.
Does that mean
you're a real assassin?
You really are, aren't you?
You're the assassin Phantom.
Yeah, that's me.
Hey...
Holy...
It's the money those
Japanese guys were carrying.
Five million dollars.
Holy crap, Cal!
Did you steal it?
No, I didn't!
I swear I didn't!
I don't want anything to do
with this dirty money!
I was hoping I'd find someone.
Someone I could pay
to help me.
You're the Phantom, Reiji?
You really are?
I'll give you
all of this damn money
if you kill them for me.
The guy in the alley.
The guy with the gun.
The guy who was
supposed to get the money.
Kill everybody that had anything
to do with Judy's murder.
Will you do it for me?
We'll discuss my fee
for the job tomorrow.
Let's sleep on it for now.
I lied to you, I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
This situation
has gone from bad to worse.
We still don't know
who the shooter is.
And I have five million
sitting on my coffee table.
If word gets out
that I've got their cash,
Inferno is not gonna be
happy about it.
Kill everybody that had anything
to do with Judy's murder.
What the hell am I gonna do?
How can I make Cal happy
without pissing off Inferno?
Would you care to tell me
what's going on?
I shouldn't really
talk about it now.
If he sees the two of us
talking alone like this,
Isaac will get suspicious.
I'm gonna explain myself
in front of everyone.
Now I believe you have
something of interest
to share, Phantom.
Yes, sir.
First, I need to clear up
a small misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding, you say?
Now it is true
that I'm sheltering
an alleged witness
to the other night's incident.
But she's just a family member
of the woman that was killed
in the crossfire,
and has no
relevant information.
Oh? And you're sure?
With the title "Phantom"
comes skills
for discovering the truth.
Sounds like bullshit to me.
I can't say
that I'm convinced.
Do you have any evidence
to back up your assertion?
Did you use any truth serum?
No.
Any recorded data?
None.
So my colleague is right,
and we are just to
trust you at word?
Yes, sir.
Not good enough for me, no way.
What are your thoughts, Claudia?
That's all, Phantom?
Trust me,
I have my reasons
for not using a truth serum.
Do your reasons
run deep enough
to excuse
why you pulled out a weapon
in the presence of Isaac?
Yes, sir.
Then illuminate me.
It's simple.
I didn't wanna damage her
any further.
So now you're some kind of
humanitarian or something?
No, sir.
I didn't wanna put the potential
that I saw in her
in any kind of jeopardy.
I see a further use
for this girl.
Do tell.
Well, sir...
She seems to possess
some rare qualities.
They may even be called
talents.
This girl has an intense
motivation to kill.
And an intense solitude.
A ghost
haunting this world alone.
Is that so?
I seem to recall hearing
similar things in the past.
I see.
You'd like to take
this girl in
and train her
in the ways of an assassin?
Yes.
If you'll allow it,
I'll personally train
this girl
so that she can serve
as my own right hand.
What proof do you have
she possesses such talent?
Just a hunch.
I am sick and tired
of hearing this crap!
I can't really
put it into words,
but I believe it's true.
It may be hard for you
to take it on faith alone,
but it doesn't change it.
You got a big mouth, son.
I have just one question.
If you're willing to go this far
to gain a new assistant,
are you saying you're displeased
with your current situation?
Your pairing with Lizzie?
Well, I can't say that we're
a match made in heaven.
The whole "partner" thing
has always seemed
just a little bit forced
to me.
He's a freaking genius,
and I'm just pretty good.
If he thinks this new girl
will work out better for him,
then she should take my place
whenever she's ready.
I ain't crying.
In regards to the prostitute
killed along with the Yakuza,
a Miss Judy Devens was her name,
if I'm not mistaken.
Are you certain
she had no larger role
in the incident?
Yeah. Just unlucky.
Wrong place and time.
Sir, I checked up
on her background myself.
Well, Isaac,
what do you think?
I still think
the whole thing stinks.
I will allow it for now.
Don't fail me.
Sir.
Phantom, I eagerly await
your report.
Quite an interesting
performance, Reiji.
I don't buy that act
for a goddamn second.
I'll be watching you, boy.
This may fly with Claudia,
but not with me.
Sorry about that.
Don't worry.
Sorry I caved to Isaac.
So now what?
Why don't you tell me?
There's no way in hell
you wanna make more people
like you.
You lied to them
to protect her, right?
You know, because of
that hard sales pitch,
it's gonna be your ass
that's on the line.
I know.
[Music]
After the meeting,
everything's
still totally up in the air.
The shooter...
The five mil...
Payback for Judy...
What the hell do I do?
[Music]
The girl's a natural.
But still,
does that make it alright
to lead her down
this same bloody path?