Despite every
precaution
this planet will
soon cease to exist.
Just like the countless
lives that it has nurtured
from infancy
to old age,
it too is about to complete
its cycle of birth and death.
The same Sun that gave
it light and warmth
is about to
claim its life
and nothing can be
done to stop it.
The next train
scheduled to depart
is the 330 Express leaving
at 3:30 from Platform No. 3.
Passengers, please proceed
slowly to the gate
in an orderly
manner. Thank you.
That means no pushing
or cutting in line.
More trains are
leaving soon.
Everyone will get free passage
to their final destination.
So let's be patient and make
this as pleasant as possible.
And please all
of you need
to have your emigration
permits out.
You can not board
without them.
The transfer of
local residents
from Blocks A thru
F is now complete.
I've also sent several search
teams into the suburbs
to see if there are any
residents still out there.
As soon as that's
taken care of,
the evacuation
will be complete.
Thank you
so much sir.
It is an honor and a pleasure
to have so many SDF members
come all this
way to help us.
Thanks. But, it was
no trouble at all.
Galaxy Headquarters has
given the highest priority
to this Emigration Project.
We don't want to lose anyone.
The people of Arbent are the
ones that should be commended.
Thanks to their
cooperation,
the evacuation has gone
off without a single hitch.
We'll close this station
tomorrow morning as planned...
Excellent
work.
I thank you
for that, Captain...
We've tried
everything, Sir.
But not even our
best scientists
can reverse the effects
of a dying star.
They said that Arbent will be
swallowed up within a year.
It's hard to believe
that everything here
will be gone soon... It's
eerie just thinking about it.
This is Louis
reporting.
Nobody's left in Block
F. What about Block G?
Nobody's here, either.
It looks pretty bleak.
How's it over in
your sector, Manabu?
Same here in Block H. I'm
heading over to Block I now.
I was in Block I
earlier, Manabu.
You can double check but I
guarantee no one's there.
Okay then, let's
bet on it!
Ten thousand Ables
if we find someone.
Yeah, right. Whose gonna
take that sucker bet?
All right,
David! You're on!
No way... It's
all still alive!
It's perfectly
healthy. But how...?
Huh? These farmlands were
supposed to be abandoned
a long time ago.
I don't get it.
Hey you!! Get your scrawny
butt outta my wheat field!
Take that!! How dare
you come out here
and take advantage of
a defenseless old woman!
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
Take advantage? But I didn't
do anything to you, Ma'am.
Finally!
I just knew you'd come home
some day! Ma-Makoto-o-o!
Say what?!
Do you have any idea how
long I've been waiting
for you to come
home?! Oh, Makoto!
Ah, excuse
me but
I think you've mistaken
me for someone else...
I'm sorry but I'm not
who you think I am.
Makoto-o-o!
It's just that you just
came back so suddenly!
I thought I'd have
a heart attack!
Only a bad son would treat
his mother that way!
Shame on
you, Makoto!
Ah, lady, please. I already
told you; I'm not your son!
So! Now you
think I'm blind?
Well let's get one
thing straight, Makoto.
It doesn't matter how
big-for-your-britches you get,
you're always
gonna be
that same little
nose-picker to me, boy!
Please, lady! Listen!
I am not your son!
You're such
a joker!
I hope you brought
your appetite.
You must be hungry
after all that traveling.
I didn't come
here to eat.
The only reason
I'm out here
is to see if there's
anyone left to evacuate.
Do you understand, Ma'am?
That's nice, so tell me
is your work going well?
U-Uhh,
it's fine...
Oh, you can
tell your Momma!
Working for the Planet
Cultivation Project
is too hard! It was
just a matter of time
before you
came home!
Planet
Cultivation?
But see! Your dream of owning
a farm came true, didn't it?
Now then, the only thing
you need is a wife...
Or do you already
have someone in mind?
No! I don't have
anyone in mind!
But you don't understand!
I'm not Makoto!
Now that's enough! There's
no reason to be shy!
Oh, no! What a bad mother
I am! I forgot the tea.
Now don't go anywhere!
I'll be right back!
Why did it
have to be me?
Why couldn't Bruce
have found her?
He could use a little
motherly affection.
Well, we do look a lot
alike... So she's not crazy.
Just a little
bit confused.
I guess she's been
all alone out here...
waiting for her son to come
home for who knows how long...
I can't just leave
her here to die.
I'd better report this to the
Captain. Maybe he can help.
Makoto...
Now don't you tell me you've
forgotten what time it is, eh?
I don't know what
you're thinkin' lady!
Oh! Ah...
Uwahhhh!
Sounds like some wild monkeys
are mating... This is strange;
all the farms were supposed to
be abandoned a long time ago.
Yeah, I never expected to see
anything like this out here...
I wonder where
Manabu is.
What in the world could
he be doing out here?
[Manabu] Hahah, S-Stop
it! Stop it...hahaha! Ow!
Manabu!
Louis!
Hold up!!
Manabu!
Are you oka...
WAIT!
Just a second!
Son, you know good and well
that you can't take a bath
with all these clothes
on, now can you?
OKAY! I'll do
it, lady!
Just let me keep my
underwear on! Please!
Good grief... Now I think
I've seen everything.
What d'you think you're doing
with that old lady, Manabu?
Are you blind?! It's not
what I'm doing to her!
It's what she's
doing to me!
And what's
that?!
Oh! I'll bet that she's the
girl we talked about earlier?
Am I right? So she's
your future wife!
And who's this
with your fiancee?
One of your
workers no doubt!
Your
future wife?
What in the world have
you been telling her?!
Wait a minute! Does she
think that I'm your employee?
Well, ah...
I guess...
Yaa!! Got 'em!
Yeow!
So, the old woman thinks that
Manabu is her son Makoto?
Right. And she refuses to
listen to a word we've said.
She's convinced that her son
made a fortune for himself
while working on the
Cultivation Project
on Planet Agri and that
he's come back home
with his his girlfriend
and butler in tow.
He's gonna owe me
for this! Big time!
A-And so you're
his butler, right?
Now that's what I
call perfect casting!
Shut up!
I understand the
situation, David.
But we don't have
much time here.
Let's get this mission
wrapped up. Understood?
Yes, Sir! We'll
do the best we can.
Search and Rescue mission...
Who would've thought?
Just wrap it up, huh...?
Who is he kidding?
Oh, and by the way:
we don't have much time.
I'd watch my tongue if
I were you young man!
You'll never get ahead with
that kind of attitude!
You are sooo
right ma'am...
If I
were you,
I'd fire that ill-mannered
excuse for a butler.
You worry me because
you're too good-natured.
Oh, I wouldn't
worry about him.
He's actually quite
good at what he does.
Besides, I have something
very important to tell you.
It's this
planet...
I know. It's
changed, hasn't it
So have you. The boy who I
once knew has become a man.
I remember you used to cry
over every little thing
but you never gave up... I
lost count of how many times
I took you to a friend's
house to patch things up...
Do you
remember that?
Manabu,
its okay...
That must have been
hard... I'm sorry.
Well, it wasn't easy but I did
manage... You're back home now.
That's all
that matters.
It's natural for a man to go
off and pursue his dreams.
I'm just glad
you're home.
And you've turned into
such a big success,
and you just
look so good!
You don't know
how proud I am.
You are going to stay with
me from now on, aren't you?
It's not right...
I can't.
I can't start playing along
even if it's just to help her.
I have to try to
get through to her.
She needs to know
that I'm not Makoto.
We need to
talk, Ine...
Lower! Lower! There!
Oh, that feels so good!
You have magic
fingers, young man.
You're too kind, Madam
Ine... It's my pleasure.
I'd also like to
thank my son's driver
for getting that
wood chopped.
Well, I'm used to hard work
so it's no trouble at all.
Let me assure
you, madam.
This is a piece of
cake for him. Really.
Ah... isn't that
right, Driver?
Shut up.
Will ya?
Goodness. Why are
you still wearing
that dirty
old uniform?
Didn't you see I left some
clean clothes for you?
Um...
And why didn't you tell me
that these other young men
who work for you
were coming as well?
If I knew, I'd have
planned a nice dinner.
Or at least I'd have
cleaned up around the house.
We don't need
special treatment.
We're just hired
hands after all.
Nonsense. Hired hands or not,
you're all VIP's in my house.
I'll do my best to
prepare a delicious meal
for you tonight...
Ah, Louis?
Ma'am?
Would you help me
in the kitchen?
Sure thing. It'd be
my pleasure, Ma'm!
Ah, you know. I'm convinced
that there's a good reason
why this is
happening, Captain.
I hope
you're right.
Yes, Sir.
This is all
my fault.
I couldn't convince her
that I wasn't her son
so I let her believe
what she wanted.
Hmm....
You know, Sir, I think Ine's
waited so long for her son
to come back that she
has to believe I'm him.
But if she could talk to her
real son I think she'd be okay.
Do you think we could
use the ship's computers
to track
him down?
That's
impossible.
But it would
solve everything!
I know it's not the
SDF's responsibility
but if we force her to
leave she could snap!
It's impossible
because her son's dead.
Now you see, Louis?
First, cut it here like so.
Ohhhh!
If you're that
impressed by this, child.
Then you've got
a lot to learn
if you want to be
Makoto's wife.
But... You see! I'm not
really his fiancee, Ine!
Oh, I've forgotten
the tomatoes.
Those're his
favorite.
I'll go get some
from the garden.
Uhh...?
Planet Agri...
Destroyed?!
But planets set for
agricultural colonization
are researched
in advance, right?
Well, I think it was
initially sound.
But all the Planetary
Renovations weakened it.
Ten years ago,
Agri's tectonic infrastructure
suddenly collapsed.
No survivors were
found. Not even one.
Then no matter how
long she waits,
Makoto won't ever
come home again.
This is awful.
It'll break her heart.
So any
ideas, Manabu?
Oh, there you
are, Makoto...
I guess the two of you
are having a meeting.
[Buldge] Oh, no. We
were just chatting.
Then I suppose
you won't mind
if I borrow my
Makoto for a bit?
What's up,
Ine...? Where to?
Not far at all. There's
something I want you to see
that I think
you'll enjoy.
Oh, darn it! Why
can't I do this?!
I wonder where
they're going.
So, have you been taking
care of this wheat field
all by
your self?
Well, you
know me.
If everything's not perfect I
can't get to sleep at night.
Besides, I couldn't
have you come home
and find that your wheat
field had gone to seed.
First she
loses her son
and now she's about
to lose her home.
I don't know how to
tell someone that.
Ine, you have to leave this
world as soon as possible!
It's not safe here anymore.
You'll die if you stay...
So say
something...
There's nothing to
say. This is my home.
I could never give all this
up. It's like a part of me.
This land has a
soul of its own.
Do you believe
that, my son?
I do.
I'm glad. Because this
place is our home,
and it could use a
friend right now.
We should go.
I love your fiance
but I don't trust
her in the kitchen.
Well, come on! I'm not
getting' any younger!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm
fine, dear.
It's
lovely.
It is, but then
before you know it...
this place'll
be long gone.
I wish there was
something we could do.
Are you sure I'm
not too heavy?
No, you're fine.
You remind me of your
father - strong; kind.
You even look
like him to me.
You know, there's
nothing more special
than getting a piggyback
ride from your son.
But I'm not your son...
I'm not Makoto...
Do you understand what I'm
saying, Ine? I'm sorry.
Wow. I've never seen
anything so beautiful.
It's like
paradise.
Over there! Do you
remember this place now?
You'd often tell me you
liked the view from here...
You said when you saw it
you felt you were home.
I said that?
Many times...
Try one of these.
The funny thing is,
this tree has never
stopped bearing fruit.
And the apples always
taste the same.
The view here hasn't
changed either...
I can't believe that
everything around me
is really going
to disappear...
I'll never see any
of this again...
Just like
my son.
Like your son?
You knew Ine...?
Delicious!
Hey, Ine... Would you mind
if I took this with me?
Huh?
This fruit's too delicious.
It wouldn't be right
if no one else
got to taste it.
I'll plant seeds from this
tree on different planets!
It will live
on! I promise!
I'll make sure the first
one'll be on Planet Agri.
And I won't
stop there.
I'll spread the fruit from this
tree throughout the universe.
That sounds like
a lot of work!
Yeah, I know. But
it'll be worth it.
Because wherever
this tree grows,
it'll be like
home to me.
And it won't
ever disappear.
And no matter how
far away it is,
it'll taste just the
same as it does here.
The same as it does here?
The same as it does here...
What's going on?! Ine?!
What's happening?!
Are you okay?!
What's going on?! Ine!? What's
happening?? Are you okay?
I'm more than okay...
Thank you so much!
Ine!!
Good bye, Ine.
[Buldge] No residents remain
on Planet Arbent now.
The transfer of
the population
has been completed
on schedule.
Can somebody please tell
me what that was all about?
Who knows? Maybe
it was an illusion.
Or maybe it was a
mass hallucination.
Whatever it was,
it wasn't real.
I disagree. It was real;
the tastes, the smells.
And how do you
explain the apple?
I think we were all dealing
with the spirit of a mother.
A mother that wanted to
live... She was scared.
She didn't want to
die and be forgotten.
She wanted to
go on forever.
Hey Shutaro, How have you been?
I'll be right with you.
Huh?!
Well I got the day off.
Is that ok?
It's more than ok, son.
Next time, while
on the 777 Express
I meet Subaru, an
old childhood friend
but he's different than
he was in the old days.
When things get crazy and we're
attacked by hostile aliens,
I'm wishing that I had
the old Subaru back.
See ya next time
on the Railways.