In the great tapestry
of the Universe
there are patterns that
are woven by the desires
of the souls
that inhabit it.
Those few who learn
to see these patterns
can also see
into the future.
But when this Universal
tapestry is torn
the natural order
of things is lost
and nothing is certain-
especially the future.
This is David
with Rigel Platoon.
Headquarters we
are breaking off
to go guard
Muller Junction.
Roger!
Manabu, Louis, I'll
see you guys later.
Stay out of
trouble, okay?
[Manabu] We will, David.
We'll be fine.
Don't worry.
You can bet on it.
[David] Ten-four.
Now that's what I like
to hear. David out.
This is Louis...
The Flame Swallow's
breaking off, as well.
Spica Platoon is heading
out to the Harloom area
to find the enemy
Destroyer and gather info.
Good luck, you
guys. Be safe.
[Manabu] Roger that,
Spica Platoon.
We will.
You do the same.
Good luck.
And Louis...
I'll see you
soon, okay?
Sure. Sounds good.
See you soon, Manabu.
You could have talked
to him a little longer.
It's going to be a while before
you get to see him again.
Oh, wait. I forgot. You
two aren't like that.
Uh, Well...
[Shelley] Captain!
What about you? Don't ya
wanna talk about Murase?
How romantic.
Two Captains in love
talking before
the big battle.
Sorry, girls...
I'll wait and say what I
want to say in private.
When this
is over.
Right now we need to be more
focused and sharp than ever!
We'll be entering the Warp
Zone in two minutes, Captain.
[Captain] All right,
Girls! Final Check!
[All] Yes,
Ma'am!
[Miki] Commander!
Capella, Alphard,
Deneb, and
Antares Platoons
are on their way to
the Harloom Area!
Their ETA is
ten minutes!
I don't know what all
the fuss is about.
It's just one Destroyer. The
SPG will take care of them.
Just wait
and see.
[Sayaka] The Destroyer
is on the move!
Harloom Junction is
no longer responding!
[SPG Member] Thirty seconds
until warp-out, Captain.
Warp-out point is
6 mega-meters away
from Harloom
Junction, Sir.
All right. Prepare
for battle, Men.
Captain, is it
wise to attack
without fully knowing
the enemy's power?
Can't we wait and join
forces with the SDF?
[Captain] This order is from
the top down. We have to obey.
But, Captain...!
We've been in impossible
situations before
and still come
out on top!
Let's not forget
who we are, Men!
[SPG Member] We're
warping out, Captain!
Scanner results!
We're not picking
up anything.
All systems are down. There
is No human life detected.
They're all
dead, Sir!
[SPG Member] Multiple
Warp-Outs detected!
We've got
company, Captain!
[Captain] Onscreen!
Full power to the
Main Battery!
Synchronize all gun-ports!
Target their main bridge!
Yes, Sir!
Awaiting your command!
Fire!!
Direct hits
from all guns!!
Magnify target image!
How bad are they?
What?! Enemy ship completely
unaffected! Not even a scratch!
Hard to
starboard now!!
Get the Recording
Probe ready!
I'm leaving a
message to the SDF!
The Recording Probe
is ready, Captain!
Launch it! Get it
out of here now!
Set it to activate when it
receives an SDF ID signal.
Captain, we're
completely surrounded!
The Enemy is targeting
our lead coach!
Please. Let them
get that probe.
Don't let our
deaths be in vain.
[Miki] The Six-six-six
is no longer responding!
Their ID Signal
has disappeared!
Their radar image
has vanished!
Captain
Johansson...
What?! Damn them! Making
light of our elite platoon?!
What was Johansson
doing out there?!
He didn't take out one
single enemy ship!
[Brad] The Alfort Fleet
is dispersing, Commander!
It looks like
they're heading out
to other Galaxy
Railways Junctions!
[Commander] Inform all
Platoons immediately!
Have them coordinate and
plot intercept courses!
[Rigel Captain] The enemy
hasn't arrived yet?
Not yet, Sir. There's no
sign of them on the radar.
Incoming energy blasts
at 9 o'clock, Captain!
[Captain] What?
What fire-power!
Enemy Ship
closing!
All available power
to the Main Battery!
Several Platoons are reporting
that they've engaged the enemy!
It looks like the
battle's begun, Captain.
David...
Manabu...
Louis! Let's
focus on our job
instead of worrying
about our friends!
Right!
Yes, Ma'am!
We've arrived at the
Warp-Out point, Captain!
The Scanner
Report's negative.
There are no life-forms
on Harloom Junction.
They're
all dead.
I'm picking up a
Recording Probe here!
It's from the
Six-sixty-six, Captain!
[Captain] Establish a laser
link. Upload the data.
Yes, Ma'am!
Onscreen! Play
back the message!
This is Johansson
with the SPG.
Our situation
here is bleak.
We are deploying this
probe in the hopes
that it will record the
enemy's communications.
Once they destroy us they
should let their guard down
and break their
radio silence.
Hopefully, the
recordings on this probe
will reveal their
purpose. Godspeed.
Maggie. Run this through our
advanced decoding program.
Guard the Main
Circuit from viruses.
Yes,
Ma'am!
[Female alien] Alfort
Fleet Invasion Force
begin Phase 2
of the attack!
Proceed to the critical
Galaxy Railways Junction
assigned to your ship
and destroy at will!
Once Phase 2 is
accomplished
proceed to the
rendezvous point
where we will
commence Phase 3-
the destruction
of Planet Destiny
and Galaxy Railways
Headquarters.
I repeat: begin
Phase 2 of the attack.
Maintain radio silence
until it's complete.
Everything that
Liffle said is true.
Ivanov didn't
believe her.
We've got to let
the council know.
AI! Get me
headquarters immediately!
Yes, Ma'am!
We're under
attack!!
They're pretty
clever, aren't they?
They managed to fool our
Orbit Network Radar somehow.
They want a fight. So let's
give it to them, girls!
Captain!
Several fighters
have just appeared
out of nowhere!
They're
attacking!
Alrakis Junction is
reporting damage!
We're also running low
on ammunition, Captain!
Sir! Spica Platoon
is engaging the enemy!
We've got to
do something!
Men, let's eliminate
the enemy here
and head to the
Harloom Area!
We've got to rescue
Spica Platoon!
[All] Yes, Sir!
[Silver]
No worries, girls!
Vega Platoon
is on the way!
Yeah! Nobody
messes with us!
That's right!
Yeah! Let's
go get 'em!
Thanks,
Captain Murase!
All guns
open fire!!
The main engine's
been hit!
We're down to
80% of max power!
We've got to
hold on, Girls!
Johansson's message must be
relayed to Head Quarters
at all costs!
I'd rather get
one good shot in
than go down without a fight!
Maggie! Ready the cannon!
Yes, Ma'am! Diverting all
power to the main cannon!
Energy level is at
the critical limit!
I'm opening the
front armor plates!
Brace yourselves!
This baby kicks!
Open fire!!
Direct hit!
Starboard side!
Our Main Battery's
out of power!
[Captain] It's over,
girls. This is it.
Captain
Julia!
We put up a good fight but
we're damaged too much.
We've done all
we can here.
Prepare to abandon
the Flame Swallow.
[Computer] Voice
recognition affirmed.
Security
clearance granted.
The self-destruct
mechanism is now set.
All crewmembers please
evacuate immediately.
[Captain] Goodbye,
Flame Swallow.
I'll miss you,
old friend.
Captain, please hurry! We've
got to go! There's no time!
Right.
No!!
Captain Julia!!
Oh no.
The Iron
Berger!
It's Vega Platoon!
They've come to help us!
Murase... always
showing-off.
[Schnader] Hey,
did you miss me?
Let's move!
This won't last for
even five minutes!
[Louis] Iron Berger this
is Flame Swallow Shuttle 2!
We're making our
approach now!
Iron Berger!
We've left the nest!
[Silver] Roger that!
We see you!
Louis! Are you
all right?!
Manabu. I'm okay but
Captain Julia's injured.
Come on!
Let's go!
Everyone's accounted
for, Captain!
[Captain] Affirmative!
Prepare for Emergency Warp!
Come on! Emergency warp!
We've got to hurry!
No! Louis!
Louis!!
Louis!
No! Louis!
Engage Warp
Engines! Let's go!
LOUIIIIIIIS!!!
This is
Iron Berger.
We've succeeded in
rescuing Spica Platoon
from a battle with
the Alfort Fleet.
Flame Swallow
was abandoned
and programmed
to self-destruct.
Three Spica members
sustained minor injuries.
They're all okay, but one's
critical... and one's dead...
The Alfort Fleet has broken
the back of our defenses.
We're completely
defeated.
Have you heard
about Louis?
We've just
lost contact
with the station
on Planet Decor!
Pleiades Junction
has been destroyed
by the
Alfort Fleet!
Atria Main Line;
completely segmented!
Regulus Main Line; inoperative
due to the destruction
of the Orbit Point!
Alphard and
Deneb Platoons
have completed their
rescue operations
and are withdrawing
from the battle lines!
The Wheel of Fate is
spinning out of control.
Our very future is
spiraling into darkness...
What will
become of us?
What?! Their
goal is to destroy
the Galaxy Railways
and Planet Destiny?
This situation is much
bigger than I imagined!
We're going to
need some help!
Ask the Planet States to
mobilize their armed forces!
The enemy has
changed course!
Their entire fleet is
converging on Destiny!
Damn them!
They're striking fast so we
can't organize our defenses!
They're making us look
like a bunch of amateurs!
Captain Bulge!
Wataru. Allow me
to borrow this.
We're going back up soon!
Fix this right now!
Captain, that's
impossible!
We'd need four days for
body work like that!
Four days?!
This planet might not
be here in four days!
Sir, we're doing the
very best we can!
You're not the only ones
fighting! We are too!
You call this
fighting?!
Murase. Keep your
head. We need you.
It's not looking good, Bruce.
What are we going to do?
Big One!
Am I dreaming?
[David] Fancy
meeting you here.
I guess us old shipmates
still think alike. Aye, Kid?
There's no other place we'd
go at a time like this.
We are Sirius Platoon
members after all!
Big One's
waiting for us...
Hey! This is a
restricted area!
What's
going on?
There aren't any dispatch
orders for Big One!
To hell with that.
We're the Sirius Platoon.
This train
belongs to us.
Sirius Platoon has
been disbanded.
The official word is that
they no longer exist.
Who said that?!
Step away from
there! Now!
You guys don't even have the
rank to take this train up!
Where's your
Captain?! Huh?!
[Wataru] I'm right here!
[Manabu] Dad!
Guards, if you have anything
to say, say it to me.
Captain!
It's you!
Welcome back!
Thank you, David...
Now let's move.
We have a mission
to fulfill.
Yes, Sir! Don't
mind if I do!
Hey! Wait
a second!
Come on! We gotta
report this!
We've been waiting
for you guys!
You're
on board?!
Yeah, we're in the
fighter coach.
I'm afraid we still haven't
finished analyzing
the Cosmo Matrix.
But we don't have to know
what it is to make it work.
We should have
the modifications
on the Main Battery finished
before you go into battle.
Great. We're
counting on you...
[Yuki] Captain?
This is for you, Sir.
Yuki.
Thank you.
Thank all of you.
I'm very proud to
be your Captain.
Big One's ready to join
the final line of defense!
Request permission
to take-off!
[Ivanov] That's Bulge!
Is he out of his mind?!
We can't let a decommissioned
officer take a train up!
Stop him! Now! I want
him arrested for this!
Big One has
permission to take-off!
What?!!
Sirius Platoon, you are
cleared for take-off!
What kind of
conspiracy is this?!
I'll report you all to
the Inquiry Commission!
Every last
one of you!
System Check!
Stand by for
Sub-atomic Warp
Generator ready!
Magnetic Barrier
Generator is a go!
Orbit Network
Radar ready!
Atomic Boiler
Pressure is a go!
Big One is now in
take-off position.
Cylinder Valves
are open!
The Main Circuit
is now on-line!
All energy levels are
ready for take-off!
The Warp Drive coupling
is now in place!
All systems green,
Captain Bulge!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
Let's move out!!
Ahead full!!
Go get 'em Sirius Platoon.
We're counting on you.
Hmm?
Manabu...
I love
you, Son.
Knowing that this may
be their last voyage,
Sirius Platoon has set
off on their mission,
determined to overcome the fear
and doubt that assails them.
With the hope
of the Galaxy
resting squarely
on their shoulders
they have no choice
but to fly bravely on
towards their
destiny.
Even with the threat of the
Alfort Fleet facing us,
it seems that our most
dangerous enemy lies within.
With a few unexpected allies
and a souped-up weapons system
is it possible to survive
against this Super Armada?!
See ya next time
on the Railways!