On the last
Galaxy Railways
many innocent
lives were lost
when a bomb ripped
apart a train.
The Space Defense Force was
on high alert trying to find
the author of this dark
chapter in Railways history.
Little did they know, the real
horrors were about to begin.
What darkness in a man's
mind is so complete
that it causes him to lash
out and murder innocent people?
What hopelessness
is so consuming
that it causes him to
destroy the hope of others?
Spica Platoon has
just reported that the
Altair Two-twenty-four Express
is completely destroyed.
There are
no survivors.
Sirius Platoon
reporting:
the Regulus Eight Eleven
Express is demolished!
No survivors found!
Dispatch all Platoons
to Addylos Junction.
I want a full report as
soon as they arrive.
[Waitress] Here you
go, guys. Dig in.
Thank you...
Here!
...Don't worry.
I'm sure they'll take
you back, Manabu.
I don't want
to go back.
Now that's
a good one!
So you got crossways
with the big brass;
you just need to kiss some
butt for a while! That's all!
Please, come in!
Have a seat!
Are you all
right, man?
Yeah, I'm fine. Just
hungry. Hey, that's good.
Not too
bad, huh?
It tastes a lot
like my Mom's.
Just what the
doctor ordered!
Y'know You just needed to
get away from the office
for a while. The
SDF can be stuffy.
That's an organization
with history.
They've got a
pecking order.
They don't want some
kid jumping rank;
they want you to do exactly
what they tell you to do.
But I've got to do
what I think is right!
You can be a lion, but you have
to be a lamb first, my friend.
It's not that easy...
I can't watch people die.
I joined because I want
to help people...
Sometimes I feel like
they're sleepwalking...
Like all they know how
to do is play it safe.
The whole
station's on fire!
It's too late to
do anything now.
I wonder how many people
are on that sub-station.
Louis. Report to Headquarters.
Tell them what's going on.
Yes, Captain...
Come in, Headquarters...
This is
Sirius Platoon.
Addylos Junction is
engulfed in flames...
Rescue operations
are impossible.
There will be
no survivors.
Who is it? What kind of
sick maniac would do this?!
So why don't you just
turn in your monkey suit
and quit
the SDF?
Just walk away
from it all?
Maybe it's
not your thing.
That seems to be the
general consensus... Huh?
Well, maybe they're
right, man...
You don't seem
like SDF to me.
I don't?
Naa, all those guys
have big egos...
they don't care about
helping people;
they just want to
boss somebody around.
That's what they live for,
buddy. Do this! Do that!
Some of 'em do
seem to enjoy it.
That's what I'm telling
you! They're lame!
This is good.
Right here, Shaw.
Hey,
Manabu.
Huh?
Good luck. You're not
like those other SDF guys.
You really want
to help people.
Don't let
'em rob ya.
Don't let those guys
steal your dream from you.
Don't let those guys turn
you into one of them...
Check ya
later!
Forget them, Manabu.
They're not worth it.
...completely destroyed.
No one survived the
bomb's deadly explosion.
The high death toll
makes this the worst disaster
in Galaxy Railways history.
Railways officials
believe that terrorists
are responsible for the
bombings but as of yet,
no one has claimed
responsibility
for either of
the attacks.
One common thread
linking the incidents...
Weapons expert, Doctor
Eugene Talbert is here
to tell us about
the bomb. Doctor?
Yes, it's called a
Dissolving Sub-atomic Bomb.
This is an early
version of the weapon.
It was first used by
the Liberation Army
on Planet Rommel in
the battle for Aldebran.
Since then the bomb has become
much more sophisticated.
By using Feglinole as
the key ingredient
the explosive power of the
bomb has increased ten-fold.
[Layla]
Manabu!
Keep moving forward.
Have faith in your self.
Who was that?
This just in:
one of the passengers on the
Three-twenty-three Express
destroyed while en
route to Great Magellan
in the first
terrorist bombing--
was brought back
to life today
after she was pronounced
clinically dead.
Yuki, the Medical Officer
assigned to Sirius Platoon,
resuscitated the miracle
child, Miss Sarah Aihara.
Her recovery marks
the only hopeful news
in the otherwise tragic
events of recent days.
Captain
Bulge!
Sarah survived
thanks to you...
She has a tough
road ahead of her.
Manabu... Sometimes we
witness horrible things
while doing this job.
It's unavoidable...
There are many times
when we're powerless
to do anything
about it.
When I decide what
action to take
I have to consider the safety
of everyone that's involved...
It's not always
easy to decide...
But I expect my decisions
to be obeyed and honored.
We have to
be a team.
Our wills have to be
as one to survive...
We have to depend on one
another completely...
I was told these same things
years ago by your Father.
Well, maybe they're right, man.
You don't seem like SDF to me.
I don't?
Naa, all those guys
have big egos.
They don't care about
helping people;
they just want to
boss somebody around.
[Buldge] I expect my decisions
to be obeyed and honored.
You want to protect the
Galaxy without firing a shot.
You can gamble your
own life on that ideal
but not the lives of
your platoon members.
Don't let them steal your
dream from you.
Don't let those guys turn
you into one of them...
Captain
Bulge! Wait!
Well, What's on
your mind, Manabu?
I'd like to make
a request...
Can you please end
my suspension, Sir?
Look, I don't know
if I can change...
But you have my
absolute loyalty.
I'll do anything for
you. Please, Captain!
Take me back!
I beg of you!
It's your choice... I've told
you that already, Manabu.
Captain!
Go to the
outfitting room
and get your uniform
on immediately!
All of our space-trains
will be shipping out
as soon as the tune
ups are completed!
Don't be
late, Manabu!
We have some terrorists
that we need to track down!
Yes, Sir!
System Check!
Standby for
system check
Orbit Network
Radar ready!
Sub-atomic Warp
Generator ready!
I am
so Sorry
for all the trouble I've
caused the platoon, you guys!
That was the past.
Take your seat, Manabu.
Right!
Big One is now in
take-off position!
Cylinder Valves are open!
Atomic Boiler Pressure is a go!
The Warp-drive coupling
is now in place!
The Main Circuit
is online!
All energy levels
ready for take-off!
Let's move out!
Ahead full!
Hope you had a nice
vacation...
Maybe now you'll take
this job more seriously.
I've always taken
it seriously.
I'm glad you haven't
lost your winning charm.
There they go,
City of Hope-
our valiant warriors riding
their trains of light
into the
darkness of space.
This next song is for the
men and women of the SDF.
The Fort Worth is
just ahead, Captain.
Point Three
Megameters to go.
Pull up
parallel, Bruce.
Will do,
Captain.
I've informed the
passengers that this is
a precautionary search
and evacuation.
They're ready to make
the transfer, Sir.
Good.
Maintain
current speed;
lower the shield and
connect the Space Walk!
I want all
passengers transferred
to the rear
coach of Big One!
The exterior is clear. There's
no bomb out here, Captain.
All clear on
the interior so far.
We're checking
the lounge now.
What is it? Did
you find something?
I hope not.
Hey,
Kinuko?
Yes,
what's up?
Your son
that you lost;
wasn't he killed in a
Galaxy Railways accident.
Hm? Oh yes,
he was.
Then why do you still cater
to the Galaxy Railways?
Doesn't that
make you mad?
That's a
good question.
I guess because my son loved
the Galaxy Railways so much...
Why the sudden interest?
You never asked before.
Just curious.
That's all.
Hmm.
No!
...Please!
I don't know
your Mother,
but I'll bet she's
one happy lady, Shaw!
How can she not be
with a son like you?!
You know, this rain's
only going to get worse...
Maybe you should close
shop early today
That's not
a bad idea.
Can you come
with me then?
I have a little
favor to ask you.
Halt! This is a
restricted area!
Only authorized personnel
can pass this point!
Stop or we
will fire!
Anything?
Not yet...
Hey!
Huh?
There's no way!
[Announcement] Rigel Platoon
has just finished disposing of
two bombs bombs on the
Five-Seventy-Six Express!
The Three-Eighty-Eight
bound for Perseus
is passing through
the Double Clusters.
Capella Platoon will
intersect in three minutes.
Security breech!
An intruder has entered
the restricted area!
The guard-bots are
not responding!
The intruder is
armed and dangerous!
Huh? Shaw! Someone
broke through security!
I'd be careful!
It could be a terrorist!
This has been a real
eye-opener for me.
Hey, Manabu! Nice work!
...Brilliant really.
Who would have guessed that
the terrorist was a vendor?
Hey, what's
the matter?
Captain... Can we please
go back to headquarters?
What are you
talking about?
...We have more
trains to check!
What's on your mind,
Manabu! Explain yourself!
I think I know
who the bomber is!
I met him when I was suspended.
He hates the SDF... It's him!
If we hadn't
discovered the bombs,
all these trains would have
blown up. Don't you see!?
He knew what Headquarters
would do if that happened!
Dispatch the
entire fleet.
That's what he wanted...
to create a disaster so big
that we were all
sent out at once!
Which means his real
target is Headquarters.
Hmm.
Would he really
attack Headquarters?
Why not? He's definitely
crazy enough to try.
Captain. I say we
head back, Sir.
Let's hope it's
not too late.
Louis! Contact
Headquarters!
Patch me through
to the Commander!
Yes, Sir!
What is it?
All channels are down!
There's no response!
Let's move!
Give our assignments
to the other platoons!
Plot a course
for Headquarters!
[All]
Yes, Sir!
[Shaw] Attention
all SDF Platoons,
yes, this is
Headquarters speaking.
From this
moment on
the operation of all lines
is officially terminated.
We greatly appreciate
your mindless servitude.
Do not return to
Destiny Station
unless you want to
sacrifice your lives
for the Galaxy Railways.
Headquarters out.
Thanks buddy... I really
appreciate the use
of your
com system
Why don't you let the
others go? I'll stay.
Now that would take
all the fun out of it.
Wouldn't it, big man.
This is a company party.
The day
has come...
The darkness has
eclipsed the light.
Just What is it that
you mean to accomplish?
Nothing
really...
Just the destruction
of the Galaxy Railways!
So then
young man...
I see you've come here
just as I expected you to.
What are you
talking about?!
You had no way of knowing I
was coming here! Who are you?!
You look so
full of yourself.
Of course! You're the Supreme
Commander! Aren't you?!
No! Please! I have to stay
on board! Let me stay!
You don't understand!
I have to get to Melder!
Tickets to Planet Melder are
available at the ticket office.
I don't have any money but
I'll pay you back! I swear!
I'm sorry, it's
against the rules.
Please! My mom's
sick! She'll die!
I have to get
to Planet Melder!
The doctor said that's
where the medicine is!
No! Please! Stop!
Halt!
No!! Wait!!
Please!! Stop!
What's wrong with you people?!
Let me get on! Help me!!!
I can feel you
inside my head!
I hope to God that I'm
wrong about you, Shaw!
I don't know what
you are, lady!
But you can't read my
mind if you're dead!
Don't
do it!!
Shaw!
No!
Manabu.
He's by
himself.
Now, now.
Cut me some slack.
Don't give me
that look, man...
I see you're back
in your monkey suit.
Why, Shaw? Why are
you doing this?
Trust me. I have
my reasons, Manabu.
But you're
a good person!
I was. But they
changed that! Heh!
Huh?!
No! Wait!
This is for all the
people you killed!
Stop it!
That's enough!
Hey! Whose side are
you on? Back off!!
Manabu!
Shaw.
Is that all
you got?!
...Come on! Bring it
you SDF freaks!
...Go 'head! Right
there! I dare ya!
You asked for
it, Crazy man!
Huh?!
Silver!
That's an atomic weapon
that he's got on!
If you shoot we're all
history! Understand?
He didn't plan to
leave here alive.
A bomb like that would
level this place.
That's what
he wants.
Had a change of heart?
...All right! I'll do it!
...You guys are more
useless than I thought!
Aim for
his head.
Shaw!
Don't do it!
Manabu! No!
Oh, crap!
No! Get out
of the way!
Shaw! Don't do
this! Please!
Yuuki.
Please, Shaw!
I don't want to
have to use this!
I don't want to have
to hurt you! Please!
Yeah,
right man.
Why, Shaw? Why are
you doing this?
Look at me,
Manabu.
The Galaxy Railways turned
me into what I am today.
They wouldn't let me
take a free ride
to save
my Mother
but they spent hundreds of
thousands giving me this body
after they
ran over mine.
Look. I was just a
boy when they did this.
They don't care
about you, Buddy.
Hmph. They don't
care about anyone.
The Galaxy Railways is a
monster without a heart.
You're wrong.
Your Father and
Brother died for them!
Do you think they care?! And
now you're defending them!
You're the one
who's crazy!
No! ...My Father and my
brother sacrificed their lives
because they believed
in the Galaxy Railways!
Whether the
trains carry hate
or hopes and dreams is up to
us! We're the passengers!
Blowing up those
trains was wrong,
no matter what
the reason.
I'm sorry about what
happened, Shaw!
But the killing
stops here!
I can't let you
hurt anyone else!
I understand your passion,
Manabu. Now understand mine!
If they were all like you I
wouldn't have to do this.
Damn!
Aaaahh!
No!!!
Oh,
Manabu.
Oh, hey,
Kinuko.
I have something
for ya.
For me?
What is it?
I'm not sure. Shaw asked
me to give it to you.
He found it in the
back of his warehouse.
It was the last one... He said
to mind the expiration date.
Three days. That's a lot
of Tabito Tea to drink
in three
days, Shaw.
Why do bad things
happen to good people?
Is it simply
happenstance?
Or are the victims of today
the transgressors of the past?
Are we simply experiencing
what we've caused others
to experience in
lives gone by?
Training under Whitman,
the SDF's Chief mechanic,
is no can of tea.
His love for
trains runs deep;
and since his prized locomotive
is heading for the scrapheap,
he disobeys orders and takes
it out for one last ride.
Usually, I'm the one
breaking the rules!
See ya next time
on the Railways!