[Narr] The Universe, home to
all life in the physical plane.
Man sets sail and
travels this Grand Ocean
fueled by his
hopes and dreams.
But sometimes his
dreams are crushed
and his
anguishing heart
can only see a dark,
cold and lonely place.
What are you doing?
Mamoru!
Catch!
You were all I had! Why did
you have to die? It's not fair!
[Wataru] Mamoru.
I'm not scared.
Not anymore.
[Kanna] Manabu Yuuki, you get
in here right this second!
[Manabu] Mom?
What's wrong?
Don't give me that, Manabu!
You know exactly what's wrong!
I do?
Mom, I really didn't do
anything. Not this time anyway.
Don't lie, Manabu.
But I'm not lying!
This is my rail-pass!
I've been accepted!
Accepted to what?
The SDF cemetery!
What's that, Manabu?
A love letter?
Hey! Who's the
lucky girl?
How could you join the SDF
behind my back, Manabu?
This is unforgivable.
But it's my life.
You mean it's your death.
First your father. Then Mamoru.
And now you expect
me to lose you, too!
Well, I won't let
you go! Never!
Come on, Mom.
No, Manabu.
Absolutely not.
If you insist on joining,
you're no longer my son.
Kanna! Let's not
lose our heads now!
Manabu was accepted.
That doesn't mean he's going.
I don't know.
Manabu's going to come and
work with us in the mine!
Aren't you?
No, I'm not. I'm going into
space, and that's that!
She didn't mean it.
She doesn't want to lose you
too, Manabu. That's all.
Wataru Yuuki.
What should I do?
He's just like you.
He's exactly like you.
Dad.
Please Son, take care
of your mother for me.
She needs you. You're much
stronger than you realize.
Manabu. Take care
of Mom for me, okay?
You can count on me.
Dad, Mamoru, I have
taken care of Mom.
But I have to
follow my heart.
I can't give up my dream.
I have to leave her now.
It's time. Off to
the Grand Ocean.
Goodbye, Mom. I'll be
back as soon as I can.
Bye, Shutaro.
[Kanna] Manabu,
wait a second.
Take this. You're going to
get hungry on the train later.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, too.
Goodbye!
[Announcer] The
space-train on track three
will be departing for
Destiny in two minutes.
Huh? You're kidding me.
Well, I'll be damned.
Now I've seen it all.
Looks like I won't
have to be chasing you
out of here
anymore.
Welcome to the Space
Defense Force, Mr. Yuuki.
Thanks. I
appreciate it.
Bye, Mom!
Don't worry! I'll be back!
[Robot] Welcome aboard
space-train 550
heading for Planet Destiny
through the Altair Nebula.
We will be stopping at Hope
and Zetsubou on the way.
Please note that our route will
be taking us by the time-knot.
We ask that you keep your
windows closed while we pass it
because we will be experiencing
electro-magnetic interference.
Thank you.
I don't even know what
a time-knot is. Do you?
Sure. It's an anomaly with
a different time-axis.
I've heard that a lot of
trains have wrecked there.
Well, that's comforting.
I didn't mean
to scare you.
I'm not scared.
My name's Louis Fort Drake.
You can call me Louis.
What planet are you from?
Don't you shake hands there?
Sorry. I'm Manabu Yuuki.
Manabu, huh?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet
you, too.
Well, it's nice to know
that there's more than one
SDF member on this train.
What do you
mean by that?
I mean that yours truly
is an SDF member, too.
Awesome.
How old are
you anyway?
I'm almost twenty.
You look much
younger than that.
More like a boy
than a man.
Thanks a lot.
It's not an
insult, silly.
It just means that
you'll age gracefully.
Yeah, whatever. How
old are you anyway?
I just turned eighteen.
What?
You're kidding.
Do I look older
or younger?
Older.
Everyone thinks I'm
older than I really am.
I don't understand why.
It's because you're
a know-it-all.
I'm not a
know-it-all!
Look, I was only
trying to help.
Yeah, well just keep your
opinions to yourself!
All right?
You're the one who asked!
What was I supposed to say?
You don't know much about
girls. Do you, Manabu?
I know enough!
We are approaching
the Time-Knot.
Please close the
cabin window.
Close that.
Would ya?
I'm too old and
decrepit to reach.
Excuse me. Will one of you
please just close the window?
What are you doing?
I-I didn't do that on purpose!
Are you out of your mind?
Catch it in the
web, not your palm!
You'll give us away.
Uh-oh.
What's the matter?
[Robot]
Ladies and Gentlemen:
we will be experiencing
a brief delay
due to engine trouble.
Please do not be alarmed.
You are not in danger.
This is a minor problem only.
Yeah, minor my foot. I'm gonna
check out the engine room!
I'm coming too!
Please! Return
to your seats!
Look! We want to
know what's going on!
Our train has derailed! We've
slipped into the Time Knot!
[Sayaka] We have an
accident by the Time-Knot!
It's the
Five-fifty Express!
They're requesting assistance
from the SDF, Commander!
We'll send Big One! Alert the
Sirius Platoon immediately!
[Sayaka] Sirius Platoon
is deploying, Commander!
[Bulge] System check!
[Bruce] Stand by for
System Check!
[David] Orbit Network
Radar ready!
[Kate] Big One is now
in take-off position!
[Bruce] Magnetic Barrier
Generator is a go!
[David] Cylinder
Valves are open!
Atomic Boiler
Pressure is a go!
[Kate] The Main Circuit
is now online!
[Bruce] All energy levels
ready for take-off!
[David] The warp drive
coupling is now in place!
[Kate] All systems
green, Captain Bulge!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
Let's move out!
Ahead full!
He's still alive.
Hey, are you all right?
Can you hear me?
Are you okay, buddy?
Mmm, yeah.
Uh, where are we?
You're on Planet Hakumei.
You're lucky to be alive.
Your train crashed.
[Manabu] No, it can't be.
You're dead.
[Mamoru] You've taken
quite a knock.
I can assure you
I'm not dead.
My name's
Mamoru Yuuki.
I'm here with my SDF unit;
the Space Panzer Grenadiers.
I must be dreaming.
The Space Panzer
Grenadiers? Wow!
That's the most
elite unit
in the Space Defense Force!
That's everyone's dream!
It's an honor to meet you!
My name's Louis.
My friend and I just
joined the SDF.
We were on our way
to headquarters
when our
train crashed.
Huh? Look out!
Get down!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Those vultures!
Attacking civilians!
Does this train have
a Stealth Module?
Y-yes, Sir! Of course!
I'll activate the Optical
Camouflage immediately!
[Mamoru] Good. Now if
you want to save
the passengers
and train,
we'll have to
act as decoys.
It'll be a dangerous
first mission,
but welcome
to the SDF!
Follow me!
Stay low!
Whoever hits them gets
a bonus! SDF swine!
Hold on back
there, guys!
You're not Panzers!
You're chickens!
We're safe now.
At least until morning.
[Manabu] Can you
tell me if we slipped
into a different
time-axis
when we passed through
the time-knot?
[Robot] I believe so.
What year
is it now?
I estimate that it
is five years
before the day
that we took off.
I thought so.
What in the world are
you talking about?
Time shifted. We're
in the past now.
Huh?
If we go back through the
Time Hole before it closes
we should be able
to return to our time.
But our train's wrecked!
Our train
has been sending
a distress signal
since the accident.
If the Time Hole hasn't closed,
a rescue team could find us.
But what would happen
to my brother then?
What do you mean
your brother?
Our friend; the one
who saved us earlier.
He's my
big brother.
He was killed
on this planet
five years ago in
the line of duty.
But if he was killed,
then that means...
That he's going to die soon.
It's unavoidable.
Well If a rescue team comes,
why don't we take him with us?
That would not
be advisable!
Please follow the Galaxy
Railways manual in this matter!
What does it say?
Article 33
paragraph 2 states
that passengers who
have time-slipped
must not intervene in
affairs of the past
or it can permanently
change the future.
Altering your
brother's fate
could have serious
repercussions.
So, how can you
change a man's fate?
You can't!
Under normal circumstances
that would be impossible!
That's for sure.
We never know what life
has in store for us.
If we did, could
we accept it?
We'll have to
move out soon.
Staying in one place
too long is dangerous.
Who are these guys?
They're space-pirates.
They're leader is Guy Sander.
Where's the rest
of your platoon?
They're guarding
our base here.
We're planning
on launching
an all-out attack
at the crack of dawn.
They know that.
The enemy, they know.
What?
They know you're coming.
They found out somehow.
They're planning to
set a trap for you.
That can't be.
Yes it can! You're all
going to die! They know!
I don't believe you.
You have to! I'm your brother!
Now I know you're lying.
I do have a brother,
but I'm five years
older than he is.
I know we look
the same age.
But that's because I
came from the future.
It's me.
I'm Manabu.
Is it
really you?
It... it is
you. Manabu.
This is crazy! Meeting my
little brother all grown up,
it's like an
incredible dream.
You look great.
How's Mom doing? Is she okay?
Yeah, she's pretty good.
I can't believe she
let you join the SDF.
That must have
been really tough.
It was.
Don't I know?
Look. Mamoru. Come with us.
Just leave this place.
I would. But it's
just not possible.
Why not?
You can't interfere
with the past, Manabu.
It's against
the rules.
Who cares?
I care, Manabu. I
care about the future.
Besides, I have no
intention of dying.
Maybe your warning will
make a difference tomorrow.
I'm a Space Panzer
Grenadier, Manabu.
When the enemy's
at the front door,
I can't slip out
the back door and run.
Dad taught me an
important lesson
all those years
ago on Big One.
He taught me the meaning
of duty, little brother.
[Robot] I estimate
that Sirius Platoon
will be
arriving soon.
[Mamoru] Sirius Platoon.
That means that Captain
Bulge is coming!
Great! We should
be fine then!
You know this
Captain Bulge?
Yeah. You do, too.
He was Dad's first officer.
He gave us Dad's
gun remember?
Dad handpicked Bulge.
He trained him personally.
He's the best
captain in the force.
Awesome.
Hold on,
guys!
Manabu, I need
your help.
They're right behind us.
Here. Take it.
A gun against a
tank! Dream on!
Go! Now! I'll take
it from here!
Get back to the five-fifty
and wait for Big One!
What about you?
Manabu.
[Train whistle]
It's time, Manabu!
Get back to the five-fifty!
Louis!
Let's go!
Pull her up a
little closer.
Looks like we've got
ourselves a Panzer Grenadier!
This time
he's mine!
Split-finger
fastball!
The Five-fifty Express
is 70 meters dead ahead!
I am deactivating the
Optical Camouflage now!
Please! Get on
board immediately!
[Louis] Manabu!
What are you doing?
[Manabu]
Mamoru! Run!
Scum! Nobody makes me bleed!
Open fire! Get him!
Manabu! Get
on that train!
Space Panzer Grenadiers, this
is Mamoru. Launch an attack.
Big One is attempting a rescue
operation and needs support.
We copy, Mamoru!
Stand by!
Slow reverse.
Let's hook her up.
Yes, Captain.
We have her, Captain Bulge. The
hitch is connected and locked.
Let's take the
Five-fifty up slow.
We don't want her
to break apart.
Right, Sir!
Let's move out!
Ahead slow!
[Train whistle]
Hey, Manabu!
This is for you!
Mamoru!
Hmm?
Keep working on that
fastball, Brother!
Mamoru, no!
Get on the train!
Not this time.
It's my destiny to stay
on this planet and fight.
I don't
plan to die,
but if I do the Yuuki's
will still live on.
Do you hear me? We
live in you, Manabu!
No! Mamoru!
Behind you! Look out!
Mamoru.
No.
Mamoru!
Stay back!
Let go of me! I can't let him
die alone! Let go! Mamoru!
Damn it. I couldn't change it.
Destiny... Why are you so cruel?
So indifferent?
So this is it.
I prayed that I wouldn't
have to die alone.
I still remember
Dad's face.
But I think I
understand now.
It's not about me.
It's about you.
You're the one,
Manabu. Huh?
Mom.
Manabu.
Who would
have thought?
It's okay. I'm not alone.
I have my family.
At times, fate can
seem cruel and arbitrary
but no life lived
for others is a waste.
No sacrifice is in vain.
Everydrop of water has
its place in the ocean.
Every life is a part of
Destiny's grand design.
Manabu, that woman's
name is Layla Destiny.
She's the supreme commander.
Wow! Awesome!
Cadets! Salute your
supreme commander!
Welcome to the
Space Defense Force.
You are no longer individuals,
but part of a team,
working together to ensure
safety of our galaxy
and the citizens within it.
May all that is good protect you
and guide you on your journey.
Dad. Mamoru. I'm here.
Thanks to both of you
I finally made it.
Huh? Is she looking at me?
She is. She is
looking right at me.
But why?
Manabu, you've come at last.
I've been waiting for you.
When I'm assigned to
my dad's old platoon,
it's a dream come true on
the next Galaxy Railways
but it's far from the heart-
warming experience I expected.
It seems like everyone
is out to get me.
If this is how they
treat their friends,
I'd hate to be their enemy.
See ya next time
on the Railways.