[Narr] A long time ago a war
broke out on a faraway planet,
and a black train appeared
and picked up the deceased.
It is said that the
same train appeared
after the big accident
on Orion Line
and then, again, during the
plague on Planet Kayazen.
The reports concerning
these last two incidents
are similar
to the first.
A jet-black train appeared out
of nowhere to pick up the dead.
Where did it take
them? Nobody knows.
Hey, Terry!
Your camera!
Terry!
Wait up!
What's wrong with you? Stop
acting like you don't hear me!
I'm your sister,
Terry, come on!
No, please.
Don't do this.
Karen's gone.
You have to let go.
There's no such thing
as a ghost-train!
It's not
going to come!
Yes it will. I have
to see Karen again.
Even if it's
just a glimpse.
Now go! Leave
me alone, Jane!
No! You can't
make me!
If you're staying I'm
staying and that's final!
Whatever.
Suit yourself.
I can't believe that you're
leaving your camera behind.
Photography
is your life.
It's your dream
to become famous
and make people happy
with your pictures.
How can you leave
your dream?
You're not coming
back! Are you?
I don't plan
to die, Jane.
I think there's a good chance
that I can see Karen tonight,
and that means more
than anything to me.
Look at this.
There's a planet
called Meridies
that orbits two suns,
in a figure eight.
Because of its orbit, nighttime
there lasts only 10 minutes.
Well, one researcher
finally connected the dots
and realized that that's
when the ghost-train appears,
during those
10 minutes.
Now, he's either
right or he's crazy,
but I have to find
out which one.
[Jane] Look!
What's happening?
[Terry] I don't know!
[Jane] This is wrong!
This station's closed!
No trains ever
come here!
That's it!
I'm scared.
No! What are you doing?
Get away from there!
It might not
bring you back!
Terry, no! Get out of
there, Terry! Jump! Jump!
Terry.
Please come back.
[Kate] Did you guys hear
that the Ghost Train
appeared again
on Orion Line?
[Sayaka] What do you mean?
What ghost-train?
[Miki] You've never heard
of the Ghost Train?
It takes souls to
the nether world.
[Kate] Once you're on,
there's no going back.
The conductor looks
like a cadaver.
He pulls up to the platform
and waves his hand:
--All aboard! All aboard!
What's got you
so worked up?
What? You don't really
believe that nonsense, do you?
No. Of course not. I'm just
telling you what I heard.
Come on, Manabu.
Fess up.
That story got under your skin.
You believe it, don't you?
Well, what
if I do?
You don't know everything
about the nether world.
It could
be possible.
I don't believe it! Manabu
Yuuki believes in ghosts!
Man, that's what I
get for being honest.
[Announcer] Attention,
Sirius Platoon:
please report to the
Briefing Room immediately.
--Sirius Platoon: please...
[Louis] --Duty calls!
[Manabu] Yeah.
Gotta go!
Wait! I'm
coming, too!
You're late!
Sorry, Sir!
The train in question must
be a one-thirty-eight model
because the witness said
that it has double headlights.
But as most
of you know,
the one-thirty-eight
was discontinued
during the
development phase
of the Galaxy Railways
many years ago.
The missing person is a 24 year
old male named Terry Goldman.
He was last seen boarding
the train three months ago
at a closed-down station
on the old Alpha Centauri Line.
Our mission is
to find Terry
and to figure out who's
operating this mysterious train.
Are there
any questions?
What's this
all about?
Weren't you listening?
It's about the Ghost Train.
Has the train been sighted
anywhere else, Captain?
The report mentions
two other appearances.
One was on
the Orion Line.
The other was on the
Aldebaran Loop.
Why has this case been left
alone for three months?
The train
only appears
when Planet Meridies
experiences nightfall.
That only happens
once every three months.
See that! My lucky coin
says it's a Ghost Train!
So who's
our witness?
Jane Goldman; a 19
year old female.
She's the missing
person's younger sister.
She's the
only witness?
Correct.
Oh, great.
Just what we need.
What do you mean
by that, Bruce?
She probably killed him
and made up that story.
Manabu, you don't believe
that a Ghost Train
took him away,
do you?
Well, yeah.
Now why does that not
surprise me, Yuuki?
All right, Sirius Platoon!
Let's move out!
--Yes, Sir!
Manabu!
Don't be late again.
Understood?
Yes, Captain.
Well, what are
you waiting for?
[Crewmen]
System check!
Stand by for
System Check!
Magnetic Barrier
Generator is a go!
Big One is now in
take-off position!
Cylinder valves open!
Boiler pressure ready!
The Main Circuit
is now online!
All energy levels are
ready for take-off!
The warp drive coupling
is now in place!
All systems green,
Captain Bulge!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
Let's move out!
Ahead full!
Was that the Ghost
Train that I saw?
No! That's
impossible!
Manabu?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. But next
time, put your own tray away!
You made me late!
What? Bologna! I did
put my tray away!
Oh, maybe
I didn't.
I'm sure it's in
there somewhere.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing!
Not even a ghost would want
to hang out in this dump.
We're probably the first
train to use this station
in well over
20 years.
Except for the "you know what"
which should be joining us
in 5 minutes
and 11 seconds.
Now how'd you
figure that out?
I charted Meridies' orbit on the
computer and extrapolated a bit.
We can bet on
it if you like.
No thanks. You
cleaned me out
on the last three
calculations we wagered on.
These must be Terry
and Jane's footprints.
I wonder if we can figure out
where Terry's prints end.
Manabu, what's that,
over there?
I guess one of
them drew this.
That's the symbol
for infinity, isn't it?
Yeah. But what do those two dots
in the middle stand for?
[Jane] Those are the
Suns of Meridies.
You're Jane
Goldman.
I recognize you from the
SDF report. My name's Louis.
Can you tell
us anything
about why your brother
got on the Ghost Train?
Yes.
[Manabu] Louis, look!
Check this out!
[Jane] That's the same
thing that happened
the night the Ghost
Train was here!
Oh, no! It's coming in too fast!
It's going to ram Big One!
This isn't
Big One.
Stop her, men!
She could die!
Jane!
Don't do it!
No! Terry's
in there!
Manabu!
Yuuki! Get off
that train!
Louis!
Manabu! No!
I.. I don't
believe it.
Louis. You're
squishing me.
[Louis] How dare
you, Manabu!
Are you saying that
I'm fat? [Smack!]
Man! You're
vicious.
Hmm! That
was nothing!
Not so close!
I haven't forgiven you yet!
You hit me!
[Conductor] Tickets!
[Louis] It's all so real. How
can this be a Ghost Train?
Excuse me, Ma'am. Do you know
where this train is heading?
Oh, well this train
doesn't have a destination.
We're bound
for nowhere.
We're the ones who
choose when to get off.
Or we can stay on
forever if we'd like.
Where are you
two getting off?
We're just
enjoying the ride.
No bills, no jobs, no
clocks, just each other.
It's like a
long vacation.
Excuse me, Sir.
Have you seen this man?
He boarded three
months ago.
Good grief. That
hair; those clothes.
He looks like a hippy
if I ever saw one.
You won't find
him on this coach.
[Conductor] Good
evening, passengers.
Our next stop is
Hazama Station.
Louis, let's go up to the
Conductor's Cabin.
Our total stop time will be
18 minutes and 30 seconds.
[Manabu] Uhh,
excuse me.
I don't have time
for tourists.
This train doesn't
fly itself you know.
SDF. My name's Manabu Yuuki,
and this is Louis Fort Drake.
Can you tell me this
train's ID Number please?
This train doesn't
have an ID Number.
Where's it going?
Well, our next stop
is Hazama Station.
I don't care what
our next stop is!
What's our final
destination?
This train has no
destination.
How can a train have
no destination?
That question is beyond
my understanding.
That question isn't even beyond
a 3 year old's understanding.
You're just being
uncooperative.
Come on, Manabu. We're
wasting our time here.
Karen,
it's me!
I know you're here!
Why won't you talk to me?
Would you care for some
coffee? It's nice and hot.
Yeah.
Huh?
You shouldn't be here.
Why have you come?
Because you're everything
to me, Karen. That's why.
I don't belong to your
world anymore, Terry.
You're going to
have to accept that.
I love you, Karen.
That's all I know.
I had to see you again
no matter what.
Please. You don't belong here.
It's not your time yet.
You're still
alive, Terry.
I'm alive because I'm
here with you, Karen.
That's all that matters to me.
I've missed you so much. You
don't know how hard it's been.
We didn't even have
a chance to say goodbye.
I keep seeing the
accident in my head,
but I'm powerless
to change it.
[Karen] Where should I
stand? Over there?
[Terry] Sure!
Karen!
Sneak!
That's good
for now!
One more.
All right.
Back up.
How far?
I don't know.
Just tell me
when to stop.
Perfect!
Karen!!!
Tough day.
There was something I
was going to ask you.
But then the
accident happened.
Will you marry
me, Karen?
Here. I'll put it on.
What's the matter?
I can't lose you
again, Karen.
Please. Don't ever leave me.
Stay with me forever.
I knew staying on this train
was my only chance to see you.
But when you got on I
was scared to face you.
I've been hiding from
you, Terry. Forgive me.
It's okay.
Everything's fine now.
[Manabu] Excuse me. Are
you Terry Goldman?
[Louis] We're with the
Space Defense Force.
Your sister filed a
missing persons report.
We were sent
to find you.
Well, you found me.
Tell Jane not to worry.
Hey, you two are
alive, aren't you?
You don't belong here! This
train is only for the dead!
Then what are you doing here,
Terry? You're still alive!
But you won't
be for long!
If you decide to stay
with her you'll die!
[Manabu] Huh?
They're gone!
Come in Big One. This is Louis.
Repeat: Come in, Big One.
We've found Terry Goldman,
Captain. Mine's not working.
Big One. Come in.
Wait a second!
What is it?
Time! It stopped!
[Bruce] He just
joined the platoon
and we're already chasing
him through the cosmos.
Captain!
Should we check with the
Network Radar at headquarters?
Forget about
the radar!
Patch me through to
the Supreme Commander!
Yes, Sir!
Yes, Captain Bulge. This is
about Manabu, isn't it?
Yes. Actually, Louis
is with him as well.
We're trying to contact them,
but we can't get a reply.
That's no ordinary train
that they're on, Captain.
Its name is Eternity;
it connects the physical
plane with the next realm.
You won't find its course
on any timetable or diagram.
I'm afraid there's
no way to stop it.
But, we have to
get them back.
They chose to board that
train of their own free will.
Let Fate take
its course.
I can't!
I have to try!
Do as your heart
tells you to, Captain.
Your actions can
make a difference.
Captain! We're getting a
signal on the Orbit Radar!
Chart it on the main
holograph, David.
[Bulge] There it is.
We found it.
[David] It's gone
again, Captain!
Damn!
Hey, Jane. Try not
to worry too much.
Captain Bulge will
find your brother.
I know
he will.
Based on their last position
they should be just ahead.
Steady as she
goes, David.
Will do, Captain.
Hey, uh... Yo, Bruce.
I'll bet you a thousand ables
that we make it back home.
That's a sucker bet. If we make
it home you get a thousand.
If we don't
we're both dead.
It was worth
a shot.
I don't
believe it!
We found
it, Captain!
This may be our only chance!
Maximum power! Don't lose it!
Yes, Sir!
[Bruce] What's happening?
[David] We're hitting some
sort of energy field!
It's draining our power!
[Terry] This is it!
Are you ready?
Yes.
Huh? Uh, excuse me there, folks.
What is this place?
It's Hazama Station. This is
where we get off, young man.
You, too?
Yes, Sir. My mother's
here to pick me up. See?
Manabu, what
are you doing?
I'm just
looking!
There's no
time for that!
We need to find Terry
or we'll lose him!
Right!
[Karen] Once you pass
through this gate
you can never return
to your world.
I know. I don't care.
You are my world, Karen.
Oh, Terry.
Terry!
Stop!
Just mind your
own business!
[Manabu] Look, I
know how you feel!
I lost my father
and my brother!
But this isn't right!
It's not your time yet!
You have to live on!
You can't just give up and die!
[Louis] Please! Think about
your sister, Terry!
She loves you!
She still needs you!
Talk to her for me. Tell her
I died with my dream in my arms.
[Louis] No!
Don't be a fool!
Stop! You don't know
anything about us!
Terry and I
love each other!
Let go! You're
hurting me!
Yes, you're feeling
weak, aren't you?
We're on the threshold
of my world now!
If I don't let
go you'll die!
No!
Stop it!
Leave us! If you don't
I'll have to kill you!
Manabu! Louis! Are
you two all right?
Terry! It's you!
You're alive!
I was so worried! I never
thought I'd see you again!
Thank goodness you're all right!
I thought you were dead!
Why did you get
on that train?
Did you ever think how
that would make Mom feel?
Do you know how hurt we were
when we thought we lost you?
I'm sorry, Jane. I
have to be going now.
What do
you mean?
I'm going to be with Karen.
It's what we both want.
No! You can't!
Karen, I'm so sorry
about the accident.
We've missed
you so much.
Please, don't
take him, Karen.
What about his dream
of being a photographer?
Isn't that a dream
worth living for?
Karen, wait!
What's wrong?
Thank you for coming
this far to see me, Terry.
You don't know how
much that means to me.
Karen.
And thank you for the ring,
Terry. It's so beautiful.
It's all I need to
remember you by.
But aren't we...
Going to be together?
Of course. Always.
Nothing can keep us apart, not
even the distance between us.
Karen?
No! Wait!
It's not our time yet,
Terry! I want you to live!
Realize your
dream for me!
No! I want to
come with you!
Be strong,
Terry!
We'll have our wedding when
we meet again! I love you!
Karen!
[Narr] In this life,
people are brought together
and pulled apart again
as sure as the tide rises
and goes back out to sea.
What can man learn
from this endless
coming together and
being torn asunder?
What else, but to
overcome his grief
and to expand his love beyond
the bounds of space and time.
I don't know how
to repay you all.
Terry's been a new
man since his return.
He's been traveling
all over the continent.
Every time I hear from him
he seems more like his old self.
He's taken up
photography again
and he's been sending me
some stunning pictures.
Manabu, Louis, you gave
me back my brother,
and I thank you, and the
rest of Sirius Platoon,
from the bottom
of my heart.
I hope this message
finds you well. See ya.
Do you believe in fate, Louis?
That we can't control it.
I don't know.
I'm not really sure.
But I did see a guy jump
on a train one time
and change a man's
fate forever.
[Beep, beep, beep...]
On the next
Galaxy Railways,
we're sent to investigate an
accident on Planet Leo Glando.
But when
things go wrong
our Platoon is ordered
to destroy Big One,
and by chance I
have to confront
the man who killed
my brother.
Or is there such thing as
chance? I'm starting to wonder.
See you next time
on the Railways.