Harga Lou... a planet
where normal tourism
is virtually
non-existent;
the result of constant
extreme winter weather.
However, somewhere
on this frigid planet,
the most beautiful jewel
in the universe exists.
For that
reason alone,
many treasure hunters have
traveled to Harga Lou
in the hopes of finding
this fabled, precious jewel.
But to this day,
none of these seekers
have ever made it
back from alive.
[Louis] Captain, we've
just received word
that a small
spacecraft has crashed
ten kilometers from
the station on Harga Lou.
Affirmative. Let's
head that way.
[Woman] Who are you?!
What do you want?!
Miss, are you all right?
Miss, can you hear me?
Irene? I don't
believe it.
Where am I?
You're
safe now.
An SDF search party found
you unconscious in the snow.
You suffered superficial
wounds but you'll be all right.
So don't
worry.
Well, it's has been
a while, Irene.
It can't
be...
Hey, Are
you alright?
Now let me guess...
you came here
looking for
treasure?
Beautiful... You haven't
changed one bit...
I knew one day
we'd meet again.
The official account is
that they got into trouble
while attempting a
landing and crashed...
Fortunately, the flight
recorder managed to document
the events leading
up to the incident.
Look! There's
something there!
Would you rewind
the tape...?
There, see!?
The people here have stuck with
old-fashioned ways of life.
That could be
a local guard.
Because of all the ancient
monuments found here,
Harga Lou has been
categorized as a
Class One Historical
Sanctuary
by Galaxy Railways
Headquarters.
But most of the
people who visit
come for a
different reason.
[Louis] Isn't a treasure
supposed to be hidden here?
That's right.
The most beautiful
jewel in the universe-
the Blue Flame
of Isperil.
Most scholars agree that
it's buried in a ravine here
known as the
Caldron of Annuve.
The Blue Flame
of Isperil?
Legend has it that
whoever possesses the gem
will have eternal beauty.
It's all nonsense.
Where do you think
you're going?
It's okay, Bruce.
Just let him be.
We can't let her go because
she's under investigation.
Once we drop her off at
headquarters, he'll be fine.
Taking off so soon?
It's been seven years
and you're leaving without
even saying good-bye?
Let go of me! Just who
do you think you are?!
You mean you don't remember?
Now, isn't that a pity.
Well perhaps
you'll remember
the one million Ables
you stole from me?
That rang a
bell, didn't it?
David, forgive me!
I'm so sorry.
I never meant to hurt
you... But you knew that.
There hasn't been a
day that's gone by
that I haven't thought about
you. Oh David, I do love you.
It's just
that I- I...
I need
your gun!
Thanks! Look, it'll never
work out between us,
trust me! But I guess
you knew that too.
Goodbye
David.
You let her
get away?
Don't tell me you're
still not over her yet.
She dodged me
for seven years;
You don't think I'd
let her get away
as easily as
that, do you?
So, What d'ya say we bet on
it Bruce? One million Ables;
if I can get Irene
back in one piece.
I'm no fool! She might
get shot before then!
That knight must be the
guardian of the jewel.
Help me! Please,
somebody... help me!
Open the door!
Please! Hurry!
Please
let me in!
Thanks, mister.
You saved my life...
All right, treasure hunter-
if you want to live
then I suggest you stay
quiet and come with me.
uh... No thanks I do
just fine on my own...
Don't take this
personally, old man.
[Manabu] So what's up with you
and this Irene lady, David?
[David] That's none of
your business, Manabu.
Her name's Irene Summer and
she's under investigation.
That's all you
need to know.
[Bruce] And she left
David seven years ago
and took a million of
his Ables with her.
Now that's what I call
a talented woman!
I can't wait to meet her! So
was it love at first sight?
How did you
two meet?!
Stop it, Louis!
Oh, don't
worry about it.
I don't want David to go
over all the gory details.
Although, I'm sure it must
have been very painful.
You know, I envy you for having
such a thrilling romance!
How
awesome!
[Bruce] Aw! Go
ahead, David!
Tell Louis the
whole story! Why not?
[David] Oh, cut me
a break, will ya?
[Louis] I get it now! David's
shy! I would've never guessed!
You're home
early tonight.
How did the hunting
go, Lady Morgana?
It was a waste of
time! Just four rats!
Not even enough to
feed the Macha Ravens!
[Louis] What a
magnificent castle.
I wonder who
lives here.
[Manabu]
I don't know,
but it's awfully late to be
knocking, isn't it?
[Bruce] How do you
know she's in here?
The signal stopped.
[David] This is the
only place around.
The castle is closed
come back in the morning!
An aircraft went
down near here.
We think one of the
survivors might be inside.
My name is Kenderick, the chief
knight of Gusfantail Castle...
Perhaps it would be better
if you spoke to Lady Morgana
regarding
this matter.
Come this way.
Please
wait here.
[Filidh] Poor,
unfortunate travelers.
So many come to seek,
but none ever leave.
The Blue Flame of
Isperil is cursed.
Put it on, and you
end up being its slave.
So you- who go to- the
jewel- will be ruled-
by the Blue, Blue
Flame of Isperil.
You who sail among the stars;
welcome to my humble castle.
How do you feel now,
treasure hunter?
Was it worth coming all the way
out here for the Blue Flame...?
All of your shipmates
are dead by now...
The Macha Ravens
are feasting
on their lifeless carcasses
even as we speak.
Should I kill you now...?
Or should I let you go free?
I take no pleasure in
killing beautiful women.
I despise the greed in your
heart that brought you here
but... I admire
your bravery.
So what do I owe
you for my freedom?
You owe me nothing. If you
really want the Blue Flame,
make your way to the
Caldron of Annuve...
Follow this hallway and it
will lead you to what you seek.
So this Irene- the woman
who survived the crash-
she's the one
you're looking for?
That's right.
It would appear that Irene
was chased to your castle
by some men
on horseback.
That's what we're
guessing in any case,
judging by the tracks that
we followed in the snow.
We were also following her
with this tracking device.
But we lost the signal when
we got close to your castle.
This is the only place that
she could've found refuge.
Well it's obvious that
your device is broken.
Now if you'll excuse
me, it's getting late.
[Manabu]
Bruce! Look!
It's working...
So she is in here!
[David] And she's
on the move!
It's a trap!
I don't trust
that guy.
I wonder if the jewel's
really down here.
Stop it,
Morgana!
I don't want to
kill anyone anymore!
Tie me up before it's too
late! No! Just kill me!
Lady Morgana it doesn't
have to end that way.
There must be something we
can do to lift the curse.
There has
to be!
Change my
fate...? But how?
The way I see it, you're merely
a prisoner of the jewel...
So it stands to reason
the curse will be lifted
if we find a new soul
to take your place.
But I can't
do that!
You know what will happen to
me if I give up this necklace!
If only it didn't transform
me into the Black Knight
and cause so
much death...
But my lady, you
know as well as I do
that there's
no other way.
Now you must hurry
Lady Morgana.
Go to the
forbidden altar
at the bottom of the
Caldron of Annuve.
That doesn't look
too inviting.
Wait my friend... You seek
the Caldron of Annuve,
do you not?
Listen! I'm just looking
for a friend of mine.
I don't care about
your precious jewel.
I see. But I believe
your friend does
so you should
know this.
The Blue Flame has
a curse on it...
There is a heavy price
to use its power.
It will possess you; and
it will own your soul.
Fancy meeting
you here.
David!
And you thought you'd
gotten rid of me back there.
I guess I should've tried a
little harder. Goodbye David.
Irene?
No way!
Where are we...? It's like
we're in another world.
Castles don't
just disappear.
The communicator's out.
One thing's certain,
this isn't right.
Who cares? I just wanna
find the Blue Flame
and get the hell
out of here.
This thing's
rock solid.
Great! David's locator signal
just dropped off of the grid.
Maybe we should
contact the Captain.
I just tried to
open up a channel.
There must
be something
interfering with
our communicators.
What's
that...?
That's it! The Blue
Flame of Isperil...
I think we must be witnessing
a scene from the past.
Irene! Are
you crazy?!
It's
beautiful.
Get out of
the way!
David!
What did we do?! Why are
you trying to kill us?!
Why do you torment me?
Don't you understand?!
I'm a slave
to the jewel!
I can't hold this sword
back any longer! Go! Now!
No way! I came here
to get that jewel
and I'm not
leaving without it!
I said go! Hurry!
Don't do it! Don't
put the necklace on!
Irene! What good
is eternal life
if it means you end
up living like that?
Just leave
it and go!
The jewel's mine; and don't
you try to stop me, David!
It's already got
you! I can tell!
No you're
wrong!
Don't you- dare to go- to the
blue, blue Flame of Isperil!
Thank you for
everything...
Somehow your love
for one another
overcame the curse
of the Blue Flame.
Goodbye... My thoughts
will be with you always.
They just
disappeared...
David, about the money
I took from you-
Ah forget it. Just
consider it a loan.
Goodness. I think you're
getting soft in your old age.
[Bruce] Can anyone tell me
what that was all about?
[David] It's a
long story...
Oh, well. At least
you're still alive.
Yeah...
If Gusfantail Castle
wasn't real, what was it?
I don't know for sure but
maybe it was the desires
of two souls who
finally realized
that this isn't what
they wanted after all.
[Bruce] Heh! Spoken like a
true pony-tailed hippy!
The Blue Flame of Isperil
has been put to rest for now.
But until man can
conquer his desires,
there will
always be greed.
For that
reason someday,
someone might try to
awaken the legend.
from its sleep.
We were able to rescue
the sole survivor
of the downed aircraft
without incident...
That's your
official report?
That's exactly how it
went down, Captain.
I see. Now prepare
Big 1 for take-off!
[All]
Yes sir!
Yuki. Have you seen
Irene anywhere?
Irene's already
gone, David...
She left
this for you.
Sorry David... I just
didn't have enough courage
to say good-bye,
face-to-face.
But I promise, I'll
come to see you again.
Know this: you mean
the world to me!
Love,
Irene.
[David] One
Thousand Ables...?
Only nine hundred
ninety-nine thousand to go.
I hope it's sooner than
seven years next time, Irene.
[Bruce] Manabu and many
others are nearly killed
when an intruder infiltrates
SDF Headquarters
and starts
reeking havoc.
But as we try to
hunt the alien down
some old demons
start hunting me!
Am I really
Toxic Bruce...?
See ya next time
on the Railways!