[Commander] All SDF
platoons and battalions
initiate First Class
Emergency Alert!
Repeat: initiate First
Class Emergency Alert.
[Kate] Yes, Sir!
Declaring state of First
Class Emergency Alert!
All active-duty SDF
troops have been notified!
[Member A] Division
#25 reporting in...
The SDF Main Gate
is now shut down!
[Sayaka]
Ten-Four...
[Member B] Gate #34
closed and secure!
[Brad]
Ten-Four...
What in tarnation's
going on now?
[Franz] Commander! The Main
Entrance has been closed!
[Commander] Good.
[Miki] Sensors indicate the
intruder is heading toward
Block N
right now!
Yuuki,
let's go!
[Narrator] While working
to protect law and order,
many dangerous
situations arise.
Often times, one
individual will die
while the one standing
next to him will be spared.
But these survivors are
usually not branded as lucky.
On the
contrary,
they are usually avoided
by their peers in battle
because they are seen
as emissaries of Death.
[Sayaka] Commander, the
intruder is now passing
through
Block 2!
I want that block locked
down now immediately!
Owen!
No... It can't... It
can't be! It's impossible!
Manabu...
MANABU!!!!
[Yuki] His vital
signs are stable...
average pulse
rate 68...
I'm going to need 2 more
units of blood here!
Manabu?
Is it happening again?
[Yuki] I need
more Zinine!
[Male Member] Hurry
up with that blood!
Damn. Right in our
own headquarters.
Manabu...
Yuuki!!
Manabu?!
Did we... did
we get him?
Please don't try
to talk now.
Yuki... How's
he doing?
His injuries are severe, but
he's doing much better now.
Very good.
Captain, what
about the intruder?
He's still
on the loose.
But I don't want you
worrying about that.
Just get better... Bruce,
David, Louis; you're done here.
Rejoin
the search.
[All]
Yes sir!
Captain... I'm
coming too!
You're not
well enough!
You heard her! You
should stay put!
Bruce?
Yuki! Keep an
eye on him!
Right.
I will.
It's just a scratch;
I'll be fine!
Lay down!
Let's go.
Yes, Sir.
The intruder's been found.
Three crewmen are down.
Send backup
at once!
Yes sir!
Cease fire!
Did we get'm?
Can't
tell...
Communication from the backup
troops has been cut off.
I understand.
The lives of many
dedicated people
are being
needlessly destroyed.
The younger generation must
take-over where they left off.
Don't let their
deaths be in vain.
Why? Lately I
thought that Bruce
had really started
to believe in me.
Don't worry about it;
I'm sure that he does.
It has to do with
Owen, not you.
Damn... guess
I screwed up.
Owen!
It's not
your fault...
I let my guard down,
Bruce... I knew better.
Try not to talk!
Yuki's on the way!
I'm all right.
I told you... I'm
immortal partner.
Stop
talking!
You just wait...
I'll prove that you're not
Toxic Bruce... anymore. Okay?
Owen... Owen!?
Don't quit on me now!
OWEN!!!
I remember him saying
at the time it happened:
It's like Death just
keeps hovering around me.
Since Owen died, Bruce has
been trying to get assignments
that don't
require a partner.
He's afraid that
working along side him
will result in someone
getting killed.
And now that you've come along,
I can tell Bruce is worried.
He's afraid that Death
is out to get you...
That's why he's
acting this way.
I see.
You should
stay put!
Manabu...?
Sit down.
Don't you understand
Yuki; I've got to go.
If that's what
Bruce is afraid of,
then I need to set
the record straight.
All this stuff
about Toxic Bruce
is a bunch
of bull-
it's nothing but
pure coincidence!
And I'm going to prove
it to him finally!
I have to!
This is Special Intelligence
Unit Eight-Three.
I have obtained the
classified information.
I should be at the rendezvous
point in ten minutes.
Someone's accessed the
Communication Terminal
on Dock 5!
Shut it down!
Yes sir!
Get some men
over there!
This might be the
best chance we get!
Yes, Sir!
All available
combat personnel!
Proceed to
Maintenance Dock 5!
Bruce here, I'm in
position on Dock 5.
Ten-four.
Be careful.
Roger that.
I'm at the terminal
on Dock 5.
No, negative. There's no sign
of the intruder. All clear.
[Buldge] Affirmative;
don't let your guard down.
I'm sending David and Louis
to back you up. Be careful.
Roger!
Bruce.
Bruce!!
Gas grenades?
Don't
breathe!
Sensors detecting
presence of gas on Dock 5!
You're right! I
think its Nerve Gas!
Anyone below ground
is in danger!
Close Block 3!! All
personnel underground
must wear a gas
mask or a helmet!
Closing Partition
Walls in Block 3!
Opening vents!
Who's
there?!
Bruce! Here! I
brought this for you!
Why did you come here?!
I told you not to!!
[Buldge] David! David!?
Can you hear me?!
What's up?
Yuuki's
out here!
Manabu?!
Let's go!
What do you think you're
doing out here, Yuuki?
I came out here to
help you, Bruce.
That's what partners
do. Did you forget?
You've got
to go back!
I won't do it! I'm
going with you.
I said stay
away from me!
Why Bruce?
I'm cursed... It's dangerous
to be with me. I'm bad luck.
Aw, come on! You're just
being superstitious!
You're wrong!
Whoever becomes my partner
always gets killed...
It's my fate!
You understand?!
I don't believe that. I'll
prove that you're wrong!
Bruce!! Manabu,
what are you doing?
Manabu? Sure
you're up to this?
Just take him back
to the Medical Bay.
Stop it!
You can't tell
me what to do!
Manabu!
No! Let go of me! I'm not
going back! Bruce, wait!
I'm not willing to put an
injured person in harm's way!
And that's final!
Bruce! No!
Just let me go!
Manabu, listen to me. You've
heard about Toxic Bruce?
His partners
all end up dead?
It's not you.
I know. But still, I want
to go with him. I have to!
I won't try to stop you.
Just be careful. Huh?
I will...
Don't you dare
get killed.
Manabu.
Louis! Come on!
We'll go this way!
Right!
I wondered how
long it'd be,
'til that gas started
to affect me.
Tell me where the intruder
is! I need answers!
We think that he's trying to
move from the Maintenance Deck
to Block B,
Commander!
Then why haven't we closed
Hatch Twenty-Eight in Block B?!
Closing Hatch
Twenty-eight now!
Status
update!
Maintenance Division
Twenty-Five is reporting
Five missing and
three injured!
Five percent of all SDF
members have been injured;
many in serious
condition.
Intruder confirmed
in Block B!
This is Julia
reporting!
Motion sensors indicate
that the intruder is moving
from Area Nine
to Area Eight!
Attention, Sirius
Platoon! David! Louis!
Go with Bruce to
Area Eight at once!
[All]
Yes sir.
Bruce? Bruce, do you copy?!
Bruce, please report!
Go on. We'll keep you
updated, Schwanheld.
Thanks.
Freeze!
Now! Stay where you are!
You move and you're dead!
Tell me what
you're doing here!
You heard me! Speak up! Tell
me what you're... doing here.
It's you!
Leave me alone!!
Ah.
Damn you.
Toxic Bruce, right?
You know...
who I am?
Of course! I'm
Owen the Immortal!
And I've come to transform
you from Toxic Bruce
to Just-Plain Bruce. But it's
going be a very bumpy ride.
Let me be!
Commander! The engine
assigned to Cargo Train
Number Five-Thirty-One at
Maintenance Dock Four
has just been
turned on!
Shut
it down!
It's not
responding!
Close the
Partition!
Yes, sir!
I'll finish you
once and for all!!
No!!!
Bruce!!!
That was a reckless move!
You could have been killed!
If you have a death wish,
join another platoon!
We don't want
you here!
You remember saying that
to me once, don't you?
This is Manab-
Quiet!
Why did you
stop me!?
Stay here, Yuuki!
No! I'm going
with you!
No you're not!
Then you're not
going either!
I have to do this
alone! Understand me?!
I don't want you
to die! Now move!!
Bruce.
Bruce, wait...
Look. Over here...
Isn't that Bruce's?
Yeah, that's
his all right.
Oh, great...
I hope he hasn't gotten
himself into any trouble.
Yeah, me too. I heard Manabu
start to call in and then stop.
I heard
Manabu, too.
But Bruce...
he isn't answering
his radio.
Manabu isn't
with him. Is he?
Yes, Sir.
Sorry, Sir. I
should've stopped him.
Easier said
than done...
All right, then. Let's go back
them up before it's too late.
[David and Louis]
Yes, Sir!
There's
no escape!
All the remaining partitions
have been closed!
All right. Let's put
an end to this...
Your time is
up, Death!!
No, not again... Manabu!!
Sorry,
Bruce.
[Alien]
Drop the gun!
No, Bruce!
Don't do it!
Do it now or he
dies! Understand?
Okay! I will! Just
don't kill him.
Don't worry about
me! Shoot!!
I can't do that.
Forgive me.
But no one else is going
to die on my account.
[Manabu]
Bruce!!!
What is
this place?
[David] Bruce? What
are you doing out here?
David! Is
that you?
[Louis] I don't think
he gets it, you guys.
Louis?
[Yuki] Bruce, aren't you
feeling a little lonely?
Yuki? What are
you talking about?
[Buldge] She means that
you're the only one
who's still
alive, Bruce.
No! That
not true!
Captain...! Yuki...!
Louis...! David...!
This isn't real!
It can't be!
[Alien] Losing all of your
friends is painful, isn't it?
They're
not dead!
You don't want to go through
this anymore, do you?
You want to put an end to
your life, isn't that right?
You want to die, just like
the rest of your shipmates
because that's the
only way to put an end
to the guilt
and the pain.
Don't tell me you've
killed them all!
Yeah, you're right...
I did kill them!
It's me!
That's right. It's
all because of you.
But with your death,
this will all end.
With my
death?
Isn't it the only way
to end all this torture?
Y-Yes.
It's okay. No more hurting.
No more pain inside.
[Manabu]
Bruce!
Bruce! No!
Manabu?
[Manabu] Bruce!
Bruce! Wake up!
Please! Help me!
You've got to try!
Manabu?
Don't give up, Bruce! Come on!
Do it! Bruce! Please! Do it!
This ends now!
Go back
to hell!
[David]
Bruce!
[Louis]
Manabu!
[Buldge] Are
you two okay?
Yes, Sir... we're
fine... just tired.
What is this
enormous power
that's trying to
manipulate our destiny?
What was it trying
to accomplish?
I don't understand.
Why can't I see?
[Yuki] You're awake. How
are you feeling, Bruce?
Well, okay
I guess.
You inhaled a lot
of nerve gas.
I gave you an injection
to neutralize the effect.
You'll still need
to rest for a while
to get you're your
strength back...
Good. Your pulse
is normal.
Now you've got
to promise
that you'll take it
easy for a while.
Oh, all
right.
That's
better...
Guess there was no rendezvous
with Death after all?
I don't think Toxic Bruce
fits you anymore, do you?
Guess not.
Well, see
ya later.
[Bruce]
Wait...
Thanks, Yuuki.
I owe you.
[Narrator] After many
disagreements and conflicts,
two men have arrived together
at an unexpected destination...
a destination known
as friendship.
[David] Next
time you see us,
we'll be livin' it up at
the Miraz family spa!
And why not? Even SDF Members
deserve a break now and then.
While we're there, maybe
I'll soak in the hot springs
and make some
snow-angels.
Let's just hope there
isn't any... trouble.
See you next time,
on the railways!