[Narrator] Regardless of
what people do in life,
there is always a need
to take a step back
and look for peace
and tranquility.
But for those who live
a disciplined life
of fighting for
justice everyday,
that peace and tranquility
can be hard to find.
Emergency transmission
from Mother Venus No. 131!
A woman on board is
going into labor!
They're requesting
that she be taken
to a medical facility
on the nearest planet!
Right!
Understood.
Let's get the Fomalhaut
Platoon on this! On the double!
We've just received word
from the Albireo Express
currently traveling
past the Veil Nebula!
They're reporting that a
troop of drunken performers
is engaging in acts of
disorderly conduct, Sir!
Send out the
Arcturus Platoon now!
Emergency
Transmission.
Creatures have woven a
web over an orbit ring.
Orion Express went
right through it.
The web got into the
train. It's everywhere.
Passengers
inhaled it.
It's causing allergic
reactions, Sir.
Dispatch Algol
Platoon at once!
[Shelley] Don't tell
me that he won again!
You're quite a
player, Manabu!
No, not
really.
It's just a game. I don't know
why you're getting so serious.
You'd think that we
were playing for money.
Ah, sorry.
I've only been losing
because I'm playing for fun!
If you want to play
serious let's do it!
Ah, okay.
I didn't want you to pick
that one, Louis! Really!
Oh, you know...? I haven't
finished packing yet.
Sit down! This
isn't over!
Uh, yes Ma'am.
Sitting down.
[Jose] Come on Silver! Show
'm what a real man can do!
[Schnader] What are you
waiting for? Take him down!
I can't wait to see
the look on your face
when I break
your arm, Bruce!
Why don't you go
ahead and give up now?
Maybe if you had a
tractor and a wench
you could pull this arm over
but all I see is you, Silver!
And your skinny butt isn't
gonna cut the mustard!
Oh yeah?! Bring
it, Blondie!
Let's see...
one packed lunch?
Why not? Nice day
for a trip, eh?
And would you like a drink
with that...? It's free.
Only if you tell
me when you're off.
Right... so... no
drink. Anything else?
Yeah. Are you
free tonight?
Would you like
desert with that?
I can't get a break with
these cards! They're cursed!
No one can lose that
many times in a row!
I knew
she'd blow.
Yep. She was showing
all the classic signs.
What a sore
loser. Goodness.
You took all the good luck
and left me nothing but bad!
How dare you, Manabu! And
wipe that smile off your face!
Hey come on guys, stop
that... That's enough.
Can't you
be quiet?!
There are other people
on this train you know!
Do you want me to
get the SDF in here?!
[All] Sorry...
Can't people just play
cards. What's his deal?
This younger generation's
gone to the dogs.
I thought you'd like to know
the last stop's coming up.
The Planet Carcalla. It's
known for its hot springs.
Look
there!
Amazing!
It's beautiful...
Would you mind if I
burned these cards?
Well, Manabu. This place
is lovely don't you think?
Murase
Family Spa!
Awesome!
Your parent's place looks
really great, Captain.
Yeah, If you
like old things.
So Captain, does this
place have a hot tub?
'Course it
does, Jose.
Hello. Welcome to
our humble spa.
We didn't know our son was
nice enough to have friends.
You must all be exhausted.
Please come in.
Thank you
so much.
It's our
pleasure.
Well, let's get in
out of the cold.
Let's go, Mr. Yuuki.
What's the hold up?
Ah, yeah
right...
Where's that
hot tub, Boss?
Well now, where'd
you come from?
Captain?
The hot tub?
Hey there, Shirobata!
Glad to see me?
Oh, you haven't
changed a bit.
Unlike Mom and Dad who have
that grey, vintage look.
You'd think you were
describing an automobile, Son.
You're not a
kid anymore;
when did you forget how
to talk to your parents?
Where's
the respect?
In my bag. Aw, come
on, Pop! Loosen up!
You still look young, you know,
for y'know... an old man!
Hey, Captain. How
about that hot tub.
(Meow)
I haven't forgotten
about you.
At least someone
here missed me.
Captain! Come on!
Where's the hot tub?!
Tell 'im it's
Hot Springs.
And if some bubbles start
coming up while he's in there,
stay clear. It
could be toxic.
Look
at that!
Oh wow.
It's breathtaking.
This is what we came
here for, isn't it?
Well, don't forget about
the food and drinks.
Not to mention the
hot springs, right?
Don't take this
the wrong way,
but doesn't it sound like
they share the same brain?
[Shelley] What are
we waiting for?
[Ai] I'm ready
for a good sweat.
[Maggie]
Tennis anyone?
Should I play the
way I normally do
or just let
them win...?
Let's win this
one, Manabu!
Ah, sure thing.
Sure thing.
What a jerk.
He thinks he's
perfect at everything.
Come on!
Serve it!
Here it
comes, guys!
Manabu!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
Fifteen-
Love.
Here goes!
Gotcha!
Figures.
Game, set
and match!
Good
game!
You too!
Thanks for making
me sweat, you guys!
Ugh! They were
all over him.
Why don't you join
us, Louis...?
What d'ya say? You wanna
play a little tennis
with some
real men?
Sure. Where
are they?
Ohhh!!
That hurt!!
She dogged us!
Hahaha! You're really
too cute for words,
you silly
kitty cat!
You're just so
cute aren't you?
You're just the cutest
thing in the universe...
You know it's
true, don't you?!
Ah, sorry...
For what?
My son's vulgar
behavior.
I hope his childish antics
aren't bothering you, Dear.
Don't worry,
I've seen worse.
You're just so cute!
I wanna eat you up!
It's nice.
Don't you think?
Oh, yeah! Nice!
You look serious,
Captain. That's not good.
Hey! Why don't we go to
a tavern? What d'ya say?
We'll take a soak; then
we can hit the streets.
I know a place that's
crawling with girls!
A nice hot soak and
a night on the town.
Bruce, what
d'ya think?
Sounds good!
Hey,
Yuuki?
We're going
to the spa.
Be there
in a minute.
Huh? You again? Oh,
you're not Murase's cat.
Tora! I've been looking
for you everywhere.
You little rascal. You love
making me worry, don't you?
This cat has always
been a curious one.
Whenever we come
to a new place,
Tora likes to do a little
exploring without me.
Ah, I guess he's
a naughty boy...
He's a rude one,
isn't he, Tora?
Tora's a female,
young man!
Oh, sorry!
I didn't know!
Maybe you should try to get in
touch with your feminine side?
Uhh, what's that
supposed to mean?
Huh?
Louis can we ask
you a question?
What's really going
on between you two?
Between who?
Don't play innocent.
Between you and Manabu?
Oh, him...
There's nothing;
We're just shipmates and
that's all there is to it.
What? It's
the truth!
So, then I guess you won't mind
if I'm interested in Manabu?
Go ahead. He's
not my type, Ai.
Now, now. Don't tease
her like that, girls.
But Captain! I am
serious about Manabu!
Hey, Manabu, do
you wanna race?
The first one to the other
side of the pool's the winner!
But you have to swim it
all underwater! Ready! Go!
Hey! That's
not fair!!
Manabu Yuuki?
Girls, we're
under attack.
Captain! It's not
what you think!
Louis! You could
have killed him!
Manabu!
Are you okay?
Nice, Kid!
That was huge!
So's the knot
on my head!
Hey, check
this out!
Not another race.
No, it's the
fresh snow!
It's like a blank canvass
waiting for us to paint it!
Lemme guess, yellow?
That's nasty! That would
be a desecration!
I'm talking about making
a snow-angel, Manabu!
Hey, knock
yourself out, pal.
Aww. It looks a lot
better if two people do it.
Age before
beauty.
I thought we came here to
relax and have some fun!
David?! Are
you okay?!
Yeah. But snow was a lot
softer when I was a kid.
It sounded solid.
Like a rock.
Really...? Oh,
you're right...
He knocked
his head!
Don't worry
he'll be fine.
Don't forget he's
part of the S-D-F...
It'll take a lot more than
that to keep him down.
Hey,
Louis?
Yes, Ma'am?
I know it's none
of my business...
But are you ever
going to tell him
how you really
feel about him?
What? What do
you mean...?
You're not fooling
me, Louis.
I think you should tell
him how you really feel.
If you wait for someone as
shy as Manabu to speak up,
you might end up
waiting forever...
Loving someone from afar
is a very noble thing,
but sometimes unspoken
love starts to fade away.
Just keep that
in mind and...
do what your heart
tells you to do.
You know... we
could teach you...
some table tennis...
what do you say?
You're wasting
your time boys.
It's never
gonna happen.
Aaahh! Dogged again!
SDF Talent
Show?!?!
[Murase] T'is a far,
far better thing I do now
than I have ever
done before.
Adieu! Adieu!
Farewell my friends.
Parting is such
sweet sorrow!
♪ Like a song that never
ends I'll be with you... ♪
♪ Oh, dreams, don't go away!
Stay please, another day! ♪
♪ Shining brightly
like the Milky Way! ♪
♪ Just like pretty Suns
and Moons at play! ♪
[Bruce] So, why the
long face, partner?
I don't know...
I guess something just
doesn't seem right to me.
It's like everybody's forgotten
about work all of a sudden.
For all we know, at
this very moment,
something terrible
might be happening
somewhere along the orbit
routes of the Railways.
Pretty view isn't
it, Yuuki...?
The air's so
fresh here.
You don't really
see your breath.
That's because the air
is so crisp and clean.
You're right- I
never noticed that...
But maybe it's
because it's so cold?
Don't think about
it, just enjoy it.
What about you, Bruce?
Are you enjoying yourself?
What? I don't look
like I'm having fun?
Not really! If you ask me,
you look bored to tears...
So, am
I right?
Well, sometimes even the
truth is best left untold.
(Choking)
...Thought I
was gonna die.
I really like this place.
It's very peaceful.
You're kidding,
right?
No, not
at all.
Well to me, this is the most
boring place in the Universe.
Sorry to
hear that.
Yeah... That's the
reason I left here.
If you like it, why
don't you move here?
Now why would I want to
move here all by myself?
Well, I'd be
out here, too.
At the most boring
place in the Universe?
I don't mean now. Maybe
when we're a little older.
You'd be a bear
if you were bored!
I think we could keep
ourselves occupied.
Oh, no! She's gone! This
is terrible! Just terrible!
What's all the
commotion about?
It's Tora! My cat;
I can't find her!
Since when?
I'm not sure! I just now
noticed that she was missing!
It's below zero!
If she's out there too long
she could freeze to death!
Sirius Platoon!
Let's move!
Front torches
are lit!
Roger! Lighting
back torches!
Communications
system, ready!
Assigning
search grids!
Equipment
check.
Anoraks -
Boots and
snowshoes - check.
Synchronize radios! Sirius
Platoon! Vega Platoon!
Gear up and
prepare to depart!
There's not much time,
troops! Let's look sharp!
Vega Platoon is
ready for search!!
Standby for
coordinates!
Isn't this...
a bit much?
We're members
of the SDF!
There's no such thing as too
much when a life's in danger!
...R- Right.
Go SDF!! You can do
it! I know you can!!
Sirius Platoon!
Let's move out!
Vega Platoon,
move out!
Kiyoji, what's
going on?
It seems that
Tora's missing.
I saw Tora
earlier...
Yes, she was by the hot
springs with Shirobota.
Hmm?!
Why didn't you
say something?!
Tora!
What's the matter?
Did something happen?
Uh, no. We thought
Tora was lost.
Tora? She's been
here the whole time.
We've become
good friends...
They've been
keeping me company.
They're very
sweet cats...
Hey! Come on!
That's enough!
Sure is some nice
scenery here...
I know. I don't think I'll be
able to sleep after that.
It is our
last night.
Maybe we should have some fun
since we're all still awake!
Let's party!
We can start out by
taking a late night dip
in the hot
springs!
Yeah!! Huh?!
Um, Captain... You
sure about that?
(Jose choking again)
Are you okay
over there?
Well son...
is there something you'd like
to tell your mother and I?
I don't think so, Dad. Oh,
yeah. Thank you for having us!
No, that's
not it.
He's
clueless.
Now wait! That's
not gonna happen!
At least not for a few
more years anyway!
Come on,
Captain!
Trust me, you'll be
the first to know!
I think she's going to make
a fine landlady someday!
I hope. She's too good
for him if you ask me.
Tora. Are you sure this
is what you want to do?
All right!
We're ready!
Smile everyone! Let's
make this one a keeper!
Okay, What station
are we going back to?!
Des-tin-y!
All
right!!
True relaxation often comes
in short fleeting moments.
Not long after it arrives,
it usually departs...
But even though these
times of peace are brief,
they leave an indelible
imprint on our hearts.
[Manabu] Next time
it's quite an honor
when the Space
Panzer Grenadiers-
the elite troop that my
brother used to belong to-
asks me to join
their platoon.
But is taking a big
step in my career
worth leaving everything
that I care about...?
See ya next time
on the Railways!