Schnader!
Shame on all of you! Is
that the best you've got?
Ah, no sir!
If you can't manage this
level of field simulation,
you should pack
up and leave!
We're S-P-G... Space Panzer
Grenadiers... not the S-D-F.
Now let's try it again!
Yes, Sir.
All of us must make our way
along the road called life.
And when that road
eventually comes to a fork,
we must rely on
instinct to make a choice
and decide
which way to go.
You've enrolled me in the
S-P-G training program?
But, Sir...
Why me?
It's to improve the interaction
between our two outfits.
So we can learn
from each other.
Well, that's the
official version anyway.
If you ask me they're doing it
to look for some new recruits.
So don't hold back.
Right.
You won't be
going in alone.
Schnader from Vega Platoon
and Ai from Spica Platoon
have both been
selected to accompany you.
It should be an
awesome experience.
These guys are the most
elite fighters in the Galaxy.
The S-P-G.
[Thinking] Mamoru was
a member when he died.
Manabu, there's a reason
I met you here alone.
I want to talk to you about
something away from the others.
Away from the
others? But Why?
So, you think the
SPG wants Manabu?
Really? Are you
sure about that?
That's what I heard
through the grapevine.
It's the unofficial buzz.
I'm sure that once he passes
the training the Space
Panzer Grenadiers will
make a formal announcement.
Well, I'm sure Captain
Murase has told Manabu
all about this
by now.
But why
Captain Murase?
Ah, wait a second;
I think I know.
It's Captain Johansson...
he was Murase's senior officer
way back at training camp.
And he's the one who
would make the call.
From what I hear the S-P-G
has had its eye on Manabu
for some time now...
I think it's wonderful!
One of our very own is being
recruited by the S-P-G!
[Louis] Manabu won't
join the S-P-G!
Well, it doesn't make
any sense does it?
Even my scores were
higher than his were!
Besides!
Just think about it!
Manabu's far too reckless and
stubborn to be an S-P-G member!
Am I right?!
Well! Am I?!
[Bruce] Manabu can be
whatever he wants to be.
Only he can decide which
direction he wants to take.
It's up to
him, not us.
Oh. Hey, Captain.
I appreciate you
giving me the heads-up.
But Murase already told
me all about it earlier.
It's not a done deal.
You can make
your decision
once you've gone through
all the training.
I know that this is
important to you...
and it's
important to us, too.
Thanks, Captain.
Look. Just try to keep
this in mind, Manabu.
No matter what you decide,
you'll be working
to preserve life and to
keep peace in the Universe.
I'm sure Captain Yuuki
would say the same thing
if he were here.
Thank you.
Gotcha!
What the...
Damn it!
We have an enemy aircraft
approaching at eight o'clock.
Uploading the
escape route, now.
New enemy aircraft approaching
your position at two o'clock.
Four bogies converging!
No, wait a second! There's six!
Your escape route's
been compromised.
They're everywhere!
Be careful! Look out! No! No!
Stupid.
Do you think you can
catch a train on foot?
What's the meaning
of this, Cadet?
You're supposed to
be sleeping now...
Getting the proper amount
of rest is mandatory.
Sir!
Sir?
What is it?
The S-P-G wants me...
Captain Murase told me they do.
But, Sir... I need to know.
Why me? Because of my Dad?
Because I'm
Mamoru's brother?
You're strong-willed,
much the same way he was.
He persevered through
all the hard training.
He never complained once.
I've never seen such
a dedicated soldier
as your brother Mamoru.
He was outstanding.
Mamoru.
I have to stay
here, brother.
Not only was he
a good soldier,
he was a fine man;
the best of the best.
So tell me, what made
you join the S-D-F?
Was it out of admiration of
your Father and Brother
or something else?
That's why I
joined initially.
But now, my reasons
are different.
I just want to protect people.
I want them to be happy.
No matter what you choose,
the work will be the same.
Whether it's SDF or SPG...
you'll work for peace.
What the SPG
needs now
are passionate and
dedicated youths like you.
Your service record
speaks for itself.
I know it would mean a
big change in your life
so I want you to take time
to weigh all your options.
I'm looking forward to
hearing your decision.
I've had it. We work 24
hours a day at this job.
And you can forget about having
any kind of personal life.
So why moan about it? You
haven't met anyone have you?
That's the point! How can
I when I'm always working?
Oh, let it go. You love
your job and you know it!
[Kinuko] Hey, boys!
Hey, what's up, Kinuko...
So, How 'bout a cold one?
Sure! No prob!
Why, thank you.
That was my last stout, Bruce.
But look what I have for you!
Not bad. But stout
sounds better.
Tastes better, too! The
perfect way to end a shift.
Right, Manabu?
Oh yeah...
I know how you
feel, David.
Things just don't seem right
without Manabu around, do they?
Well, I'll bet
that he stays!
Manabu wouldn't leave
all of his friends!
I'll put 5,000
Ables on it, Bruce!
That sounds like
a sucker bet.
Hey! Don't give him any
tips! That's not fair!
Well, Bruce, what's he
gonna do? Stay or go?
Only he knows. But my money
says that he goes to the SPG.
I'm not worried. I'm sure
that he'll come back...
Manabu would never leave his
platoon and all of his friends.
He's staying and that's
all there is to it.
But he may not...
Becoming a
member of the SPG
would be a huge
honor for anyone.
Who could blame Manabu
for going for it?
We should be happy
for him, you know?
This is the
opportunity of a lifetime.
You're right Louis.
Conducting training
tests in a magnetic storm?
Only the S-P-G would
be this extreme.
If we get thru in one
piece we'll be set...
No screw-ups.
Okay, Manabu?
Right...
No more screw-ups.
Rescue Shuttle Pod Docked.
We are now entering
the Six-Five-Oh.
Request permission to
begin search and rescue.
This is Six-Six-Six...
we copy.
Begin search and
rescue immediately.
You must also restart
the Six-Five-Oh's engine
and get it out of
the magnetic storm.
Please proceed in an orderly
manner to the rescue pod.
Let's move!
Don't worry! You're
all going to be fine!
No matter what
you choose,
the work will
be the same.
Whether it's SDF or SPG,
you'll work for peace.
[Thinking] I need to let go
and stop worrying about it.
This way; please
hurry, folks!
There's nothing
to be afraid of!
[Ai] We've got a
log-jam here!
Please stay calm
and keep moving!
Let's go already people!
Get the lead out!
I love when they stop walking.
That's my favorite part.
That's the last
one! All clear!
Double check! I'll get the
shuttle pod ready for take off!
Now the only thing left is
to do is restart the engine.
Right. I can handle that.
Be careful.
The Sensors are
detecting an anomaly.
There's a sudden increase
in magnetic energy levels.
Hold on!
I'm heading back!
Schnader, wait! Manabu's
still on the train!
Manabu!
Manabu! Are you receiving me?
Please come in.
No signal! The communication
link is down!
Captain! All sensors
are failing, Sir!
There's no way to know what's
happening on the Six-Five-Oh.
[Captain] Redirect our ship
to intercept the
Six-Five-Oh immediately.
Yes sir.
What's happening?!
The Main Engine's damaged!
We're losing power!
She's shutting down!
Switch to auxiliary! Now!
The Six-five-oh is gone,
Captain! It just vanished!
Manabu!
Expand the search
to include Area G!
Monitor all frequencies! He
might be trying to reach us!
Yes, Sir!
I expect you to do
your duty out there.
Just be the best that
you can be, Manabu.
Uhh, man. I feel
like a train hit me.
Huh?! What happened?!!
From the looks of it I'd
say we were attacked!
This is Manabu Yuuki
on the Six-five-oh!
Can anyone hear me?
Please come in! Over!
I'm adrift in the middle of
nowhere. What do I do now?
When are you gonna
learn? Just calm down.
Then you'll be
able to figure out
exactly what
you need to do.
The Song of the Engine!
Thank Whitman I'm not dead yet!
Hang in there,
Manabu. You can do it.
I've got five-thousand
riding on you!
You just have to make
it back, Manabu!
Can you do
that for me?
Yes!
This is it!
I don't have
a choice!
You can do it, Manabu...
I know you can.
Thank you, Louis.
It's not looking
good, Captain.
We've been searching for
six hours and still no trace.
Should we call
it off, Sir?
Manabu.
We can't just give up! He's
gotta be out there somewhere!
He's Manabu Yuuki
of the SDF
and he's gonna make
it, understand?
Is that it?
It's him!
He's alive!
Yeah!
Manabu here...
Mission complete.
Manabu really did a
great job out there.
Anybody else would have
been a goner for sure.
The SPG would be
fools not to take him
after a performance
like that.
Don't say that.
What? Oh, sorry.
Well it is an honor.
Looks like I owe you
5,000 Ables. Aye, Bruce?
Guess so.
I'm going to miss him.
Come on now! Be happy
for him! My goodness!
The least we can do is
send him off with a smile!
What does that guy think
he's doing? Is he crazy?
What guy?
Manabu Yuuki. He's out
of his mind, Bulge.
He just turned
down a commission
with the Space
Panzer Grenadiers!
Manabu, at least tell me the
reason for your decision.
There's a lot I
can still learn
from the Sirius Platoon,
Sir... And besides...
Yes...
Well, someone told me that
no matter what I chose
the work would be the same,
whether it's S-P-G or S-D-F.
I'll still be working
to uphold peace.
Manabu really
said that?
What a guy!
This is terrible!
His head's going to be so big
it won't fit through the door!
And his grades aren't anywhere
close to what mine are!
Louis?
He was already cocky enough.
Now he'll be impossible.
Somebody needs to teach
him a lesson if you ask me.
I think you're right.
Just a little something to
put him back in his place.
I know exactly how
to handle this.
Now guys. Don't be
too hard on him.
Of course not!
Never!
Sometimes even ambitious people
turn down a higher position...
To these rare few only
feelings matter, not status...
They realize that without the
love shared between friends
and a joyful
outlook on life,
even a promotion
can be a step down.
So... did
you miss me?
Next time we receive an
Emergency Rescue Signal
from Kowloon City...
one of the most dangerous
places in the Galaxy!
Is this just a trick or
is this former enemy
really trying
to help us?
Looks like we're
about to find out!
See ya next time
on the Railways!