The infinite universe.
Inconcievably vast.
Where giant stars are
mere pinpricks of light.
What man can fathom this
amazing ocean of life?
Are we not but
specks in creation?
And yet we dare to leave
the comfort of our planet
and venture fourth
into boundless space.
Is there anything more
magnificant to behold
than the swirling
colors of a planet
illuminated by the pure
light of a nearby star?
And yet, as beautiful
as the universe is
just a few pebbles out
of place can cause
a catastropic
amount of destruction.
Huh?
Mommy, look. I see rocks
flying through the sky.
You do? Where?
Right there!
Huh?
See!
Whoa. What's up?
[Conductor] Please remain
calm. There's nothing to fear.
This train is equipped
with Orbit Shields
and the Railway itself is
protected by a Magnetic Barrier.
You're perfectly safe.
[Little Girl] I'm scared!
Emergency! Emergency!
Engine Number 707 has stopped!
We have a full shutdown
3500 mega-meters
from the
Tabito System!
It looks like
asteroids!
[Brad] Their Orbit Shield
has been compromised!
Maximize the power
to the Magnetic Barrier!
They're requesting
an SDF dispatch!
When it rains,
it pours!
I'm showing a White Hole
forming 500 mega-meters
from the
accident site!
The gravitational
pull is increasing!
I want the Space Defense
Force out there right away!
Dispatch the Sirius
Platoon! Now!
[Layla] So the Wheel of Fate
has begun to turn
and nothing can be
done to stop it.
Even the mightiest of men
are powerless to resist
the pull of
their own destiny.
They rush to it, even if it
means their destruction.
[Male Passenger]
What's going on?
Why hasn't your headquarters
sent out a rescue team yet?
[Female Passenger] What
are they going to do?
Just leave us out here in
the middle of space to die?
[Conductor] Calm down, everyone!
The SDF is on the way.
Please go back to your seats
and relax until they get here!
But we've got injured
people on board!
This isn't the time for an
in-flight movie, you idiot! Huh?
Here comes the SDF
now. Thank goodness.
All right people, we need to do
this as efficiently as possible.
If that barrier
breaches, we're sunk!
Let's get them the
hell out of here!
Yes, Sir!
Let go of me!
I'm not a criminal!
I didn't do anything!
You big bully!
[Officer] I found
these two stowaways
in the hangar-coach, Sir.
They both claim that
they know you, Captain.
What do you have to
say for yourselves?
I'm sorry, Dad.
Me too, Dad.
These boys are
your sons, Captain?
Well, they were until today.
Sorry, Dad. We really didn't
mean for this to happen. Honest.
I want to help you with
the rescue mission, Dad!
I'll check this one.
Please! Let me help! I want to
join the SDF, Dad! Like you!
Don't be stupid!
[Yuki] Does he
belong to you?
Yes, thanks very much.
But she's actually a girl.
Of course. How
silly of me.
Captain Yuuki.
What is it, Bulge?
This is the last of the
passengers. We're clear.
Very good. Let's
get out of here.
Right.
Many thanks, Captain.
Yes, of course. That was quite
an ordeal you went through.
You should be proud of
yourself. Well done.
Thank you, Captain.
Check Dad out.
Doesn't he look cool?
Yeah.
Captain, we've got
an emergency!
What is it?
There appears to be a ship
emerging from the White Hole.
What?
They're firing at us, Sir!
Energy blasts on the way!
Quick! Full ahead! Now!
[Bulge]
Indirect hit, Sir!
[Wataru]
Damn it!
Permission to return
fire, Captain!
Negative! We need to get
these passengers to safety!
We'll only return
fire if they pursue!
Yes, Sir!
Incoming fighters!
Opening Orbit Shield, Captain!
Pulse Cannons ready to fire!
[Wataru] On my mark! Fire!
[Wataru] Get away from
there, boys! It's dangerous!
Right. Sorry, Dad.
Dad, I'm scared.
Don't worry.
We'll be fine.
Whoa! A Space-Train! Awesome!
They look so cool at night!
I wonder if
that's Big One?
That is Big One!
I know it!
It's him!
He made it! Dad's back!
I'd know Dad's
train anywhere!
Stay, boy.
[Villager] Clear for
take-off, Mamoru!
[Mamoru] I wish!
[Mamoru] Mr. Ooiwa!
Your delivery's here! Hello?
[Ooiwa] Does that thing
have wings on it or what?
How'd you get
here so fast?
[Mamoru] You sure can put
it away, Mr. Ooiwa.
[Ooiwa] That's because
I work so hard.
What about you? Mamoru,
you can't deliver food forever.
What are you going
to do after you graduate?
I don't know.
You're going to join the SDF,
aren't you? I thought so.
Off to the Universe! Ya know,
if I was your age, I'd go too!
[Manabu]
Hey! Mamoru!
I know that voice.
He's back! He's on his way
to the station! Dad's back!
I saw Big One coming in!
But Dad's not due back yet.
Mom told us the schedule.
Let's go see! Come on!
It's against the rules!
You can't go into the
station without a pass!
What, are you crazy?
But those are
SDF rules, right?
Well, I'm not
in SDF! So there!
Manabu, wait!
Don't be a
party-pooper!
Dad's here! Tell Mom we'll
be home in a little while!
This is easy enough! Who needs
a pass anyway? Pass Schmass!
[Announcer] Attention:
An SDF train is arriving.
Passengers will disembark
on Platform Three.
What am I
going to do?
[guard-bot]
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
This threat must
be neutralized!
No! Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
I just came to meet
my Dad! I swear! Huh?
[Wataru] Is there a
problem here?
[Guard-bot] We found an
intruder, Sir.
Yes, I see. I'm afraid
he happens to be my son.
[Manabu] Dad!
You're back! I knew it!
You could have
been killed!
What would your Mother
and I do if we lost you?
Come now.
Let's go home.
By the way, how did you
get past the guard-bots?
That's a secret. The SDF
can't know everything, right?
I guess not.
[Manabu] Dad, do you
get to stay a while?
[Wataru] I'm afraid not.
Same as always, huh?
I guess it's
not easy
having a ship's
captain for a dad, is it?
I know how you can
make it up to me!
How's that?
By taking me
aboard Big One.
Sorry, I can't
do that.
Why not?
It's against
the rules.
You have to be an SDF member
to go aboard a space-train.
But that's just it!
I'm not a member of the SDF so
the rules don't apply to me!
Good try.
All right then!
I'll do it!
Do what?
I'll join the SDF!
When I grow up
I'm going to be a captain
in the Space Defense Force,
just like you!
Hey, boy.
How are you?
[dog barks]
Welcome.
Have a seat.
You didn't know it
was me, did you?
Where have you been?
Your father's going
to hear about this.
He already has.
You look lovely, Kanna.
Wataru, you're back!
You're blushing, Mom!
You're all red!
That's enough, young man!
[Mamoru] Dad! You're back!
Told ya, Mamoru!
That was Big One!
I was right!
Hello, Mamoru. It's
good to see you, Son.
You too, Dad. We
really missed you.
I missed you, too.
Remember your promise, Dad? You
said you'd play catch with us!
Remember? The next time
you came in! Remember?
I did say that.
Mamoru, are you ready?
Mmm-hmm!
[Wataru] Nice one!
Now show me that split-finger
fastball, Manabu!
Bring it on!
All right!
You asked for it!
Hey! Not bad!
Mamoru! Your turn!
All right Dad! But look out!
I've been practicing!
What's wrong?
Just a little too much
heat for your old man!
Catch it in the web,
not in your palm!
I think I'm the one
who taught you that!
Well, you
obviously forgot!
Well, that's it
for me boys.
[Mamoru]
Aw, come on, Dad!
I have to spend time
with your mother, too.
Ewe! They're going
to get mushy!
They're something
else, aren't they?
Mmm-hmm!
They love it
when you're here.
They're both such good boys.
They're growing up fast.
[Kanna] That's for sure.
[Manabu]
Full count!
Bases are loaded!
Strike three!
He's outta there!
Thank you, Kanna.
You're doing such a good job.
[phone ringing]
Wataru Yuuki here.
Yes. I understand.
Pick me up
on your way.
You're leaving already?
Sorry, Kanna. Meteorites have
hit a train, and it's stalled.
Let's not tell the boys yet.
I'll wait 'til morning.
I'm so sorry, Kanna.
It's not your fault.
I have something for you.
For me?
It's for your birthday.
I know it's a little early.
Oh, Wataru. It's beautiful.
Just come home safely.
I will.
[Wataru] Good
evening, Bulge.
Captain.
[Mamoru] Hold it.
Just where do you think you're
going? Isn't it a little late?
Please, don't tell!
I'm going to see Dad off!
I have to, Mamoru!
Be quiet! You'll
give us away!
Manabu, where
are we going?
To the platform, silly.
Where do you think?
I can't see.
Slow down.
[Wataru]
Sirius Platoon...
We've been assigned to
rescue a damaged train.
The safety of the passengers
is our number one priority.
Let's get them back
safe and sound.
[All] Yes, Captain!
Begin take-off
sequence now!
[Officer] Magnetic
Barriers are intact!
[Officer] Atomic Boiler
pressure rising!
I must be
out of my mind.
[Manabu] Would you feel
better if we had a pass?
[Mamoru] Yeah!
Do you have one?
[Manabu] No.
Thanks a lot.
Mamoru, over there!
That's Big One!
I've never seen it this
close. It's awesome.
I wonder if Dad's
on board already.
He must be.
[Guard-bot] Intruder
alert! Intruder alert!
Don't move or
we'll shoot!
Come on!
[guard-bot]
Stop!
[Officer] Atomic Boiler
Pressure is a go!
[Bulge] Cylinder
Valves are open!
The Main Circuit
is online!
[Officer] All systems
green, Captain Yuuki!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
You're gonna have to
leave me behind, Mamoru!
I can't keep
up with you!
[guard-bot] This is
your final warning!
Grab a hold!
[Manabu]
I can't go on!
Full ahead!
[Train whistle]
We're dead!
Dad's going to
kill us all right!
Maybe we should
jump train.
Are you crazy?
Goodbye, Wataru.
It's so
beautiful!
[Wataru] Manabu!
Manabu! Can you hear me?
Wake up, son.
It's me.
[Manabu] Dad?
Yes, Son. I'm here.
Let's get you
back on your feet.
Dad! You're bleeding!
You're hurt!
I'm more worried about Manabu.
Are you all right?
Uh-huh. I feel fine, Dad.
You boys are brave and strong.
I'm proud of you both.
[Bulge] Captain!
They're almost out, Sir!
They'll clear the
hole in five minutes!
We can't let that
happen, Bulge!
I understand, Sir.
Captain! You're wounded!
It's nothing.
Launch all deep-space
fighters immediately!
All fighters have
been destroyed!
Fighter Coach
seriously damaged!
I'm isolating
the Fighter Coach!
The partition walls
are closed, Captain!
The destroyer will clear
the hole in three minutes!
We've got to
do something!
Incoming!
Divert all power
to the shields!
[Bulge] There's not
enough time, Sir!
[The boys] Dad?
Don't worry. It's
going to be all right.
Boys, I'm sending you
back to your mother.
You'll both be
fine, I promise.
For real?
Mmm-hmm.
[Officer]
Captain?
[Wataru] Alright then,
Sirius Platoon.
It's time we
show this enemy
that our true strength
goes beyond guns and steel.
[All] Yes, Captain.
From this moment on I'm placing
the command of this Platoon
in the hands of First
Officer Schwanheld Bulge.
What do you
mean, Captain?
Listen! I want all of you
to move into the Coach Block.
I'll use Big One as a decoy
to distract the enemy.
Use auxiliary power to
get yourselves out of here.
Support ships will
be arriving soon.
What about you, Dad? Big
One's no match for that ship!
What's going to
happen to you?
Listen, boys. Whether I
make it through this or not,
one thing will
never change.
I will always be
your father. Always.
Mamoru, you have no idea
how proud I am of you, son.
Manabu, I'm
counting on you.
Please Son, take care
of your mother for me.
She needs you. You're much
stronger than you realize.
No Dad! Don't do it!
You can't just leave us!
Manabu.
Please, Dad.
All of you! Evacuate to
the coach-block immediately!
Bulge... This ship is
under your care now.
To our commander and
friend, Captain Yuuki!
Dad! Come back!
Manabu.
I love you.
No, Dad! Don't leave us!
I can't live without you!
Goodbye, my Sons. This
Universe has been my home
but I must leave it
for the Ocean of Spirit.
Be brave, boys. I will
always be with you.
Father.
Father!!
[Computer] The destroyer will
clear the hole in one minute!
All available power
to main battery!
Target enemy
destroyer!
[Computer] Affirmative,
Captain Yuuki.
Kanna. It'll be long this
time, my love. I'm sorry.
Supreme
Commander.
Are you really
going, Wataru?
Then I will
escort you.
I am destiny.
I am Shula.
[Bulge] I'm sorry, Kanna.
Wataru was more than
a commander to me.
He was my
best friend.
Hmm?
[Kanna] Mamoru, are you
certain this is what you want?
Yes, Mom. There's
no doubt in my mind.
All right then, Son.
Manabu, take care
of Mom for me, okay?
You can
count on me.
I know I can, Manabu.
I know I can.
Take care, Mom.
I love you.
I love you too, Son.
[Villager]
There he is!
The next great Yuuki is taking
off! Go Mamoru! Bon voyage!
Bon voyage!
Well, now. The dream has
become a reality. Take care.
I will, Ooiwa.
Thanks, guys.
Gosh. I sure wasn't
expecting all this.
Wait a second. Where's your
pass? All right. Move along.
This is it. Once I enter
there's no turning back.
Mamoru!
Hey! Come
back here!
Mamoru it's me!
Mamoru!
Manabu?
Is he crazy?
What are
you doing?
I want to give you something!
Here, Mamoru! Catch!
Bye, Manabu!
Mamoru.
Plagued by visions of
his father's demise
and beset with a
torrent of emotions,
Mamoru Yuuki
courageously set off
on his adventure into
boundless space.
But what lay ahead
was most unexpected.
[phone rings]
[Manabu] Hello! Galaxy Diner!
Yes, she is. Mom! Phone!
Hello?
Kanna speaking.
It can't. No.
[Phone]
Mrs. Yuuki?
Mom! What's the matter? Are
you all right? What happened?
[Phone] Mrs. Yuuki?
Are you still there?
Who is this?
[Manabu] Yes, I'm his brother.
What? Mamoru's dead?
On the next Galaxy Railways.
The space train I board slips
into a different time axis
and I meet Mamoru
who's supposed to have
been dead for five years.
Our dream of serving in the
SDF together comes to life
but the experience
is bittersweet.
See ya next time
on the Railways.