[Narr] Sometimes a person's
beliefs are like the influence
of the Sun's gravity
on a planet;
they cause that person to take
a certain unwavering path.
Unable to change the
course of their orbit,
when they meet with an opposing
will with different beliefs,
they have no choice
but to collide.
The Wheel of Fate has
begun to turn again.
I see conflict.
Sirius Platoon! I was
just assigned to this unit.
I'm Manabu Yuuki. Reporting
for duty as ordered, Sirs.
[Louis] Manabu!
Mmm! Aahh!
Shut up!
Hush!
If the cash isn't here
in the next ten minutes
this woman is history!
Do you hear me?!!!
Answer!!
You don't think
I'll do it, do you?!
I'll off
her right now!
No!!!!!
Give me some cash now or
I'll paint this floor red.
So be it.
Ahhhhhh!!!
Fool!!
Well, congratulations.
You're dead.
How many times
does that make?
That's three deaths... Sir.
Well, when you're out in space
you only have one life, Cadet.
How can you do your part to help
your platoon if you're dead?
Did you ever
think of that
or were you too busy
trying to be a hero?
Look, hotshot, I don't care
what the Captain's orders are,
I am not going
to waste my time
training someone who
refuses to listen.
Now go have Yuki take a
look at those wounds...
You're dismissed.
Hmm? Yes?
...Come in.
Hello? ...Miss Yuki?
...Are you there?
Forgive me.
I was changing.
Controlled
training blasts
may still bruise your
internal organs.
Being reckless may prevent
you from doing your duty.
[Manabu]
I'll try.
Here. This is the
Operations Manual.
You may want to start
memorizing it, Louis.
Right.
Thanks a lot.
Watch where
you're going.
You watch where
you're going!
You're the one
who bumped into me!
Hmm? Ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha!!!
She's a feisty
one, isn't she?
We belong to the
Vega Platoon.
Normally, I would kill a person
for talking to me like that
but I'm actually kind of
impressed. You're all right.
Hmm. I saw you in the Sim
Room with the Sirius Platoon.
Are you kidding? What are
you doing with those hacks?
We're the best platoon in the
SDF. Why don't you join us?
What for? So I can
walk around the halls
knocking girls down.
No thanks.
Man, she's like a
big mouth with legs.
Ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha!!
What a bunch
of jerks.
Huh?
Who would still be training
in the Sim Room at this hour?
[Louis] Are you trying to
kill yourself or what?
Hey.
I didn't know you
were so dedicated.
I can help if you want. I'm done
with my training for today.
Are you crazy, Manabu?
You could get hurt.
Huh? ...Oh, yeah.
The training level.
I thought if I cranked it up
I would improve faster.
I guess so. These
results are incredible.
Yeah, but my ranking
still isn't as high
as the top guys from the prep
school because of my academics.
So what? That
doesn't matter...
Hmm?
Grades are important, but they
only get you so far in life.
I'd like to see one of those
guys from the prep school
survive in the simulator at this
level. There's just no way.
Besides, rankings
aren't everything.
It's what's on the inside that
makes a person a good officer.
Right?
Hmm.
Hmm, I guess I'd better
call it a day.
If I overdo it and get injured I
won't be any good for tomorrow.
So you do have a brain.
You had me worried.
Huh?!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
No worries.
That training level
was dangerous.
I didn't know
it was that high.
Bruce is the one who set it
for me before he left.
What in the world
was he thinking?
He either thought
I could take it
or he was intentionally
trying to hurt me.
[Crewman] Emergency signal
has been received
from the Six-twenty Express
traveling from Kaitos to Sigma.
They're being
hijacked.
Right.
Affirmative on that.
It's a code red
hostage situation.
They're requesting an
immediate SDF dispatch, Sir.
Notify Spica Platoon. Have them
in the air in two minutes.
I want all updates to
come directly to me.
Yes, Commander.
Understood.
[Kinuko] Well, hello
there. Wha's up?!
Hmm?
Over here, dude. Yoo, hoo.
I'm talkin' to you.
Who me?
Here!
Power up!
Huh?
You seem kind
of bummed out,
like something's
got you down...
Here, this is loaded with
calcium and protein.
Uh. Thanks.
That's okay.
Now don't be shy. That won't
get you anywhere with me...
Besides, I'm no stranger.
I knew your father.
That Wataru was one hot
space-ship captain.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
You're not so bad
yourself. You Yuuki's...
really have all
the right stuff!
[Beep, beep, beep...]
Manabu speaking.
Report to the main platform
immediately. We're shipping out!
Yes, Sir!
Oh, yeah...
Thanks very much!
Go get 'em, Manabu! Remember!
You're a Yuuki! You can do it!
[Crewman]
System check!
Stand by for
System Check!
Sub-atomic Warp
Generator ready!
Orbit Network
Radar ready!
Magnetic Barrier
Generator is a go!
Big One is now in
take-off position!
Cylinder Valves are open!
Atomic Boiler Pressure is a go!
The Main Circuit
is now online!
All energy levels ready for
take-off, Captain Bulge!
The warp drive coupling
is now in place!
All systems green,
Captain Bulge!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
Let's move out!
Ahead full!
The hijacker has taken control
of the Six-twenty Express
traveling from
Kaitos to Sigma.
Right now he's in the
third passenger car.
He's demanding
that we bring
his ex-girlfriend
to him immediately.
He's considered to be
extremely dangerous.
Bring Catherine or
I'll kill them all!!
No! Please, Sir! Wait a second!
Give them some time!
I'm sure they're
bringing her right now!
Shut up! ...You're
lying! Where is she!
If they don't bring her in five
minutes I'll start shooting!
Man, this guy's bad news.
He's out of his mind...
Get me Captain
Bulge, pronto.
Right.
I just spoke with the
Captain of Spica Platoon.
They've been scanning
the Six-twenty Express.
She has offered
little hope
of negotiating a
peaceful resolution.
She thinks the
hijacker's insane.
If he thinks that we're not
going to meet his demands
he'll open fire. So we're going
to have to operate carefully.
Louis we're going to fly
you to the Six-twenty.
I want you to act like
this guy's girlfriend.
Right.
Let's see. David,
I want you with Louis.
Yes, Sir.
I need you two to buy us
as much time as possible.
While you're docking
with the Six-twenty
at the front of the train, we'll
come up on the rear in Big One.
Bruce, Manabu, I want you
two to board the Six-twenty.
Yes, Sir!
Once you're
both on board
proceed to the hijacked
coach immediately.
The first time
you see a chance
to seize the hijacker without
hurting any of the passengers,
I want you
to take it.
Let's be precise people.
I want a clean operation.
Yes, Sir!
Captain, I'd rather not go
on this mission with him.
Let me go alone, Sir.
Hey what's your problem, Bruce?
What have I ever done to you?
Why do you treat me like
this, huh?! I don't get it!
There's nothing to get...
I just don't like
you. That's all.
Your Dad was an SDF Captain
and your brother was a Panzer.
Both of them were killed
in the line of duty.
And now you've joined up. You've
got a lot to prove don't you?
Is that why you're so
reckless in the Sim Room?
Well, I don't want
to get killed
just because you're
trying to be a hero
to get the monkey
off your back.
I don't plan
to die...
I know what it
takes to survive.
What do you know
about surviving?!
...This is your first
mission! You're a novice!
You don't know anything!
Bruce! That's enough!
Who's in command here?!
You are, Captain.
There will be no changes to my
plan. The mission stands as is.
Prepare to board
the Six-twenty.
Sirius Platoon, suit up!
We're approaching our target!
We have you on visuals Big One.
It's about time you showed up.
We'll take it from here. Thanks
for the reconnaissance, Julia.
It was nothing,
Captain. Anytime.
Spica Platoon is heading
home. We wish you luck.
Scan download from Spica
Platoon is now complete...
Let's move in. Eagle One
you're now clear for take-off.
Opening hangar.
Eagle One is ready
for take-off.
Launch, Eagle One!
Come in, Six-twenty Express.
We're requesting
permission to come aboard.
I have Catherine with me.
Catherine's here. Answer
him, you fool! Say yes!
Please! Don't shoot!
This is the Conductor of
the Six-twenty Express!
Permission to come
aboard granted!
Please dock with
the main engine.
All right, Louis. Move
slowly. Act scared.
We're trying
to buy time.
Right.
What's taking
them so long?
What are they doing? Just get on
the freaking train! Hurry up!!
What are you waiting
for? Let's go!
Right!
Man. Thanks, Bruce.
Sorry about that.
You're a hindrance, Yuuki.
You can thank me by going
home! Quit the SDF!
I won't do it!
Don't expect any more favors.
David, Louis,
so far so good.
Bruce and Manabu
have made it on.
Well, did I seem scared? Do I
get an award for my acting?
Don't give me that.
You really were scared
to jump, weren't you?
Hey, give me a little credit.
I'm tougher than that.
Heh... Let's go.
Right.
Captain. We're
in position, Sir.
Standby.
[Hijacker] She boarded the
train two minutes ago.
She should be here by now.
What's taking so long?!
[Conductor] I don't
know. I'll go see.
No! You stay!
[Baby cries]
Shut up! Shut that
thing up now!
I can't! He's scared!
Please don't hurt him!
He's just a baby!
He can't help it!
I'll try to get
him to quiet down!
David, where are
you? Hurry up!
We're almost there!
Hang tight!
Stop! I can't take it! Shut
him up now or I'll kill him!
No! Please!! No-ho-ho! Don't
hurt him! Don't hurt my baby!
Get away from him!
Don't touch my baby!
Shut that little
monster up right now!!
Bruce! They're in position!
Attack in thirty seconds!
No, ho, ho! Get away!
Leave my baby alone!
Ple-hee-hease! Shoot me!
Not him! Don't hurt my baby!
I can't take it anymore!
I'll kill you all if he
doesn't shut up right now!!
No! Give my baby back!
Give him back!
No!!
Space Defense Force!
...Liars!
...Get away from me
or I'll kill her!!
Don't do i-i-it!!
No!!!!!!!!
Damn him!
Manabu.
Passengers, everything
is safe and secure.
Please move to the rear coach
in a calm and orderly fashion.
Thank you very much.
What have I done?
It's over. We're going
to get you some help.
You are one crazy kid.
Hey, Yuuki.
That was a reckless move!
You could have been killed!
If you have a death-wish
join another platoon!
We don't want you here!
All of the passengers
have been taken care of.
No one was
seriously injured.
Manabu! You've
been hit!
Why didn't you say something!
That needs to be sterilized!
[Bruce] Manabu's gun
doesn't fire?
[Bulge] No... It's just a
keepsake of his. It's an FW308;
the model that the SDF used to
use back in the old days...
It belonged to his
father, Wataru Yuuki,
the former captain
of Big One.
To our commander and
friend... Captain Yuuki!
Goodbye, my sons... This
universe has been my home
but I must leave it for
the Ocean of Spirit...
Be brave, boys. I will
always be with you.
Father.
Father!!!!
Kanna. It'll be long
this time, my love.
I'm Sorry.
There he is.
Well, well.
Hey there, hero.
Hey.
How's your arm,
Manabu? Is it okay?
Yeah. It actually
feels normal again.
The medical technology here is
amazing. They can do anything.
They can't bring the
dead back to life.
No amount of technology
can do that.
Here, Yuuki.
Take it.
But I have
a gun already.
It's broken.
A gun that doesn't fire
is worthless, Yuuki.
Put that old relic on a shelf
where it belongs and take this.
I know my duty.
It's to protect the people and
I don't need a gun for that.
You can gamble your
own life on that ideal
but not the lives of
your platoon members.
Now take this side-arm or quit
the SDF. It's your choice.
All right, then.
I'll take it.
Good call.
I said I'll take it...
but I'm not going to use it.
There... are
you satisfied now?
You'll use it someday,
Yuuki. It's inevitable.
You can't avoid
it in space...
You have to kill if
you want to survive.
[Narr] Their two
opposing wills
are like two trains
on a crash course.
The collision is imminent.
Which one will survive
and emerge from the
wreckage is the unknown.
That is a question that
only destiny can answer.
[Operator A] We have an
unidentified train
at Alpha Centauri.
[Operator B] Affirmative.
I'm picking it up, too.
Planet of origin: unknown.
Planet of destination: unknown.
How can this be?
I recommend alerting the
commander immediately.
Roger that. Calling Galaxy
Railway Headquarters.
This is Deep Space Substation 7
reporting an unidentified train.
Come in, headquarters.
On the next
Galaxy Railways
we encounter a train
bound for nowhere
and an unsuspecting
passenger who's in danger
of losing his soul forever.
Can we get him to see the light
before his ticket is punched
for a journey that has no end?
See you next time
on the Railways!