Stations... the places that
we greet our loved ones
and the places that
we say goodbye...
The platforms are stained
with tears of elation
and tears of grief.
The sadness of a departure
soon turns into the
joy of an arrival.
But on occasion,
due to fate,
the promise of a happy
return is shattered
and an ordinary departure
turns out to be final.
Attention!
Please! Wait!
I brought you your
favorite drink, Bruce.
I hope it hits the
spot. Oh, Manabu!
Don't cry. We're here
to honor Bruce's memory
and he didn't like
tears, remember?
Bruce J. Speed of
the Sirius Platoon-
we commend your brave
service! We salute you, Bruce!
I don't understand. Why
did this have to happen?
There'll be hell
to pay for this.
Well, Bruce. Until we meet
again someday, my friend.
Goodbye.
That was reckless move.
You could have been killed.
If you have a death-wish,
join another platoon!
It's to protect the people.
I don't need a gun for that.
You can gamble your
own life on that ideal
but not the lives
of your platoon members.
Now take this side-arm
or quit the SDF.
All right, then.
I'll take it.
Good call.
I said I'll take it, but
I'm not going to use it.
I told you not to carry
this gun anymore.
But it was
just training!
Training's how we
prepare for real missions.
It's not to be
taken lightly.
That was a reckless move!
You could have been killed!
If you have a death-wish,
join another platoon!
We don't want
you here!
Come on! Do i-i-it now!
Bruce! Please! Do it!
This ends now!
Go back
to hell!
I don't think Toxic Bruce
fits you anymore, do you?
Guess not.
Thanks, Yuuki.
I owe you.
Why! Why did
Bruce have to die!
All he did was
help people!
He was a good man!
It's not fair!
He was all alone!
It's all my fault. If
I didn't get injured
Bruce would have never
gone to the hospital.
Louis, don't
blame your self.
Please... That would
make Bruce sad.
You had nothing to do with it.
It's just the way things are.
Hey, David... Do you think
that Bruce would mind
if I kept his
harmonica?
Just ask him. You were
his partner, Manabu.
What d'ya say?
Is it okay, Partner?
All right,
then, Bruce.
Bruce...
I don't like
your attitude!
What does a renegade
punk like you
know about the
SDF?! Well?!
Bruce!
That's enough!
Yes,
Captain.
Sorry, Sir... I
took it too far.
You're being too hard
on him, you know...
I know... It's just
that Sirius Platoon
is like a family to me. We
have our way of doing things.
Manabu's like
the adopted son
who comes in and starts
trying to change everything.
I see... And what role
do I play in this family?
Come on. Isn't that obvious?
You're the Father, Captain.
What about
David?
He's special.
He's our dog.
That's cruel.
[Yuki] Captain,
it's Murase.
Schwanheld. You're
ordered to report to the
Galaxy Railways Constitution
Inquiry Commission.
I see.
What?! Captain, no way!
He can't be serious!
Yeah.
That's crazy.
General Ivanov...
He did this.
Please come
with me.
Of course.
You know this is a
load of crap, Captain!
Why are you going
along with this?!
That's
enough.
But it's
wrong!
It's
my duty.
Ivanov!
[Ivanov] Captain Bulge's
behavior on Big One
in the Sutherland Planetary
System is in violation
of Paragraph 5 in Provision
23 of our Constitution.
I recommend that he
be punished severely.
[Commissioner] Mr. Bulge,
do you have any objections?
[Bulge] No I don't.
However, I'd like to mention
that the Alfort Galactic
Empire and the Cosmo Matrix
were both omitted from
General Ivanov's report.
These issues are vital to
our Galaxy's security.
[Commissioner] General
Ivanov has assured us
that the Secret
Intelligence Division
will conduct an investigation
into both of those matters.
But if we don't take
immediate action,
I'm afraid it'll
be too late.
Enough! Your
opinions are irrelevant
to this inquiry,
Captain Bulge!
[Commissioner] I'll look into
the investigation
of the Alfort
Empire personally.
Let us proceed
with the inquiry.
[Commissioner]
Mr. Bulge,
you have violated the
Galaxy Railways Constitution
and committed an act of
violence against your superior.
You are hereby relieved
of your captaincy
until this commission
reaches a verdict.
Sirius Platoon is
temporarily disbanded.
Understood, Sir.
I advise you to stay clear
of our investigation, Bulge.
Captain...
The word is that the Secret
Intelligence Division
doesn't believe the
alternate Universe exists.
They've dropped
the ball.
They're just ignoring
the Cosmo-Matrix.
It figures.
So What are you
gonna do, Captain?
I'll do whatever's
required of me.
That sounds like
you, Bulge.
How can they
do that?!
They can't just relieve
you of command!
[Louis] You were just trying
to save Big One, Captain!
That's not fair!
[Manabu] This is absurd!
Isn't it?!
I disobeyed orders and
struck a superior officer.
Worse than that, I lost
the life of a crewmember.
All of this
is true.
Just because it's true doesn't
mean that it was wrong!!
We'd all be dead now if you
didn't disobey Ivanov!
Including him! Are you
just gonna accept this?!
I will not resign my post
voluntarily... I can't.
But I'll have to accept
whatever verdict
that the Commission
hands down.
You're wrong!
Manabu!
Don't let them do this!
Fight for what's right!
Hey! Get a hold
of yourself!
Please,
Captain!
Prepare for your
new assignment!
You're now with
Vega Platoon.
Louis you're with
Spica Platoon
and David's with Rigel.
Yuki stays
here for now.
No, Sir! Forget it! I
will not obey that order!
I don't know what
to tell you.
Either report to your new
platoons tomorrow or quit...
It's
your call.
Let's not
underestimate the Captain.
I'm sure he has
some kind of plan.
Okay I want every bolt just
as tight as that one...
[Ivanov]
Hey under there!
Which one of you is
the head mechanic?!
We've got company, men...
I'm the head mechanic.
Then you're the one I need
to talk to. Come up here...
What can I do
for you, Sir?
Well, there was
a small object
that was being analyzed
on board Big One.
Do you happen to
know where it is?
Would you say it about
the size of a ruler?
That's right.
I haven't
seen it.
Where
is it?!
Oh! Yeah! Hey!
Now I remember!
This is the Secret
Intelligence Division's.
Glad to be
of service.
To hell
with it.
We're approaching
Planet Hyde, Captain.
Good.
Reduce speed.
Yes, Sir.
Yuuki! You're a Vega
member! Get off your butt!
Stop your
daydreaming, Yuuki!
Bruce!
Hang in
there, Kid.
Ready!!
Right! Let's get
her hooked up.
Yes, Sir.
Bruce...
Don't go.
Wake up,
Yuuki!
Sorry, Sir.
Yuuki!!
What was that?! Are you trying
to get yourself killed?!
Look, Kid. I know that
you're shaken up over Bruce.
But that's
no excuse.
You've got to stay focused
on the task at hand...
Right.
We don't want
to lose you.
Sorry, Sir. I swear I'll do
better next time. I promise.
Do you know what's going to
happen to Captain Bulge?
I don't really know at
this point, Manabu...
I can't imagine how
he feels right now.
[Layla] I can't see the
fate of the Galaxy Railways.
[Shula] It's being obscured
from us for the moment.
We'll be able
to see it soon.
What does the Alfort
Galactic Empire want
from our
Universe, Shula?
[Shula] There's no
answer to that yet.
Excuse me!
Please forgive me
for overstepping my
authority, ma'am,
but I'd like to have a word
with you, if you have a moment!
[Ivanov] Hey! What do
you think you're doing?!
How dare you come here
without permission!
We've already briefed
the Supreme Commander!
You have no business
here, Bulge!
[Bulge] Forgive the
intrusion, Ma'am!
Hey! Watch where
you're going!
You just splashed water
on my pants, you idiot!
SDF.
Ha! Look what
I've got!
Your turn. What's
the hold up?
Oh, Bruce...
Watch where you're going
next time, you jerk.
There will be no
stopping them.
The fate of the entire
Universe is in the balance.
This
is it.
Stay loose. We'll take
it one step at a time.
One step. That seems
like an eternity ago.
Where did we go
wrong, Bruce?
Why are all these bad
things happening to us?
Why did you
have to die?
Louis?
Manabu.
[Soldier] General,
our advance troops
encountered
resistance.
We lost a Destroyer. But the
Dimension Invector worked!
The Hole was
stable! We did it!
Now there's nothing holding us
back any longer, my General.
This is the day we've
been waiting for.
[General]
Launch the Invectors!
Let the
invasion commence!
[Soldier] Yes,
my General!
Launching all
Dimension Invectors!
The energy is stabilizing.
There are no enemy ships
detected near our
point of entry.
[General] How long
will it take
for the Dimension
Holes to fully open?
[Soldier] They should
be stable and ready
for use in 20
Weaves, General.
[General] That's too long.
I want them ready
in 10 Weaves.
[Soldier] But that
could compromise
the integrity
of the holes!
Any more
objections?
That's the
Captain's coat.
Yeah.
He must have a plan.
Don't you think?
Let's
hope so.
You win
again.
Good morning.
I brought you and the
boys a little breakfast.
You're one of a
kind, Captain.
So how's
it coming?
Well, she was pretty banged
up when you brought her in,
but we're
gettin' there.
She'll be as good
as new soon.
Any progress
on the other?
That one's a bit more
complicated, Captain.
'think I'm going to
need some more time.
There's not
much time left.
Not much time left
until what, Sir?
Doomsday.
[Commissioner]
Mr. Schwanheld Bulge,
the Commission has
reached its decision.
You are hereby relieved
of your command
as Sirius Platoon Captain
and are disqualified
from being an SDF member
from this day forth.
[Kinuko] Bruce,
I don't know
what we're going
to do without you.
Hey! Wait!
What's going on?!
What's happening,
you guys?! Is it true?!
Was the Captain
really fired?!
Yeah.
That's
insane!
He called us here to
tell us about it.
I'm afraid you
just missed him.
What?
The Captain said to
do what we should do.
What's that mean...?
[Miki] This is an SDF
Battalion Emergency!
All Platoons get
ready for take-off!
[Sayaka] Confirming
the location
of the enemy destroyer
that disappeared from
the Kowloon area!
[Kate] Location confirmed!
It's in the southern quadrant
of the
Harloom sector!
Launch and deploy all
Platoons immediately!
What are you going
to do, Manabu?
I'm going for it! Louis...
Be careful, okay?
So you two
are... you know.
Yeah.
What?! What am I
missing here, you guys?!
David! You be
careful, too!
Bruce. I need you
with me on this one.
Magnetic Barrier
Generator is a go!
Main Circuit
on-line!
Atomic Boiler
Pressure is a go!
All energy levels
ready for take-off!
The Warp Drive Coupling
is now in place!
All systems green and ready
for take-off, Captain!
Put the hammer
down! Let's roll!
Perhaps the brave men and
women on this mission
will help us rediscover
what we have lost...
the vision of our own destiny.
I pray that it is so.
Too often people in
positions of power
cannot see the solution
to the problem at hand
because of their own
narrow-mindedness.
Their lack of
vision then causes
the death of
many people.
Next time, the
Alfort Galactic Empire
begins its all-out
assault on our Galaxy!
As the lifelines
of our Universe
are being destroyed by
their radical power,
hope begins to
slip away.
What do these alien
invaders want from us?
See ya next time
on the Railways!