Take it.
But I have
a gun already.
It's
broken.
A gun that doesn't fire
is worthless, Yuuki.
Now take it or
quit the SDF.
All right. I'll take it...
But... I won't use it!
You'll use it someday,
Yuuki. It's inevitable.
You can't avoid
it in space...
You have to kill if
you want to survive.
Galaxy Railway trains stop
not only on planets,
but also at numerous
Space Junctions
located throughout
the Galaxy.
There, people can change trains
and choose their destinations.
Every so often
these stops
become a turning point
in people's lives.
Attention all
personnel:
Prison Train arriving at
Alpha 32 Space Junction.
We're having
a party?
Uh, huh!
Sirius Platoon's planning a big
get-together. I can't wait.
How nice!
That sounds
like fun.
Yeah, and I just won
a bet the other day.
If you like, we can
all share the prize
together this weekend...
Expensive Wine!
Awesome!
What
about me?
Yeah. You, too...
Of course...
Hey, Captain. You're gonna
be there too, right?
Come on, Captain! You
just have to be there!
She's right!
Hmm... Well, let me
see what I can do...
But whether I can
make it or not,
I'm still planning to
cover the expenses.
Wow! Thanks,
Captain!
That's great! You're
the best, Captain!
Oh, well- I had planned on
covering the whole thing...
Well, hey! If our
expenses are covered...
Let's add some caviar... and
some mozzarella cheese...
Yuki- You'll be
there, too. Right?
She went to
the Med Coach.
I guess she's gonna
stand us up again...
What's the
big deal?
Yuki's never come to one of
these little off-duty shindigs.
Well, I guess the
verdict's out.
She just doesn't
like us. That's all.
C'mon! Now where's
your sense of humor?
Uh, huh. I knew
you were kidding.
Try and locate
an escape-Pod!
Affirmative!
Our sensors are indicating
that 4 prisoners have escaped
from a Prison Train docked at
the Alfa 32 Space Junction!
Send out the
alarm signal.
The prisoners are
heading to the A25 Block
of the Space
Junction right now!
Attention! This is
an Emergency Alert!
Close down the Alfa 32
Space Junction immediately!
Yes, Sir!
Yes...
Come in.
Manabu. What's the matter?
Are you feeling sick?
Huh...? Oh, no, I feel
fine... It's just...
Is this about work? Or is
it something personal?
You don't have to worry. I'm
programmed to keep secrets.
Huh?
So am I to
understand that
you're not here for
counseling then?
Check the grid to see if
there are any SDF trains
near the Alpha 32
Space Junction.
It looks like Big 1's coming
back from Ariadne Junction.
Sorry you think
it's so funny.
But you said that
you weren't sick.
So, well, I
just assumed...
That's okay. I was worried
about you. That's all.
Well, it's
about the party.
Oh... I'm sure you'll
have a very good time.
Yuki. Is
there something
that you don't really
like about us... you know?
Of course not.
Oh, well, hey! Why
don't you join us?
You've never
gone to a party?
It's a lot of fun to get
together with your shipmates!
Shipmate? As I understand
the term it is by definition
meant to describe a human
being. Is it not...?
I'm just a Sexaroid
that's been assigned here
for medical care... So the term
doesn't really apply to me.
What d'ya mean?!
What in the world could make
such a nasty smell like that?
Acetic acid?
Well. Whatever it
is, it's awful...
Do you think it could it be
from him? Oh yeah... It is him!
Careful! Don't
touch the blood!
Uhhh...
It's just that the
chemical composition
of Antlian blood
is very unique.
It starts to oxidize
once it's exposed to air
and the process continues
until the blood
actually turns into acid.
It's quite dangerous.
This chemical will
reduce the effect.
That should
neutralize it.
Amazing!
All right, Sirius
Platoon, everybody listen.
Four prisoners have escaped.
At least one of them is armed.
He's carrying a handgun that he
took from a fallen SDF member.
Two of the prisoners
are traveling together.
The other two don't
know each other.
They're by
themselves,
traveling solo in
different directions.
What's
wrong, Liza?
Huh? Nothing. Don't
worry about me!
Keep up or I have no choice...
I'll leave you behind!
No! I can
do it!
All of them are
convicted criminals,
imprisoned after being
found guilty of murder.
No one
searches alone.
They're too dangerous
and unpredictable.
You'll each work
with a partner.
Yuki. Unfortunately, I need you
to join the search this time.
Yes,
Captain.
David, you go with Louis.
Manabu, you take Yuki.
Bruce, you're with
me. Let's move out!
[All]
Yes, Sir!
There's a good chance you'll
need to use a gun this time.
These are very dangerous
people... Play it safe.
Your real gun is
loaded, right?!
Yes.
All right, then. Good
luck. You'll need it.
Well, I'm over thirty and I'm
still playing hide and seek.
Well, you know the old
saying. What goes up...
Must
come down!
Let's go!
This is Manabu. We've found
nothing in Block A-25.
We are now moving
to Block B-18.
[Buldge] Okay. Remember,
one of them is armed.
Don't relax
your guard!
Yes, Sir!
He's alone!
Let's go!
Bruce and I are in pursuit
of one of the prisoners!
We're currently headed
toward Block F9! Standby!
Stay where
you are!
Man!
He's fast!
We'll get 'im!
Well what
d'ya know!
Looks to me like you've just
come to the end of the road.
Get your
hands up!
We nabbed
one, Captain!
Good work!
Which way?!
Right!
Once we're in the
dark, it's my game!
You might be able
to see in the dark,
but you have a lousy
sense of direction.
We got
another one!
Two down;
two to go.
Manabu!
See that... That's
oxidized Antlian blood.
Over here, too... The blood
trail leads this way.
One of them must've
had Antilian blood
splashed onto
their body.
Whoever it
is will die
if we don't get to them
and treat it them soon.
Right! Let's
get a move on!
Get up! Liza!
We've got to go!
Can you
keep going?
The blood trail
ends right here...
Look out!
Get Over here!
We can't forget
that they're armed!
They might be
right next to us!
They're smart; they tried
to stop the bleeding.
But it can't
be stopped.
We should be able to see
more bloodstains soon.
They're covering
their tracks.
But they can't get too
far with that wound.
We don't have
much time!
They'll die if we
don't find them soon!
Stop it!
You can't treat their wound
if you're dead, Yuki!
There! You see! Hey!
You can't escape!
So why make things
worse for yourselves!
Heh! That's
a laugh!
We'll be sent to Alcarz no
matter what we do here!
It can't get any
worse than that!
You're on a junction
in deep space!
There's no way
out of here!
We'll see
about that!
Let's go!
We've just made contact
with the two prisoners!
They're armed and heading
towards Block C-48!
We're on
our way!
Come on!
She doesn't
have much time.
Her body will oxidize
in a few minutes...
If she doesn't get the proper
treatment now then she'll die.
Listen to me!
She's gonna die soon
without the
proper medicine!
I'll die?
Toss your gun where I can
see it and surrender!
While there's
still time!
Nice try, kid, but
I'm not buying it!
It's the
truth!
She's come in contact with
Antilian blood, hasn't she?!
You're lying!
Please! Throw your
gun out... now!
Your friend is
running out of time!
Damnit!
Listen to me, if you
don't surrender right now
we may not be
able to save her!
Good. You did
the right thing.
We're coming over
with the medicine.
I missed them! Liza, we've
got to get out of here now!
Come on!
I can't go on.
It hurts too bad.
We're out of time. She's
dying... I have to go now.
Yuki! Wait! What do
you think you're doing?!
It's too dangerous to
go! You'll be killed!
Please don't worry.
It'll be all right.
You see, if I'm shot I
won't feel any pain...
And besides, if I am destroyed
it won't affect the platoon.
Another Sexaroid
will take my place.
That's crazy! Don't
you know by now
just what you mean
to us, Yuki?!
I'm the certified
Medical Sexaroid
currently assigned to
the Sirius Platoon.
No! You're our
shipmate! Understand?!
And I can't allow a shipmate
to foolishly expose herself
to danger
like that!
Shipmate... The truth is
I'm a Medical Sexaroid...
one who's been programmed
to help humans...
And whenever I see a human
in front of me who's in pain
it's impossible for
me to ignore it.
Now get out of
my way, Manabu.
Leon... I don't wanna die...
please let them help me...
Our medical expert is coming!
She can help your friend!
So don't shoot! Trust
me! This isn't a trick!
Okay then... But she comes
alone! You Understand me?!
Don't worry. You'll
be well in no time
once I give you
the treatment.
All right. Get
up. Right now!
Not before
I treat her!
You can do whatever you want to
her later! Right now stand up!
Yuki! You
let her go!
Don't move!
Drop your gun! Now!
And then go and find
me an Escape-Pod.
Sorry! I
can't do that!
Didn't I tell you? Things
can't get any worse for me.
You're dealing with someone
who has nothing to lose.
Don't you
understand?
She'll die if we don't
treat her immediately!
So What's it going to
be?! The gun or her life?!
Manabu!
The other
one, too!
Please! I don't
wanna die!!
Leon, just let her do her
job before it's too late...
How long could it take?
Please, Leon. I need help!
You don't
care... Do you?
What?! No! You're-
You're out of your mind!!
Come on, she wouldn't
have made it anyway...
The way I see it
I did her a favor.
But she would've made it
once she got the treatment!!
You mean... if...
What?! ...You were never
gonna let her have it?!
What do
you think?
You...
murdered her!
All right, now.
Throw your gun down
and put your hands
up! ...Or else!
Don't you do it,
Manabu! Forget about me!
You've got to carry out your
duty! No matter what happens!
Manabu!
Hurry up!
I'm warning you!
Manabu!
Why...?
Hey, forget about
that space pod!
I'll be better off
if you're dead!
Damn, you!
Yuki!
Yuki!!!
Manabu!
Are you
all right?
Yuki!! Yuki! Are you injured?!
A little help! She's been hit!!
Yuki, can you
hear me?
Can you
stand?
I think so.
Do you regret
doing that?
Do you need me
to carry you?
No.
No. I don't
regret it at all.
Thanks...
for everything.
Let's go, Yuuki!
Get the lead out!
Right!
Yes, Sir!!
Courage and compassion;
such a rare combination.
You've taken another bold step
toward your destiny, Manabu.
It was the easiest
bet I've ever won!
What are you waiting
for? Here! Have a drink!
Thanks. I
love wine.
Don't have too much; you might
have to drive us to the store.
Sorry I'm so
late, you guys.
Now there's a young woman
who can light up a room!
Wow. I guess clothes
do make the man!
That's it?!
What a geekoid!
He may be a little
tongue-tied
but you should have seen
the look on his face
when you
walked in!
Who...? Me...? You're
just saying that.
Yeah,
right!
Sorry, I'm late. I had
to draft a report.
It's my first day
back on the job...
I'm really looking forward to
working with all of you again.
Things just haven't
been the same.
Well, then. I think Yuki's
return to Sirius Platoon
calls for a toast!
What d'ya say?!
In life, we build
so many walls
to protect the delicate and
innocent beauty within us.
But occasionally, life leads us
to friends who truly love us;
friends who need not be
boxed out of our hearts.
Captain! Will
you do the honors?
To Yuki! The best medical
officer in the fleet!
[Attendant]
Please be seated.
As Captain it's imperative that
I not be controlled by emotion.
Stern detachment is
the shield I use.
But occasionally someone
slips through my defenses.
And for me that
someone is Catalina.
See you next time
on the Railways!