Kowloon-a city
that is infamous
for being one of the most
dangerous places in the Galaxy.
No one dares go close to
this lawless metropolis.
Kowloon is also known
by another name;
it is often called the
Labyrinth of Death.
Why? Why can't I see
the flow of time?
Why can't I
see our Fate?
[Sayaka] Receiving a weak
distress signal
from the
City of Kowloon!
It's an SDF signal requesting
an emergency rescue!
But that's impossible,
Commander.
There aren't
any SDF trains
on duty in that area
right now, Sir.
Find out who's
sending that signal!
Dispatch Sirius
Platoon!
System Check!
System Check
standby!
Sub-atomic Warp
Generator ready!
Magnetic Barrier
Generator is a go!
Orbit Network
Radar ready!
Big One is now in
take-off position!
Atomic Boiler
pressure is a go!
The Main Circuit
is now online!
All energy levels
ready for take-off!
The Warp-drive coupling
in now in place!
All systems green,
Captain Bulge!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
Let's move out!
Ahead full!
[Bulge] Listen up,
Sirius Platoon:
General Ivanov from the
Secret Intelligence Division
is coming with us
on this mission.
[Louis] But why
Secret Intelligence?
That info is on a
need to know basis...
And none of you on
this train need to know.
Let me be clear. I'm not
asking for your cooperation.
I'm demanding it.
Transmission of SDF
Signal confirmed, Sir.
It's definitely
a rescue signal.
It's coming from the Southern
part of Kowloon City.
David. Land by
that signal.
Never mind that! Land
away from the signal!
Did you hear
what I said?
Yes, Sir...
Taking her down
in the Southwest
sector of Kowloon.
[Louis] The nerve
of that guy!
Who does he think
he is anyway?!
Did you see the way he
treated the Captain?
I couldn't
believe it!
I wanted to punch
him in the face!
Louis.
What is it?!
He can hear
what you're saying.
You liar! It's off!
How dare you!
Don't ever do
that to me again.
Haha. I know exactly how
you feel, Louis.
That guy's definitely
an S.O.B...
But don't let your
mind be distracted
by your emotions
while you're on duty.
You can get
killed that way.
Right. Thanks, Bruce.
I wonder what Ivanov
is doing here anyway.
What's so special
about this mission?
I don't know...
But it must be serious for the
Secret Intelligence Division
to barge in
like this.
One thing's for sure...
We're about to find out.
It's definitely
coming from here.
This is SDF
Sirius Platoon!
We've come to help!
Is anyone in here?!
SDF...
Who are you?
I am...
Captain. Come in.
It's her.
Yes, the same alien who
invaded Headquarters...
Search her for
explosives immediately!
They're about the
size of a fist!
They look like
large plant seeds!
Find any?
No. She's all clear.
Hmmm...
If they're trapped,
they'll do anything to escape.
They've killed many
of my subordinates.
So you've had
prior contact.
You two kids,
go outside!
Make sure none of her
buddies are around.
You other two stay
with the alien.
There's no need to show
mercy if she puts up a fight
but don't kill her.
I want her alive.
We can't get
information from a corpse.
Plenty of orders
but no explanations.
Are you
feeling okay?
Please! You must help
us! I beg of you!
[Ivanov] Bring her in.
She can plead her case
to Secret Intelligence.
Listen to me, please!
My name's Liffle!
I came from
Istarion;
the 42nd Planet in
the Alfort Galaxy!
[Ivanov] Shut up!!
Come on now.
If you're gonna lie,
you're going to have to
do a better job than that.
Or maybe you
can tell me why
I've never heard of a
Galaxy named Alfort.
It doesn't exist in this
Universe. That's why.
Please...
Let me show you.
This is my home...
Planet Istarion.
I come from a Universe that
exists outside of your own.
Like your Universe,
ours is very beautiful.
My home
planet, Istarion,
is renowned for its remarkable
scientific technology...
peaceful technology
that was used
to enhance the
quality of life.
Mother!
Look up in the sky!
What are
they, Liffle?
I don't know. They look
like... battleships!
The ships were from the
Alfort Galactic Empire.
They threatened to destroy
our planet and people...
They said the only way
we could stop them
is if our scientists did
exactly what they were told.
We had no choice
but to cooperate.
At this very moment my
colleagues are being forced
to make weapons for their
Empire... If they don't...
their children and everything
they love will be destroyed.
Now, those same weapons that my
colleagues are manufacturing
are about to be
used against you.
This Universe is
facing the same crisis
that our planet did.
You have to try to stop them!
You people have armaments!
We didn't! We had no
choice but to surrender
and do what
we were told!
And now we've made
them great weapons.
There's no way that you
can defeat them in battle.
Unless...
Unless you use this.
This Cosmo Matrix
is my invention.
It can greatly amplify the
strength of your weapons.
[Ivanov] That's a convincing
lie you've concocted.
Don't take us for a
bunch of amateurs.
I know your intentions.
You plan to gain our trust
by giving us
false information
so you can study
our operation
and leak it back
to your people.
That's not
true! I swear!
Do you mind if I
take a look at that?
Hey, Captain. It does
resemble a storage chip
but I can't tell without using
the ship's computers...
Should I return to
Big One, Sir?
[Ivanov] You fool!
You'll do no such thing!
Did it ever occur to you
that they can gain access
to the SDF's main computer
through Big One's computer?!
Use your brain!
But if we don't
analyze the chip,
how are we gonna know if she's
telling the truth or not?!
[Ivanov] You won't.
That's none of your concern.
The Secret
Intelligence Division
will be the
judge of that.
If you don't believe
me you'll all die!
We only have a
little time left.
Soon a Dimension Hole will
open up between our Universes
and the invasion will begin.
Then it will be too late.
We refuse to be manipulated
by your false information.
General Ivanov... Perhaps
we shouldn't automatically
assume that she's
lying to us.
When I want your advice,
I'll ask for it. Captain!!
I'm trying to help!
You can help by obeying
my orders, Bulge.
You must
believe me!
There is still a chance
to save your people!
I don't think that the
images she showed us
were manipulated
in any way.
I wasn't able to detect any
tampering or alterations.
[Ivanov] Those images
prove nothing!
Why don't you
believe me?!
There are millions
of lives at stake!
Look out!!
Now! Take cover! Go!
Manabu!
Coming!
They're trying to kill
Liffle all right.
Does that mean that
she's telling the truth?
Well, I'd say that
there's two possibilities.
One is that they're
trying to execute Liffle
because she's really
trying to help us.
What's the other one?!
They're staging
this chase
to make us believe she's
telling the truth.
They're freakin'
everywhere!
David! Turn at the
next corner and stop!
Roger that!
I'll buy
some time!
You guys get
back to Big One
and prepare for emergency
take-off! I'll be there!
Whoa! Bruce has his
bazooka! He's serious!
I'm staying
with you!
I'll be fine! You go on! Help
them get back to Big One!
Manabu! Hurry up!
This is all my
fault. I'm sorry.
Yuuki! Go!!
Mother!! No!!
Manabu!
Liffle!
Liffle.
Please... don't worry.
I'm just glad you're okay.
What's the
situation?
Kowloon's teeming
with aliens!
Bruce was buying us time!
He's still out there!
Emergency take-off
green! Initiating now!
Bruce! Get back to Big
One! We're taking off!
Bruce!! Come on!
The coordinates of
the Dimension Hole.
In the Cosmo
Matrix... Please.
No, don't talk! You need
to get your strength back!
Promise that you won't lose it.
It's your only hope.
They're still
after us!
Take care of her!
They're attacking!
Arm the Main Battery!
Prepare to intercept!
Captain! The enemy
fighters are retreating!
I don't like this.
Direct hit!
Hangar Coach damaged!
They're the same.
All right!
Now it's your turn!
Direct hit!
N-No effect!
Link all Main Batteries!
Fire simultaneously!
Direct hit,
Captain!
No effect!
Enemy ship undamaged!
Unless you use this.
It amplifies weapons strength.
It's your
only hope.
Captain! Liffle's
Cosmo Matrix!
It's the only way
to fight back!
Absolutely not!
You're incompetent. Can't
you see this is all a plot?
They want us to panic
and use that device
so they can
gain access
to all our vital information...
She's a terrorist spy.
You're wrong! She's
telling the truth!
She took a
bullet for me!
Hmm! You're out of line!
Direct hit!
Second battery coach!
How far are we from
the Warp Zone?!
Point five
mega-meters, Captain!
Big One is sixty-five
percent damaged, Sir!
We'll never make
it! Please, Captain!
All right then.
How dare you, Bulge! You're
disobeying a direct or...
I'm sorry. But I have
to do what's best
for the welfare of
my crew, General.
They're my
responsibility.
I must go.
Go where?
To the bridge...
Help me...
Or we'll die.
Error! Damn! Not again!
What am I doing wrong?!
[Liffle] It's okay.
I can help. I'll show you.
Liffle!
You're mad! We can't let
a prisoner on the bridge!
Get her out!!
[Ivanov] This is treason!
You're jeopardizing the
safety of our Galaxy!
I'll have your
jobs for this!
[Liffle] There.
It's uploading now.
The computer has
accepted the Cosmo Matrix!
Atomic Boiler Pressure
increasing rapidly!
It's in the red
zone, Captain!!
Rotation Speed reaching
critical levels!
Divert All Energy to
the Main Battery!
Lock all gun-ports
on enemy ship!
Turning guns! All Gun Ports
are locked on target!!
All guns! Open fire!!
Liffle! It worked! Yuki!
Lay her down!
Help her!
Hello, Mother... And Trille,
my sister, you've come to.
[Manabu] Liffle!
Don't die!
Captain! We're losing
power! I can't stop it!
Weapon Systems down!
The Main Circuit's
off-line! It's fried!
They're attacking, Captain!
Energy decreased by 30%!
How far to the Warp Zone?!
At our current
speed; forty seconds!
Divert all available
power to the engine!
Warp Zone in
twenty seconds!
Engage Warp Engines
the instant we enter!
Incoming
seeker missiles!
It's damaged, Sir! I can't
enter the coordinates!
Go ahead! Do it now!
You're mad! Without coordinates
we could hit something and die!
If we don't try
we'll die anyway!
Louis!!
Emergency Warp!!
I can't see anything. I
can't do anything to help.
An opportunity will arise.
We must keep trying.
All I see is darkness.
The lights are vanishing.
No, it can't be...
Shula... we must fight.
It seems that Destiny
itself has derailed
from its
appointed track.
The future of the
Universe is now careening
into the darkness
like a runaway train.
What will happen? Where will
it end up? Nobody knows.
After an
emergency warp,
Big One is forced
to crash land
and I'm hanging
on by a thread!
While Bruce and Manabu
race to save my life
some of the
other Platoons
engage the Alfort
Destroyer in battle!
Looks like the
war has begun!
See ya next time
on the Railways!