Stay alert! D'you
wanna get killed!?
Sorry!
It has been said that,
deep in our hearts,
a solitary flower blooms. This
flower is a vivid reminder
of someone made up from
the scents and colors
of half-forgotten
memories;
in essence a
portrait of someone
who is
unforgettable to us.
Out of the 11 smugglers, we
took 7 to the Prison Coach.
The rest, who
were injured,
were taken to the
Medical Care Coach.
Mission complete...
We'll return to Destiny.
Yes, Sir!
Wait a
minute!
There's time... if
you guys hungry?
Sure. We could eat,
Sir... That'd be great.
Then may I suggest we try
this Station's packed lunch?
Big 1 is scheduled to
take off in 30 minutes.
U-Um?
Ah?
But we have
rations, Sir.
I know, but use this
to buy us all lunch.
Y-Yes sir.
I can't let you make a
personal call from Big 1.
Huh? Oh.
Thanks Captain.
No, it's fine. So
how have you been...?
Oh, that's good...
Don't worry about me;
you're the one with
the dangerous job.
As long as I know
that you're safe.
That's all that
matters to me.
Well, anyway Catalina;
happy Birthday.
Thank you!
I'll give you your
present next time, okay?
Oh, you don't need
to do that...
Hearing your voice is my
present. That's all I need.
Talk to
you soon.
Captain?
I'm glad you like them.
It's too drab in here...
I think they freshen up
the room a bit, don't you?
Yes, you're right...
They do add something...
Oh, is
that for me?
My Vacation Form. It
still needs your signature.
But I guess you
already knew that!
Of course.
Well, that was weird. It's not
like him to be absent-minded.
Yeah. Except when he's thinking
about his old girlfriend.
No way... Not our
Captain Bulge...
Wanna bet?
Why not? I've got ten thousand
that says you're wrong.
You're on!
Stop me if
I'm wrong Louis,
but didn't you just
take a vacation?
As a matter of fact Louis
has taken three vacations.
But statistics say that it
isn't unusual for a rookie...
Spare us the details, okay?
So, what kind of mischief
are you getting into
this time, Louis?
Just the usual stuff. You
know... cleaning my room;
reading a book,
doing some shopping;
Maybe take a few dance lessons
and watch all the TV shows
I've been recording; and, oh,
did I say cleaning my room?
Well, I guess that
should take about a year.
So Bruce, why don't you ever
bother taking any time off?
What's up
with that?
There's nothing that
I really want to do.
Oh, bologna. It's just
that once you're an officer-
there's never enough time.
You may not realize it
but our own Captain Bulge has
never taken any time off
except for
a single day.
Well, that doesn't
make any sense to me!
Why wouldn't you
take any time off
when you're entitled to
it? That's ridiculous!
Emergency! The 134 Express is
stuck in the Melbiunous Zone
of the Ulysses
Planetary System!
Sirius Platoon dispatch and
head for the scene immediately!
Today's menu was
extraordinary as always.
Simply
delicious.
Why don't you two
take the afternoon off?
Going shopping for more
interesting foods again, aye?
You're right. I'm always
trying to improve our menu.
Oh, no. What you're
serving's just fine.
But it's just that
I'm never satisfied
with serving the same
old things. Huh?
That's odd- It's too early
for the regular train...
You're right. And the whistle
doesn't sound familiar, either.
This is
Manabu.
I've just finished
escorting 45 passengers
to the Cornelia
Royal Hotel.
Bruce here, Captain. I've
completed my final run
to the Garden
Palace Hotel;
that's 90 passengers
in all, Sir.
Good work...
Now I'd like you all to
remain where you are for now.
When the back-up
train arrives
return the passengers
to the station.
Aw, Captain!
You have to take the
easy missions, too!
It's all part
of the job!
Captain?
What?
Couldn't've been... All
because of that flower.
Is something
wrong, Captain?
It's nothing, Yuki.
Sorry... Just a mistake.
Huh. Doesn't look
like anyone's here...
Did you find a place
that looked open?
Nope!
Man, I'm
starving...
At least they were nice
enough to leave a note...
Be back soon... I say we wait
here. This place looks good.
Who knows when they'll
really come back?
Look... Maybe we
should just move on?
Thank you so
much for waiting!
Oh, well we're
glad we did!
Your place looks great!
We're really hungry.
Yeah...
It's okay.
It couldn't be helped.
Let me get the door.
See? We didn't have
to wait after all.
Can you believe the
Captain calls this work?
No kidding. No wonder he
doesn't need a vacation.
Oh, well. We might as
well make the most of it.
Look!
Hmm? Well,
wha'd'ya know?
Hi, Wataru!
Oh! Sorry
to interrupt!
Couldn't this wait
'til later, Bulge?
Perhaps I overestimated
you, Captain.
Acting like this in a public
place where everyone can see!
And you; a
married man!
The Procyon Spatiotemporal
Accident? I know it well.
It's considered to be
the biggest disaster
in Railways
history.
Yes. Miss
Catalina here
is the sole survivor
from that accident.
That's why she still comes
to see me from time to time.
I came here to tell Captain
Yuuki that I graduated.
I-I had
no idea...
I'm sorry that I was
rude to you earlier.
I understand how it
might've seemed to you.
I think you're
forgiven, Bulge.
I recall reading the official
report on the accident...
The survivor was
quite young.
Yes, I was 10 years
old when it happened.
What a brave girl...
And you've grown up to be
such a beautiful woman.
I never thought
the day would come
that I'd see you look
a woman in the eye
and give her a
compliment, Bulge.
Well... You see... it's
just that... uh...
It's okay. I
understand. Well done.
Captain! Please!
It's not funny!
Despite the fact that this
fellow's a little rough
around the edges, he's still
one of the SDF's finest.
In fact he's quite
serious about his job.
He'll make a good
Captain someday.
I don't think anything scares
First Officer Bulge except,
perhaps, being alone
with a beautiful woman.
Captain. Have
some mercy.
Oh... I
almost forgot.
There's something I need to
take care of at Headquarters.
I'm sure you
two understand.
And congratulations!
Thank you! It was nice
seeing you again, Captain.
Take care of
things, Bulge.
Ah, right...
Will do, Captain.
So, Mr. Bulge, tell me:
why did you join the SDF?
Huh...? Oh,
yes... Of course.
Well, ever since
I was a child,
it was my dream
to join up.
Something big
happened back then.
It left an
impression on me.
What was that?
It was a terrible
accident; involving you.
The reports said that there
would be no survivors.
But then word came that an
SDF member rescued a girl,
injuring himself
in the process.
His heroism made
an impression on me.
And that's
why you joined.
I never knew who
that SDF member was.
I didn't find out
until a few hours ago.
That very same day... I lost
both my parents and my brother.
But... if the accident
had never happened...
I'm not sure if I'd have
discovered my own life's work.
The accident really
did that...? I get it!
It's a medical
related job!
And now you've just
graduated from med school!
No... I'm afraid
that's not it.
Huh?
At first I couldn't overcome
the shock of the accident.
I stopped eating and
became anorexic.
Wataru... I mean,
Captain Yuuki,
helped me to
understand my situation.
Do you know that
your mommy and daddy
are watching
you right now,
praying that you'll
get well soon?
They want you to start
eating again, Catalina.
So you'll
get strong.
At first, everything I ate
tasted like the sand...
But gradually I started
to enjoy the taste
of all
sorts of food.
That's when
it happened.
That's when I found
my calling in life.
You see, it was food that
gave me my strength back.
It was so clear to me; I
wanted to help other people
gain strength and
health in their lives
by serving wholesome,
delicious food.
That's why I became a
chef... Isn't that strange?
No... I don't think
it's strange at all.
So, is that what you wanted
to tell the Captain today?
Yes.
Would you like me
to tell him for you?
No. But thanks.
But, um...
Yes?
Well... If it's
all right with you...
could I... Could I call
you from time to time?
This is great! Dee-lish! Hey,
can I try some of yours?
Wait!! Where'd
you get your manners?
You're acting strange,
Manabu... What's up?
It's like you're
nervous or something.
What?! Why would I be
nervous? That's ridiculous!
You're acting
like a teenager
taking his girlfriend out
to eat for the first time.
Forgive me for interrupting.
But I was wondering
if you're somehow
related to Wataru Yuuki.
Oh! Yes, ma'am.
I'm Wataru's son.
Yes, I
knew it.
So you must've
known my father...
This is quite
a coincidence.
Your father must
certainly be proud
that you've taken
his old job.
Oh... No...
I haven't made it to
the rank of Captain yet.
Manabu, I think
you're blushing!
Well... If it isn't you,
then who is Captain?
Here
ya go!
Don't worry this one's on
me... for all your hard work.
Much obliged.
You don't say? Good ol'
Schwanheld Bulge, huh?
I'm so glad that
you're still safe.
You know, you may not
be so lucky next time.
I'll be fine.
Besides, don't forget
all of my duties are
not that dangerous.
I'm sorry, Schwanheld... It's
just that I couldn't bear...
Catalina...
Hey... You know
there's a restaurant
I've wanted to
go to with you.
So...
Let's go.
That'll
be great.
Don't
answer it!
But it might
be an emergency.
There's never enough
time, is there?
Sorry,
Catalina.
Thank you.
Listen dear...
That was Catalina.
She said she'd like to
discuss the new catering menu
with us before
we leave.
Talk about being
committed to a job!
There's something that
I'd like you to have.
I'm on
Tabito now,
but I'll be leaving soon
to come and see you.
The Express Train bound for
Kleznard will be arriving soon
at Track Number One...
For your safety,
all passengers are required
to wait behind the white line.
Catalina...
So how are things
going back home?
Fine... You know
it's amazing
how fast kids grow
up these days.
It must've been hard
getting called so soon.
You only got to see
them for a few hours.
I'm sure they'll
understand, someday...
But enough about me;
how'd Catalina react?
She had no
choice...
Still, I'm hoping
that she'll understand.
Life's tough
sometimes, isn't it?
Yes, Sir.
It sure is.
Guess that means
I won the bet.
No way, the
bet's mine.
I'm the one who put
money on his old flame.
Yeah! Right! That
means that I win.
How's
that work?
'Cuz what went down wasn't
with his old flame.
How can you
be sure?
He's not
coming back!
I've got one day off. No
matter what happens out there,
I'll be back to see
you. I promise.
Schwanheld, I knew the
next time I saw you,
you'd be coming
to say good-bye.
You've lost Wataru and
you've seen his wife suffer
and you'd tell me that
you don't want me
to experience
that same pain;
the pain that I felt when I
lost my family as a girl.
I thought I'd save you the
trouble. Goodbye, my love.
Wait. I thought you should
know; I proposed to her.
Unlike you, I'll always
be there for her.
She deserves that...
She needs someone to help
make her dream come true.
Her dream...?
I wish you both
the very best.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Man, was
she beautiful.
He has a crush on
another man's girl.
You might as well
give it up, Manabu...
You haven't got a chance.
She's already spoken for.
Oh, yeah?
Who is it?
I don't know who
specifically.
I just know that she's
in love with someone;
someone in
outer space.
And how do you
know that, Louis?
Because I'm a
woman. That's how.
Hey! I've got a
vacation to plan for!
And Captain, won't you
please take a vacation soon?
David and Bruce said
they're scared to ask
because you
never take one.
Uhhh...
We didn't
say that.
Don't blame it on me...
If you want one take one.
Yes, Sir!
Maybe it's time I
take a vacation, too.
[Narrator] It's possible
that the flower
that blooms in our
heart may wither;
but it will
never die...
Nourished by the thousands
of emotions and feelings
which flow thru
our heart,
it lives and
blossoms forever.
Next time we have to
evacuate a planet
that's about to be
destroyed by a nearby star.
But one stubborn old lady
isn't about to leave!
She's so convinced
that I'm her lost son
that even we start to
wonder if she's right.
But there's more to this
old lady that meets the eye.
See ya next time
on The Railways!