The infinite Universe...
Each of it's enchanting galaxys
teeming with individual lives.
Each life like a bubble
in a vast ocean.
Here one moment
and gone the next.
But even though
they are impermanent,
each life is so vital,
each one a thread
in the grand design.
How we live is everything.
It is our contribution,
our brush stroke on
the painting of reality.
Some hold back nothing.
They give back to existence
what it has given them:
life itself.
Silver... Schnader,
Jose... Captain Murase!
So many wasted lives.
I don't get it.
Manabu.
Sometimes there is no
reason. It's just life.
We did the best that
we possibly could.
Multiple spatial distortions
detected at 1,000 mega-meters!
Dimension Holes,
Commander!
What?!
Good God. What
do they want?
[Narrator] As for those who
give their very life
to protect the
lives of others...
their examples live on
and give us great strength.
Oh, no!
More enemy ships detected!
About 200 of them, Sir!
[Commander] What?!
They're breaking in!
[Commander] What do
you mean?!
They're hacking into our
Communications System, Sir!
I am Forecis.
Surrender Planet Destiny and the
Galaxy Railways Headquarters
to us immediately or you
will all be destroyed.
Your defenses
are no match
for the arsenal of
the Alfort Armada.
Surrender and you
will survive.
Resist and
you will die...
I will not ask again.
This is your final warning.
Captain?!
Listen up... I want to thank
you for the job you've done...
You have no idea how
proud I am of you...
All of you.
David... Yuki...
Bruce... Louis...
And you, Manabu.
No! Stop!
It's not over!
I won't leave Big One,
Captain! There's no way!
Me either. How can I?
It wouldn't be right.
Not after what Murase
did. He died for us.
Captain.
Very well.
Here, Sir.
Thank you...
Attention all hands.
We have been ordered to
surrender by the Alfort Fleet.
But Big One refuses to
fall prey to their demands.
The SDF will not hand
the Galaxy Railways over
to invaders. Our duty is
to protect it at all costs
and that's what
we intend to do.
Somehow we'll make it
through all of this. Bulge out!
[Yuki] The Magnetic Barrier
Generator is ready!
[David] Boiler Pressure
is back to normal!
General Forecis!
With all due respect
I beg you to reconsider
your decision.
It's clear that they've
figured out how to use
the Cosmo Matrix! If
we don't withdraw now,
we could suffer immense
losses, Madam. Even defeat!
You disappoint
me, Trille.
Forgive me, General!
How dare you talk of
defeat in my presence!
Your sister gave them the
Cosmo Matrix and you beg me
to retreat like a coward.
Both of you are a disgrace.
Take her to the lab
for brain-wave therapy
and mental rehab!
Yes, Ma'am!
Let us advance
to Destiny.
The Grand Command Ship
is accelerating, Sir!
They're at 800
mega-meters!
Captain... I think
we should retreat!
What?!
Their fleet's
too big.
We can't beat them even
with the Cosmo-Matrix.
But if we retreat, it'll
give us time to study them
and find their
weak point.
A decisive attack could
cause enough damage
to bring them back to
the bargaining table.
I'm in.
Me too, Sir.
Hmm... Very well then...
We'll follow Manabu's plan.
Yuki! Analyze
that ship!
Right!
David!
Yes, Captain!
Turning hard about!
This is their nerve
center...
Big One!
Captain! David!
Yuki! Manabu!
Big One has turned away
from the Alfort Fleet.
You're not going
to like this.
What do you mean,
Mr. Akatsuki?
I'm relieved to hear
that we've got more time.
We got a problem. The stopgap
bypass device was damaged
during that
full-scale attack.
How much more time
are we talking about?
I'm not sure. I...
--Are you all right?!
--Mr. Akatsuki?!
Sir, It's
too big...
We're going to need help
with the structural analysis
of the
command ship.
Are you okay?!
Yeah. I'm fine.
Besides.
How can I complain
knowing what he did?
You're right! Whitman
never gave up!
That train has caused enough
trouble. Destroy it! Now!
Big One needs
assistance!
We must put everything we've
got into analyzing that ship!
We've got to find
their weak point!
Julia.
Captain Julia!
Structural analysis
is right up our alley!
You need to connect that
blue cable there, Manabu!
And Don't forget to
synchronize the two signals!
Right.
We've got to protect the
Main Battery at all costs!
Right!
I've located the
main power source
and five back-up systems
on the Command Ship!
It's got 3 main engines
and 2 auxiliary engines!
I'm projecting the parameters
of their living quarters
so we don't target them!
The red dots you see are
their Energy Control Systems!
If we can attack
these with precision,
we can paralyze them without
destroying the ship itself!
Identify the target points
and sequence of our attack!
Yes, Ma'am!
Transfer the attack plan
to Big One immediately!
And let's pinpoint the location
of their Command Center!
Uh, oh. Looks like
we've been discovered!
They've blocked us
from their system!
If you ever need a
job, give me a call.
So, will it work?
Hey, we did the best we could.
It'll hold for a while.
What's a while?
One attack.
[Bulge] Turn us about!
[David] Yes, Sir!
The SDF train is
heading straight for us!
What an annoying
little gnat.
[David] What should we aim
at with just one round?
[Bulge] One of their
Energy Control Systems.
One system. That's not
going to do it. Is it?
The Grand Command
Ship just sent us
the location of
their power reactor
along with ballistic
trajectory calculations!
There's incoming audio!
[Louis] Big One, please
respond and verify
--that you've received the data.
[Bulge] --It must be a trap.
Come in Big One. This
is Louis Fort Drake.
--Please respond.
[David] --Louis!!
[Yuki] Receiving visuals!
Louis!
Good to see you, Captain.
Please stand by for more data.
This is the location of the
Control Center
on the Grand Command Ship
where General Forecis directs
the Alfort Fleet. I'm hoping
that you can come on board
for a direct negotiation if
you can disable their ship.
Louis... Excellent
work. Be careful.
We don't want
to lose you.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine. I promise.
Hang in there, we'll
make it through this.
Target those
coordinates!
Yes, Sir!
Captain, Where's Manabu?
Can you look at Mr.
Akatsuki's injury, Yuki?
Sure.
Manabu.
Louis!
It's good to see you.
I... I thought
you were dead!
No, I'm fine... They picked
me up from the wreckage.
I missed you so much.
Look out! Behind you!!
No!
Louis!
Louis!!
[Yuki] A massive detachment
of enemy fighters is
approaching, Captain!
All right. We'll
counter with our fighters
to protect Big One! This is it,
Sirius Platoon! Let's do it!!
--Yes Sir!
Manabu.
Louis?! Why?!
Trille! You're hurt!
Are you okay?
Why did you stay?
I had to, to
stop the war.
That's not
possible.
Why?!
It's too late... We
can't turn back. Not now.
Why?! I don't
understand!
Why do so many innocent
people have to die, Trille?!
Even your own sister
was killed! My God!
Isn't that enough?!
I know your heart aches
for Liffle. It has to.
She was your
flesh and blood!
If we don't try to stop this
war, she died for nothing!
[Trille] Come. Help me.
I'll show you the way.
Well. Time to
place your bets!
[Bulge] All Space
Eagles: launch!
Come. Race
to your death.
Commander. We're making
our final approach.
I want to thank you all
for the help you've given us
on this mission.
Bulge out.
Go, Big One!
[Bulge] Initiate the
Cosmo-Matrix!
[David] Here we go!
[Bulge] Cylinder rotation
exceeding the maximum limit!
[Manabu] Whoa!
[David] Look out!!
[Manabu] Got him!
[Bulge] Compressor Injector
is at twenty-eight hundred!
Pressure is red-lining! The
Valves are about to blow!
Rotate the Main Battery!
Lock on target! Fire!!
[Alfort Forces
Screaming]
You worthless worms!
[David] Big One's
completely unarmed!
We've got to protect
it no matter what!!
[Pilots] Right!!
[Manabu] Three enemy fighters
coming in at 9 o'clock!
[David] I see 'em! You're
messin' with the wrong train!
[Pilot] They're on my
tail! Augh!
Whoa-
[David] Manabu! Heads up!
[Manabu] David! You're hit!
[David] I'm okay! She
can still fly!
[Bulge] David! Manabu!
Disengage! Get out of here!
[Manabu] Captain! No! We're
staying with Big One!
That's an order!
Pull off!
Ready... Break!!
Yuki. Is everyone
all right?
We're all in one piece,
Sir. How 'bout about you?
I'm good.
Dammit! I screwed up.
Come on!
No. I'm staying
here... You go on!
David.
You've got to find
Louis, Manabu!
I'll be just fine
I can take care of
myself! Just Go find her!
Don't you die!
I won't... Go!
Manabu.
[Forecis] I will not tolerate
insurgents on my ship!
I want that train and
everyone in it destroyed!
Prepare to fire!
This is going
to be tricky...
What are you
doing here?
Looking for you!
Thank God
you're here.
You must
be Manabu.
That's right.
This is Trille.
She's Liffle's sister.
She's been helping
me this whole time.
Thank you.
I can't
believe my eyes.
You both seem so kind.
You're not barbaric.
We've heard so
many awful stories.
They're not true.
We're just like you,
Trille. We have hearts, too.
I believe you...
So did Liffle.
It's endless!
Why is this
happening?!
They hit our power
reactor when they attacked!
It's got to end,
Forecis! Right now!
You have no power
in this place.
You were doomed
when you walked in.
Why are you
attacking us?!
Don't come
any closer!
Just tell me why?!
First you must
learn respect!
[Louis] Manabu!!
General, please! They mean no
harm! They're trying to help!
Enough!
Trille!
The Galaxy Railways that you've
spread throughout your Universe
and the Orbit Pipes that
have been laid out endlessly
like a nervous
system have started
causing disturbances
in our Universe.
This imbalance
must be corrected.
The Railways must
be destroyed.
No! There has to
be another... Augh!
Manabu!!
There is no other way! The
Galaxy Railways is a disease
that is corrupting the
equilibrium of our Universe!
It has to be
annihilated!
Manabu.
Manabu... Manabu!
Bruce?
You're going to be
okay. I promise.
Am I dead?
Am I? Know this...
What you really are,
Manabu... can never die.
Manabu!!
Oh, God... Manabu, can you
hear me? Please don't die.
I'm okay...
Careful!
The Galaxy Railways is
not a disease, General...
You're wrong...
My father... my brother...
many of my friends...
they've all died... they
gave their lives for it!
The Railways are the ties
that link all life together
in our Universe. They
connect our hearts and minds
and unite us as one.
If the orbit pipes are causing
disturbances in your Universe
then there has to be some
scientific solution...
This war has to
end right now!
Manabu! No!
Our Master sees
what we can not.
He made it clear that
this war is unavoidable.
It is part of our
destiny- it is our Fate!
No!!
Not this time.
It's my destiny to stay
on this planet and fight.
We're in charge
of our destiny.
We shape it with our
actions! Can't you see?!
Enough!!
Don't hurt him!!
Manabu!
Trille. How could
you? I am your master.
Not any more.
Trille.
It had to be done...
Take this. Go.
Your people are waiting for
you... There's not much time.
Thank you, Trille.
[Louis' Voice] Come with
us to Destiny!
[Trille's Voice] No. I must go
back to my own Universe.
I have to tell
them what happened.
They must know the
truth about your people.
Will we see
you again?
I hope so.
Manabu! Hold on!
I've got you!
Louis! Let go!
You have to!
No! I won't!
If you don't let
go we'll both die.
I don't want that.
I want you to live!
I can't! I won't
let you go!
Louis!!
I can't live without
you! I'd rather die!!
I love you.
Manabu.
I think we've got a train to
catch... Come on. Let's go.
Thanks, David.
Captain! They made
it! They're alive!
Hey! Over here,
you guys!
Hi, everyone...
We did it.
[Shutaro Barking]
What are you
so excited about?
What is it, boy? Do you
know something I don't?
I'm proud of you,
Son... Well done.
Thanks, Dad.
Uh, excuse me.
Huh?
You're crying.
I was wondering why.
You were huh?
Well, some friends died
and I got to see them
all one last time.
Wow! You mean you saw ghosts?
No. No ghosts.
It was really them.
Oh... Hey, are you in the SDF?
Mhmm.
Wow! No way! That's so cool!
Have you ever been on Big One?
Mhmm.
Awesome! I wanna ride
on Big One someday.
Here.
Huh?
Keep that. It brought
me good luck.
Thank you! See ya later!
The dreams of a child
seem like innocent folly
but if carried through
they have the power
to change the Universe.
[Narrator]The Galaxy Railways
continues to connect the hearts
of all life in the Universe,
offering endless possibilities
to those who travel
on its lines.
As it continues to expand,
so do the dreams of man.
So long as we desire to
embrace the Infinite,
the Railways will
always be there.
And if there is ever a time
when life takes a troubled face
and darkness clouds the mind,
just look up and you'll see
the light of a train
heading to new horizons.
It might even be Big One,
the legendary locomotive
that saved the Universe!