Among the Galaxy
Railways trains,
there is one that has no
destination scheduled;
not even its
next stop.
It is the fate of the
passengers on board
that determines the route
of the 777 Express.
This mystical train
brings each passenger
to a place that is along the
path of their own destiny.
Those who ride it are
people who are disatisfied
with not knowing what the
future holds for them;
people who are
searching for the key
that will unlock the mystery
of their own fate...
But occasionally someone
boards the 777 by accident.
Or is there such a thing in
this life as an accident?
Manabu, you'd
better hurry up!
You're going to
miss your train!
What are you
doing up there?
I'm packing.
They might not give
you another vacation
if you're late getting
back from this one!
Now get your
rear in gear!
All right! All
right! I'm coming!
Please be
safe, Manabu.
I will, Mom.
I love you!
He'll be
back, Shutaro.
Wait!
One more!
Made it. The Five-fifty
is supposed to go
straight to
Destiny Station.
Great. I'm going to be late
from my first vacation.
I'll be cleaning
trains for weeks.
Oh. Good.
Uh. Excuse me.
Yes, good day, Sir.
Can I be of assistance?
Yeah. Does this train
stop at Destiny Station?
Destiny Station...? Well,
I can't say for sure, Sir.
But if you
stay on board,
I'd say there's a pretty
good chance that it might.
Look, just tell me
where our next stop is
and how long 'til
we get there.
Where this train stops
next is our next stop.
And we'll arrive
when we get there.
It was a
serious question.
Yes, Sir. And I provided
you with a serious answer.
I wish I had more information
for you but I don't.
That's the nature of
riding the 777 Express.
What? You're
kidding me!
I didn't think the
777 really existed.
Yes, Sir.
I've heard all
about this train.
It has no destination;
no terminal station;
its track keeps extending.
So it really exists after all.
I just assumed
that it was a myth.
No, Sir! We're here
and we're ready to serve!
I hope you enjoy
your flight!
Aw, man! Am
I in trouble!
Sir?
I'm supposed to be
back at headquarters.
I got on
by mistake...
Was it a mistake...?
Or was it your destiny?
I'm starting
to believe
that there are no such
things as mistakes Manabu.
It's all fate...
Huh?!
Is this man an acquaintance
of yours, Sir?
Saboru?!
...Is that you?!
[Bully]
Get 'em!
[Bully 2] Damn!
You're crazy, kid!
Let's see that curve
ball of yours, Manabu!
Okay!
Not bad!
Thanks! Hey, why don't we
all join the SDF when grow up?
I'll be
the Captain.
Mamoru, you and Saboru
can be on my crew.
No way! One of us should
be the Captain! We're older!
I think
I'll pass.
I don't want to join
the Space Defense Force.
I want to
be a painter.
I want to travel the Galaxy
just as much as you guys
only I want to do it
with my sketchbook.
After I draw all
the amazing sights,
I'll come back to Tabito and
become a famous painter.
Hey, that's your
sketchbook, isn't it?
Cool! Can I
have a look?
Aw, yeah.
These are nice...
Man, Saboru, you've
really gotten good.
These will make great
paintings! This is your dream!
They're all blank...
Are you okay?
Why did you stop, Saboru? Did
something happen? What's up?
I started
thinking.
What do
you mean?
What's the purpose
of it all, Manabu?
Our fate has already
been decided.
Why live life if
we're not in control?
If we're only acting
out something
that's been pre-determined?
It's not worth it.
Of course
it's worth it!
Receiving an
Emergency Transmission
from the
777 Express!
[777 Conductor] I don't
know what's happening!
Only three coaches are
attached to the engine!
The other six are
missing! Please...
Communications are
down! We've lost them!
Quickly! Dispatch
Sirius and Spica!
Headquarters! Come
in! Can you hear me?!
Please come in!
We need help!
Emergency dispatch requested!
Sirius Platoon! Spica Platoon!
Take off
immediately!
The 777s ID Signal
has disappeared!
The 777 isn't supposed
to be lost yet.
A dark force is trying
to disturb the order
of our Universe. We cannot
allow it to alter our Destiny.
Yes, Shula...
I understand.
The train's drifting!
What's going on?
We've derailed, Sir!
We're being pulled!
Pulled
by what?!
A Spatiotemporal Planet! We're
in its gravitational pull!
There are no Spatiotemporal
Planets near Tabito!
But if we're not near
Tabito, where are we?!
We're under
attack!
By who?! None of
this makes any sense!
Here! Put
this on!
What's the use? We
can't escape it.
Escape
what?!
Our fate. This is
the triple seven...
If this train took us
here, this is our destiny.
So, you're just going
to let them kill you
without putting
up a fight?!
Can a man win a fight
against his own Fate?
I've seen others fight death
against impossible odds
with every breath
in their body!
Come on man, what's
the matter with you?!
Where's the Saboru
I used to know?!
The one with
a heart!
This darkness; it's
not from our Universe.
They're from
another dimension.
Yes. But what are
their intentions?
Why the 777?
I don't know.
Why can't we see?
This is the
777 Express!
Please stop your
attack! We are unarmed!
This is a civilian vessel!
Please hold your fire!
We can't just let ourselves
be pulled into that Planet.
We've got to try going
backwards! Full reverse!
We need all the
power we can get!
[777 Conductor]
Yes, Sir!!
Here they come!
Quick! Get down!
It's no use,
Manabu... Why resist?
This is the way it
was meant to be.
What are you talking about?!
Who knows how this'll end?!
We might not make it out of
here! But we've got to try!
We've got to fight, Saboru!
You can't just give up on life!
What about
your dream?!
Headquarters!
Do you read me?
This is the 777! We are under
attack! Please send help!
Don't you see? Fate
drew us both here!
It doesn't matter what
we try to do, Manabu!
We can't change our destiny.
Why can't you accept that?!
If I accept it then I'm dead.
I want to live! Don't you?!
Sir! It's useless!
I can't get through!
[Alien language] Are
there only three?
Don't underestimate them.
Be efficient.
Slaughter them.
Yes, Sir!
Saboru!
Calm down!
Hey, Conductor. Take
him to the front car.
Y-Yes,
Sir!
Please, Sir!
This way!
Good shot,
Sir!
Go, Saboru! Get
out of here! Now!
Manabu.
Go! Now!
Do it!
Please,
Sir! Hurry!
But...
Manabu... Why can't I sense
your spirit...? Where are you?
Commander! Our radar
has picked up a train
six thousand mega-meters
from the Tabito System!
Identify it
immediately!
Identity confirmed!
It's the 777, Sir!
The main engine and
three of the front cars
are unaccounted
for, Commander!
Rescue any survivors! Find
the front end of that train!
Urgent news from Headquarters!
They've found it!
The 777
is adrift
six thousand mega-meters
from the Tabito System!
Spica Platoon is
just now arriving
at the accident
scene, Captain!
Sir! They're beginning rescue
operations as we speak!
This is Spica
Platoon reporting.
The rescue operation
is 80% complete... However,
The conductor and some of the
passengers are unaccounted for.
An SDF member who
boarded at Tabito
is among the
missing passengers.
Manabu.
That idiot!
Look sharp platoon! This
mission is far from over!
We've got to locate the engine
and the missing passenger cars.
We'll continue to sweep the
area until we find them.
[All]
Yes, Sir!
This is the 777 Express!
Headquarters! Please come in!
Sorry. You leave
me no choice.
Oh, no! I hope
he's not hurt!
Sir! Thank goodness you're all
right! I thought you were dead!
You've
been hit!
I'm okay.
Saboru! What's the
matter? Are you all right?
No! Of course I'm
not all right!
I'm about to be butchered
by aliens! How can I be?
There's nothing we can do!
They're going to kill us!
It's our
destiny, Manabu.
You don't know that! Maybe
we're supposed to survive!
Go ahead and do
it, Manabu! Hit me!
Maybe I should! It
might wake you up
from this coma you've
gotten yourself into!
Sir! The door!
It's melting!
Look out!!
The power's cut off!
What's going on?
Over there, Sir! They've
hit the main power line!
We've got
to fix it.
We've got to
connect these.
Not with your
bare hands!
Manabu... Why do you try so
hard to do the impossible?
Why can't you just accept that
this was all meant to be?!
Remember when those bullies
surrounded us on Tabito?
We didn't just accept that we
were going to get beat up;
that it was our destiny.
We fought back and we won!
Mamoru never gave up. He
gave it everything he had.
He challenged his
fate to the very end.
What?!
Mamoru's dead?!
Yeah! Mamoru's dead but
you're still alive, Saboru!
You have everything to live
for! You can't give up!
What about your dream of
becoming a great painter?
Don't just throw that
away! It's your life!
You've got to fight for
it! We'll do it together!
We'll fight side by side!
Just like in the old days!
All right,
Manabu... Lead on.
Look out!!
Manabu!
Cover me!
Conductor...
Are you all right?
No... vital circuits...
damaged... Here, Sir...
This is yours... Please. Don't
let them take it from you.
I won't. I promise. I won't
let them take my dream!
Saboru! No! What
are you doing?!
Saboru! Why
did you...
Saboru...
Saboru!!!
Louis. Any
further reports
on the missing
part of the 777?
Negative... All channels
are open. Nothing so far, Sir.
Damn! This
is crazy!
How can an engine and three
cars vanish into thin air?!
Keep trying to
reach the 777!
Maximize
frequency range!
Yes,
Captain!
This is the 777
Express. Please come in.
It's
Manabu!
We need immediate
assistance. Do you read?
It's
really him!
That's
my boy!
Locate that
transmission!
Prepare for an
emergency rescue!
Yes, Captain!
Somebody! Please...
We're under attack!
Father! What am
I going to do?!
Manabu... Manabu, it's over.
Everything is all right.
Supreme
Commander...
Everything is as it should
be thanks to you Manabu.
Come, let
us go...
I am Destiny.
I am Shula.
[Cadet] Sirius
Platoon is reporting
that they've
found the 777!
Two passengers have
been rescued safely!
What an ordeal. It feels good
just to be alive, doesn't it?
Manabu...
I owe you.
Paint me
a picture.
Manabu.
Take good care of
him for me, Yuki.
I will.
Thanks for
everything, Manabu!
No problem.
Hang in there.
Manabu.
Way to go!
You did
it, Manabu!
Hmm!
Well done, Manabu. I'm
glad you're all right.
Thank you,
Captain.
It's been quite a
homecoming, hasn't it?
What is this mystery
known as destiny?
Is the path of a man
truly determined
before he ever
takes birth?
Has his every footstep
already been made
before he ever learns
to walk? Perhaps...
For some this possibility
is used as an excuse
to give up on
life; for others,
it is the comfort they
need to strive even harder.
It was you who came to me
on the 777 and saved me.
Wasn't it?
That was Shula.
I am Layla.
But I was there as well.
The two of us are one.
I know I seem like a
mystery to you, Manabu.
But you, too, are
a mystery to me...
You see, sometimes I
lose sight of your Fate
and I... I don't
know why...
I often wonder what this
means to our Universe.
Don't be concerned...
Just... follow your heart.
It hasn't steered
you wrong yet.
[Woman] It's time,
Mr. President.
Very well.
Our next mission is to
guard President Drake
of the Clarious Stellar
Cluster-also known as my Dad;
the worst Father
in the Galaxy.
He's not my
favorite person,
but when some
assassins ambush him
we have to put our
differences aside.
See ya next time
on the Railways!