Are machines alive? Do they
have souls? Of course not.
And yet there is an
unmistakable feeling of sadness
when one of our metal
companions meets its end.
They serve us; and
we depend on them.
It is this relationship that
creates an inexplicable bond.
Fantastic. The
future of our Galaxy
is in the hands of
a punk like this.
Hey, Kid... Battle stations!
We're under attack!!
Where are
they?! ...Huh?
If you were
awake, you'd know.
Uhhm. Sorry.
I was all finished.
I must have
dosed off.
Finished, huh? We'll
see about that.
This, bolt's
loose!
There's hundreds
of 'em.
And each one
has a purpose;
which is to keep guys
like you alive!!
Now check the
other bolts!!
All of 'em?!
Whitman really loves dressing
down SDF brats! Doesn't he?!
I've seen that kid
down here before.
This isn't his first time.
He must get in trouble a lot.
Well, after taking Train
Maintenance 101 from Whitman
a few more times he'll learn
the value of behaving.
Look! He's already got his
tail between his legs!
Guarding a train for rich
people; what an assignment.
It's right
over there.
Thanks.
Manabu's lucky he
missed this assignment.
Can I
help you?
You're an SDF! I
see you guys on TV!
TV? I see... This is a
big place to be all alone.
Where's your
Mom at? Huh?
Charlie!
Is that
your Mom?
Uh, huh.
You'd better go
protect her.
Right!
See ya!
Alrighty, mate.
Pegasus... you,
the beautiful one
that gallops through the air;
your wings will be broken
and you will be
covered with soil.
Every bolt? That old codger has
a few screws loose himself...
I heard that! ...You
might want to check,
behind you every
now and then.
Listen, Kid. I'll keep
this simple for you.
Each train has
its own character.
Unless you know which
parts tend to come loose,
you can't work as a mechanic.
And until you know that,
the only way to find out
is to check each bolt.
Look, I'm an officer. I'm
just here for training.
No... You're here because
you lack discipline
like most
kids your age.
All I'm saying that
I'm not a mechanic!
I don't want to know
everything about trains.
I see. You wanna fly 'em. And
you want to do battle in 'em.
But you don't want to know
how they work. Is that it?
Now get busy...
Every bolt.
Go on...
Crazy old coot. I've been
around trains my whole life.
My Dad was
a Captain.
I never saw him with
a wrench in his hand.
Wow. What
a classic.
What's this baby doing
in a scrap yard?
She's in mint condition. Should
be in a museum or something...
There's not a speck of dirt
on it. This is amazing.
Hey! What was
that for?!
Keep your filthy
hands off that train.
I didn't even touch
it! All I did was look!
Well, go look
somewhere else.
Why are you giving me
grief over this thing?!
It's an
old train!
It's just going to
be scrapped anyway!
Are you crazy?!
What are you doing?!
I didn't do anything
to deserve this!
Tell you what. You can
have a free shot. Go ahead.
No. Let go of me! I've
had enough of this!
No, I'm serious! She's
dating a Mongoran!
You look a little worse for
the wear there, young man.
Did a train
hit ya?
You could
say that.
Ha! You must have touched
the Eight-twenty-five!
Whitman's baby!
That's dangerous!
Don't take it personal, Son...
He's obsessed with that train.
The Eight-twenty-five
was the first train
ever assigned to Whitman
as a young mechanic.
If you think it's shiny now
you should have seen it then.
He had it so polished you could
see your reflection in it.
He was probably the
happiest man on Rosamund
until he lost his sister
when the asteroid hit.
I brought you lunch!
Can you take a break?
Yeah!
Sure!
At that time the
mines were booming
and Whitman was
going back and forth
to Destiny Station
carrying magnetic ore.
The asteroid came as
a complete surprise.
It destroyed half
of the planet.
Whitman was on an ore run
when the asteroid hit.
When he got back everything
he knew was gone...
his sister, his
parents, his house,
the mine, Rosamund
station-all gone.
The only thing that he
held dear in life
that wasn't destroyed was
the Eight-twenty-five.
Now you can see why
Whitman's so sensitive
about that old locomotive.
The Eight-twenty-five is more
than just another
train to Whitman;
it's the last link he has to
a life that he once loved.
But now, even that's
about to change.
Time doesn't wait for
anybody, especially the old.
The Eight-twenty-five
is on death row-
it's scheduled to be
scrapped tomorrow.
So hang in
there, kid!
...Please don't take what
old Whitman does to heart.
He doesn't mean anything
by it. I promise.
[Announcement] Good evening
passengers, we are now entering
the beautiful Magnetic
Caverns of Planet Rosamund.
In the past, these caverns were
mined for rare magnetic ores.
The exquisite colors in the
caverns' rock formations
are from the ore itself.
If you listen closely,
you can hear the mystic,
subterranean rhythms
created by the dripping
water and the magnetic ore.
Please enjoy
the ride.
That's
unusual.
Damnit!! The Magnetic
Shield has been breached!
Mommy!!
[Announcement]
Attention, passengers.
We have encountered severe
magnetic interference.
We are correcting
the problem
and we should be
underway again shortly.
Man! Thank
goodness!
This is the
Pegasus Express!
We have encountered
a Magnetic Avalanche
in the caves
of Rosamund!
We are now adrift
without controls.
Please send
some help!
Emergency Transmission
from Pegasus Express!
Their systems are down!
Communications lost!
Dispatch Sirius Platoon!
Get them in the air now!
Yes,
Commander!
Sirius Platoon! The
Pegasus Express has been hit
by a Magnetic Avalanche!
All systems are down!
Communications
have been lost!
Proceed to
Rosamund immediately!
That's
Whitman's planet.
I repeat! The Pegasus
Express is adrift
in the Magnetic Caves of
Rosumund. All systems are down!
Communications
have been lost!
Sirius Platoon
dispatch immediately!
All systems green,
Captain Bulge!
Awaiting your
command, Sir!
Let's move out!
Ahead full!
Hey! Have you seen
Whitman around?!
He's probably on the
Eight-twenty-five.
Thanks!
Easy now... not as
young as you used to be.
I'm not either,
old friend.
We're flying one
last time, Audrey.
This mission's for you.
Well, let's do it, old timer!
Mister
Whitman!
No way...
[Announcer] Number
Eight-twenty-five,
you are now on
a direct path
to Destiny's main ascending
launch. Stop immediately.
You do not have
clearance to take-off.
Whitman!
Wait!!
Hey!
What the-
I'll be damned...
[Buldge] The Pegasus
is located here-
about one fourth of the way
into the Magnetic Cavern.
We'll be entering the
cave in just a moment
and taking the same
route as the Pegasus.
Hopefully, the
magnetic surge
that overloaded their
systems has subsided.
I'm not
so sure.
Our electrical system is
already becoming unstable.
Can we
make it?
We will if our shields
hold but they're magnetic.
They may
get disrupted.
If worse comes to worst
we can always blast a hole
in the side of the cavern and
get the Pegasus out that way.
The Pegasus is
just ahead.
Their communications
are still down.
I can see them
from here.
We just need our shields to
hold a little bit longer.
Now this
is odd.
What is
it, Louis?
I'm not picking up any sound
in the cavern. Nothing.
It's dead quiet... It's like
the calm before the storm.
Captain! The Pegasus!
It's free falling, Sir!
Our Magnetic Shields
have failed, Captain!
The Main Control
System is down!
Get us out of
here! Now!
No! It's too late! The Cruising
System is down, Sir! ...Huh?
What's on your
mind, Bruce?
I'm going to try it
manually, Captain.
Bruce!
Wait!
Come on!
Please! Respond!
The Pegasus
is on the move
but her Cruising
System is still down!
She's being propelled by severe
electromagnetic activity!
What about
Big One?
We've lost
communication!
[Yuuki] Big One's down!
The Pegasus is in trouble!
[Shitman] I heard! I'm
old, but I'm not deaf!
Whoa! Man! This
baby's got some kick!
[Whitman] Not bad, aye? This
engine was designed to run
at marginal speeds with
a full load of ore.
But without the freight
coaches in tow,
she's got more speed and power
than some of the new rigs.
[Yuuki] Wow! But why
destroy a train like that?
Isn't she supposed to
be scrapped tomorrow?
[Whitman]
Who told you that?
Mister
Akatsuki.
That fool; always
talking too much.
Big One!
Another train?
That's impossible.
Back up wouldn't
get here this soon.
Yuuki!
I give up!
Hey. Why did you come
with me anyway, kid?
After you hit
me, you mean?
...I guess because I knew you
were only trying to help...
And that you were
going out on a limb;
risking your job
and your reputation
for something you believed
in. And that you were going
to be in big trouble
whether it worked or not.
You see: you
remind me of me;
except for the old
and cranky part.
Hmm? Hahaha... You're
too much, kid!
You are really something
else! Heh, heh!
Look out!!
It's okay! The shields are
holding! We're not dead yet!
The manual over-ride
failed, Sir.
Who went by?
It was Whitman's old rig;
the Eight-twenty-five, Sir.
I see... What about
the Cruising System?
Almost
ready, Sir.
Someone,
help us!
Don't worry, Mom. The SDF is
going to rescue us. You'll see!
Not good. The magnetic
activity is increasing.
David, What's
our status?
The Cruising System
has been reinstalled,
and the Sub-Control System
has just stabilized.
We're good
to go, Sir!
All right!
...Let's move!
Yes, Sir!
Yuuki...
Listen to Whitman.
If you work together
you have a chance.
Man. That was insane. Mister
Whitman! Are you okay?!
I'm
alright.
Let me take over. You can't
fly in your condition.
These caves are
treacherous, kid...
If you don't know them
they'll eat you alive.
You can guide me then!
Just tell me what to do!
Audrey...
[Yuuki] Is that
your Sister?
Yes... He told you,
didn't he? I lost her.
I lost them all. I was too
late... I was too late.
But not this time. We
gotta get to the Pegasus
before the next magnetic
storm hits! Full throttle!
Rosamund's core has
become unstable!
The computer is
projecting an eruption
that would destroy
half the planet!
Then Big One
is too late.
Our only hope is the
Eight-twenty-five.
There it is! I see the
Pegasus, Mister Whitman!
Stay with her, kid!
You'll only have one chance!
We've got to make
that connection!
Right!!
Can't stop... I have to try
letting go of the passengers!
Mom! Look!
Over there!
Pegasus! This is Freight Train
Number Eight-twenty-five!
We are attempting
to connect to you
with our coupler unit
and take you in tow!!
Am I dreaming?!
The 825?!
[Whitman]
Yes! That's it!
Now once the arms are
out pull the Foot Lever!
...That will cause the
Control Lever to pop out
and the rest is just
timing! You can do it, kid!
Don't rush it, Kid! Relax!
You've still got a little time!
Listen to the song
of the engine!
Get in sync
with its rhythm!
The song of the
engine? What's that?
It's the song I grew
up with! Just listen!
You'll hear it!
I promise!
We're closing
the gap!
We can do it! We're almost
there! Full speed ahead!
Aah!!
Missed!
We've
got it!!
Great!
Hold on!!
[Whitman] Come back
in! We're reversing!
Let's get this
baby out of here!
[Yuuki]
Right!
Huh?
Mister Whitman!
Are you
okay?!
Hey, Kid.
I wasn't late.
Good job, old friend.
We were right on time.
Mister Whitman!
This is
Captain Bulge.
Maintain your speed and
prepare to connect.
Rosamund is
unstable.
It is imperative that
we leave immediately.
Captain! Something's
wrong with Whitman!
Manabu?!
Please! Somebody!
...Help Whitman!
...H-He's not breathing!
...Somebody, help us! Please!
Ready!
...Fire!
Mister
Whitman...
Tighten those
bolts, kid!
That's what old Whitman would
have been saying all right!
I wish I could say that
I'm sad, but I'm not...
You see, Whitman was
at the helm of the 825
saving lives when he passed...
He was living his dream, Son.
You were right on time.
Like clockwork...
You saved them all,
Mister Whitman;
every one of them...
you and your Old Friend.
It's the 825,
Mom! Look!
Sometimes the failures
and disappointments
of our past are but
building blocks-
stepping stones that give us
the drive and determination
we need to succeed
in the future.
The heroic rescue on Rosamund
by a man and his old friend
will be talked about
for many years to come.
On the next Galaxy Railways
we meet a mythical being
that has the power to
steal memories from people.
And when Bruce has some painful
memories from his past taken,
he becomes a new man. But
can true happiness be found
by merely forgetting? ...See
ya next time on the Railways!