In this remarkable journey
called life we hurry about
trying to get everything
done from day to day.
There's little time
for anything else.
But occasionally this rhythm
is broken by unexpected events
that pay no heed
to the timetables
we have set
for ourselves;
events that matter-of-factly
change our lives forever.
Why do tragedies happen?
This question has
puzzled mankind
since the
beginning of time.
Move and
you're dead!
I think he's
had enough.
Crazy
daredevil...
That was the
last variation.
I've beaten all of
the levels now.
Step inside.
What is it, Bruce? Do I get
a gold-star or something?
Well, Yuuki. Do you know
where you made your mistake?
You were in serious danger out
there. You couldn't see it.
I told you not to carry this
gun anymore. You disobeyed.
But it was
just training!
Training's how we prepare
for real missions.
It's not to be
taken lightly.
But I wasn't taking it
lightly! You saw me!
Huh? Mommy, look
at all the bubbles!
...Aren't
they pretty?!
What is that
stuff...?
What's
going on?!
I don't know!
All passengers please remain in
your seats. Do not be alarmed.
Please remain
in your seats.
Sarah, honey.
I want you to put on this
space suit. Here you go.
Mom, I'm
really scared.
Don't be, honey.
There's no need to be.
Look, Ralph's not
scared. Hold on to him.
All right! What is it, Bruce?!
It's not just the gun!
You were treating
me like this
before you found out
that it didn't work!
What's the deal?!
Just say it!
Or aren't you man enough to
say what's on your mind?!
You're like these strawberries;
too sweet and naive to take.
And What the heck is
that supposed to mean?
I'm not sweet!
You want to protect the
Galaxy without firing a shot.
I call that being
naive and sweet.
How can I trust a guy
like you to cover my back?
A guy like me?! You just
stuck a gun to my head
and pulled the trigger! You're
a freakin' lunatic! Huh?
[Announcement] Emergency
Signal received!
An accident has occurred on
the Three-twenty-three Express
bound for Great Magellan.
The cause: unknown.
Scale and details:
unknown. ID Signal lost.
Communication
not possible.
Sirius Platoon,
Spica Platoon,
and Vega Platoon
dispatch immediately!
I repeat: dispatch
immediately!
All right, Sirius
Platoon! Let's move out!
Yuuki, one word
of advice.
...Don't assume that you can
diffuse a dangerous situation
with your
daredevil moves.
Look, I
know that...
Don't make me out to
be something I'm not.
Full
System check!
Standby for
system check!
Sub-atomic Warp
Generator: ready!
Flame Swallow is now
in take-off position!
Cylinder Valves open! The
Main Circuit is online!
The warp drive coupling
is now in place!
Ahead full!
Hold your horses, Julia!
We're going first!
Maximum Power! Iron
Berger, take-off!
Negative! We have
clearance, Murase!
You're the ones who have
to wait! Stand down!
Forget it! We don't have
time for this crap!
We're
taking off!
That fool... Murase
will never change.
Flame Swallow,
ready! take-off!
Big One!
Ahead full now!
Hmm? Man! That's
five times in a row.
What does that
mean, David?
Five tails. Look, just be
extremely careful today, okay?
Okay.
What's up with
this mission?
Why would it be different
than any other?
You tell me. Three platoons
...dispatched at once;
circumstances unknown.
What do you think it means?
Bad news.
I guess they're preparing
for a worst case scenario.
That's not
good, is it?
No,
it's not...
This is the kind of
rescue mission you go on
and wonder if you're going to
need to be rescued yourself.
Man, what
a mess.
It's
awful.
Now we know why they didn't
answer our communications.
No kidding.
What a nightmare.
We might be next if
we're not careful!
Heads up, men! Whoever did
this might still be out here!
Arm yourselves! I don't want to
be caught sleeping! Silver, you
stay in the Turret Coach! Keep
those guns hot and ready!
You got it,
Captain!
Maggie, take Falcon 1
out and patrol the area.
Stay within a twenty
mega-meter radius. Be careful.
They may have some sort of
optical camouflage.
Will do,
Captain!
Jose! Go with Maggie! I want
another bird out there!
Yes, Sir!
We'll search the immediate
area for survivors.
Spica and Vega Platoons will
help. Let's spread out.
If you
find anyone,
bring them to the
medical coach immediately.
[Both]
Yes, Sir!
Huh? ...Where'd you
come from, little guy?
Maaan. This is
like a scrap-yard
and a graveyard all
wrapped in one.
Yeah, this is freaky. I
don't think anyone survived.
They're
all dead.
What a way to die;
all alone in space.
It must've
been horrible.
This was definitely
no accident.
We're they sniped? ...No,
it had to be a bomb.
Luise. Are
you okay?
Yeah. Sure.
I'm fine.
Hey! Sirius
Platoon!
Do something about
this guy, would ya?
He's just getting
in the way.
Panic attack. Try to
take deep breaths, Yuuki.
You're
hyperventilating.
Manabu,
breathe.
Bruce. Get Manabu
back to Big One.
Have him wait
for us there.
Yes,
Captain.
Looks like you had a pretty
rough ride, little fella.
Hey! This one's still alive!
Captain! We have a survivor!
It's a child!
A girl!
David!
Report!
She's wearing a
space suit, Captain!
Breathing is faint
but audible!
Her suit is
leaking oxygen!
We need to get her
back on the double!
Hello,
Manabu.
Hi, Yuki.
How is she?
She could
be better.
Do you think she has a
chance to make it, Yuki?
A lot of that
depends on her...
Hmm?
Thank you so much,
Sir. You saved him.
Can I hold
him, though?
He doesn't like to be
upside down like that.
Oh, right.
I knew you would never leave
me, Ralph. Good puppy.
Ralph told me that
you're very brave...
You don't scare
him. He likes you.
Excuse me... Can you tell
me... where my mother is?
Mommy! ...Please!
...I need you!
Mommy! Mommy!
No, Dad! Don't leave us!
I can't live without you!
Yuki!
Is she...
I believe so. Her vital
signs aren't registering.
Her body is
shutting down.
Do something...
please!
You can't just give up!
You've got to try to save her!
There's got to be
something you can do!
Don't walk away
from her, Yuki!
Manabu, her body has
ceased to function!
How do you know?!
You've got to try!
She's not a machine!
She's a person!
What do you think
you're doing?
I was only trying
to help, Captain.
It doesn't look that
way to me, Manabu.
You've gone too
far this time.
You're suspended from duty
until further notice.
Based on our inspection
of the wreckage,
it's clear that this
was not an accident.
The devastation of the
Three-twenty-three Express
was the result of a
deliberate terrorist act.
They obviously
used an explosive.
We think the device was a
Dissolving Subatomic Bomb.
As you know, the volatile
gel from this weapon
can spread over the
length of an entire train
before it explodes; so we
have no way of pinpointing
where the bomb was
originally hidden
or how many of them
were actually used.
Has anyone claimed
responsibility for this?
No. We've done a thorough media
check on all of the planets
on the Three-twenty-three's
route. As of yet,
no one has made
any claims.
No motive. I
don't like that.
Yeah, no
kidding.
Some sicko could have
done it for pleasure.
That's crazy!! Who would
do something like that?
That's what we
intend to find out.
I suggest that
we tighten security
on all lines and closely
monitor any movements
made by the Space
Mafias or Pirates.
Are we in
agreement, Captains?
[All]
Agreed!
Manabu. What
are you doing?
I thought I made
myself clear, Manabu.
You're suspended
until further notice.
Can you tell me how long
that will be, Captain?
Indefinitely.
I don't want to
see you here again
until you've decided if
this really is the path
you want to
take in life.
Captain!
Please!
Your father and
brother both
lost their lives
on this job, Manabu.
It was courageous of
you even to join.
But now you have to decide if
it was the right choice or not.
You're still
a young man.
It's not too late to
begin a whole new career.
Captain Bulge. Aren't you being
a little too tough on him?
I don't blame him.
It's my fault.
Manabu,
wait.
Maybe I really
don't belong here.
I can't seem to
do anything right.
I've got five hundred ables
that say he'll be back.
Hey, Manabu!
What's goin' on?!
Huh?
I can tell by lookin' at ya
that you haven't had breakfast.
Here! Power up! It's got
all the major food groups.
I'm real not
hungry. Thanks.
Will you stop being so
darn polite! Take it!
Space is no place for an
empty stomach, young man!
Let go of me! Leave me alone!
I just want to see the cockpit!
Let go! The Fort Worth
is my favorite train!
I have to
see it!
You're not allowed in here!
I have to take you in!
Eh! But I didn't
do anything wrong!
I just want to look
in the cockpit!
What's so bad about
that? No! Let go!
Uh,
excuse me.
What are
you doing?
Conductor, why don't you
just let him have a look?
Illegal intruders must
be taken into custody.
That's the
rule, Sir. Hmm?!
Forgive me, Sir!
Whatever you say!
Oh, man!
This is awesome!
Please! Don't
touch the controls!
Some one could get hurt if
you push the wrong button.
There was a terrible
accident here years ago...
A kid was trying to get
onboard without a ticket
and he ended up
on the tracks.
That's why the rules
are so strict now.
The kids
don't get it.
They think that the rules
are there to punish them.
But they're really just
there to protect them.
I remember being in his
shoes not too long ago.
All I wanted to do was get a
close look at my Dad's train.
My brother thought I was
crazy for breaking the rules.
And the one time he decided to
come with me we got too close.
We saw more than
we wanted to see.
Dad. Mamoru. Why can't
I be more like you?
I've made a
mess of things.
Maybe I'm not cut out
for the SDF after all.
What are you doing
out of uniform?!
I saw you cleaning Big One
the other day. Remember?!
Oh. Yeah.
That's right.
You must be good
to get that gig!
Oh.
Thanks.
Don't mention it. I know
you're one bad-boy janitor.
I've never seen
Big One so clean.
Those SDF guys
never pay attention
to that kind of
stuff but I do.
They're too full of themselves
to notice us little guys.
They think their
crap doesn't stink
because guys like you
keep their toilets clean.
What's your
name anyway?
Manabu.
Nice to meet you,
Manabu. My name's Shaw.
I'm the
drink guy.
If you ever need a drink
you talk to me. Okay?
So you knew I was an SDF
member the whole time?
Yeah, I've seen
you around.
Of course you wouldn't
remember one of us little guys.
Kinuko was worried about you
because you got suspended.
She asked me to talk
to you to cheer you up.
She knew that...? She
needs to get a life.
She just cares about
you, that's all.
Kinuko lost a son of
her own way back when.
He'd be our age if he
was still alive now.
The old gal's
not meddling.
She's just trying to be a
mother. You know what I mean?
Hey! Your highness!
Do you want to help
or are you scared
you'll break a nail?
Oh, uh,
Shaw?
Yeah?
I just remembered. The vending
machine by the Meeting Room
isn't working
very well.
That's weird. That's a
brand new machine...
They usually
don't misbehave
unless they've been in
action for a while.
It was fine until
just the other day.
Hey, I know what happened.
Now tell the truth;
I'll bet you kicked it when
you got suspended! Didn't you?
Ha!
Whatever...
Huh? Hey! We gotta
leak in here!
Let me guess. This is
about Manabu, isn't it?
Do you want him to resign
from the SDF, Captain?
That's what it seems
like to me, Sir.
It's Manabu who will decide
if he wants to resign or not.
Well, you certainly didn't make
him feel welcome, Captain.
I did what I thought was
necessary to discipline him.
I would have treated any one
of you the same way, Rui.
He has a problem
following orders.
He follows his heart,
Captain Bulge!
What's wrong with that? It's
obvious that he respects you!
An order is an
order. You know that.
If he followed every order Big
One would be destroyed now!
And David
would be dead!
Can't you see that
he's trying his best?
That all he wants
to do is help!
Look, Louis. I'm not
forcing Manabu to resign.
But you're not exactly
encouraging him to stay either!
Emergency Signals received!
The Altair
Two-twenty-four Express
and the Regulus Eight-eleven
Express are both missing!
Their ID Signals
have disappeared!
Communication links
have been lost.
Thanks,
man.
Hmm? Watcha
lookin' at?
This store.
It looks a lot like our
family restaurant back home.
You guys own
a restaurant?
Yeah, my Mom's running
it by herself right now.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Hey, Shaw?
Yeah, buddy?
Does your company
carry Tabito Tea?
Well, we used to... It
didn't sell very well.
It kind of has
a funky taste.
What? It's true. Have you
ever tasted that stuff?
Yeah, all the time. I used
to drink it every morning.
Easy there, man. I didn't
know you liked it so much.
I'm not the one who
took it off the market.
I just stock what
they put in my truck.
Are you from
Tabito or what?
There they go again. Somethin'
serious is goin' on.
Nothing renders a
man more powerless
than when he loses
faith in himself.
Don't give up now, Manabu. Your
heart is innocent and pure.
Your soul has no dark cloak
over it... Believe in yourself.
How is it that the same Fate
which seems to smile upon us
and offer us hope can suddenly
enshroud our lives in darkness
and end our dreams
without any warning?
...Does everything in life
truly happen for a reason
or are we simply
experiencing a series
of random,
unconnected events?
On the next Galaxy Railways
Captain Bulge and I
have a heart
to heart
but there are more
pressing matters at hand!
Whether it's with my
new friends or the SDF,
I have to try to figure out
who's behind the bombings!
What kind of
insane madman
would kill all of
those innocent people?
See you next time
on the Railways!