It was the day after Obon.
Smack-dab in the middle of summer.
Nothing special. Just an ordinary day.
The game on TV was between schools from another town.
I had nothing to do with either school, but
because I tend to sympathize with underdogs,
I found myself routing for the losing team.
And that's right about the time
my cell phone started ringing.
Haruhi.
Hey, you're free, right?
Good, then meet us at 2:00 in front of the station.
But I...!
And just like that, she hangs up.
How does she know I'm not doing anything today?
I mean, I could be.
Yeah, I know, I'm not doing anything,
but still...
What?
I forgot to tell you something.
Bring your swim trunks. And your bike, too.
Oh, and money! Bring money.
That's it! Over and out!
Uh. No.
What was that all about?
He is not having a good day.
You gotta feel bad for that guy.
Oh, that is tragic. He looks like...
Oh, well.
Even the fans are quiet.
They're not even booing Suzuki anymore.
So, with that, the score is now eight, zero.
Kuyamoto's really got their work cut out for 'em.
You're late, Kyon! Penalty!
You have absolutely no motivation whatsoever.
How dare you keep your brigade leader waiting!
You're gettin' a penalty for this!
I'm here 15 minutes early.
How come I'm still the last one to arrive?
Okay, now that we're all present
and accounted for, we can go.
Koizumi, you're gonna have to
give Mikuru a ride over there, okay?
Yuki and me'll hop on the back of Kyon's bike.
Do you mind if I ask where we're going today?
To the public pool. Where do you think?
We've got lots and lots of summer
vacation-y things to do during our summer break.
We've only got so much time, and once
it's gone, it's gone for good, ya know?
So we're gonna do everything we can while we can
during our one and only summer as tenth graders.
Once it's gone, it's gone, huh?
Can you smell the chlorine? That
really makes it feel like summer.
Let's go!
Hurry up and get in, guys!
The water's warm. It's perfect!
Can't she see the no diving signs?
I mean, they're everywhere.
It kind of makes me smile, though.
I mean, to see Miss Suzumiya
enjoying herself in a normal way.
It's rather charming, isn't it?
She called me outta the blue,
ran down a list of things to bring,
and ordered me to meet her
without telling me what was going on.
Yeah, there's nothing charming or normal about it.
Well, as long as Miss Suzumiya's having a good time,
we don't have to worry about any earth-shattering events.
Man, I hope you're right.
I don't think you need to worry about it.
I mean, there haven't been any
problems since our outing a few weeks ago.
And right now, as far as Miss Suzumiya's concerned,
and as far as we're concerned, the world is at peace.
Okay, guys, lunch time!
And, surprise, surprise! Mikuru's made us sandwiches!
Whoa.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much!
I'm gonna have another piece of fried chicken!
Pour some tea, Mikuru.
Okay.
Things do seem peaceful, that's for sure.
We're sorry!
Yeah, here I come!
Now I know why they call it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone in town's here today.
Oh, some on, Mikuru! You're supposed to catch it!
This isn't a bad way to spend a summer vacation.
Kyon!
These two guys are my brigade members.
They do what I say, so if you
want somethin', you can ask them.
Okay!
I had a couple ideas about the rest of our vacation.
Check it out!
What's that thing?
It's a schedule of all the things the
brigade's gonna do before our vacation ends!
The SOS brigade?
You know it! We've only got two more
weeks of vacation left, right, guys?
But it still feels like there's
a lotta things left for us to do.
I say we gotta pick up the pace.
So, you made a schedule of things
to do before our vacation ends, huh?
Go on a trip, go to the pool, to a Bon festival,
see fireworks, part time job, stargazing...
That's a lotta stuff.
And she expects us to do all this in the next two weeks?
Great.
Can you think of anything else you wanna do?
I'd like to try goldfish scooping.
Okay! Then goldfish scooping it is.
We'll start on the list tomorrow.
Does anyone know if there's a Bon
festival happening some place close by?
Or if there's a firework show?
Why don't you look this stuff up yourself?
I'll check around and try to find something.
I'll call you if I do, okay?
Oh, and don't forget about the goldfish scooping.
It's Mikuru's only request.
Got it!
How come I always get stuck with the check?
Because you were late, that's why!
And don't you make us wait tomorrow!
That's it. See ya!
Awesome.
Looks like we're gonna be running around everyday, now.
The next morning, I was waken from my
peaceful slumber by a call from Haruhi.
She said they'd found a Bon
festival, and it was happening tonight.
At a park somewhere.
Well, that was fast. And convenient.
I was just beginning to appreciate
that fact when Haruhi suddenly said...
We're all gonna go out and buy yukatas!
Yuki doesn't have one and neither does Mikuru.
But I know a place that sells 'em cheap, so, let's go!
Haruhi picked out yukatas for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then, headed for the changing rooms.
This was gonna take a while.
After about an hour of standing there
and getting strange looks from people,
the girls finally decided to
come out of the changing room.
Kyon!
You all look really wonderful in them. I mean it.
Of course we do! I picked them out myself.
Especially Mikuru's.
Look at you, you're so cute. I'm a genius!
I have awesome fashion sense, don't'cha think?
Of all the costumes Haruhi has forced her to wear,
this had to be the best one yet.
She looks awesome. Yes, she does.
I always wondered what it would be like
to wear traditional Japanese clothing.
It's a little tight around the chest, but it's beautiful.
We're ready to go!
And now it's off to the Bon festival to have some fun!
A Bon festival, huh?
I haven't been to one of these
things in a really long time.
Look, Mikuru!
They've got goldfish scooping, just like you wanted!
I bet you're gonna catch a ton!
Don't forget the black demikens are worth 200 points!
Do you wanna go scoop some fish, too?
We could have a contest to see how many we can catch.
I think I'll pass.
Besides, I'm more interested in the food around here.
How 'bout you, Nagato? Do you wanna get some food?
Are you actually into that stuff?
That.
Hm? It's yours for 800 yen!
Thirteen!
I caught a whole bunch, but I only kept one
'cause I don't have any place to keep all of 'em.
I tried, but I couldn't catch a single one of them.
Scooping them up is a lot harder then it looks, huh?
Yeah, well, it's rare for anyone
to catch a lot, let alone one.
If you can figure out the trick, it's easy!
What's with the mask you've got there, Yuki?
I bought it.
I know, but why that one?
Maybe she felt some kinda connection to it, or something.
Cause she's an alien.
Well, okay then.
Anyway, there's a ton of stuff over there we haven't seen!
You still in fun mode?
Of course! Come on! Hurry up!
Here.
Go ahead and have one, but only one, 'kay?
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Pretty good, huh?
You know it.
Okay, we've seen just about everything there is to see.
So now we're gonna go shoot off some fireworks.
Really? Fireworks?
We went to all the trouble of dressing up,
so we'll end our day with a firework show.
Why not? There's a booth over there that's selling them.
Let's go down by the river bank.
This is going to be so much fun.
Come on! Let's do this!
Kakizaki!
It's pretty.
So, we did the Bon festival, fireworks.
That's two down.
And tomorrow, we're gonna go catch some bugs.
Uh, Haruhi, I don't wanna spoil your fun or
anything, but have you finished your summer homework?
I should talk. I haven't even touched mine.
Are you kidding? That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it all in about three days.
Yeah, I finished doing all of my homework in July.
Ya have to get rid of that junk first so you can spend the
rest of your summer having fun and not worrying about it.
That's the only way to really
get the most out of your vacation.
Why does she have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying up the stats for us.
So anyway, we're gonna go bug catching tomorrow.
And the prize for catching the most bugs is gonna be...
The winner gets to be brigade leader for a whole day!
No thank you.
That sounds like fun.
But can we catch just any random bug?
Hm... No.
Only cicadas!
That's it! I'm calling it the SOS
Brigade's cicada catching contest!
Whoever catches the most cicadas wins!
The next day, I wanted it to rain so
bad, I drove a nail through a teruteru bouzu.
But, despite my efforts, the day was clear and beautiful.
It was the warmest day of summer so far,
and all the cicadas were happy because of it.
I wonder if anyone's ever tried eating a cicada...
No idea.
They could be good fried in tempura.
Bon appetite.
I always wondered about food that's deep-fried in tempura.
Maybe the batter they use is
what makes everything taste so good.
'Cause then cicadas would taste great!
Apologize to the tempura chefs! Do it!
What's wrong with this picture?
High schoolers carrying nets and little plastic boxes?
Hello? What're you thinking making us hike
all the way up here carrying all this stuff?
What're you talking about?
If we didn't have the nets and the
bins, we wouldn't be able to catch cicadas.
That's not the point I was trying to make.
Okay. Let's go hunting.
Remember, winner gets to be brigade leader for a day.
Ya ready? Go!
Ignored.
She looks determined to win, doesn't she?
And that would be a good thing, don't you think?
Jeez. I haven't done this since elementary school.
I know, me too.
Come on. Let's go have some fun.
What's that? You catch one?
Yeah, no. That's not a cicada.
Oh.
A Hercules beetle?!
Let's tally 'em up!
Mikuru caught one.
Yuki caught four.
Koizumi caught seven.
Kyon caught nine.
But the one who caught the most is...
Don't say it, we already know.
Me, with 12!
I guess I just can't give up being
brigade leader, even for one day.
Sorry about that, you guys.
Please tell me that you're not gonna
batter those things up in tempura and fry them.
What? Do you really wanna eat 'em?
No, I don't wanna eat 'em.
Just kidding.
It's important to follow the spirit
of catch and release with these guys.
You never know. If we let them go now,
they might return the favor some time.
Hurry! Go back to the mountains
and try not to get caught anymore!
Wait. No.
You act like you did a good deed,
but all you did was catch 'em and let 'em go. Come on.
So, the day after our bug hunt, Haruhi was kind
enough to get us part-time jobs at a local supermarket,
that really needed the help.
See, they were having a big sale.
Well, don't work too hard, okay?
And our job was to attract customers.
Thank you for coming.
Balloon? No?
Here.
Can someone please tell me why I have
to wear this unbearably hot costume?
Part-time job?
She could've found something a
little more appropriate for summer.
Look at her. All cool and breezy.
I swear. If she gets more money then us, I'm gonna riot.
Now I know how a snake feels when it sheds its skin.
That's a clever way of putting it.
Knock, knock.
The manager's super grateful
for all the hard work you did.
Who cares how grateful he is. What about our pay?
This is it.
This cool frog costume is our pay.
Can't tell ya how long I've had my eye on him.
The manager said we could have it 'cause
he thought Mikuru looked so darn cute in it.
We'll keep him in the clubroom as a souvenir of today.
Mikuru, you have my permission to
wear him whenever you want, okay?
Isn't it great?
Ribbit.
The pool, the Bon festival,
bug catching, and a part-time job.
Next on Haruhi's schedule, stargazing.
Wow, that's what a telescope
from this time frame looks like?
It doesn't seem too different
from the ones in Kepler's time.
Yeah, no. It's pretty different.
Did you buy this just for tonight?
Oh, no. Astronomy was sort of a
hobby of mine when I was younger.
All it took was a glimpse of the moons
of Jupiter, and after that, I was hooked.
I've found Mars. Have a look.
I wonder if they're real.
What's real?
Martians, of course!
I kind of hope they aren't.
I mean, octopoid-like monsters, wriggling
around, plotting to take over the planet?
Nothing about that sounds appealing to me.
Oh, what do you know.
And who cares what they look like anyway.
They might be friendly.
For all we know, they could be a reserved race of
beings living in underground caves. Think of that.
Whoever they are, I'm sure they're
just trying not to scare us earthlings.
The martians in your imagination
sound unbelievably boring.
I've had enough of Mars.
Let's look for UFOs.
On a night like tonight,
I bet there's some kinda alien scouting fleet up there.
All right, come on, Mikuru. Help me with this.
UFO. UFO...
Our summer vacation continues.
And the next thing Haruhi said was...
We're going to the batting cages today!
Why there?
I was watching a high school baseball
game this morning, and then it hit me!
Why should we settle for baseball in some sandlot?
What we need to do is turn the SOS
brigade into a national league team!
Chuka soba!
She sure is something. Where does she get her energy from?
I bet she's got special mitochondria packed in her cells.
More than the average person, anyway.
If only she'd use her gifts for good.
After that, we kept going.
Haruhi was determined to stick to the schedule she made.
So we were constantly on the move,
day after day, with no time to hit pause.
We went to a real firework show.
The fireworks burst into bloom
in the sky, one after another,
leaving us with a grand feeling in our hearts.
And on another day, she made all of us enter
a goby fishing tournament down by the river.
Mikuru, your pole!
Don't worry, I see it. I'll go get it.
And still, another day was the the "test of courage."
It's a summertime must, but I
doubt anyone really does it anymore.
Then we went and saw this over-hyped summer blockbuster.
Turned out to be the same old, same old.
We went to the beach.
Right in the middle of jellyfish season.
Then, bowling.
But, you-know-who made a rule where no
one could leave until everyone got a strike.
Then, an excruciating karaoke session
designed to push our vocal cords to the limit.
Sure, there were a couple of non-summertime
things that slipped in, but looking back,
I can honestly say we had the time of our lives.
The past two weeks were a blast.
I declare that on this day, August
30th, we've done everything on our list.
And no one died in the process.
But now I wonder if we did enough.
Maybe if we... No, I guess we did do everything.
Unless there's something else you guys wanted to do.
No, not really.
I think we've done enough.
I think I'd like to sleep for a while.
How 'bout you?
Oh.
Oh, well. That's cool.
We did just about everything we wanted to do this summer.
We wore yukatas, and caught a lotta cicadas.
We went all over the place.
I guess that's about it, huh?
Please don't tell me there's
something else she wants to do.
Okay, we're done for today.
I set tomorrow aside, just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
I'll see everyone at the clubroom on Monday.
I still haven't done any of my homework.
August 31st. The last day of vacation.
No matter how hard I tried, I
wasn't gonna finish my homework.
Besides, I was still recovering
from all that running around.
So, I made a decision to spend
the rest of the day in lounge mode.
What the heck?!
Boring.
Homework? Yeah, whatever.
I guess I'll go to bed now.
I got school tomorrow.
Beep.