Something's wrong.
That's what it felt like anyway.
The game on TV was between schools from another town.
I had nothing to do with either school, but
because I tend to sympathize with underdogs,
I found myself routing for the losing team.
And it was right about then that I
suddenly got the feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
What does she want?
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
I know, I know.
Hey, you're free, right?
Good, meet us at 2:00 in front
of the station. Don't be late!
I didn't even have the chance to say anything.
What?
I forgot to tell you to bring your swim trunks.
And some money, too.
Oh, wait, and your bike. Definitely bring your bike.
That's it! Over and out!
Uh. No.
That was weird.
It's like I knew what Haruhi
was gonna say before she said it.
Yeah, no. Actually, it felt like we'd
had the exact same conversation before.
Like déjà vu or something.
There's the wind-up. It's outta there!
Home run! What a shot!
Summer's almost over, isn't it?
You're late, Kyon!
Where's your motivation, huh?
Yeah, yeah. I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, I just got here too.
Now that we're all present and accounted for, we can go!
Where?
To the public pool! Where do you think?
Figures, considering what I brought.
We've got lots and lots of summer
vacationy things to do during our break,
But there's only so much time, and
once it's gone, it's gone for good.
So we're gonna do everything we can while we can
during our one and only summer as tenth graders.
And for starters, we're gonna ride bikes over to the pool.
So, did everyone ride their bikes today?
No. The only bikes we have to
take are the ones you and I brought.
Huh?
All right, Kyon. Don't let Koizumi beat you over there.
Come on, full speed ahead!
Boost!
Come on, guys. Hurry up and park your bikes already.
We're trying to have fun, Kyon.
Stop acting like you're tired.
And whose fault is that?
Ah. Can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes it feel like summer.
Hurry up and get in! Water's all warm. It's perfect!
Can't she see the no diving signs? They're everywhere.
Doesn't that look like fun?
In a way, it makes me smile.
Such a peaceful scene, isn't it?
I mean, seeing Miss Suzumiya enjoy the day in a
normal fashion, rather charming, don't you think?
She called me, told me what to bring, and ordered
me to meet her without telling me what was going on.
There's nothing charming or normal about it.
Well, if you ask me, none of what you
mentioned is anything to make such a fuss over.
As long as Miss Suzumiya's having a good time, we
don't have to worry about any earth-shattering events.
I hope you're right.
Something wrong?
No. It's just my imagination.
With everything that's happened since we
met, you could say I've become slightly paranoid.
Hot...
Hot. So hot.
Jeez. Now I know why they call
it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi chose this place.
There's that feeling again.
It's like I've seen this happen once before.
With Nagato looking kinda bored like that. Alone.
Kyon!
And then Haruhi's supposed to say something like...
These two guys are my brigade members.
And they do what I say.
So if you want somethin', you can ask them.
It's time to have some fun!
Let's all go play water soccer!
Yeah, yeah.
Oh well. Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
Here is comes, Mikuru!
Okay!
I have a couple ideas about the rest of our vacation.
Check it out!
Two weeks to do all of that?
Is there anything you want to do, Mikuru?
Umm... I'd like to try goldfish scooping.
Okay. Goldfish scooping it is.
Could I see that?
Thank you.
We'll the list tomorrow.
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening close by?
Or a firework show?
I can check and see if there's anything.
Don't forget about goldfish scooping.
It's Mikuru's only request.
I'll get right on it.
I always get stuck with the bill.
Well, that's it. See ya!
I'm off, too.
Bye, bye.
Nagato!
Uhh, it's...
I guess it's nothing important. Anyway, how've you been?
Is everything okay?
I am fine.
Well, that's good to hear.
Yes.
What the heck? Why did I wanna talk to her?
The next morning, I was waken from my
peaceful slumber by a call from Haruhi.
She said they'd found a bon festival.
It was happening tonight. At a park somewhere.
We're all gonna go buy yukatas!
So, we went to a clothing outlet.
Haruhi picked out yukatas for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then marched them straight into the changing room.
After making us wait about an hour
or so, they all three finally came out.
Whoa.
You look wondering in those.
Of course we do! I picked them out myself.
Especially Mikuru's.
Look at you, you're so cute. I must be a genius.
Uh... Uh, yes.
The blushing makes her cuter!
Wow.
A bon festival, huh?
It figures that it'd be so crowded.
I haven't been to a bon festival in a while,
But it feels like I just went to one.
That tower.
Those vendors.
Look, Mikuru!
They've got goldfish scooping just like you wanted!
You're gonna catch a ton!
Do you wanna go scoop some fish?
We could have a contest.
I think I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato? Wanna get some food?
Don't tell me you're actually into this kinda stuff.
I got it.
No.
That.
It's yours for 800 yen!
I wish she would've let me buy that for her.
It's the least I could do after all she's done for us.
Wow! What an unbelievable haul!
But I only kept one, 'cause I don't have any
place to keep 'em. And I gave one to Mikuru.
Go ahead and have one, but only one.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, Yuki. What's up with the mask, huh?
I bought it.
Oh, okay.
Fireworks! That's what we're gonna do next!
We'll go set up some fireworks!
Do you even understand the meaning of the word moderation?
It was summer, and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I wanted to forget about it.
But the truth was, I couldn't ignore it any longer.
Tomorrow, we're gonna catch some bugs.
Haruhi, I don't want to spoil your
fun, but have you finished your homework?
Are you kidding? That stuff's totally
easy. You can finish it in like three days.
Three days?!
You have to get rid of that junk first so you
can spend the rest of your summer having fun,
And not worrying about it.
That's the only way to really
get the most out of your vacation.
Why does she have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying up the stats for us.
Listen up! We're gonna go bug catching tomorrow!
And whoever catches the most bugs is gonna
get to be brigade leader for a whole day!
No thanks.
That sounds like fun. But, can we catch just any bugs?
Hm... No. Only cicadas!
That's it! I'm calling it the SOS
Brigade's cicada catching contest!
The next day was beautiful, sunny and bright.
And although everyone caught
bugs the best way they knew how,
The winner of the contest ended up being, you guessed it,
Haruhi.
It's important to follow the spirit
of catch and release with these guys.
You never know. If we let 'em go now,
they might return the favor sometime.
Now, what could a cicada possibly do for me?
Hurry! Go back to the mountains!
For some reason, I kinda feel
like Pandora opening her box.
W-Welcome to our store!
We met the next day, even though
we had no idea what was going on.
Our cluelessness continued as we
were made to wear frog costumes,
And hand balloons out in front of the local supermarket.
Welcome to our part-time job.
Good work, you guys!
What's with the special treatment?
You're the best.
The manager's super grateful for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful he is. What about our pay?
That's it.
Huh?
I've had my eye on this for a while.
The manager gave it to us
'cause Mikuru looked so cute in it.
We were working, sweat pouring
down our foreheads, for that?!
We'll keep 'em in the club room as a souvenir.
Mikuru, you have my permission
to wear 'em whenever you want.
Isn't he the greatest?
Later that night, my peaceful
slumber was interrupted by a phone call.
Damn it.
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
Yes, it's me.
Something really bad... I don't know...
Wha...?
Hello. It's Koizumi.
Why are you with Miss Asahina in the middle of the night?
We have a situation here.
Do you think you could come meet us right now?
Absolutely. Where?
Miss Asahina! What happened?
Oh... Oh, Kyon. I can't...
I can't go back to the future.
I'll explain it the best I can.
Currently, we're stuck in a time
loop that seems to be infinite.
It's hard to believe you're
serious with that smile on your face.
Come on, Koizumi, do you realize what you just said?
Of course I do. More than I want to, believe me.
Earlier, I was having a word with Miss Asahina.
Next time, call me when you have a word with her!
And that was when we both realized that
something seemed off about our current flow of time.
Actually, Miss Asahina discovered it.
Thanks to her, my suspicions were confirmed.
What kind of suspicions?
That we'd been reliving the same
period of time over and over again.
You already said that.
We've been repeating the days
between August 17th through the 31st.
It's a never-ending, endless summer.
The future doesn't exist in this world anymore.
Time stops at September 1st.
That's the reason Miss Asahina
can't travel back to the future.
It's only natural.
There's nothing natural about not having a future.
Who's gonna believe such a thing?
Well, for starters, we were sort
of hoping you would believe it.
I can try to help explain it.
Here goes.
Because I have to classified information,
I used classified information
to get in touch with the future.
The thing is, I haven't gotten any
classified information for about a week.
And I started to think how weird that was.
I was so surprised.
I classified information, I really did,
but it was classified information, too.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know how to help you, but I'm wondering,
Are all the classified things you're
talking about stuff you can't say on TV?
What about those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Maybe we're trapped in one of those.
It's not one of those.
A specific section of time has been torn away.
At exactly midnight on August the 31st, everything resets,
And then time reverts straight back
to the morning of August the 17th.
That's the process.
What about our...?
Wait, what about the whole world's memories?
Their memory is reset.
Everyone's memory starts over from the beginning.
Another problem involving time. Perfect.
I guess that figures when there's a time traveler around.
No.
Miss Asahina didn't have anything to do with this.
Then what's causing it?
Miss Suzumiya.
Somewhere inside her, there's a desire
to have summer vacation last forever.
I'm sure she doesn't even realize it.
Oh, come on.
You mean she still hasn't had enough fun?
That's what it looks like.
Perhaps she feels like there's something else that
needs to happen before our summer vacation is over.
Man, the trouble she gets us
into is always galactic in scale.
All right, what do you want me to do?
If I knew that, we'd have this problem solved by now.
You're too close.
You seem like you're enjoying this.
You wanna tell me why?
Please don't take it the wrong way,
But this explains the feelings of déjà vu I've had,
And the ones you've been feeling as well.
Now that I think about it,
they were most likely the residue of our memories
from every instance where time had been reset.
Are we the only ones? Or can other people feel this, too?
I doubt that.
You and I are acceptations to the rule, though.
The only people who can sense this strangeness,
Are the ones closest to Miss Suzumiya.
What about Haruhi?
Does she even know this stuff is happening?
No, I don't think so.
Besides, it would be very bad for us if she did.
However, there is someone who is
unaffected by the feelings of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact,
This person remembers everything that's happened.
Oh, yeah? Who would that person be?
You already know.
It's Miss Nagato.
The data integration thought entity
transcends space and time. So does she.
Is that true?
Yes.
Then, you remember everything?
Really?
So, how many times has this happened to us?
This would be 15,498 times?
Fifteen thousand, four-hundred and ninety-eight?
What do you mean 15,498? What are you saying, Nagato?
And, you're being completely serious?
Yes.
So, you're saying we've done the exact
same things every time that many times?
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,498 repetitions,
We did not attend a bon festival the 2,391st time
And the 11,054th time.
We went to the festival but did not
go to a fish scooping booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time jobs
9,025 times and there were six...
Okay. I got it.
Fifteen-thousand, four-hundred ninety-eight.
That's what she said. Times
two weeks. That's... 594 years.
She's the only one who remembers
everything we do all those times.
And she's had to repeat them over and over again.
Nagato...
I can't even begin to image what it's been like for you.
That's gotta be the craziest story ever.
The next night, we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony of Nagato's
apartment, since her place had the best view.
Koizumi brought the telescope.
I wonder if they're real.
What's real?
Martians.
I kinda hope they aren't.
I can't see anyone on the surface.
You know, I bet there is a reserved race of beings
living underground. They're probably friendly, too.
Yeah. Dream on.
Whenever us humans finally land on Mars,
I'm sure the Martians will pop out from wherever
they're hiding and say, "Welcome to Mars," or something.
It'll get mistaken for an attack.
Oh. I'm bored. I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
I wish I knew what else she wanted to do.
Yes, what indeed.
If we knew that, we'd be on
our way to solving this problem.
Here's something. Why don't we try this?
What if someone were to grab Miss Suzumiya from behind
and then they whisper, "I love you" right into her ear.
And who's going to be doing this?
Who else could play that role other than you?
I'm vetoing that idea!
All right. Shall I give it a try?
No, I'm just kidding. That isn't a role I can play.
Besides, it would just confuse Miss Suzumiya.
The next day, we swung for
the fences at the batting cages.
Hey, Nagato.
You knew about this time loop we're in way
before Miss Asahina figured it out, didn't you?
Yes.
So, how come you didn't say anything about it?
My function is to observe.
Right.
We kept chugging along, doing
all kinds of summer vacation things.
We just kept going and going and doing stuff.
And the whole time, all I could think was
that none of it was going to be enough for Haruhi.
But what could I do about it? Nothing.
So, we ended up like we always did at August the 30th.
That's it, we've done everything on our list.
But now I'm wondering if we did enough... if...
No, I guess we did.
Hey, is there anything else you want to do?
Oh, okay.
I guess we did everything we wanted
to do over the summer, so that's enough.
No, it's not. Not by a long shot.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case,
but you can take the day off, I guess.
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday.
No, wait! Haruhi!
There's that feeling again.
It's strong... Stronger than all the others.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
We'll end up reliving the past two weeks
again and again for a thousand more times.
But... what should I do?
What should I say?
There must've been a clue in something Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What's she been saying all this time?
I don't know. I can't remember.
It's August 31st.
And I still haven't touched my homework yet.
Whatever. Doesn't matter.
There's no point doing it. I mean, we're just
gonna keep reliving the last couple of weeks.
Whatever happens next, whether tomorrow comes or not,
A different version of me will have to deal with it.