Something's wrong... That's what it felt like anyway.
I didn't care about the baseball game
on TV, but I ended up watching it anyway.
And right about then, I suddenly
got the feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
Hey Kyon, your cell phone's ringing.
Yeah I know; you don't have to tell me.
Hey, Kyon! You're free today, right?
Good. Meet us at 2:00 in front of the station.
And don't be late!
I didn't even have a chance to say anything.
Now what?
I forgot to tell you something.
Make sure and bring your swim trunks and some money, too.
Oh, and don't forget to bring...
Don't forget to bring my bike, I know.
Uh... Right! Yeah, bring it.
And if you're late, you're buying lunch!
How did I know about the bike just now?
Look! I think that one's gonna make it over!
I knew it!
I wonder where I put my swim trunks.
Summer's almost over.
You're late, Kyon!
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry if I kept you guys waiting.
No worries. I just got here, too.
You have absolutely no motivation whatsoever.
Now that we're all present and accounted for, we can go!
Where are we going today?
To the public swimming pool! Where do you think?
That figures... considering the stuff I brought.
But, we've only got so much time
because once it's gone, it's gone for good!
So we're going to do everything we can
during our only summer as tenth graders.
Hey, Kyon? Are you listening?
Uh... Yeah.
For starters, we're gonna ride the bikes over to the pool!
Okay. Did everyone ride their bikes today?
Well, actually...
The only bikes we have are the ones you and I brought.
In other words, you mean...
You gotta be kidding!
All right, Kyon, you can't let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
You demon! You fiend!
What are you doing?
We're trying to have fun, so stop acting tired!
And whose fault is that?!
Wow! Look at all the people!
And can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes it feel like summer!
Come on, guys, it's perfect! Let's find
a place to dump our stuff and go swimming!
Okay.
Hey! Wait a se... cond...
Can't she see the "no diving" signs? They're everywhere.
Come on! The water's warm! It's perfect!
Mikuru! Yuki! Don't just stand there!
Guess you better go have fun. We're
never gonna hear the end of it, if you don't.
Oh! Okay!
Miss Suzumiya! Wait up, we're coming!
Slow poke!
In... you... go!
It's such a peaceful scene, isn't it?
What?
I was talkin' about Miss Suzumiya.
She's enjoying herself in a normal way.
It's rather charming, don't you think?
She called me and told me what to bring.
And then, she ordered me to meet her
without telling me what was going on.
That's not charming or normal.
If you ask me, none of what you
mentioned is anything to make a fuss over.
As long as Miss Suzumiya's having a good time,
we don't have to worry about any earth-shattering events.
I hope you're right.
Something wrong?
Nothing...
I guess it's just my imagination.
With everything that's happened since we
met, you could say I've become slightly paranoid.
Him too? Weird.
Now I know why they call it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone in town's here today.
She's been over there this whole time?
Why's she sitting over there by herself?
What the...?
That's so weird!
It's like... I've seen this happen before.
Nagato... all alone...
Kyon!
Haruhi...
Yeah... That's right...
She shows up and says...
"These two guys are my brigade
members. They do what I say.
So if you want something..."
...you can ask them!
It's time for some water soccer.
I need everyone in the pool!
Yuki!
Have I become like a psychic or something?
Heads up, Kyon!
Ugh!
...or not.
Oh, well. I guess déjà vu's happen sometimes.
That's all it was.
I've been thinking of some fun things to do!
What's that for?
I came up with this schedule of how we're
gonna spend the rest of our summer vacation!
We've only got two weeks...
Two weeks to do all that?!
Is there anything you wanna do, Mikuru?
Um... Maybe goldfish scooping?
Okay! Goldfish scooping, it is.
Um... Could I see that for a moment?
Thank you.
We'll start the list tomorrow!
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening close by?
Or a firework show?
I can check around for them. I'll
give you a call if I find anything.
Don't forget about the goldfish scooping.
After all, it's Mikuru's only request.
I got stuck with the bill again.
Yeah, well, that's what happens when you're late!
That's it for today, guys! Okay? I'll see you tomorrow!
Well, I'm off, too.
I'll see you later!
Okay!
Nagato!
I... I was... It's nothing important or anything...
So, uh... How have you been?
Is everything going okay with you?
It is.
Okay, then. I guess that's a good thing.
Yes.
Ah! Well, uh, that's all I was wondering.
So yeah, I'm, uh... sorry to keep you.
What the heck?
What was that? Why'd I talk to her?
The next morning, I got another call from Haruhi.
They found a bon festival.
It was happening at a park tonight.
Sorry, guys!
Well, it's about time...
The three of you look wonderful in those!
Well, of course we do!
I picked 'em out myself, y'know.
Especially Mikuru's! You're so cute! I'm a genius!
Oh, Miss Asahina! Yes! Yes!
There's a lot going on here, but I
wonder where all the things we wanna do are.
What the...?!
It feels like I was just here!
That tower... Those vendors... I remember them.
Look! Mikuru!
See? They have goldfish scooping, just like you wanted!
We're gonna catch a whole bunch!
Miss Suzumiya, don't pull so hard!
Do you wanna go scoop some fish, too?
Nah, I think I'll pass.
So how 'bout you, Nagato?
You wanna go grab some food or somethin'?
Are you actually into that stuff?
Okay! I got it!
No.
But...
That one.
It's yours for 800 yen!
I wish she would've let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do after all she's done for us.
I caught thirteen!
But, I don't have enough room for all of 'em.
That's way too many fish.
So I kept one, and gave one to Mikuru!
Here! Go ahead and have one! But only one, okay?
Okay. Thanks.
Woah! Hey, Yuki? What's the deal with the mask?
I bought it.
Oh! Okay...
Let's shoot off some fireworks next.
It'll be a great way to end the day!
It was summer, and summer vacation.
I guess that's why I wanted to forget about it.
Truth was, I couldn't ignore it any longer.
Tomorrow, we're gonna catch bugs!
Hey, Haruhi?
Yeah? What?
I don't wanna spoil your fun,
but have you finished your homework?
Finish my homework?
Aw, that stuff's easy. You can
finish it in like three days.
You have to get rid of it first, so you can spend
your summer having fun and not worrying about it!
That, is how you get the most out of your vacation!
The gods can be so cruel...
So tomorrow, we're all gonna go bug catching!
But only cicadas.
I'm calling it the SOS Brigade's cicada catching contest!
The next day was unbelievably
beautiful, sunny, and bright.
Perfect for the SOS Brigade's cicada
catching contest, which was currently underway.
And although everyone caught bugs the best way they
knew how, the winner of the contest ended up being...
Surprise! Haruhi...
It's important to follow the spirit
of catch and release with these guys.
I mean, if we let 'em go now, they
might return the favor some time.
Now, what could a cicada possibly do for me?
I sorta feel like Pandora, opening her box.
We met the next day, even though
we had no idea what was going on.
Then, we had to wear frog costumes and
hand balloons out in front of the supermarket.
This was our part-time job.
I feel like the Gundam Virtue after it pops its armor.
Good work, you guys!
What's with the special treatment?
You're the best!
The manager's super grateful for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful he is? Where's our pay?
That's it!
Huh?
I've had my eye on him for a while now.
The manager said we could have it
'cause Mikuru looks so cute in it!
We were working, sweat pouring down our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep him in the club room as a souvenir.
Mikuru, you have my permission
to wear him whenever you want.
Isn't he the greatest?!
Uh... Okay...
Um... Thank you, I guess...?
Later that night, my peaceful
slumber was interrupted by a phone call.
Shut up...
Shut up!
Ugh, dammit...
Hello?
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
I don't know...
At this rate... I... I...
What's wrong?
Hello, it's Koizumi.
What are you doing with Miss
Asahina in the middle of the night?
We have a situation here.
Is it possible for you to come meet us?
Oh, absolutely!
Miss Asahina!
What happened? Are you okay?
Oh, Kyon! I can't... Future...
Future? W-What?
I can't go back to the future!
I'll explain it the best I can.
We're currently stuck in a time
loop that seems to have no end.
It's hard to believe you're
serious with that smile on your face.
Come on, Koizumi. Do you have any idea what you just said?
Of course, I do. Much more than I want to, believe me.
Anyway, I was having a chat with Miss Asahina earlier.
Next time, call me when you have a chat with her!
And that's when the two of us realized that something
seemed a little off about the current flow of time.
Actually, Miss Asahina discovered it.
Thanks to her, my suspicions were confirmed.
What kind of suspicions?
That we've been re-living the same
period of time, over and over again.
Yeah, you already said that.
We've been repeating every day
between August the 17th through the 31st.
We've become stuck in the middle of what
seems to be an endless summer vacation.
Well, at least it's summer vacation...
A never-ending, endless summer vacation.
The future doesn't exist in this world anymore.
Time stops at September the 1st.
That's the reason Miss Asahina can't travel to the future.
It's only natural.
There's nothing natural about not having a future.
Who's gonna believe such a thing?
Well, for starters, I guess we were
sort of hoping that you would believe it.
Maybe it's one of those closed
spaces you were talking about before.
Could we be trapped in one of those things?
That's not it. This time, it's different.
A specific section of time has been torn away.
At exactly midnight on August the 31st,
everything resets. Time reverts
to the morning of August the 17th.
That's the process.
Perfect, another problem involving time.
But I guess I shouldn't be surprised, considering
there's a time traveler hanging out with us.
No...
Miss Asahina didn't have anything to do with this.
Okay... Then what's causing it?
Miss Suzumiya.
Somewhere inside her, there's a desire
to have summer vacation last forever.
I'm sure she doesn't even realize it.
You mean she still hasn't had enough fun?
That's what I think anyway.
Perhaps she feels there's something else that needs
to happen before our summer vacation can truly end.
All right, what do you want me to do about it?
If I knew that, we'd have this problem solved by now.
You seem like you're enjoying this.
Please don't take that the wrong way, but this
explains the feelings of déjà vu we've both been having.
Are... we the only ones?
Or can other people feel this happening, too?
It doesn't seem like it.
But then, you and I are exceptions to the rule.
The only people who can sense these strange feelings
happening are the ones who are closest to Miss Suzumiya.
But, what about Haruhi?
Doesn't she get that weird feeling, too?
No, I don't think she does.
Besides, it would be very bad for us if she did.
But...
...there is someone else.
Someone who isn't affected by the time loop,
or the feelings of déjà vu we've had.
She remembers it all.
I can't imagine what that would be like for someone.
Okay then, who is it?
You already know. Don't you?
The thought entity transcends
time and space, and so does she.
Nagato, is that true?
It is.
So, then you can remember everything?
I can.
Okay then, how many times did we
re-live the last two weeks up till now?
This would be 15, 513 times.
Fifteen thousand five-hundred thirteen times?
What do you mean 15,513 times?
Nagato, do you know what you just said?
And... you're being completely serious?
Yes.
So, you're saying that we've done the exact
same things every single time, that many times?
Not necessarily.
What do you mean?
Throughout 15,513 repetitions, we did not attend a
bon festival the 2,391st time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival but did not
go to a goldfish scooping booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time jobs 9,031
times and worked six different jobs.
In addition to handing out balloons,
we worked as movers, cashiers...
Got it. I got it.
Fifteen thousand five-hundred thirteen times...
That's what she said.
Times two weeks...
That's, uh... about... 594 years.
She's the only one of us who remembers everything we did.
And she's had to repeat them over and over and over again.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the same things that many times?
I wonder if they're real.
Who?
Martians.
I kind of hope they aren't.
I bet they're a noble race of
beings who have to live underground.
They're probably friendly, too.
Yeah, dream on.
This is boring... I know!
I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
You know, I wish I knew what else she wanted to do.
Yes, what indeed.
If we knew that, we'd be on
our way to solving this problem.
I know! Why don't we try this out?
What?
What if someone were to grab Miss Suzumiya from behind?
And then they whisper, "I love you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be doing the whispering?
Can you think of anyone better
suited to play that role than you?
I'm exercising my right to veto!
I won't do it.
If that's how you feel...
All right, then I'll give it a shot.
Just kidding.
That role requires a certain something which I lack.
Besides, it would just confuse Miss
Suzumiya, and we wouldn't want that.
Hey, Nagato.
You knew about this time loop thing we're stuck in
way before Miss Asahina figured it out, didn't you?
Yes.
So, how come you didn't say anything about it?
My function is to observe.
Understood.
All right!
I did it! Look! I got a home run! Yay!
We were always doing something, always on the move.
We went to a real firework show, and we
even signed up for a goby fishing tournament.
We did the test of courage, went to the beach,
went bowling, did some karaoke, and went to the movies.
And the whole time, all I could think was
that none of it was going to be enough for Haruhi.
But, what could I do about it?
Nothing.
So, I just bit my lip and watched as the
last days of our summer vacation went by.
And then, before I knew it, it was August the 30th.
That's it. We've done everything on our list.
But, now I wonder if we did enough.
Hmm, oh well... Yeah... I guess we did a lot.
Unless... does anyone else have anything they wanna do?
Oh, okay then.
We pretty much did everything we set out to
do this summer, so I guess that's good enough.
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, then. We're done for today!
I set tomorrow aside just in case, but
I guess you can all take the day off now.
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday, okay?
Wait.
Haruhi, wait.
Don't go.
Wait, come back.
If I let her walk out that door,
we're gonna have to re-live the
past two weeks over and over again,
maybe for a thousand more times.
But... what should I do?
What should I say?
There must have been a clue
in something Haruhi said, but...
...what was it?
What's she been saying all this time?
I... I don't know.
Wait...
Stop...
Haruhi...
Thank you! Come again!
It's August the 31st.
I haven't touched my homework.
Whatever... It doesn't matter anymore.
There isn't any point in doing it.
We're just gonna keep re-living
the last couple weeks anyway.
Whatever happens next, whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me will have to deal with it.