Something's wrong... That's what it felt like anyway.
I didn't care about the baseball game on TV;
it was between schools from another town.
But because I tend to sympathize with
underdogs, I ended up rooting for the losing team.
And it was right about then, that I
suddenly got the feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
What the heck does she want?
Hey, your phone's ringing, Kyon.
Yeah, I know that. You don't have to tell me.
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
Meet us at 2:00 in front of the station.
And don't be late!
I didn't even have a chance to say anything.
Yeah, what?
I forgot to tell you, make sure and
bring your swim trunks and some money, too.
Oh, and your bike. Definitely bring your bike.
That's it. Over and out!
Weird... It was like I knew what
Haruhi was gonna say before she said it.
Yeah... No...
Actually, it felt like we'd had the
exact same conversation once before.
Kinda like déjà vu or something.
Summer's almost over...
You are late, Kyon!
Where's your motivation?
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Now that we're all present and accounted for, we can go!
Where?
To the public swimming pool! Where do ya think?
That figures... considering the stuff I brought.
We've got lots of summer vacation-y
things to do during our break!
But we've only so much time because
once it's gone, it's gone for good!
We'll do everything we can, while we can
during our only summer as tenth graders!
And for starters, we're gonna ride the bikes to the pool!
Did... everyone ride bikes today?
No, the only bikes we have to take
are the ones you and I brought with us.
Huh?
Kyon, you better not let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
Well, here we are. Hurry up and park the bikes!
We're trying to have fun, Kyon, so stop acting tired!
And whose fault is that, huh?!
Aah, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes it feel like summer!
Crowded...
Here's the plan, you go dump our stuff
somewhere, and then meet us in the pool.
We're gonna have a little race.
Come on, Mikuru, you and me!
Hurry up and get in, guys!
The water's warm! It's perfect!
Can't she see the "no diving" signs? They're everywhere!
Doesn't that look like fun?
It's such a peaceful looking scene, isn't it?
And in a way, it makes me smile.
I mean, seeing Miss Suzumiya enjoy the day in a normal
fashion. It's a rather charming sight, don't you think?
She called me, told me what to bring,
and then ordered me to meet her without
telling me anything about what was going on.
That isn't charming or normal.
Well, if you ask me, none of that
is anything to make such a fuss over.
And as long as Miss Suzumiya's
laughing and having a good time,
we don't have to worry about any
earth-shattering events happening any time soon.
I hope you're right.
All right!
What?
Nothing. It's just my imagination.
With everything that's happened since we met,
you could say I've become a little bit paranoid.
Here you go!
Oh, thanks for making the tea.
Oh, it's delicious!
Come on, let's go swim some more!
Geez...
Now I know why they call it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi chose this place.
Huh?
There's that feeling again...
It's like I've seen this happen before,
with Nagato sitting there like that, looking bored.
Kyon!
Yeah... And then Haruhi shows up, and says...
These guys are my brigade members.
They do what I say.
So if you want something, ask them!
Time for some fun!
Let's play water soccer!
Uh. Yeah, sure...
Oh, well. Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
Get ready, Mikuru, surf's up!
I've been thinking about some fun things we could do.
What's that thing?
I came up with this schedule of how we're
gonna spend the rest of our summer vacation!
I realized something...
We've only got two more weeks
of summer vacation left to go!
That fact totally blew me away.
I know we've done a lot of cool things
so far, but we've only so much time,
and there's a bazillion more things left for us to do!
So, we're gonna pick up the pace!
Two weeks to do all that?!
Mikuru, is there anything else you wanna do?
Huh?
Uh... I'd like to try goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping, it is...
Could I see that for a moment?
Thank you.
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening close by?
Oh, I could check around for one.
That'd be awesome.
Okay, tomorrow, we start the list.
And I guess that's it for today.
Nagato!
Hey, it's nothing important or anything, but...
I was just wondering...
Is everything okay with you?
It is.
Uh... Great, that's good to hear.
Yes.
What the heck?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
I guess that's it.
The next morning, I was wakened from my
peaceful slumber by a call from Haruhi.
She said they'd found a bon festival.
We're all gonna go buy yukatas.
I guess Yuki doesn't have one, and neither does Mikuru.
And I don't have one either,
but I know a place that sells
them in sets for really cheap.
So, we went to a clothing outlet, and Haruhi
picked out yukatas for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then, she marched them straight into the changing rooms.
After about an hour... they emerged.
Whoa! Blinding!
The three of you look absolutely wonderful in them.
Well, of course we do!
I picked them out myself, especially Mikuru's!
Look at you, you're so cute!
I'm a genius!
Oh? Uh, yeah!
Miss Asahina... Aah!
Wow!
They've got goldfish scooping, just like you wanted!
I bet you're gonna catch a ton!
A bon festival, huh?
It figures that it'd be so crowded...
I haven't been to a bon festival in a while,
but it feels like I just went to one.
That tower... Those vendors...
Do you wanna go scoop some fish?
We could have a little contest.
Leave it to the expert!
Mm, I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato? Do you wanna go get some food?
Don't tell me you're actually into this stuff.
I got it.
No.
That one.
It's yours for 800 yen!
I wish she would've let me buy that for her.
It's the least I could do after all she's done for us.
What an unbelievable haul!
I caught thirteen! But, I only kept one 'cause
I don't have any place to put all those fish.
I gave another one to Mikuru!
Go ahead and have one, but only one!
Okay, thanks.
Hey, Yuki, what's up with the mask you got there?
I bought it.
Oh... Okay.
Anyway, let's go shoot up fireworks!
We'll end the day with a firework show!
Do you even understand the
meaning of the word "moderation"?!
It was summer, and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I wanted to forget about it.
But the truth was, I couldn't ignore it any longer.
Tomorrow, we're catchin' bugs.
Hey, Haruhi, I don't want to spoil your fun,
but have you finished your homework?
Are you kidding? That stuff's easy.
You can finish it in like three days.
Three days?!
You have to get rid of that junk first,
so you can spend the rest of your summer
having fun and not worrying about it!
It's the only way to get the most out of your vacation!
Why does she have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying up the stats for us.
Kay, listen up! We're gonna go bug-catching tomorrow!
And whoever catches the most bugs is gonna get...
Lemme see... I know! They'll get
to be brigade leader for a whole day!
No thanks!
That sounds like a lot of fun!
But, can we catch just any random bug?
Um... No, wait... Only cicadas!
That's it, I'm calling it the SOS
Brigade's cicada catching contest!
The next day was beautiful, sunny, and bright.
In fact, it was the perfect day for us to
have our SOS Brigade's cicada catching contest.
And even though everyone caught
bugs the best way they knew how,
the winner of the contest ended up being...
You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to follow the spirit
of catch and release with these guys.
I mean, if we let 'em go this time,
they might come back and return the favor!
What could a cicada do for me, even if it did come back?
I sorta feel like Pandora, when she opened her box.
W-Welcome to our store!
We met the next day, even though we
had absolutely no idea what was going on.
Our confusion continued as we
stood outside the local supermarket,
wearing frog costumes and handing out balloons.
Hey, it's a living.
I feel like I just escaped the Adzam's leader beam.
You guys did an awesome job!
What's with the special treatment?
You guys are the best!
The manager's super grateful for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful he is? What about our pay?
That's it!
Huh?
I've had my eye on this little guy for a long time now.
The manager gave it to us 'cause
Mikuru looks so darn cute in it!
We worked in the sun, sweat pouring down our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep him in the club room as a souvenir.
And Mikuru, you can wear him whenever you want.
Help yourself!
You have my permission, 'kay?
Later that night...
My peaceful slumber was interrupted by a phone call.
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
What's wrong?
Hello, it's Koizumi.
What are you doing with Miss Asahina at this hour?!
We have a situation here.
Is it possible for you to come meet us right now?
Miss Asahina! What happened? Are you okay?
It's terrible... I can't...
I can't go back to the future anymore!
I'll try to explain it the best I can.
We're stuck in a time loop that, as
far as I can tell, seems to have no end.
It's hard to believe that you're serious
with you standing there, smiling like that.
Come on.
Koizumi, do you have any idea what you just said?
Of course, I do. Much more than I want to, believe me.
In fact, I was having a word with Miss Asahina earlier.
Call me when you have a word with her!
It's like this, we came to the conclusion that something
seemed a little off about the current flow of time.
Well, actually, it was Miss Asahina who discovered it.
And thanks to her, my suspicions were confirmed.
What suspicions?
That we've become stuck in a time loop.
We're re-living the same period
of time, over and over again.
I know; you already said that.
We're being forced to repeat every day
between August the 17th through the 31st.
In other words, we're in the middle of
what seems to be an endless summer vacation.
Well, at least it's summer vacation, right?
It's a never-ending, endless summer vacation.
In the world we're in now, the
future doesn't exist anymore.
All time stops at September the 1st.
That's the reason Miss Asahina can't travel to the future.
It's only natural.
Look, there's nothing natural about not having a future.
And who's gonna believe such a thing?
Well, for starters, we were sort
of hoping you would believe it.
For what it's worth, I can try to explain it, too.
Here goes...
Because I have to classified information,
I have to use classified
information to contact the future.
The thing is, for a week now, I haven't gotten any...
...classified information.
That's kind of weird.
I was so surprised that I... classified information.
I did, but it was classified information.
And now, I don't know... what to do...
I don't know how to help you, but I'm wondering...
Are all the classified information things
you're talking about stuff you can't say on TV?
What about those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Do you think it could be one of those?
No, it isn't one of those.
What happened is that a specific
section of time has been torn away.
At exactly midnight on August the 31st,
everything as we know it, is reset.
Then time loops back on itself,
back to the morning of August the 17th.
That's the process.
Then what about our...
Wait, what about the whole world's memories?
Those get reset as well.
Everyone's memory starts over from the beginning.
Perfect, another problem involving time.
But I guess that's to be expected
when there's a time traveler around, huh?
Oh, no, Miss Asahina didn't have anything to do with this.
Okay then, what's causing it?
It's Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't even realize it though.
But I do think that deep down inside herself,
she'd prefer it if summer vacation would last forever.
You're kidding me!
You mean she still hasn't had enough fun?
That's what I think.
Perhaps she feels there's something else that
has to happen before our summer vacation can end.
Oh, man... The trouble she gets
us into is always galactic in scale.
Right, what do you want me to do about it?
If I knew that, we would have this problem solved by now.
You sure seem like you're enjoying this an awful lot,
what's up?
Please don't take that the wrong way.
But, this explains the feelings
of déjà vu I've been having.
And the ones you've been having as well.
And now that I think about it,
those feelings were probably the residue of our
memories from all the instances where time was reset.
Are we the only ones?
Or can other people feel this happening, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
But then again, you and I are exceptions to the rule.
The only people who can sense this strange thing happening
are the ones who are closest to Miss Suzumiya.
But what about Haruhi?
Do you think she has any idea what's been going on?
No, I don't think she knows about it.
Besides, it would be very bad for us if she did.
Although...
There is someone else who isn't
affected by feelings of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact, this person remembers
everything that's happened since this whole thing started.
Stop holding out on me. Who is it?
You already know who it is.
It's Miss Nagato.
The thought entity transcends space and time,
and so does she.
Is that really true?
It is.
Then you can remember everything.
I can.
So then, do you know how many times
this has happened to us up till now?
This would be 15, 524 times so far.
Fifteen thousand five-hundred twenty-four?
What do you mean 15,524?
Nagato... What are you saying?
You're completely serious about that?
I am.
So what you're telling me is that we've done
the exact same things, every time, that many times?
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,524 repetitions, we did not attend a
bon festival the 2,391st time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival but did not
go to a goldfish scooping booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time jobs...
Okay! I got it...
Fifteen thousand five-hundred twenty-fourtimes...
That's what she said.
Times two weeks... That's, uh... about... 595 years!
And she's the only one who remembers
everything we did all those times.
She's been repeating them, over and over.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the same things that many times?
That, has gotta be the craziest story ever.
The next night, we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony of Nagato's apartment.
And Koizumi brought the telescope.
Oh... I'm bored.
I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
I wish I knew what else she wants to do.
Well, that's the question, isn't it?
I think I just might have an idea though.
What if someone were to grab Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be doing this?!
Who else could play that role, other than you?
Yeah, I knew you were gonna say that.
Like hell.
All right, how 'bout if I give it a try?
Of course, I'm only kidding.
Anyway, the next day, we went to the batting cages.
Hey, Nagato...
You knew about this time loop
thing before Miss Asahina, didn't you?
Yes.
So how come you didn't say anything about it?
My function is to observe only.
All right!
I win again, losers!
Yay!
More time!
I guess that's it. We've done everything on our list.
Hmm... But now I'm wondering if we did enough.
Hmm... Oh, well. That's good.
Unless there's something else you guys wanna do?
Oh, okay then.
We did everything we set out to do this
summer, so I guess that's good enough.
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, guys, we're done for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case,
but I guess you can take the day off now.
I'll see you all at the club room on Monday!
Wait, Haruhi.
There's that feeling again...
It's strong, stronger than all the others.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living the past two weeks
again and again for a thousand more times!
But, what should I do? What should I say?
What's she been saying all this time?
I don't know... I can't... remember...
It's August the 31st,
and I still haven't touched my homework yet.
Whatever... It doesn't matter anymore.
There's no point in doing it. I mean, we're just
gonna keep re-living the last couple of weeks, right?
Whatever happens next, whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me will just have to deal with it.