I brought some tea.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks a lot.
Wow, it's really good.
Here you go.
Why, thank you very much, Miss Asahina.
The SOS Brigade was officially created by Haruhi in May.
It's already June now.
During that time, I was involved
in an incident that's, well...
It was like the world got a sudden case of leg cramps.
All that aside, today's episode
goes a little something like this:
Hey, you guys!
We're gonna enter ourselves in a baseball tournament!
Since the day of that "incident,"
nothing really out of the ordinary's happened.
We were enjoying our brief moment
of peace and boredom as best we could.
And boy, was it a brief moment.
You might be wondering why.
Because when she turns on that smile of hers,
somehow I'm the one who always
ends up completely exhausted.
What did you say we're gonna do?
We're gonna do this!
"Announcing the ninth all city
amateur baseball tournament."
And, who's gonna be entering
this little sandlot baseball game?
You've gotta be kidding! Us, of course!
So when you're saying "us,"
you're talking about everyone here...
Somehow, we need to find at least four more people.
As usual, if somebody's opinion's
inconvenient, she doesn't even hear it.
Hey, do you even know the rules for baseball?
Of course I know the rules.
When I tried out for the baseball team,
they gave me the rundown of all of the basics.
But I wasn't having any fun,
so I hurried up and went home.
Well, if you think baseball's so boring,
why do you wanna enter the tournament so badly?
Because it's our chance to show
the entire world just who we are!
If we win this baseball tournament,
the SOS Brigade will take on a life of
its own and be known all over the world!
It's a great opportunity!
Right, Mikuru? Isn't that a great idea?!
Huh? B-But I wo...
Don't you think baseball is great?!
In fact, we're gonna shoot for the championship!
We can't afford to lose a single
game because you know how I hate losing!
You got that?
Well, I think it would be all right.
Don't smile like that and give into her demands.
Why don't you try disagreeing
with her every once in a while?
Actually, I think this is much more sensible than
walking around the city looking for aliens and UMAs.
All right, when's this tournament supposed to happen?
It's this Sunday!
Day after tomorrow? Are you kidding?!
Don't you think that's way too soon?
But I already turned in the application.
Oh, don't worry about it. It's all set.
I put "SOS Brigade" as our team name.
That's one thing I made sure of!
And as for the other four players we need,
you got any ideas on where to find them?
If I come across anybody walkin' around lookin' bored,
I'll just grab 'em.
Scary thing is: She really means that.
All right, Haruhi, just hang on a second.
I think that Taniguchi and Kunikida
might have some free time on their hands.
They'll do.
It's true: Haruhi thinks of her classmates as objects.
Okay then... Let's see, we need two more.
Uhm... If you don't mind, I think I might have a friend.
Perfect!
Apparently anyone will do.
Hey, wait, Miss Asahina's friend?
Okay, that's interesting.
Friend from where? And what time period?
It's okay, she's from this time... Uh!
I mean, she's just a friend I met in one of my classes.
I know someone. It's an acquaintance who's been
curious about our group for some time now and I think...
I'll handle it, thanks.
Now that that's settled,
it's time for some intensive training!
Intensive training? You mean, right now?
Yeah!
Yeah, but where?
Over there!
So, all of us got roped into entering
a baseball tournament just like that.
Why, you ask? The reason's very simple:
It was because... Well, Haruhi was... bored.
Hey, you guys! Can we use the field now?
And we also wanna borrow your equipment.
Huh? What the heck are you talkin' about?
We need to have baseball practice,
and we're also kind of in a hurry,
so would ya get lost?
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
It'll only be for a little while, right, Mikuru?
Adolescence is so predictable.
For starters, we're gonna
practice catching 1,000 grounders!
Oh, come on, the future of the SOS
Brigade is riding on that ball, so get ready!
This is the first time that I've heard
that our future was riding on such a tiny ball.
Okay, Mikuru, here comes some more.
That hurts! No! Stop!
Miss Asahina, are you all right? Can you stand?
If you're too nice to me, it'll happen again.
Please don't.
Dammit, you guys! Get back to your positions right now!
She's injured, okay?
Fine, then!
Next up, the baseball team!
Why do we have to do it?!
All right, you guys! That's it for today!
Well now, that's surprising.
Miss Suzumiya batted exactly 1,000 hits.
Frankly, I'm more surprised by the fact
that you counted every single one of them.
Hm? Oh, hey, Nagato.
On the day of the tournament, I was
wondering if it was possible to make it rain.
You know, a big one that'd
cancel the game with a rain delay.
It is possible, but I would advise against it.
Yeah, why's that?
Any alteration of the regional climate could possibly have
devastating after-effects on the eco-system of the planet.
And about when would these after-effects happen?
Several hundred to 10,000 years.
Then I guess we'd better try not to do that, right?
Right.
The day of the baseball tournament has finally arrived.
So, you're Kyon?
I hear an awful lot about you from Mikuru.
Oh, this is Miss Tsuruya, that friend I was talk...
I'm Taniguchi. It's very nice to meet you.
And I'm Kunikida.
Yeah, see, when he asked me, I just
couldn't turn down my good buddy, Kyon.
Oh, brother...
Kyon!
Come over here for a minute.
Okay, what were you thinking? Seriously?
You gonna make something like her play baseball?!
Hey, don't go calling my little sister a "something."
She's a person!
Yeah, well, she introduced herself
as a ten year-old fifth grader!
I mean, she's so sweet! I can hardly
believe she's related to someone like you.
This baseball tournament's open to the general public,
it's not some crummy little league game!
You are aware of that?
Yes, Miss Haruhi.
All the more reason to bring my little sister today.
We really don't have a chance of winning,
but since this is Haruhi we're talking about,
watch us win the championship by accident.
That would be a pain.
But, if we have a fifth grader in the lineup,
then we're sure to lose.
Huh. Fine, whatever.
Guess it'll be a handicap.
I'd feel bad if we won this thing too easily.
She still thinks we can win this thing.
By the way, has it occurred to you that you need to
decide the batting order and our positions on the field?
Oh, I thought about that already.
Here, take a look at this: Two types!
One for batting order, the other for field position.
Oh, and I'm the pitcher, and I'll be batting first.
So you're saying all you've figured out
was how we're gonna decide those things.
Yeah, and? You gotta problem with that?
This is the democratic method.
In ancient Greece, they picked numbers
out of a hat to elect their leaders.
Don't compare picking the batting
order for a sandlot ball game...
in modern Japan to how the Greeks picked their leaders.
Besides, you get to do whatever you want.
How's that democratic?
Whatever. All the more reason to go home early.
I mean, from what I hear, our first opponent is a
team of college students, the Kamigahara Pirates.
Apparently, they're the favorites to win the tournament,
and the game is called when one team gets a ten-run lead.
So it's not too early to start
packing up to go home right now.
Play ball!
Hah! You kidding? You call that a pitch?!
Come on, everybody, follow my lead!
I'll try to do my best toda...
Strike!
Why's he throwing so hard at Miss Asahina?!
If he hits her, I'm gonna
charge the mound and deck that guy!
Strike!
Mikuru!
Like this! You swing it and bang!
You're out!
Damn you! Why didn't you even swing the bat?!
Strike!
You're out!
Yuki, if you don't swing, you'll never hit the ball!
Kyon, you're batting cleanup!
You'd better hit the ball!
What do you expect from a
cleanup hitter picked by a lottery?
Strike!
Haruhi hit that thing into the outfield...?
Strike two!
Strike three, you're out!
I have dishonored my family...
Let's take 'em out!
Yeah!
Play ball!
Strike!
Strike three! You're out!
Nice pitching.
Piece of cake, no sweat, guys!
Foul!
She can only throw straight
pitches through the strike zone.
When they figured it out, it was only a matter of time.
On top of that, our defense has more
holes than an anthill in the Savanna.
We're so toast.
The fact that they only scored
two runs off of us must be...
because the opposing teams'
goddess of victory's running late.
I guess everyone wants to relax on a Sunday.
Well, the top of the second inning went by really quickly,
and in the bottom of the inning,
we gave up a few more runs.
Looks like we'll be heading home next inning.
Out!
Phew, that was hard!
It's all I can do to just hit the ball with the bat.
Looks like I'm gonna be needing it after all.
Time out, ump!
W-Wait a minute! Miss Suzumiya!
Come on!
Hurry up!
N-N-No!
Get out of those right now and put this on!
You look good in that!
Can I get a picture of you guys with my phone?!
I wonder if up in a ponytail would be better...?
Fine! Cheer on!
I'm not really sure how to do this!
You do it like this, and yell as loud as you can!
Yo!
Everyone, pl-please hit the ball! I'm begging you:
Do your best out there!
Yeah, I'll knock this sucker out!
Strike out!
Hah, the sun was in my eyes...
Don't sweat it, I wasn't counting on you anyway.
Safe!
Mikuru! Just make sure to hit the ball this time!
Go for it, Mikuru!
Strike!
Mikuru! Like this! Like this!
What is she doing...?
Looks like she's trying to reduce the magic
points of the other team's pitcher or something.
Well, it seems to me that she's
trying to signal for something.
Did we ever decide on signals?
No. But I think that she's
signaling for a squeeze-play right now.
She's signaling for a three bunt squeeze with two outs?
Even the most senile coach in the league
would make better decisions than that.
The chances of Miss Asahina actually
hitting the ball are close to none.
However, if we can catch the Pirates off-guard,
by going for a squeeze-play that normal people
wouldn't think of, there's a possibility that...
one of their infielders might make an error.
Or, maybe she's thinkin' that somehow, Miss
Asahina might even hit the ball with the bat for once.
Well, it looks like they figured it out now.
Strike!
And you're out of there!
Mikuru, get your butt over here
and get ready for some pain, girl!
Take your punishment!
Let everyone have a good, long
look at that funny little face.
Please stop, it hurts!
Hey, numbskull.
It's all your fault for giving confusing signals.
Maybe you should've tried to
steal home yourself or something.
Things aren't looking so good anymore.
I don't wanna hear it, but go ahead.
A closed space larger than anything
we've seen before is starting to form.
And it's spreading at an alarming rate.
It will continue growing,
and the you-know-what's will keep tearing
things apart till Miss Suzumiya's mood improves.
And that's happening just because we're losing?
Oh, man, you've gotta be kidding me.
You're still talking as if it has nothing to do with you.
Believe me, you're involved
with what's happening now, Kyon.
Do you remember how we all had to pick numbers
to determine the batting order for the day?
As a result, you're batting cleanup.
I'm not all that happy about it, you know.
That's not the point. Miss Suzumiya
wished for you to bat cleanup and you are.
That is not a coincidence.
Because you're not performing like one would expect from
a cleanup batter, she's feeling a little disappointed.
Well, excuse me.
In any case, we should all try to play the best we
can so that they don't and call the game this inning.
Because if the game ends here, you can say it's
the equivalent of this world coming to its end.
Let's go, dammit! Take your positions!
This inning, we need to hold
them to two runs no matter what.
Two outs, man on first and second,
and we're down by nine.
If they score another run, this game will be over.
It's coming this way!
Gotta catch it...
Gotta catch it!
Wow! Amazing!
Nice catch!
Getting back to what we were talking about earlier...
Little close there. What's up?
The other day when you and Miss
Suzumiya were stuck in that other world,
I was wondering how you managed
to get yourselves out of it.
Do you have to remind me of that?
It's just that if you use that trick again,
maybe everything here will start getting better.
Forget it.
That's exactly what I thought you'd say.
Very well, let's just go and win this game instead.
After all, she shares the same concerns we do.
Miss Nagato is finally...
What, are you saying there's
something the matter with her?
It looks like she's casting a spell...
A spell? Wait, what're you talking about?
Let's see... That's classified.
A spell, huh?
Take it. I changed the elemental boost information.
Elemental what?
Homing mode.
Wow! It's flying!
I see. Homing mode, huh?
Oh man, there's gotta be a limit to this.
This is great, but if we keep doing this,
things are gonna get ugly... in all kinds of ways.
Well, that should be enough.
I see.
Strike! Strike! Strike!
I had forgotten about it, but the
first round has a 90-minute limit.
That means this is the last inning.
If we can keep them from scoring, we win!
Is it all right for us to win?
It is necessary for us to win.
Thanks to all of our efforts, the expansion of the closed
space looks like it's stopped at least for the time being.
But if they suddenly make a comeback,
then that'll be the game right there.
It's a waste of time to think about how
Haruhi's mood will turn if that happens.
I've got a plan.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am dead serious.
It's the only option we have if we're to get
through this inning without givin' up too many runs.
Oh, brother...
Foul!
Damn you! Be serious about this!
If you lose, you're buyin' everyone lunch after the game!
I know that. After all, the fate of the
entire world is resting on my pitching.
I guess the world's not worth very much...
Thanks to my Mysterious Ball...
I named it myself... it looks like the
world will be spared from certain annihilation.
St-Strike two!
You're out!
In just three pitches, yet another batter struck out.
And now it seems the last batter's
at the plate with two strikes on him.
Kyon, wrap it up with the next pitch, okay?!
There was no doubt about that happening.
Sorry about this, Kamigahara Pirates...
Yeah!
Pick up the ball, Nagato!
Pick up the ball and throw it!
Hurry! Hurry!
Over here!
What the...?!
I'm terribly sorry, but you see, we're not the
typical team of athletes you're used to playing.
That's game!
Thanks to Nagato's magical cheating,
we were able to win the game.
What're we going to do about the game in the next round?
I'm gonna feel bad for the Kamigahara Pirates if
we beat them in the second round like we just did.
I'm really sorry about this, but I'm afraid I'll
need to go and help my colleagues out in a little while.
So we're gonna be short a player then.
How 'bout we forfeit?
Sounds like a good plan.
After today, it looks as if it's a
bad thing when Miss Suzumiya's bored.
We should probably keep that in
mind during any future activities.
Had enough fun for today?
Koizumi had to bail on us because he had
something pop up suddenly, and to tell you the truth,
my arms and legs are killing me right now.
I guess if you're all right with it, then, oh well.
Anyway, I'm hungry. How 'bout
we all go and get some lunch?
You got it.
Thank you, thank you! I can't thank you enough!
No, it's nothing! See you around!
Wait, you know, that bat...
Eat up, everyone! Kyon's treating us today!
What a game, huh, guys?!
Oh, well. Thanks to the Pirates,
I gained a little extra cash today.
Kamigahara Pirates, I wish you luck.
Sorry I'm so late!
So, which one do you think we should try next?!
Soccer or American Football?!
How many do we need to play each?!
Is the number of people we had last time enough?!
As I looked over at Haruhi's brilliant smile,
I was trying to think about which
sport would require less people.
American Football?! No way! How 'bout bowling?!