Something's wrong... That's what it felt like anyway.
I didn't care about the baseball game on TV
because it was between schools from another town.
But, because I tend to sympathize with
underdogs, I ended up rooting for the losing team.
And it was right about then, that I
suddenly got the feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
I know, you don't have to tell me.
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
Meet us at 2:00 in front of
the station. And don't be late!
I didn't even have a chance to say anything.
Now what?
I forgot to tell you, make sure to
bring your swim trunks and some money, too.
Oh, wait, wait. And your bike. Definitely bring your bike.
That's it. Over and out!
That was weird.
It was like I knew what Haruhi was
gonna say before she even said anything.
Hang on... Actually, it felt more like
we'd had the exact same conversation before,
like déjà vu or something.
Summer's almost over...
You're late again, Kyon!
Where is your motivation?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries. I just got here, too.
Now that we're all present and accounted for, we can go!
Where to?
To the public swimming pool! Where do ya think?
That figures... considering the stuff I brought.
We've got lots and lots of summer
vacation-y things to do during our summer break!
But, we've only so much time because
once it's gone, it's gone for good!
So we're gonna do everything we can, while
we can during our only summer as tenth graders!
And for starters, we're riding the bikes to the pool!
Okay. Did everyone ride their bikes today?
No... The only bikes we have to ride
over are the ones you and I brought.
Huh?
All right, Kyon! You can't let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
No ESP allowed!
Come on, guys, hurry up and park your bikes.
Kyon! We're trying to have fun, so stop acting tired!
And whose fault is that?!
Mmm, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes it feel like summer!
Hurry and get in!
Come on, the water's warm! It's perfect!
Can't she see the "no diving" signs?
They're everywhere!
Well, that looks like fun. Don't you think?
I mean, seeing her enjoy the day in a normal fashion.
It's a rather charming sight, isn't it?
And as long as Miss Suzumiya's having a good time here,
we don't have to worry about any earth-shattering events.
I hope you're right.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
It's probably my imagination.
Come on, let's go and have some fun, too.
It's so bitter! May I have another?
That's weird. It's like I've seen this before.
Nagato... sitting all alone, looking bored...
Kyon!
Yeah... And then Haruhi shows up, and she says...
So, these two guys are my brigade members.
They do what I say.
So if you want something, you can ask them!
Time for some fun!
Let's play dodge-ball in the pool!
We're coming!
Oh, well. Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
I've been thinking of some fun things we could do!
Check it out!
What is that?
It's a schedule of how we're gonna
spend the rest of our summer vacation!
I realized something...
We've only got two more weeks
of summer vacation left to go!
That fact totally blew me away.
We've done a lot of cool things but we've only got so
much time, and there's a bazillion more things left to do!
So I say, we gotta pick up the pace!
We've got two weeks to do all that?!
Mikuru, is there anything else you wanna do?
Huh?
Um... I think I'd like to try goldfish scooping?
Okay! Goldfish scooping, it is...
Could I see the list you made?
Okay, thanks.
We'll start the list tomorrow!
Do you guys know if there's a
bon festival happening anywhere?
Or even a firework show?
I could check around for those.
I'll call you if I find one.
Don't forget about goldfish scooping.
After all, it's Mikuru's only request.
Okay, I'll get right on it.
That's it for today! See ya!
I'll be going, too.
Me too. Bye!
Nagato!
Hey, sorry, it's nothing important or anything...
So, how have you been? Is everything okay?
It is.
Oh! Good!
What was that all about?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
A bon festival, huh?
Figures it'd be so crowded.
That tower... Those vendors...
I haven't been to a bon festival in a
while, but it feels like I just went to one.
Mikuru!
They have goldfish scooping
over there, just like you wanted!
Come on, you're gonna catch a ton!
Okay...
Do you wanna go scoop some fish, too?
We could have a contest.
Think I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato? You wanna go get some food?
I didn't know you were into this kinda stuff.
I got it!
No.
That one.
Sure, 800 yen!
I wish she would've let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do after all she's done for us.
Thirteen fish!
It's like the most unbelievable haul ever!
But, I don't have any place to put 'em all.
So I just kept one, and I gave another one to Mikuru!
Go ahead and have one, but only one!
Thanks.
Hey, Yuki, what's up with the mask you got there?
I bought it.
Oh... Okay.
It was summer, and summer vacation.
I guess that's why I wanted to forget about it.
Truth was, I couldn't ignore it any longer.
Haruhi, I don't want to spoil your
fun, but did you finish your homework?
Are you kidding?
That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it in like three days.
Three days?!
You have to get rid of that junk first,
so you can spend the rest of your summer
having fun and not worrying about it!
Why does she have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying up the stats for us.
You guys! Tomorrow, we're gonna go catch some bugs!
And the prize for whoever
catches the most bugs is gonna be...
...um... I know! They get to be
brigade leader for a whole day!
No thanks!
That sounds like a lot of fun!
Can we catch just any random bug?
Um... No... Only cicadas!
In fact, I'm calling it the SOS
Brigade's cicada catching contest!
The next day was beautiful, sunny, and bright.
In fact, it was the perfect day for us to
have our SOS Brigade's cicada catching contest.
That's not a cicada.
I-It's a yanbaru long-armed scarab!
Although everyone caught bugs the best way they knew how,
the winner of the contest ended up being...
You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to follow the spirit
of catch and release with these guys.
You never know, if we let 'em go now,
they might come back and return the favor!
What could a cicada do for me, even if it did come back?
Hurry! Go back to the mountains!
I sorta feel like Pandora, when she opened her box.
W-welcome to our store!
We met the next day, even though we
had absolutely no idea what was going on.
Our confusion continued as we
stood outside the local supermarket,
wearing frog costumes and handing out balloons.
It's a living.
I feel like Unit Zero after it got hit by that beam.
Hey, guys! Awesome job today!
What's with the special treatment?!
You're the best!
The manager's super grateful for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful he is? What about our pay?
There it is!
Huh?!
I've had my eye on this little guy for a long time now.
We worked in the sun,
sweat pouring down our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep him in the club room as a souvenir.
Oh, and Mikuru, you have my
permission to wear him whenever you want.
Help yourself, okay?
Sure! Uh...
Yeah? What?
Oh, it's nothing.
Don't stare at me.
Come on, Mikuru!
You're the cutest little froggy ever!
Put it back on, you know you want to!
Watch the popsicle, ladies.
Later that night,
my peaceful slumber was interrupted by a phone call.
The number you have dialed is no longer...
What the heck?!
Kyon...
Miss Asahina, is that you?
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
I don't know... Wha...
What's wrong?
Hello, it's Koizumi.
How about you tell me what you're doing
with Miss Asahina in the middle of the night?
We have a situation here.
Would it be possible for you to come meet us now?
Miss Asahina! Is everything okay? What happened?
Oh, Kyon! I-I-I can't go back to the future...!
I'll explain it the best I can.
Currently, we're stuck in a time
loop that seems to be infinite.
It's hard to believe you're serious
with you sitting there, smiling like that.
I mean, come on, Koizumi.
Do you have any idea what you just said?
Yes, of course, I do. Much
more than I want to, believe me.
Earlier, I was having a chat with Miss Asahina.
Next time, you guys are chatting, call me!
And then suddenly, we came to the conclusion that there
was something a little off about the current flow of time.
But the truth is, Miss Asahina discovered it.
Thanks to her, my suspicions were confirmed.
What suspicions?
We're currently stuck in a time loop, re-living
the same period of time, over and over again.
Yeah, you already said that.
We've been repeating every day
between August the 17th through the 31st.
We're in the middle of what seems
to be an endless summer vacation.
Well, at least it's summer vacation anyway...
It's a never-ending, endless summer vacation.
The future doesn't exist in this world anymore.
Time stops at September the 1st.
And who's gonna believe such a thing?
Well, for starters, we were sort
of hoping that you would believe it.
I think I can try to explain it.
Okay, here it goes...
Because I have to classified information, I used
classified information to get in touch with the future.
The thing is, I haven't gotten any
classified information for about a week now.
And that's kind of weird.
I was so surprised, I classified information.
I really did.
But it was classified information.
I don't know what to do.
What about those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Maybe we're trapped in one of those.
No, it's not one of those.
A section of time has been torn away from time-space.
At exactly midnight on August
the 31st, everything will reset.
Then time reverts straight back
to the morning of August the 17th.
That's the process.
What about our... No, wait.
What about the whole world's memories?
Their memories are reset.
Everyone's memory starts over from the beginning.
Perfect, another problem involving time.
I guess that figures when there's a time traveler around.
No, Miss Asahina didn't have anything to do with this.
Then, what's causing it?
It's Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't even realize it.
I think subconsciously, she wants
to have summer vacation last forever.
You're kidding!
You're telling me she still hasn't had enough fun?
Yeah, that's what I think.
Perhaps she feels there's something else that needs
to happen before our summer vacation can really be over.
You seem like you're kind of enjoying this.
Do you wanna tell me why?
Please don't take that the wrong way, it's just...
This explains the feelings of déjà vu I've been having.
But, now that I think about it,
those feelings were most likely the residue of my memories
from all the other instances where time had been reset.
So, are we the only ones? Or can
other people feel this happening, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
You and I are exceptions to the rule though.
The only people who can sense this strangeness
are the ones closest to Miss Suzumiya.
But, what about Haruhi?
Does she have any idea about
the stuff that's been going on?
No, I don't think she knows about it.
Besides, it would be very bad for us if she did.
But there's someone else who isn't affected by the time
loop, or the feelings of déjà vu we've been experiencing.
This person remembers everything
that's happened since this started.
Is that true?
It is.
Then... you remember everything?
I can.
Okay then, how many times has this happened so far?
This would be 15,521 times so far.
Fifteen thousand five-hundred twenty-one times?
Wait... What do you mean 15,521 times?
And... you're being completely serious?
I am.
So then, you're saying that we've done the exact
same things that many times, every single time?
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,521 repetitions, we did not attend a
bon festival the 2,391st time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival but did not go to
a goldfish scooping booth exactly 437 times.
We obtained part-time jobs 9,048 times,
and performed six different types of jobs.
In addition to handing out balloons, we
worked as movers, cashiers, we handed out...
Okay! I got it...
Fifteen thousand five-hundred twenty-one times...
That's what Nagato said.
Okay... So... times two weeks...
That's, uh... about... 595 years.
She's the only one of us who
remembers everything we've done.
And she's had to repeat those
same things over and over again.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the same things that many times?
That's gotta be the craziest story ever.
I wonder if they're real.
What's real?
Martians.
I kind of hope they aren't.
I can't see anyone on the surface right now,
but I bet they're a reserved race of
beings who have to live underground.
Whenever us humans are finally able to land on Mars,
I'm sure the Martians'll pop out from wherever
they're hiding, and say something like, "Welcome to Mars!"
I don't think they should pop out.
Ugh, this is boring.
I'm gonna look for some UFOs now.
That night, we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony of Nagato's
apartment, since her place had the best view.
Koizumi brought the telescope.
I wish I knew what else she wants to do.
Well, that's the question, isn't it?
If we knew the answer, we could solve this thing.
I have an idea we can try if you want.
What if someone were to suddenly
grab Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be doing the whispering?
Is there anyone who could play that role other than you?
Yeah, no thanks.
All right then, how 'bout if I do it?
Of course, I'm kidding.
I don't think I could pull that off.
And besides, it would just
confuse Miss Suzumiya in the end.
Hey, Nagato.
You knew about this time loop before
Miss Asahina figured it out, didn't you?
I did.
So then, how come you didn't say anything about it?
My function is to observe.
I see...
We kept chugging along, doing
all kinds of summer vacation things.
We went to a real firework show, and we
even signed up for a goby fishing tournament.
We went to the batting cages, we watched some movies,
went to the beach, bowling, karaoke.
Oh yeah, we were always doing something.
And the whole time, all I could think was
that none of it was going to be enough for Haruhi.
But, what could I do about it?
Nothing.
So, I just bit my lip and watched as the
last days of summer... vacation went by...
And then, before I knew it, August the 30th was here.
That's it. We've done everything on our list.
Hey! Don't mess that up!
Hmm... But now I'm wondering if we did enough.
Oh, well. Yeah, I guess we did do a lot of stuff...
Unless there's something else you guys wanna do?
Oh! Okay, then.
I guess we did pretty much everything
we set out to do, so that's good enough.
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
That's it then! We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case, but I guess
you can go ahead and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday!
Wait, Haruhi.
That's it then! We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case, but I guess
you can go ahead and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday!
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living the past two weeks
again and again for a thousand more times!
That's it then! We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case, but I guess
you can go ahead and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday!
What should I do?
What should I say?
There must have been a clue in something Haruhi said...
But what was it?
What's she been saying all this time?
I don't know...
I can't... remember...
That's it then! We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case, but I guess
you can go ahead and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday!
Whatever... It doesn't matter.
It's August the 31st.
And I still haven't touched my homework.
Who cares?
There's no point in doing it. I mean, we're
just gonna keep re-living the last couple of weeks.
Whatever happens next, whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me will have to deal with it.