Self-proclaimed humanoid interface created by aliens.
Self-proclaimed time traveling girl.
Self-proclaimed squad of ESPer boys.
They've shown me enough proof that I may now safely
remove the words "self-proclaimed" from their titles.
The three of them, each for their own reasons,
mind you, are currently focused on Haruhi Suzumiya.
Even if I believe everything I've
seen, I still can't figure out one thing:
Why me?
An alien? A girl from the future, and an ESPer boy
all migrated toward Haruhi because, as Koizumi put it,
that's what she wished for.
What about me?
Why have I been dragged feet-first
into all of this weird stuff anyway?
I mean, I'm a 100% ordinary high schooler.
No special powers or anything here.
I mean, who wrote this scenario?
Was it you, Haruhi?
Yeah, right. It's not like it's my problem anyway.
Why do I have to get all worked up about it?
All of this is Haruhi's fault.
Seriously, she's the one who should be worried
about all of this weirdness going on, not me.
Nagato, Koizumi, Miss Asahina...
From now on, they should just go speak to her directly,
and whatever happens after that,
well, that's Haruhi's problem.
I've got nothing to do with it.
Everyone else can go do whatever
they want as far as I'm concerned.
Yo.
Hey.
Taniguchi, do you think I'm a normal high schooler?
Huh?
I don't know. Normal high schoolers don't
go around pushing girls down in classrooms,
know what I'm sayin'?
Especially Yuki Nagato, who, according
to my ranking system, scores about A-.
I shall explain myself.
Taniguchi's memory of the events was a
complete fiction; a fantasy, merely a dream.
Nagato's the victim of Haruhi, who's
turned the Literary Club into her lair.
Upset by this turn of events,
she merely consulted me for advice.
I sympathize with the poor girl, and
agreed to help out as best as I could.
After Haruhi'd gone, we'd decided to meet in
the classroom so that we could discuss her options.
That's when Nagato, an anemic
all her life, suffered a seizure.
She toppled over, and as I lunged to prevent
her from falling to the hard, linoleum floor,
you came walking through the door, Taniguchi.
Once you find out the truth about something, ten to
one, it's always gonna turn out to be something trivial.
You liar.
Tch..
Even if I was dumb enough to believe that lie,
the fact that Nagato, who's famous for being
anti-social, mind you, came to you for advice?
Well, that automatically makes you not normal, buddy.
I never realized Nagato's that famous.
Also, you happen to be one of Suzumiya's henchman.
So if you think that you're just
a normal, male high school student,
then I'm about as normal as a water flea.
Hey, Taniguchi, you don't have
any supernatural powers, do you?
Huh?
I knew it. You've finally become poisoned by
Suzumiya's extreme brand of nuttiness, haven't you?
Don't get too close to me, buddy,
or I'll catch the Suzumiya bug.
Why didn't you change outta your gym clothes?
Because it's hot.
Don't worry about it. I'm gonna
change again when we get to the clubroom.
Besides, I've got cleaning duty and
it's easier for me to move around in this.
Yeah, well, can't argue with that.
I was thinking, what do you
want Mikuru's next costume to be?
Hm... We've had the bunny girl, the maid...
I guess she could...
Wait, what do you mean next?!
Kitty cat ears? Or a nurse? Or maybe a dominatrix...
Kitty cat ears... Nurse's outfit... Maybe a dominatrix...
What an idiot.
Hey, you're the one who brought it up.
Oh man... I'm so bored...
I see... There it is.
You working on anything important?
No, nothing.
Really? Hey, what's this?
I'm screwed!
Why does that folder have my name on it, huh?
Come on, let me see, let me see, let me see!
Oh, this? Well, yeah, I warned her.
It's probably nothing to worry about, though.
That sounds like a lie.
Miss Asahina, could you step back a little, please?
Please let me look. Can't I see?
Let me look!
Come on...
What do you two think you're doing?
So, you're into maid outfits, huh?
What're you talking about?
We're gonna change.
Sure, fine with me.
I said we're changing now!
So what?
Get out now!
What's with her?
She never cares if people see her
when she's changing in our homeroom...
Well, now my arms and shoulders are cool, but the
rest of this crummy outfit doesn't breathe at all!
Hello?
So I guess today's the day of the costume party?
Don't make this story more complicated.
Mikuru.
Come here. Have a seat.
They're like a couple of sisters.
She just wants to make a maid with braids.
In the end, it was actually a
pretty normal day at the club.
There wasn't really anything we wanted to do.
Actually, we didn't know what we should do.
It was like a moratorium on life:
As time flowed by, the life we took for granted,
an ordinary life.
And despite feeling dissatisfied about
the overwhelming lack of things to do,
you keep thinking about the next day.
You keep telling yourself you still got lots of time.
But that was unusual in and of itself.
And it really wasn't a bad thing at all.
Almost getting killed by a classmate, or perhaps meeting
a monster tearing up a deserted world with gray skies.
Now, those things don't happen every day.
It's true, I wished that days
like this would last forever,
and wouldn't you think that way, too?
But there was someone that didn't think so.
And, of course, it was Haruhi Suzumiya.
What d'you think you're doing?
Scissors! I need 'em for art class.
Well, okay, I guess, but just
ask for 'em next time, all right?
She knew that she could get away with it.
By the way, do you what makes people have dreams?
There are two kinds of sleep: REM sleep,
and then there's non-REM sleep.
The two repeat in intervals throughout the sleep cycle.
During REM, when the body's asleep, but the brain
is still somewhat active, that's when we have dreams.
Kyon. Kyon!
The alarm hasn't gone off yet, has it?
Wake up!
No way.
I'm telling you to wake up!
Do you know where we are right now?
I thought I woke up,
and then I found myself in this place
with you lying there, passed out next to me.
What's going on? And why did we
wake up outside our school like this?
A closed space.
I thought I was sleeping in my bed at home,
so how did we end up in this place?
The sky, it's weird.
Have you seen Koizumi?
No, why? Is he here?
No, just a hunch I had.
First off, let's get out of the school.
We might be able to find someone somewhere else.
You don't seem very surprised by all of this somehow.
Oh, I'm surprised all right.
Especially at the fact that you're here.
What is this?
This thing runs all around the perimeter of the school.
Does that mean we can't get out of here?
Well, if you're scared, just go
ahead and grab my arm, why don'tcha?
I'm sure it will help get me in the mood.
Jerk.
I can't get a dial tone.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Hey, Kyon, look.
Where are we...?
It's really weird...
You thirsty?
No thanks.
What's going on? What is this?
I don't get it at all.
Where are we? And why am I here anyway?
And on top of all that, why am I alone with you?
How should I know?
I'm gonna look around.
You stay here, got it?
I'll be right back.
Typical Haruhi behavior.
Koizumi, that you?
Well, hello there.
Took you long enough to show up.
Although I guess I was sort of expecting
to see you looking a little more normal.
Yeah, that. I need to talk to you about something.
Frankly speaking, this is what
I'd call an emergency situation.
Normally, I can get into closed
space without too much trouble,
but this time, even with some
extra power from my colleagues,
it was all I could do to show up in this incomplete form,
and I'm not gonna last too long either.
Looks like our ESPer powers are fading.
They could disappear any minute now.
Then, do you know what's going on?
And are Haruhi and I the only ones stuck in here?
That's it, the thing we've been afraid of
happening all along is starting to happen right now.
It seems Miss Suzumiya's finally
given up on the real world.
She's decided to create a new one now.
In other words, this is the end of the world.
What was that?!
The top brass at the organization
is seriously panicked right now.
Nobody knows what will happen to the
real world now that we've lost our deity.
If Miss Suzumiya's feeling merciful, we might
get to keep living on this side of the bubble.
But it might disappear into nothing the next minute, too.
Wait, now why's this...
Who knows? In any case, both you and Miss
Suzumiya have completely disappeared from our world.
You two aren't in an ordinary closed space.
It's a new dimension that Miss Suzumiya's created.
I dunno. Maybe all the other closed spaces
were practice for the one you're in right now.
The space that you're in right now is probably
the world that Miss Suzumiya wishes she was in.
I don't really know what she wants, so,
I'm at a loss as to what could happen next.
Do you have any idea why I'm the one in here with her?
You honestly have no idea why?
You were chosen by Miss Suzumiya.
You were the one and only person from the other
world that Miss Suzumiya really wanted to be with.
I thought you'd have realized that by now.
Looks like I'm almost out of time.
Way things are going, I don't think
we'll be seeing each other again.
So you're telling me that's it? I gotta live all
alone here with Haruhi in this dull world of gray?
You're the new Adam and Eve.
Go on, procreate and increase the population.
I'll punch you for that.
Just joking. It's only a theory,
but I think in a little while,
this place will start looking more familiar.
However, it's not going to be
exactly the same as over here.
Well, if I ever get reincarnated on your side,
be sure to say hi for me.
So we can never go back to that side ever again?
Only if Miss Suzumiya wishes it.
Although I hate to say it, the
chances of that are pretty slim.
I'm gonna miss you guys a lot; I would've
liked to get to know both of you better.
The whole thing fills me with a bit of regret.
Oh! Almost forgot. I've got messages for
you from Mikuru Asahina and Yuki Nagato.
Miss Asahina told me to deliver an apology to you.
"I'm sorry, it's all my fault."
And Yuki Nagato told me to
tell you, "Turn on the computer."
Goodbye...
What kind of joke is this anyway...?
'Course I can see it.
What should I do?
That what?
Nagato!
What do you want me to do...?
Nagato... Koizumi...
Kyon! Something's here!
What is it?! A monster?! It's not an illusion, is it?!
Maybe it's an alien?!
Or is it some kind of super weapon that a race of
ancient people created that's been awakened in our world?!
What're you doing?!
That thing's not trying to attack us, is it?
What're we running away from it for?
I don't think it's evil or anything.
Who knows?
Do you know what's happening?
This weird world, and that giant...
Don't you wanna go back to the world we used to be in?
We can't stay in a place like this forever.
I mean, if we get hungry, there
aren't any places to eat here.
It's strange, but I have a feeling we'll get by somehow.
I'm having fun right now. I wonder why...?
What're you going to do with the SOS Brigade?
You created it. Are you just gonna throw it away?
It doesn't matter anymore.
I'm having the strangest, most wonderful
experience I've ever dreamed of having!
I don't need to search for it
when it's happening right here.
But I wanna go back!
It took something like this to make me realize:
Even though I complain a lot, I
really liked my life up till now.
Kunikida, and that idiot Taniguchi...
Koizumi, Nagato, Miss Asahina...
And that Asakura girl who disappeared,
you could put her on the list, too.
What're you talking about?
I wanna go back and see all of them again.
I don't know, I feel like I've still got so
many things that I wanna talk to them about.
You'll see them again. It's not like this place
is gonna be covered by a big, gloomy shadow forever.
Once tomorrow comes around, I'm
positive the sun's gonna shine again.
I know it will, I can tell!
That's not it. I'm not talking about seeing them in here,
I wanna see everybody from the old world in the old world.
I don't understand you...
Weren't you sick and tired of
the boring world we were living in?!
Didn't you want something really weird
and interesting to happen like I did?!
I used to.
You know something, Haruhi?
For the last couple days, I've had all
these strange things happening around me.
You had no way of knowing this, but I guess you
could say the world's been revolving around you.
You've been completely unaware of it,
but actually, everything in the world was
getting more and more weird and interesting.
Nagato said she was the potential for evolution.
Miss Asahina called her a distortion in space time.
And Koizumi treated her like a god.
Then, what about me?
What does Haruhi Suzumiya mean to someone like me?
Haruhi is Haruhi, nothing else but Haruhi.
Great, using tautology to dodge the question.
I can't help it, I just don't
have a definite answer for it.
I mean, think about it.
If somebody pointed at a classmate of yours and asked
you what that person meant to you, how would you answer?
What would you say?
Sorry, I'm dodging the question again.
But to me, Haruhi isn't just a classmate,
and of course, she's not the potential for evolution,
a time distortion, or a god either.
That's impossible!
Do you know the story of Snow White?
What's wrong?
I've sorta got a thing for girls with ponytails.
What?
I don't remember when it was,
but you had your hair in a ponytail,
and it looked so good on you, it was criminal.
Huh?
What're you, an idiot?
What kinda dream was that?!
Sigmund Freud's gotta be laughing at me!
I never had a dream that was so realistic before...
Or maybe... Maybe this isn't the old world anymore.
Maybe this world is a new one that Haruhi created.
And if that's the case, how
would I go about confirming it?
Yo.
How you doin'?
I dunno, not so good.
I had a nightmare last night.
Really?
Yeah, I couldn't really get any sleep because of it.
I've never wanted to ditch school so badly like today.
Is that so?
Haruhi.
Yeah, what?
Looks good on you.
I believe I should be thanking you right now.
Looks like I get to keep my
part-time job a little while longer.
Well, I don't think we can deny
the distinct possibility that...
the world we're in now was
freshly created by her last night.
In any case, it is an honor to
see you and Miss Suzumiya again.
Be seeing you after class.
You and Haruhi Suzumiya disappeared from
this world for two hours and 30 minutes.
So, tell me, how many more of
your kind are out there anyway?
A lot.
And, is somebody like Asakura going to
come around and try and kill me again?
Don't worry.
I won't let that happen.
Kyon, you're back!
I'm so glad to see you again.
I thought... that you'd... never make it back...
Miss Asahina...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
If Miss Suzumiya saw this, it'll be like
birds of a feather repeating their mistakes again!
I don't have any idea what you're saying.
By the way, Miss Asahina, I believe you've got a star
shaped mole on your chest right about here, am I right?
H-How did you know that...?
I-I didn't even know it was
shaped like a star till just now.
W-W-When did you realize it?
And what are you two doing?
Mikuru. I bet you're bored with the maid outfit, so...
I gotcha a new one.
What?
Stop squirming!
Resistance is futile!
This time it's a nurse's outfit!
Or should I say doctor's aid?
Oh, whatever you call 'em, it's cute!
Now, let me tell you about what happened afterwards.
The SOS Brigade finally submitted
all the necessary paperwork,
to register as an extra-curricular
group within the school.
I was sure that the name "Spreading Excitement
All Over the World With Haruhi Suzumiya Brigade"...
...would've been rejected outright.
So we changed it at the last minute to:
"Spreading Cheer to Our Student Body Brigade."
And we still patrol the town for strange phenomena.
Today's our second tour of duty.
By some strange coincidence,
Miss Asahina, Nagato, and Koizumi
all had errands to run,
so I'm waiting for Haruhi by myself.
I made sure to arrive an hour
before we had agreed to meet.
Remember, we had a rule that regardless of whether or not
you were late, the last person to show up gets a penalty.
I'm not quite sure why she's scowling.
Perhaps it's a reaction to the low attendance rate today.
Or could it be regret that she's shown up last?
I dunno.
But I'll have lots of time to find out...
...when she's buying me lunch at the café.
And when we sit down,
I'd like to talk to her about all sorts of things.
About how the SOS Brigade is going to operate from now on,
my wish-list for Miss Asahina's cosplay, etc., etc.
But I digress. I already know exactly
what I wanna talk to her about first.
Yeah, that's right.
For starters, I'm thinkin' I'd like to talk to her a
little bit about aliens, time travelers, and... ESPers.