Something's... wrong.
That's what it felt like anyway.
I didn't care about the baseball game on
TV 'cause it was between some other schools.
For some reason, I got into anyway,
and started rooting for the losing team.
And that's when I got the feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
What does she want?
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
I know; you don't have to tell me.
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
Meet us at 2:00 in front of
the station. And don't be late!
I didn't have a chance to say anything.
Now, what?
I forgot to tell you, make sure to
bring your swim trunks and some money, too.
Oh, wait, and your bike. Definitely bring your bike.
That's it. Over and out!
Well, that was weird. It was like I knew what
Haruhi was gonna say before she even said anything.
Yeah... No...
Actually, it felt like we'd had that exact same
conversation before, like déjà vu or something.
Summer's almost over...
You're late again, Kyon!
Where's your motivation, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
You're the only reason I showed up anyway.
Thanks, that's really sweet.
Now that we're all present and
accounted for, we can get going!
Where to?
To the public swimming pool. Where do ya think?
That figures... considering the stuff I brought.
We've got lots of summer vacation-y
things to do during our summer break!
But we've only so much time because
once it's gone, it's gone for good!
We have to do what we can, while we can
during our one and only summer as tenth graders!
It's up to Kyon and Koizumi to get us to the pool.
I know I'm gonna hate asking this,
but what did you mean by that last thing?
You guys are taking us there on your bikes!
Mm, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes it feel like summer!
Restrain thyself!
Canst thou not see the "no diving" signs?
Hurry up and get in, guys! The water's warm! It's perfect!
Doesn't that look like fun?
I mean, seeing Miss Suzumiya enjoy
the day in such a normal fashion.
It's rather charming, don't you think?
First, she called me up and told me what to bring,
And then, she demanded I meet her
without telling me what was going on.
I'm sorry, but I don't see anything
charming or normal about that.
Well, when she gets an idea, she
tends to strike while the iron's hot.
Yeah, but every time she strikes, something goes wrong.
And by wrong, I might nightmarishly wrong.
You have a point,
but it's peaceful enough around here.
And as long as Miss Suzumiya's
laughing and having a good time,
we don't have to worry about any earth-shattering events.
Now what is it?
It's nothing...
Just my imagination, I guess.
With everything that's happened since we
met, you could say I've become slightly paranoid.
Let's race one more time!
It's like...
Yum! It's strawberry-licious!
Get it!
Geez...
Now I know why they call it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi chose this place.
There's that weird feeling again.
It's like I've seen this happen before.
Nagato, sitting there... all alone, looking bored.
Kyon!
Yeah... And then Haruhi shows up and says...
"So, these two guys are my brigade members.
They do what I say, so if you want something, ask them!"
Okay!
Time for some fun!
Let's go play water soccer!
Yeah, sure...
Oh, well. Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
I've been thinking of some fun
things to do, so I came up with this.
What is that thing for?
It's a schedule of how we're gonna
spend the rest of our summer vacation!
A schedule for who?
For us, that's who!
We've only got two weeks of vacation left.
That fact alone blew me away.
We've done a lot of cool things,
but we're running outta time.
There's still a bazillion more things left for us to do.
I say, we gotta pick up the pace!
Two weeks to do all that?!
Mikuru, is there anything else you wanna do?
I think I'd like to try goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping, it is.
Could I see that?
Okay, thanks.
We'll start the list tomorrow!
Do you guys know if there's a
bon festival happening anywhere?
Or a place to see fireworks?
Why don't you find that stuff yourself?
I can check around for those.
I'll call you if I find anything.
Perfect!
I'll leave it up to you!
That's it for today! See ya!
Hey, Nagato?
Uh, well... It's nothing important or anything,
but I was just wondering... Is everything okay?
It is.
That's good to hear.
Yes.
Okay...
That's it. You can go.
Sorry to keep you.
What was that?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
And just like that, Koizumi managed to find
a bon festival happening the very next day.
Wow!
So this is what festivals were like back in this time.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised it's so crowded.
Look, Mikuru!
They've got goldfish scooping
over there, just like you wanted!
Let's catch a ton and break some scoopers!
Don't break the scoopers.
I didn't know you were into stuff like that.
I got it.
No.
That one.
Okay, it's yours for 800 yen!
Thanks!
I wish she would've let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do after all she's done for us.
What an unbelievable haul!
But, I don't have room for all
those fish, so I just kept two for us!
Anyway, let's go shoot off some fireworks!
It's the perfect way to end the day!
Come on! Don't you ever get tired?
Oh, well. If anything, Haruhi's endless
energy is one her better qualities.
Reckless as always.
It was summer, and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I wanted to forget about it.
Truth was, I couldn't ignore it any longer.
Tomorrow, we're gonna catch some bugs.
I don't want to spoil your fun, but
have you finished your homework yet?
You gotta be kidding. That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it in like three days.
Three days?!
You have to get rid of that junk first,
so you can spend the rest of your summer
having fun and not worrying about it!
That's the only way to get the most out of your vacation!
Why does she have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying up the stats for us.
So anyway, tomorrow we're gonna go bug-catching!
And the prize for catching the most bugs is gonna be...
Um... He, he, the winner gets
to be brigade leader for a day!
That's the last thing I'd wanna be!
That sounds like a lot of fun,
but can we catch just any random bug?
No... Only cicadas!
That's it, I'm calling it
the SOS Brigade's cicada catching contest!
The next day was another beautiful day, sunny and bright.
And the winner of the contest ended
up being... You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to follow the spirit
of catch and release with these guys.
I mean, if we let 'em go this time,
they might come back and return the favor!
If something were to come back and return the
favor of being randomly captured and released,
I'd say they'd have to be as dumb as a bug.
Hurry! Go back to the mountains!
Wel-Welcome to our store!
The next day, our fearless
leader got us some part-time jobs.
Would you like a balloon?
No?
Take it.
Gimme!
Sure...
Thank you!
Wearing a costume in heat like this isn't a job.
It's more like a test of endurance.
Like I said, our pay is the costume Mikuru's wearing.
I've had my eye on this little guy for a long time now.
The manager gave it to us
'cause Mikuru looks so cute in it!
We worked in the sun, sweat pouring down our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep this froggy in the club room as a souvenir.
And Mikuru, you can wear him whenever you want to, okay?
You have my permission!
Dammit...
Hello?
Kyon...
Miss Asahina, is that you?
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
Is this really Miss Asahina?
Oh, hello! It's Koizumi.
How about you tell me what
you're doing with her at this hour?!
We have a bit of situation here.
And it's a pretty dire one, at that.
You could even say it's an emergency.
Sorry we had to call you out so late.
Miss Asahina! What happened?
I'm gonna kill you, Koizumi!
Oh, Kyon...
I-I can't go back to the future!
Because I have to classified information,
I used classified information
to get in touch with the future.
I haven't gotten any classified
information for about a week.
And I started to think how weird that was, and I...
I was so surprised, I classified
information, I really did.
But it was classified information, too.
And now I don't know what to do!
Are all the classified information things
you're talking about, stuff you can't say on TV?
I'll explain it the best I can.
We're stuck in a time loop that seems to infinite.
We're repeating every day between
August the 17th through the 31st.
You see, time doesn't exist after September the 1st.
It's only natural Miss Asahina
can't go back to the future,
when there's no future to go to.
There's nothing natural about not having a future.
I mean, who's gonna believe such a thing?
Actually, we were sort of hoping you would believe it.
They say, "Believe and you'll be saved,"
but I've yet to be saved from anything, even once.
Well, what's causing this to happen? Got any ideas?
Wait, you mean you don't already know?
I don't want to, so there.
It's Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't even realize it's happening.
It's a result of her subconscious desires.
She wants summer vacation to last forever.
You're kidding! She still hasn't had enough fun?
That's what I think.
Perhaps she feels there's something else that needs
to happen before our summer vacation can really be over.
Oh, man... The trouble she gets
us into is always galactic in scale.
Well, anyway, at least now I have an explanation for
all those weird feelings of déjà vu I've been having.
You too? Do you think it's possible
other people are having the same feelings?
I doubt it, but you and I are different.
The only people who can sense this strange thing
happening are the ones who are closest to Miss Suzumiya.
However, there's someone who doesn't seem
to be affected by these feelings of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact, this person
remembers everything that's happened.
Well, are you gonna tell me who it is or what?
I think you already know that, too.
Is that true?
It is.
You can remember everything?
I can.
Then, how many times has this happened to us?
This would be 15,532 times so far.
Fifteen thousand five-hundred thirty-two?
Nagato, I'm having a hard time processing all this.
But are you serious?
I am.
You're saying we've done the exact
same things, every time, that many times?
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,532 repetitions, we did not attend a
bon festival the 2,391st time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival but did not
go to a goldfish scooping booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time jobs 9,056 times
and performed six different types of jobs.
In addition to handing out balloons,
we worked as movers, cashiers...
Stop!
Okay... I got it.
Fifteen thousand five-hundred thirty-two times...
That's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks... That's, uh... 595 years!
She's the only one who remembers everything we've done.
And she's had to repeat those
same things, over and over again.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the same things that many times?
That's gotta be the craziest story ever.
The next night, we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony of Nagato's apartment.
And at first, Haruhi was all over that telescope.
But eventually...
Oh, man. I wish I knew what else she wants to do.
That's the question, isn't it?
If we knew the answer, we'd be
well on our way to solving this thing.
I have an idea we can try if you want.
What if someone were to grab Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be doing this?!
Can you think of anyone better suited for that role?
My turn! I summon my veto card!
All right. How about if I do it?
I'm just kidding.
I don't think I could pull that role off anyway.
Besides, it would just confuse Miss Suzumiya.
We chugged along, doing all
kinds of summer vacation things.
We went to a real fireworks show, and we
even signed up for a goby fishing tournament.
We did the test of courage, watched some
movies, went to the beach, bowling, even karaoke.
We were always doing something, always on the move.
And the whole time, all I could think was
that none of it was going to be enough for Haruhi.
But, I couldn't do anything about it.
So, I just bit my lip and watched as the
last days of our summer vacation went by.
And then, before I knew it, August the 30th was here.
Well, that's it. We finished everything on our list.
I know we did a lot, but now I wonder if we did enough.
Hmm... Oh, well. Yeah, I guess we did do a lot.
Unless there's something else you guys wanna do?
Oh, okay then.
We pretty much did everything we set out
to do this summer, so I guess that's enough.
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
I guess that's it for today.
I set tomorrow aside just in case,
but I guess you can take the day off now.
I'll see you guys at the club room on Monday!
Wait, Haruhi!
There's that feeling again!
And it's stronger than all the others!
Now I know we've done this ten thousand times before,
I can't let Haruhi leave. If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living the past two weeks again and again!
But, what should I do?
There must've been a clue in something Haruhi said.
But what? What? What?! Come on! Remember!
It's something I'm worried about,
but I'm putting it off for some reason.
If I don't do something now, she'll go home!
I can't let that happen! If I do, nothing will change!
Try to remember! What've we done up till now?
What didn't we do?!
There's no time to think about it anymore.
It doesn't matter if it doesn't work.
Just say something, anything!
Hang on a second!
We're not done yet!
Homework! Homework!
What are you talking about?
None of my homework's done! I haven't even started it yet!
My summer can't be over until I finish it!
Are you nuts?
Koizumi! Did you finish your homework?
No, uh, we were so busy, I'm only half-way done with it.
Let's do it together!
You too, Nagato. I bet you're not done yet.
And you're coming with us, Miss Asahina.
Uh, where are we going?
We're all gonna meet at my house!
Bring all your notebooks and
textbooks, and we'll work on it together!
We'll finish our summer activities once and for all!
Nagato, Koizumi, I need to copy whatever you've got.
Roger that!
We're gonna start first thing tomorrow morning.
And we're gonna go all day until we finish!
Hold it right there!
How dare you give the orders?!
I'm the brigade leader, and as your
superior, you need to get my permission first!
Who do you think you are, huh?!
Acting without my permission is against the rules!
I wanna come over, too!
It looks like I hit the jackpot.
Miss Suzumiya is a smart and talented person.
She's always been that way, and she always will be.
And that's probably why it never occurred to her that
summer homework could also be a bit of a pain for others.
Since she's never had to do the study group thing before,
I can see how she'd overlook an opportunity like that.
It was the first day of the new term.
I should have gone home by now,
but I ended up coming here instead.
Koizumi showed up, too. Probably for the same reason.
It was weird though. Nagato wasn't there.
I couldn't tell by looking at her, but
I'll bet she must've been pretty exhausted.
The thought of us re-living the past two weeks
tens of thousands of times seems like a bad dream.
I'm not at all surprised you feel that way.
We don't share any memories with the versions
of us who had to go through 15,531 time loops.
That's because on the 15,532nd time, we
snapped back into the normal time flow.
How about a game of poker?
Yeah, sure. Why not? I don't have any money though.
Then we'll play for fun.
I did get a lot of hints,
hints like those feelings of déjà vu,
especially the last one.
I wonder if it could've been a memory
sent by one of the previous versions of us.
I'm here because of all the us'es, if that's
even a word, who had to repeat those last two weeks.
That's the way I have to think about
it, so that it wasn't all for nothing.
If I did forget, then I'd be like Haruhi,
who's unaware those summers even happened.
How many?
I'm good.
Then, so am I.
If I had the chance to live today all over again...
Whoa!
I hope I remember to put some cash down on this hand.