Do you want me to do anything?
Nope, not a thing! You're good to go.
You can go home now. We're done for today!
You heard what she said.
Our Haruhi-esque activities are over for the day.
Either through skilled negotiations or outright
blackmail, she managed to score all this stuff.
No money changed hands; it was 100% free.
There's an old saying: "There's nothing
scarier than something that's free."
As far as I can tell, Haruhi isn't afraid of anything.
But if anyone out there knows of something
that would scare her, give me a shout.
I wanna know what it is.
Whatcha got there? Presents for all the good little kids?
Yeah, what do ya think?
'Course not.
Model guns, right on. Didn't know you were into those.
I'm not, these things belong to Haruhi.
Ohh... Suzumiya's, huh?
Well, guess it must be tough for ya.
That reminds me.
Hm? What's up?
Well, the arts festival is coming up.
I was just wondering what you guys were gonna be doing.
What are you asking me for?
Yeah, like I'm definitely gonna
get a serious answer from Suzumiya.
Nagato doesn't say anything,
so there's no point asking her.
Miss Asahina won't come anywhere near me,
and the other guy's kinda creepy, ya know?
I'm outta options, so that's why I'm asking.
Yeah, that's me-- PR guy, nice guy, whatever.
You're definitely in the latter category.
Well, yeah. I mean, you're so nice,
you'd stick with someone even if you knew
they were headed straight for the edge of a cliff.
The typical nice guy.
Okay then, when I find anything
out, you're gonna be the last to know.
Hey!
I already knew that Haruhi's latest path
to fun and adventure was gonna lead nowhere.
I didn't need to be reminded of that.
The thing is, me and Haruhi weren't
the only ones walking down that path.
There were three others who
were shuffling right along with us.
Now, I didn't have to worry about two
of them; they'd be okay on their own.
But Miss Asahina wasn't safe.
I mean, you'd think if she was from the future, she
could predict all the crazy stuff she gets put through.
But, since that's not the case,
it was up to me to protect her.
What? I'm just helping you get undressed!
Stop struggling!
Come on!
Come in!
What the?!
Well?
She looks amazing in that outfit!
I wonder if it's Kyonic.
Hello, everyone!
Oh, pardon me.
Ooh, wow! That looks wonderful on you, really!
Yeah, guy, no kidding.
I'm having a hard time understanding
why we've got a waitress here.
This is a club room, not a cafe.
I'll tell you why.
This is the costume Mikuru's
gonna wear in our awesome movie!
Really?
Won't the maid outfit you make
her put on work just as well?
Of course not!
A maid provides a more personal service,
usually she's in a big mansion somewhere.
But waitresses are different.
They work at restaurants and cafes, and the
services they provide are for the general public.
Yeah, I know the difference.
But that doesn't explain why
Miss Asahina has to wear that.
Oh, you get so hung up on the tiny details.
She's dressed like that because it feels right!
Anyway, I'm cool with it.
Okay, but is it cool with Miss Asahina?
Well, this feels like it might be a bit too small for me.
I... I can't... I don't...
It's perfect!
The fit's perfect, you look
perfect in it, everything's perfect!
No use, she's made up her mind.
People! This is gonna be the
concept for our awesome movie!
As the director, I've dedicated myself to
providing quality entertainment for the masses!
And when the credits roll, everyone will be
on their feet! I'm talking standing ovation!
Yes! Yuki! You totally understand, don't you?
Yeah! That's it!
Not sure what "it" is, but that has to be her
costume for her class's fortune-telling thing.
At least, that's what I could figure out based on the
answers Nagato gave to Haruhi's rapid-fire questions.
Either way, I wonder what she was thinking, walking
all the way over here from class dressed like that.
That costume couldn't be more perfect
for the character I have in mind.
How is that supposed to be perfect?
Look!
No way! Is this my fault?
You're right, it's perfect!
But then I shouldn't be surprised.
I'd expect nothing less from you, Miss Suzumiya.
It's wonderful casting.
Don't smile at me, I'll turn to stone.
Yeah, I hear ya.
Okay, Kyon. I want those guns ready
for some action by the end of the day!
We start shooting tomorrow, so we'll need 'em.
Oh! And you have to figure out how to use the camera, too.
Got it?
Do you think there's going to be trouble?
When have we ever not had any
trouble with her crazy schemes?
Trouble, he says. Don't make me laugh.
Well, it's not a laughing matter, per se.
But there's no reason to worry, either.
How can you be so sure? The parts she's
cast us in are just characters in her movie.
I seriously doubt Miss Suzumiya believes
I'm a teenage ESPer. It's just a coincidence.
It's like this: The Itsuki Koizumi in
the movie is just a character I play.
The fact that he's an ESPer, too? Again, coincidence.
And if you're worried about
her putting two and two together,
it's hard to believe anyone would
confuse an actor with the role they play.
I'm sure some people might, but I
highly doubt Miss Suzumiya is one of them.
Yeah well, that still doesn't
make me feel better about it.
There's no guarantee that what you said is the way it is.
If she was the kind of person
who'd mix reality and fiction,
then you can be pretty sure our world
would be much more fantastic than it is.
Consider that for a moment, and you'll see.
Miss Suzumiya is a rational human being, after all.
A rational human being, he says.
Well, thanks to her rational god-like ways,
I've had the pleasure of being dragged head-first
into some of the weirdest situations of my young life.
Haruhi doesn't even know what she's capable of.
Of course, we can't let Miss
Suzumiya find out who we really are.
I'm sure at some point, we might very well
have to reveal our true identities to her.
But now is definitely not the time for it.
Thankfully, Miss Asahina and Miss Nagato's
respective groups are in agreement with mine.
To be honest, I wouldn't mind if
things just stayed they way they were.
Then that makes two of us.
I'm not too crazy about seeing the world go to pieces.
If I might make a suggestion, you should
stop worrying so much about the world.
You should be more worried about yourself.
If necessary, there are others
who can replace Miss Nagato and I.
However, there is no understudy for you.
Man! All this festival crap pisses me off!
Why?
Every time I turn around, I'm seeing people having
a blast. I'm like the only one not having any fun.
And seeing all the couples is the worst.
I'm gonna kill somebody!
Jealousy rears its ugly head.
What does our class wanna do? A freaking survey!
Lame!
If you've got a better idea, why didn't
you say something when you had the chance?
If you had, maybe Haruhi wouldn't
have come up with this movie idea.
Yeah! No thanks!
I don't wanna be in charge of putting it all together!
Yeah... I wish Miss Asakura were still here.
She'd do it.
I know.
She was double A+!
It really sucks she had to transfer out of school.
I wonder if it's too late for me to change classes.
Which one would you wanna go to? Are
you thinkin' about Miss Nagato's class?
Hang on, I just remembered! I saw her walkin'
around in some kinda witch costume yesterday.
What was that about?
Yeah, like I'd know. Sorry, pal.
I just remembered!
That time I walked in on you and her
all tangled up on the classroom floor.
That was nothing.
Yeah, I know. It was just something
Suzumiya cooked up or something, right?
Oh... Yeah...
Taniguchi's complete and utter
misunderstanding of that day gave me some relief.
Thanks, Taniguchi. Your stupidity will save the world.
Man... This is boring...
Okay, people! Let's shoot a movie!
This is sudden.
I looked all over the school for a good location.
But nothing worked, so we'll have to find some place else.
Come on, Mikuru! Get ready!
Um, do I really have to go too?
Well, yeah... We can't shoot
anything without our lead actress!
Uh, okay, but... do I have to wear this outside?
You sure do!
Can't I at least wear a jacket over this?
No! The more you think about it,
the more nervous you're gonna get.
How do you expect to win the Golden
Globe if you're behaving like this?
I thought we were trying to be the
#1 event of the festival or something.
Oh, yeah! Yuki!
Here! Hang onto this!
I changed your character into an
evil alien witch. So, what do you think?
She's already rewriting the script!
I guess Nagato's powers could
be considered magical, though.
Come on, Kyon! Get the camera ready!
Right! Let's shoot a movie!
Here we go!
God help us. She looks like she's serious.
Huh?! The heck's that?!
Hey, Haruhi, wait a sec.
It's just... I don't think it's a good idea for
these two to get on the train dressed like this.
I don't see anything wrong with it.
There definitely is!
Uh-uh! If they were butt-naked, then yeah, they'd
get arrested, but they're both wearing clothes.
Or maybe, you'd prefer the bunny-girl outfit!
Oh, you shoulda said so earlier.
After going to all the trouble to find this
waitress costume, I'm shocked to hear you say that!
Wait, didn't you say her being a
waitress was part of the concept?
Right now, what's important is your
ability to adapt to the situation.
Adaptability is how all life
on this planet evolved, right?
And if you don't evolve, you're gonna get left behind.
Then if the planet were sentient, it would
have chucked Haruhi way out into space by now.
Look! The train's here!
Come on, Mikuru! Stop stalling!
Hey, there! We're here!
Oh, and right on time, I see.
Is this the same girl from yesterday?
I didn't recognize her.
Okay then, you better get to it!
Just leave everything to us!
All right, people!
We're gonna have a quick meeting, so gather 'round.
Here's the deal, we're gonna shoot a commercial!
Hi... Um, this store is neat, and the
owner's a really friendly person, too...
H-He's a really nice guy, too!
And, um, they've been in business a long
time, ever since Mr. Eijiro's grandpa opened it.
It's all right here, from batteries
to refrigerators, they have it all!
And, um... Anyway, come on down to Ohmori
Electronics, where good deals are made every day!
Okay! Cut it!
I'm just not feeling the emotion in this scene. The
vibe's all wrong, but I'm not sure how to tweak it.
Mama, what's that?
Shh, those are crazy people.
I've got it!
Oh, for the love of God, please don't "get" anything else!
A waitress doesn't belong outside an electronics store!
That's what you "got"?!
Gimme that small bag over there, Koizumi. I need it.
Right.
"Give me a camera and I'll put a commercial
for your store in the middle of the movie!"
"Sounds good!"
That's the conversation Haruhi and the owner had.
Cut down to five seconds, though.
C'mere, Mikuru!
What a relief!
Doesn't look like I'm gonna get any lines in this today.
You see, I'm also supposed to be acting in my
class's stage production for the arts festival.
Thing is, I've having a little
trouble remembering my lines.
You don't say...
I'd actually prefer it if the role I'm playing
in the movie didn't have too much dialogue.
I know! What if you took over the lead role for me?
Haruhi's the one to talk to about the casting decisions.
If you want to switch with me,
you should probably talk to her.
Do you honestly think I'm capable
of doing something so frightening?
After all, these are Miss Suzumiya's orders.
Imagine the consequences if I disobeyed
her. That's something I don't wanna think about.
That makes two of us then.
Now you know why I'm just standing
here, biting my lip and running the camera.
We're back!
Whoa!
It's the return of Miss Asahina's greatest
costume ever! The flawless bunny girl!
Last time I saw her in that was six months ago.
So much has happened since then.
Looking back, they're all such fond memories now.
Yeah! Like hell they are!
Okay! Now that's much better!
There's nothing like a hot bunny girl to sell a product!
Get ready! We're gonna take it from the top!
Kyon, fire up the camera.
Take two's up!
Anyway, we wrapped the commercial
for the electronics store.
Our day wasn't over though. If you
recall, there was another sponsor we visited.
We were trudging over there right now.
Okay, Mikuru, you ready?
Do it just like before. There wasn't
anything wrong with your performance.
Everything was wrong with it!
And... action!
Ah... I'm standing here in front
of Keiji Yamatsuchi's Model Shop.
He opened it last year after
quitting his dead-end corporate job!
And... models were his hobby, so
he figured why not open a store?
Unfortunately, his sales have been down for a while...
And... compared to last year, his first-half
earnings for this year are down about 80%...
And so, everyone should come
down here and buy lots of models!
Thank you!
Huh? You want me to hold it?
Y-You should never shoot this
while pointing it at other people.
You should only shoot empty cans with it.
Huh? You want me to shoot?
And... cut it!
Not too shabby for a day of shooting.
But get ready 'cause tomorrow, we start on the movie!
We've already got 15 minutes
worth of commercials in the camera.
How long is this movie supposed to be?!
We'll just shoot as much footage as we
can, and then figure it out when we edit.
Cutting it together on the computer should be a snap!
And who's gonna be doing all this "snapping"?
I have a feeling "editor" was one of
the jobs that was listed under my name.
Tomorrow's Saturday and there's no
school, so I want everyone to show up on time.
We'll meet at Kitaguchi Station at 9 am.
Hang on a sec, Haruhi. Don't you think you should
maybe do something about Miss Asahina's costume?
There's gotta be something else should could wear
that's a little more... appropriate for fighting.
Maybe something like a plug-suit or a stealth suit.
Tsk, tsk, tsk. Then there would be no
surprise when she actually started fighting!
I want the audience to freak out when this
timid little waitress starts kicking butt!
It gets their attention!
That's what a concept's all about!
I wonder if she even understands
the meaning of the word "concept."
Thanks for explaining what a concept's about.
We all know she's from the future,
but why's it so important to the story?
Uh... That is--I-- I mean her character!
Her character doesn't have to
be from the future, does she?
Don't worry.
Those are details we can figure out
when we get to that point in the story.
And, if we can't figure something out, we just ignore it.
As long as it's entertaining, it's gonna be cool!
But for that to work, it's gotta
be entertaining in the first place!
There's no point in making this if
you're the only being entertained!
Are you trying to get a Golden
Raspberry for amateur film-making?!
Are you kidding?
We've only got one goal: To be the #1
event in the arts festival this year.
And after that, we're aimin' for the Golden Globes, too!
Show me the script then. I
wanna see how it's coming along.
Don't worry about that. I've
got all that stuff right up here.
The script and the storyboards are
done, and they're all ready to go!
See?
You don't have to do any thinking!
If that's the way you want it.
You don't have to do any thinking either.
Sit and stare out the window for all I care.
You could be as cute as Miss Asahina if you could
just figure out how to be more pleasant to deal with.
Hm? What?
It's nothing.
Okay, guys, let's get fired up for tomorrow!
The only way to grab the glory
is to have a positive attitude!
When you free yourself from the stuff that holds
you back, your hidden strengths will be revealed!
Then, you'll be able to tap into unimaginable powers!
You sound like a character in a
manga unleashing a counter-attack.
Look! It's a balloon!
The next day,
we were about to find ourselves thrown into the
middle of some totally bizarre situation that...
Wait, I lost my train of thought.
What did Haruhi say again?
Something like, "When you free yourself
from the stuff that's holding you back,
your hidden strengths will be revealed,
and you'll tap into unimaginable powers."
Yeah, but Haruhi, you did it.
You have that kind of power.
You just can't ever find out about it.
You're late again!
It's not even 9:00 yet.
You're the last to show up.
As punishment, you're gonna pay for lunch!
Yeah, whatever.
I have decided to cover everyone's bus fare.
It's a necessary expense.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah! I need to put this on!
You're wearing your uniform on Saturdays now?
She told me yesterday I had to wear it.
It's for my part.
Since I'm supposed to be an ESPer
disguised as an ordinary high school student,
the uniform is essential to the character.
So you're just playing yourself.
There, that should do it.
Okay, guys, the bus stop's over there!
Come on, Kyon! Hurry up!
After half an hour of rattling around on a bus,
and another half hour of walking, we ended up
at a location that could only be described as...
...the place where no one ever goes.
Man, it's hot. It's hot.
Would you like some?
I hope you don't mind, I drank out of it first.
Thanks! I'll totally have some!
You can have a drink later, got it?
That goes for you, too!
You don't have time to be givin' the PAs a
drink when we've got so much work to do today!
As soon as the camera comes out, we shoot!
Get changed!
But I...
No one's gonna see you... Just
go behind a tree or something!
Uh, thank you!
Hey, no peeking!
I wouldn't dare.
Ta-da! It's a colored contact!
It's super important for any self-respecting
heroine to have different colored eyes.
If one eye's different, it
enhances the character's mystique!
Besides, it's symbolic, so there!
It's all about the secret behind her blue eye!
Okay... But it wouldn't really make sense if her
eyes were different colors for no reason, right?
So, what's the secret?
It's still a secret!
Come on, Mikuru. Now's not the
time for you to get cold feet!
Oh, come on, Mikuru!
Don't be so shy, keep running!
Get into the character! Become the heroine!
Let's try it one more time from the top, okay?
So... It looks like this is our opening sequence, folks.
I was expecting to see a script
or at least a treatment by now.
But Haruhi said there wasn't gonna be one.
If I wrote it down and it got leaked,
it would be the worst thing ever!
That's the reason she gave.
I wonder when this turned into a Hong Kong production.
Okay! Hit me one more time!
Just like you did in take three!
Next up, we got the fight scene between Mikuru and Yuki!
Mikuru, empty your clips into Yuki, okay?
What? But I thought you weren't
supposed to shoot anyone with these.
No, it's okay! I doubt that you're
even gonna hit her, so just fire away!
Besides, Yuki can dodge the
pellets if they get too close to her!
Go on.
Shoot me.
See? She's cool with it!
Light her up!
Oh, but don't fire them at the same time. Alternate.
It's the basic technique of two-gun shoot-outs!
Yeah, sure, I guess that'll work.
Can I say something?
This doesn't seem like a movie.
I have no idea what's going on or anything.
Don't worry.
It'll all come together in editing after
a little cutting and pasting, you'll see.
And who's gonna be doing all
this "cutting and pasting," huh?
You could at least put some dialogue in the movie.
It's okay. We'll take out the
sound and stick the dialogue in later.
I wanna put in some cool sound effects and music anyway.
Don't think so hard, just go with the flow.
Yeah, well, since the story's all in your head,
I guess there's nothing for us to think about...
...even if we wanted to.