Okay, I wanna know what you've got up your sleeve.
Nothing. Really, there's nothing.
I know that the organization
doesn't have anything to do with this,
although, I did report it to them.
No, we're just going on a little retreat.
A little retreat that you set up.
I'm just making sure nothing funny's going on.
Miss Suzumiya was interested because it's
a deserted island that's privately owned.
She said it was a closed circle or something.
Okay, what's a closed circle?
Like in mysteries, it's a situation where all
contact with the outside world has been cut off.
Like a cabin in the mountains during a blizzard,
or someone who can't get back to civilization
because a typhoon destroyed the bridge.
Exactly. A person or group of people
get trapped because of their surroundings.
In other words, they get closed in.
And how does that tie in to this retreat we're taking?
We're going to a deserted island.
It's the perfect close-circle
setting when you think about it.
All we need is a storm to whip up around us
and voila! Much better than a cabin in a blizzard.
You might be wondering why I'm chatting with
Koizumi on the deck of a ship in the middle of the ocean.
This all started as I was recovering from getting
my final exams back. In other words: Black Monday.
On that fateful day, the SOS Brigade had a meeting.
Good, everyone's here.
Now, today's meeting is super important.
If any of you happened to show up after me,
I was thinking of making that person
"it" whenever we play "Kick the Can" forever.
Naturally, I had no idea we were
having an important meeting today.
I've decided during the summer break, the
SOS Brigade's going on its very first retreat!
Going on a retreat?
Yep! Retreat.
What good is that gonna do any of us?
And Koizumi's already planned our destination.
Correct. It just so happens that I have a
distant relative who is incredibly wealthy.
He has so much money, that he actually bought his
very own deserted island and built his summer house on it.
In fact, the construction was
finished on it not too long ago.
Koizumi, get ready to hit the roof!
For your distinguished service and dedication to
the brigade, I'm promoting you to the rank of...
...Deputy Chief!
I gladly accept.
No, I'm not jealous...
We'll have a luxurious three nights
and four days on a deserted island!
And I'm sure we're going to find something
very interesting waiting for us there!
In fact, I've already figured out
what my role in this adventure is!
Now then, let's think about detectives for a minute.
The great detectives in mystery novels always seem
to find themselves getting involved in
one incomprehensible situation after another.
Why do you think that is?
Because if they didn't, you wouldn't have a story.
That's right. No story.
Their cases are entirely fiction.
They exist only in the surreal world of the story.
Although, maybe it's better if we don't get too
wrapped up in a metafictional conversation just yet.
I mean, after all, Miss Suzumiya seems pretty
gung-ho about throwing herself into a world like that.
Come to think of it, she created
the SOS Brigade to do just that.
If you're in search of surreal
happenings like the kind in mystery novels,
you need to go someplace that has the
right environment for that kind of thing.
When you think about it,
that's how every single one of thegreat
detectives in fiction got involved in their cases.
Yeah, but there's no way we'd
just stumble across a case that easy.
True, nothing ever happens in
reality like it does in stories.
However, the island we're heading for right now
is a spot that everyone in the world would think
the perfect place for a gruesome murder mystery.
Everyone in the world, huh?
That's a heck of a world you got there, sport.
Look at it this way: Wherever a great detective
goes, a strange case is practically guaranteed to happen.
See, it says if all great detectives have a kind of
supernatural power that attracts all their cases to them.
Are you sane?
I always act with a reasonable amount of sanity.
All that stuff about great detectives, closed
circles and stuff aren't my personal views on the subject.
I was merely pointing out the
way Miss Suzumiya was thinking.
In other words, well, she wants to be one.
A great detective.
This one!
So close!
What's close? We're playing old maid.
Hurry! Next one!
Too bad.
Hey, do you wanna know something?
My big brother Kyon tried to leave me at home.
That's because I didn't intend
to bring you in the first place.
No!
Well, we're all happy you're here now.
Yay!
She won't be any trouble, I promise.
Thanks to Miss Asahina's smile, the kid was off the hook.
How much longer till we get there?
It'll take about six hours by ferry.
Then, an acquaintance will be waiting
to pick us up when we arrive at the port.
From there, we'll board a private cruiser
and it'll be another hour on the water.
A deserted island with a towering mansion
will be waiting for us at the end of our trip.
I've never actually been there, so it'll be
interesting to see what the mansion looks like.
I bet it'll be a really strange building.
Hey, do you know the name of the architect who built it?
Why do you care?
Never really thought to ask about that.
Yay! I'm out first!
Amazing!
Come to think of it, I did hear the architect
they commissioned to design it was somewhat famous.
Perfect. "Somewhat" famous.
For starters, if the mansion is anything like
what Haruhi's expecting, I'm sure it's totally weird.
It'll probably look like something Antoni Gaudi built,
after drinking himself stupid and
staying up for three days straight.
An island. A mansion. It's the ideal
location for the SOS Brigade's summer retreat.
Woo-hoo! I'm the third to get out!
How 'bout the loser has to buy drinks for everyone else?
I'll take a can of 100% fruit juice, please.
And I want some cola.
And I'll be having the royal milk tea.
Hey, you haven't won yet, buddy.
Yep, deserted islands are all about weird happenings.
I hope nothing happens, I hope nothing happens...
I'm not too sure about that. Whether
or not anything weird actually happens...
...I'm hoping that this trip will
at least be a fun one for us all.
Hey, Mikuru, Little Sister, let's go up to the deck!
Maybe we'll see a monster squid or something.
Sure!
Squid, squid!
If a giant squid shows up, Nagato'll have to deal with it.
Oh brother...
You dork, are you sleeping? Come on, wake up!
Are you just gonna sleep through our entire trip?
I just took a picture of you waking up.
And I took a couple of you sleeping.
You were sound asleep, weren't you?
Huh? Really? Why would Miss Asahina
wanna take pictures of me sleeping?
Maybe she wants to put a picture of me
in a cute frame, keep it next to her bed,
and every night, just before
she drifts off to sleep, she...
What's with the goofy face?
You might wanna stop 'cause you look like a moron.
I've temporarily given Mikuru the responsibility
of being the SOS Brigade's photographer!
It's important to maintain a record of the
brigade's activities for future generations.
But I decide what pictures to take.
Why would anybody care what I look like
when I'm sleeping or when I'm waking up?
While you're sleeping, the rest
of us are on an important mission,
and I'm gonna use the pictures of you
loafing as a warning to future generations.
You got it?
For a lowly member to lie around snoring,
while his leader is awake is against
morals, orders, and the rules of the brigade.
We're movin' out, people!
A mysterious island awaits us!
Mysterious island indeed.
It's not Panorama Island or Infant Island, is it?
I hope this island doesn't float away or start to swim.
That'd ruin my day.
It'll be all right.
It's just your typical desert island.
Believe me, you can relax because there
aren't any monsters or mad scientist anywhere.
I promise you. In fact, I'll guarantee it.
Guarantee it all you want, I still don't trust you.
Mr. Arakawa! It's been a while since I last saw you!
Ms. Mori! Thank you for coming to meet us.
I'm sorry for troubling you both.
Now, I'd like to introduce the two of
you to my incomparable group of friends.
The boat we'll be taking is right over here.
It should only take us about a half an
hour or so to reach the master's island.
My apologies in advance for any inconvenience.
You're kidding! I don't mind at all!
The more remote it is, the better!
Another half hour? Take as long as you need!
A deserted island in the middle of
the ocean's exactly what I'm looking for!
Hey, you two should be totally excited about this.
This island's got a mansion and a
suspicious-looking butler and maid!
What's with you guys? I bet you'd maybe
find two islands like this in Japan, tops.
There aren't even two.
Oh, wow, that's so amazing!
I'm really looking forward to this.
I wonder if Miss Asahina is trying
to pick up some maidisms from Ms. Mori.
She's looking at her so intensely.
So does the house on the island
have some kind of cool name?
I'm sorry?
"The House of Black Death,"
"Lyra Manor," "Kouketsu Castle"?
The mansion has to have a name like that, right?
No, it doesn't.
Maybe it's got a dungeon full of funky contraptions
where the architect died unnaturally,
or a room where, if you sleep in
it, you die a horrible death, right?
No, there isn't.
Way to kill the mood.
Hey, does the master of the house wear
a mask 'cause he's horribly disfigured?
Or maybe there's three psychotic sister living there.
Or maybe, everyone's disappeared!
No, not at all. At least, not yet, anyway.
But there's a good chance something weird
like that'll happen at some point, right?
There's always a possibility, yes.
Wow, I think I see it! Is that the mansion?
Yes, that would be it.
It looks so normal...
Someone's waving at us.
Who's that? He looks too young
to be the master of the house.
He's also been invited to stay a few days.
That's mister Yutaka Tamaru, the master's younger brother.
I remember meeting him once before.
Thanks for the heads up. You think you could
let us know about these things ahead of time?
This is the first I've ever heard about any other guests.
Welcome!
Ah, welcome, everyone.
On behalf of my colleagues, I would like
to thank you for inviting us to your home.
It's truly an honor to be able to stay
in such a grand estate as yours, sir.
We appreciate your kindness and generosity.
My, oh my. I have to say you're quite
different from what Itsuki's told me.
Indeed, I think I was expecting
someone who was more direct.
You were?
It's really cool to meet you, Mr. Master!
But let's cut to the chase; has anything
strange ever happened in this house?
What about the island? You hear any story from the locals?
Do they have a spooky name for the island?
Are they afraid to come near it?
That's the kind of stuff I'm in to!
Sounds like you have quite a hobby there.
Although, I've yet to see anything strange happen here.
Construction on the house was
finished the day before yesterday.
And as for the island, I don't
recall anyone saying it was haunted.
After all, it was deserted.
Now, why don't you all come
in and make yourselves at home?
The mansion's western-style, so
feel free to keep your shoes on.
Wow, what a lovely room!
It's Okay.
It's nice we each get to have our
own room instead of having to share.
By the way, the doors do have locks, right?
Of course. And they're not automatic
locks, so you won't get stuck in the hall.
However, I would appreciate
it if you didn't lose your keys.
If you want, you can stay with me in my room.
Only if you behave, you got that?
Okay...
It's suspicious because nothing looks suspicious.
And if it looks suspicious to begin with, well, then what?
It'd be suspicious, of course! Geez...
In other words, to her, everything, including
things that aren't suspicious, are suspicious.
I got it!
Got what?
The culprit!
What culprit? What're you talking about?
Look, nothing's even happened yet.
We just got here, okay?
My gut says it's the owner of this house!
Keiichi did it! And the first victim will be...
...Mikuru!
Would you stop saying stuff like that?
We're their guests!
Can't you just act like a normal high school student?!
I guess you're right. Maybe we should go swimming.
We got the whole ocean to ourselves down there,
so we might as well take advantage of it, right?
Oh, man...
Although, I'm sure Haruhi would never seriously wish for
anyone to die, it's scary to hear her go off like that.
This moment is the best part about this whole trip.
Now this is what having a retreat by the sea's all about.
You know, we all have different ideas of what's fun.
A person should spend their time on
vacation doing the things they like.
That's especially true for Miss Suzumiya.
We need to keep her occupied
so that she doesn't get bored.
And we wouldn't want that to happen, now, would we?
Kyon, Koizumi! Come on, stop
sittin' around and get over here!
Heh, heh! I'm coming, too!
Over here! Over here!
Too many beach balls!
That was so much fun today.
Wow, this is so delicious! Who made all this?
I'm glad you like it. The butler,
Arakawa, is also the head chef around here.
I'd like to personally thank him.
Please call him in when he's done.
Can I have some of that?
Wow, she sure eats a lot.
Would you like something to drink?
What's wrong?
I don't like bell peppers...
If you wanna grow up to be like Miss
Asahina, then you're gonna have to eat them.
It's not often we get to eat this good.
Wow! I can't believe this is free!
I just wish the school cafeteria had a spread like this!
It'd be like heaven!
So after living it up, courtesy
of Mr. Tamaru's hospitality,
we were able to get through the first day
without anything terribly strange happening.
Now, if the story ended there, it would've been perfect.
No such luck, though...
The next morning, as if on cue, a huge storm rolled in.
The master's not what you'd call a morning person,
and he tends to be... difficult when he wakes up.
Please excuse his absence at the table in the mornings,
and I do appreciate your understanding in the matter.
Great, that's just our luck. A typhoon
hits as we're starting our vacation.
The storm seems to be moving fairly quickly.
Things'll be back to normal in a couple days.
You'll see. It'll disappear as quickly as it appeared.
It's strange, though. I don't remember
hearing anything about a typhoon yesterday.
Whoes head did this massive storm come creeping out of?
Okay, what we've got here is a
deserted island in the middle of a storm.
This is a rare opportunity.
We might even experience something weird.
Awesome...
Taking the boats out that day was not an option.
The waves were just too big.
Now, thanks to Haruhi's wish, we found ourselves the
unwilling guests trapped on a spooky deserted island.
A closed circle...? No way...
Since we couldn't go outside, we decided to spend the
day in the game room which was in the mansion's basement.
Here's my Super Ultra Miracle Eccentric Serve!
Hey, whatcha readin'?
Is it good? Huh?
I call... Reach!
Wrong! My hand's wroth 10,000 points.
That is definitely a full hand, Miss Suzumiya.
Good we're not playing for money.
I'm glad to see you're all having a good time here.
If you guys don't mind, can I sit in for a hand?
Please.
What's it mean when you pitch in a piece?
Please excuse me, everybody. I'm afraid
I have some work that needs to get done.
Enjoy yourselves.
Keiichi and Yutaka Tamaru. Mr. Arakawa and Ms. Mori.
They seem normal even though
they're acquaintances of Koizumi's.
We'll meet a couple more characters
before something strange can happen.
I call Reach!
Who is the king?
I am the king!
Okay, number 2! You have to turn around,
look back at us, and say, "I love you!"
Who has number 2?
I love you.
No, not like that, Yuki!
You have to say it with more feeling, all right?!
I love you.
Go on, Kyon. Show her how to do it.
Why do I have to?
It doesn't matter why. It's the king's orders, okay?!
I love...
Psyche!
Selfish king...
That's typical Haruhi for you.
I thought I'd be able to skip the rest of this
chapter of adolescence, with little more than a laugh.
But that's not how the dealer cut the deck.
Now, I don't know who this "dealer" is, or what
kind of deck they were cutting for that matter,
but if I knew who this dealer was,
I'd make sure they'd never shuffle cards
or cut a deck for the rest of the year.
Hey, Haruhi...
What a wimp!
You should expect pillow fights when you're on a retreat!
Where does that girl get her energy?
She was up all night.
Pillow fights, huh?
No wonder Miss Suzumiya was going through all the rooms.
It looks like she went around and
confiscated all the pillows on the second floor.
She's stealing all of the weapons before the battle, huh?
Mr. Arakawa, is there anything wrong?
I sent Mori up to Mr. Yutaka's room a while ago.
When she came back down, she told me that he wasn't there.
He isn't in the house?
His bed hadn't been slept in, and we looked for him in
the usual places, but I'm afraid he's nowhere to be found.
Have you gone in Mr. Keiichi's room and checked with him?
Yes. Well, we tried calling the phone in
the master's bedroom, but there was no answer.
What's that? Did you say that Mr. Yutaka's
missing and Mr. Keiichi isn't answering his phone?
If asked to summarize, yes, that is exactly what I said.
We should probably check Mr. Keiichi's room.
Mr. Arakawa, do you have a key?
The master's chambers are different from the other rooms.
Unfortunately, he's the only one with the keys to it.
It's a precaution. He brings
work-related documents to the island.
We'd better go up to his room and try knocking.
Come on, Kyon. I've got a bad feeling about this.
Yuki, Mikuru, let's go, guys.
Stay here, Little Sister, we'll be right back.
Mr. Keiichi! Mr. Keiichi!
If you're here, answer us!
No good, it's locked.
I don't think we have a choice. We're going to
have to break the door down to get in this room.
We can't waste any more time
talking, he might be in trouble.
All right.
Very good, sir.
Breaking doors like this only
happens in the movies, right?
Impossible... You're joking, right...?