We're movin' on to the next scene!
In this one, Yuki, I want you to use
your magic to zap the heck outta Mikuru!
Your answer should be, "No!
There's absolutely no way I'd let
you hurt Miss Asahina with your powers!"
Look at her...
She's so terrified, she's
turning blue and shaking like crazy!
Oh, well...
I guess we'll have to use CG effects in this scene.
Hey, Kyon, don't forget to make a couple
of beams come out of Yuki's wand, okay?
How am I supposed to know how
to make a visual effect like that?
Okay, Mikuru! I want you to scream,
and then fall down like you're in pain!
We need a scene with pigeons.
What?
There's a shrine nearby. We're going there next.
I wanna shoot Mikuru walking
heroically as pigeons fly all around her.
It would be so awesome if the pigeons were all white.
But I guess it doesn't matter what color they are.
Can't you read Japanese?!
What am I supposed to be shooting?
Kyon! That's the shot! Hurry up, roll the camera!
Don't just sit there, look heroic!
Hey! Whaddya think you're doing?!
Retreat!
Oh, Mikuru...
You don't eat much, do you?
You'll never get any bigger if you don't eat more.
If your boobs are the only things growing,
you'll only appeal to a small
fan-base. You need to get taller.
She'll grow up, all right.
I dunno how many years it'll take, but Miss Asahina
is gonna grow up to have a face and body so fine,
she could be a contender for the Miss Universe pageant.
But I doubt she knows that yet.
Hey, Haruhi. What are you gonna do if that
priest decides to file a complaint with our school?
Koizumi's wearing his uniform today,
and that's pretty much a dead giveaway.
Aw, don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
Besides, jackets like that are common. If
the priest says something, we'll just play dumb.
Once we show this movie to
everyone, our cover's gonna be blown.
I mean, I seriously doubt there are that
many waitresses coming out to the shrine,
just so they can run around with the pigeons.
Anyway, what next? Where are we shooting?
I'm thinkin' we go back to the park and shoot some more.
I just realized that we didn't get
enough footage for the fight scene.
I wanna get Mikuru running for her life
through the forest, with Yuki chasing her!
Then, we could have Mikuru fall off a cliff!
But Koizumi just happens to be walking
by and saves her at the last minute!
What a slap-dash way to come up with a story.
Wait, what if she really does
make Miss Asahina fall off a cliff?
You should fall off instead!
Why don't you wear her costume and be her stunt double?
You're not as busty as Miss Asahina, but still...
Hey, what are you thinking about?
If you think I'm gonna put on her waitress
outfit, you've got another think comin'!
She's a mind reader?
Is anyone else going to be in
the movie, or just the three of us?
Don't ask stupid questions!
You've got a point. Three characters might not be enough.
Thanks for the head's up, Koizumi!
I almost missed that one!
You just got more screen time!
Oh, wow! Thank you!
Serves you right.
You go stirring up a hornets'
nest, you get what you deserve.
Notice I didn't say anything.
Before the boss can be defeated, the good
guys have to beat up a buncha minions first.
Are minions gonna work, though?
Minions are good.
I know, right?
Taniguchi and Kunikida, the perfect supporting characters.
Ultimate minions.
A lot of bad stuff has to happen to Mikuru in this movie.
After all, the theme of the story
depends on how hard she suffers.
She has to overcome horrible odds
before she can have a happy ending.
And the more we can make Mikuru suffer in the
movie, the bigger the pay off is gonna be in the end!
What's with that look she just gave me? Does
she really think I'm gonna let this happen to her?
Later, we returned to the park and the woods for more fun.
We're not gonna use the guns in the next scene.
I was hoping for something cooler and
flashier, but ours don't shoot smoke or flames.
They're just not realistic enough.
Mikuru, you stand here.
Yuki, you're over here.
Don't move from your marks.
I wanna shoot you guys staring each other down, okay?
Grab the reflector board, Koizumi.
And, action!
What the... ?!
Action?
All you did was tell them to stand there.
What kind of action were you expecting out of them anyway?
Oh, come on! You call this a battle scene?!
What do you expect? They're just standing there.
What is your problem?
Just because you're cute doesn't mean
you have the right to slack off, you know!
There are lots of other girls who are
just as cute who'd kill for your spot!
If you don't get with the program,
you're gonna be left in the dust
by someone even younger and cuter!
What's she talking about?
Do something, Mikuru! At least
try shooting a beam out of your eye!
I can't do that!
That's the whole point of your
left eye being a different color!
I didn't just make it blue for no reason!
There's incredible power hidden inside that eye.
That's what the beam's all about!
It's the Mikuru Beam, so start firing it!
I can't!
Get into it! Fire it!
You're hurting...
You idiot!
Hey! Cut it out!
What are you doing?!
I said, cut it out!
Let go!
Stop! Calm down...
What, are you crazy?! People
can't fire beams from their eyes!
Humph. I know that.
All I was trying to do was get her to
act like she could really shoot a beam.
It's hard to believe she's the
hero when she's not that into it.
You never get it when I'm joking around.
That's because your jokes never turn out to be jokes!
What if Miss Asahina actually does shoot a
beam out of her eye? What happens then, huh?!
You... can't, can you?
If I might make a suggestion,
maybe after we shoot the scene,
we could figure out the CG part.
Thank you.
And who's gonna do that?
That's what I was gonna do anyway.
I didn't like that last take. So we're gonna do it again.
When you strike this pose,
you're gonna shout, "Mikuru Beam!"
Uh... Is this right?
No, it's like this.
And you gotta shut your right eye, like this.
Okay, Mikuru, go for it!
Mi-Mikuru Beam!
Ugh, you gotta do it louder than that!
Mikuru Beam!
Don't be shy! Louder!
Uh... Mi-Mi-Mikuru Beam!
Project from the diaphragm!
The stares from the families
watching us are starting to hurt.
Okay, good! Let's do this for real!
Unleash the beam!
Mi-Mi-Mikuru Beam!
Wha?!
What's up, Yuki?
How'd you end up back there? You're off your mark.
Wait! Stop! Cut!
Miss Nagato!
What are you doing, Yuki?! Stop!
Nagato! What are you doing?! Come on, get off her!
Are you all right?
Ugh, what do you guys think you're doing?
If it's not in the script, then knock it off.
Mikuru, what happened to the contact lens?
Huh? It's not there?
At times like this, you ask the person
who looks like they know what's going on.
Nagato, do you know what happened to
the contact Miss Asahina was wearing?
I do not.
Liar.
Maybe it fell out when you two were struggling.
Oh, it's gotta be around here somewhere.
You could at least help us look.
It's so light, it could've been blown away by the wind.
That's what I think.
What happened?
Did it break?
That's weird. It must have been cheap.
Huh. Oh, well. It's the photo
club's equipment, so go figure.
Just tape up the back, Koizumi.
That should fix it for now.
You got it.
If you don't have the contact lens,
then the shots aren't going to match up.
What'll we do now?
I've got an idea!
We could have her eye color
change right after she transforms!
Tr-Transform?
Of course! It's not realistic if
you're always in the same costume!
You need an alter ego!
There's something unreal about people
who want realism in their fiction.
I think that's a wonderful idea!
I'd really like to wear some normal clothes for a change!
That's what we'll do!
When you're in normal mode,
you'll wear the bunny girl outfit!
What?! Wh-Wh-Why?!
Well, because that's the only
other outfit I brought along.
Besides, if you wore your normal clothes,
it wouldn't look as cool on the big screen.
Wait! Hold that thought! I just got another idea!
Mikuru's alter ego is a bunny
girl who's got a job at the mall,
getting customers to come in and shop at the stores.
And she only transforms when she senses danger.
That's when she changes into a battling waitress!
What do you think? Pretty cool, huh?
What about the realism you were talking about before?
Come on, let's go!
Your efforts... are appreciated.
Okay, you wanna explain the deal with all the ad-libbing?
Here.
So you were the one who took it.
A laser.
Hey, Nagato,
your explanations tend to be a bit short.
D'you think you could try maybe talking
for at least, oh I don't know, ten seconds?
It's a narrow, spatially coherent
beam of light invisible to the eye.
Got it. A narrow, spatially coherent beam-y thingy...
Sorry, I'm even more confused now.
A laser?
Yes.
Well, that's unexpected.
May I?
There's nothing unusual about this contact lens.
What are you looking for?
Would you please show me the palm of your right hand?
Sorry, I didn't mean you. I meant Miss Nagato.
It broke through my shield.
You act like it's no big deal! Just looking at it hurts!
It was strong; I had to act fast.
Did the laser beam that damaged your
hand come from Miss Asahina's left eye?
Yes.
"Yes?" That's it?!
It will repair itself.
You gotta be kidding!
Miss Asahina was just shooting
particle beams out of her eye!
It wasn't a particle beam. Cohesive beam.
Laser, mazer, marker-like fop?! Whatever!
They're all the same to us normals.
The thing I'm having trouble with is
that she has the ability to fire heat rays.
It's not a heat ray. Photon laser.
Again, we don't need to get all scientific about it!
Do you think Miss Asahina's always
had the power to do something like this?
No. Currently, Mikuru Asahina is a normal human being.
She is no different from anyone else.
Could there be some sort of tiny mechanism inside?
It is a simple cosmetic accessory.
This is amazing.
If Nagato hadn't stepped up when she did and
blocked the laser beam Miss Asahina shot at us,
it would've gone right through the camera lens.
Then... it would've gone through my eye,
cook some stuff and then come out the back of my head!
Not a pretty picture.
Miss Suzumiya was the one who caused it.
She wanted to have a Mikuru Beam in her movie,
so reality changed and provided one for her.
Very interesting.
Wait a second! Nobody cast a
magic spell on that contact lens!
So even if Haruhi wished for it,
how can a killer beam come out of it?
That's easy. Miss Suzumiya doesn't
need magic spells or strange technology.
All she has to do is believe
something exists, and it will.
Yeah, but she wouldn't really expect
a beam to come shooting out of her eye!
Yes, that's true.
Miss Suzumiya has enough common
sense to know fact from fiction.
However, it's also true that the common
sense of this world doesn't really apply to her.
Today's incident is most likely the
result of a phenomenon of some sort.
I think that...
Uh-oh, she's on her way back now.
We'll have to continue this discussion a little later.
Would you stop complaining?! Geez!
Act like an actress!
To get on the fast track to a Blue Ribbon
award, you can't be so shy about stripping!
Sorry to keep you guys waiting.
Zoom... in!
Confirmation obtained. It's the real Miss Asahina.
What're you doing?!
You're not supposed to be
shooting anything unless I tell you!
Yeah, I know... I didn't press the record
button, I was just... focusing the camera.
Okay, okay, everyone! Listen up now!
Let's make this happen!
I shot footage that was supposed to be
"day in the life of Mikuru Asahina" stuff,
but I'm still not sure what kind
of life she's supposed to have.
And after making Poor Miss
Asahina run this way and that...
I'm not feelin' the whole
mountain-in-the-background thing.
We're gonna go into town!
Oh, geez!
So... Miss Asahina wore her bunny
girl outfit until the sun went down.
In fact, all she ever did that
day was walk around in that costume.
Not that I'm complaining.
Asking for permission to film
was a foreign concept to Haruhi.
In her mind, she was free to shoot
wherever and whatever she wanted.
But then, her notion of what "free" actually
was was similar to the domination of the papacy,
during the age of Pope Innocent III or something.
She doesn't get what "free" means.
Yeah! That's good for today.
That was a long day.
But tomorrow's Sunday, so I get to chill out.
Okay! See ya tomorrow!
You know the drill - Same
place, same time, same everything!
She said, like it's no big deal.
I hope she gives us time to change our clothes.
What was that? We're on a tight schedule.
We can't take it easy for even a second!
You're gonna have plenty of time to
kick back once the arts festival is over.
Consider your calendars booked
until we get this thing finished!
Here.
We're gonna do our best to make this movie awesome!
Actually, since I'm the one directing it, this
movie's awesomeness is practically guaranteed!
Everything else depends on how hard you guys work!
Make sure you're on time tomorrow.
If anyone shows up late, I'm gonna bust some heads!
Don't worry, I'll take care of telling Miss Asahina, okay?
Now what are you talking about?
The laser, of course!
Beams won't shoot out her eye
if she doesn't change the color.
On second thought,
perhaps we should take further precautions against it.
I'm sure she'll cooperate with us.
After all, beams are dangerous things.
Oh, man...
Nagato keeps jumping in and saving my life.
You totally lied! What's the deal, Kyon?!
Where's Miss Asahina, huh?!
The only reason I came is 'cause
you said she was gonna be here!
I don't see her, do you?! I want
my eye candy, bro! Where is she?!
Thirty percent of this picture's success
is riding on you and that bunny tail!
Yeah, all I'm seeing is Suzumiya's
angry face. It's a scam, man!
What the hell?!
Then stare at Nagato. Just die already.
I kinda think that costume
looks pretty cool on Miss Nagato.
Hey, Kyon!
So what's up with Mikuru?
It looks like Miss Tsuruya's been
tricked into being an extra, too.
What are we supposed to be doing today, huh?
I was told to show up if I wasn't doing anything!
Hey, so what's it say on Miss Suzumiya's arm band?
Ooh! What's the video camera for?
Hey, what's up with Yuki's crazy outfit?
Koizumi's looking super hot today! Whoa!
What a spaz.
What did you just say?!
Your stomach hurts?!
Idiot! Seriously, what are you, still
in junior high school or something?!
You've got 30 seconds to get over here!
Miss Asahina appears to be suffering
from a sudden bout of shut-in syndrome.
Anyway, I'm gonna have to go get her.
Where is that bag?
I think I can understand Miss Asahina's apprehension.
It looks like she might actually become a real-life
version of the transforming heroine she plays.
The laser beam shooting out of
her eye is a bit much, though.
Anyway, not to worry.
It's safe to say we won't have to
deal with any strange beams again.
And why is that?
Miss Nagato gave us a hand with it.
What did you guys do to Miss Asahina?
She neutralized the laser beam.
I'm not sure how, though.
Unlike some of the other TFEI terminals
out there, Miss Nagato isn't very talkative.
Okay... What's a TFEI?
Just an acronym my organization assigned to them.
Its meaning isn't anything important, though.
But as far as Miss Nagato's concerned,
I have to admit, she's most unusual.
Compared to the other TFEIs, that is.
Anyway, it was pretty dark that night.
I was on the way home from the store,
and I passed this taxi parked by the curb.
Oh yeah?
So, I'm lookin' at it,
and you know that light that
tells you if it's available or not?
I coulda sworn it said "love."
You don't see that every day.
Before I could take a closer
look at the thing, it drove away.
So I'm standing there, right?
And then, I realized the sign didn't say
"love." Love's what's missing from my life!
Well, you never know. Maybe
the sign really did say "love."
Maybe it was a private taxi.
I never thought we'd have to rely on these two Einsteins.
Unbelievable.
Pretending to be sick! You outta be ashamed of yourself!
You're shooting today, period!
Hiya, Mikuru! Wow, you're
looking super sexy in that dress!
I'm sorry I'm so late!
Oh, that's okay. I don't mind.
Hiya, Miss Suzumiya!
Sorry about yesterday.
I don't know what happened; I just
started firing lasers all over the place.
Oh, don't worry, it didn't hit me or anything.
I was bitten.
Really? By what?
Miss Nagato.
She injected some nanomachines into me.
And now, nothing's gonna come out of my eye anymore.
Thank goodness.
What did she inject you with?
Nanomachines!
Last night, her and Koizumi came over...
Whatcha whisperin' about, huh?!
Ooh, you're so cute, Mikuru!
I wanna keep you as my pet!
Don't stare. You'll wither her cuteness.
I've got our location for today.
There's a big lake by Koizumi's
house that's perfect for the next scene!
Come on, everyone! There's a ton of movie left to shoot.