Surreal and incomprehensible,
cobbled together during an all-night editing session,
the movie, spawned from the director/producer's
whacked out mind, was finished.
The SOS Brigade was now free to spend a
peaceful first day at the school arts festival.
Fortunately for me, Haruhi decided she'd handle
all the negotiating and promoting stuff by herself.
My job was to drop off the DVD with the
Film Club, who was screening the movie for us.
After that, I wandered around the campus with a
cloud-free conscience, enjoying the festival atmosphere...
despite my sleep-deprived state.
However, there was still one important
duty that I had to take care of.
Unlike my class of slackers, whose
activity was some kind of campus survey thing,
Nagato, Koizumi, and Miss Asahina were working
the attractions their classes had organized.
You will buy soft-serve ice cream five
minutes and fifteen seconds from now.
You will drop it in five minutes
and twenty-eight seconds from now.
You will hit your head on a sign
seven minutes and six seconds from now.
And then, you will bump into
your girlfriend and fall over.
The items in her bag will scatter, leading to quarrel...
Take it easy, Nagato. You're telling
their fortunes, not predicting their future.
You and I both know very well that the law of
probability governs all of nature and the world around us.
And yet, having witnessed this phenomenon, I
now find it difficult to believe in such a thing.
Perhaps we should think on this
occurrence in a different way,
that we are in the midst of something supernatural,
a far cry from anything we have ever known.
For example, let us say that we have six...
What is this?
Could you just let us know when we're supposed to laugh?
Come on in and check out our stuff today!
You'll be sorry if you don't!
Yo!
You guys have any luck?
Nope. Not as much as I expected.
Table Tennis Club had ping pong ice cream, though.
Senior year, class 3, had some good udon.
Junior year, class 5, had chocolate-covered
bananas that were more bananas than chocolate.
You're kidding! All you're doing is eating?
Yeah, we're just sampling the food.
Now it's time to get to the real deal, though.
The cosplay cafe!
Man, that bunny girl outfit
from a while back was unbelievable.
I wonder what she's gonna wear today.
Yeah, well, we acted in your movie for free.
And then I was pushed in the water for free.
And all we got to show for it is a
coupon for 30% off some fried noodles?
You ask me, it really wasn't worth it.
You don't like it, don't come! Just go home!
Yeah, right! Not before I sneak a peek
at Miss Asahina in all her cosplay glory.
I wonder if she'll be a waitress in a tight
little miniskirt like she was in the movie.
Her sense of style isn't the same as Haruhi's, buddy.
But a waitress outfit handmade by one of her classmates?
I'm so there!
Thank you.
Hey! It's Kyon and his buddies! Come on over here,
Thanks for coming by. Table for three today?
Oh, wait. What do you think about my outfit?
Doesn't this thing look totally awesome on me, megas?
Aren't I cute, kyon?
Oh, absolutely. You're packing them in!
The fish always take the bait!
I mean, it's just bad fried noodles
made with really cheap ingredients,
but look at all these people standing in line!
We're raking in so much money, I can't stop laughing!
Yeah, and I'm sure it's just coincidence
that all your customers are guys.
Oh, head over there! It's the end of the line!
Go on, get in line!
Here we are. Please pay in advance.
Oh! And another thing, we've only
got fried noodles and tap water.
Now, the noodles are 300 yen each, but
the water's free, so it's all you can drink!
So, what's this get us?
Let's see, so it's just the three of you...
With these things, we're talking 500 yen!
Some deal, huh?
Okay, boys, hang out here for a sec,
and your turn'll be coming up shortly!
Wow, she's a hyper girl.
Is she a member of you and Suzumiya's buncha whackos, too?
Nope.
By the way, don't forget to split the change with us.
He got me.
The, uh, "shortly" that Miss Tsuruya
was talking about was 30 minutes.
So, we stood outside and waited
until she finally let us in.
Okay. Oh! Welcome to our cafe!
She's a dazzling waitress who'd put a
million dollar view of the city lights to shame.
She's got a different glimmer here than back at the club.
Welcome! And thank you so much
for stopping by to see us today!
Thank you for your help on the movie.
I see...
If they let you take pictures, there'd be a riot for sure.
I'd give those costumes the award for best design.
Then you've got those two,
who could be on the cover of a teen fashion magazine.
Put 'em together, and it's a magnificent sight.
Mikuru's in charge of collecting the tickets.
She's also the one clearing the empty plates and
refilling the water. If I let her serve the noodles,
she'd probably trip and spill 'em on somebody!
Wow, she really gets it.
In the end, pressured by the
super fast customer turn-around,
we inhaled the fried noodles in about five minutes,
and left the place feeling slightly less than satisfied.
So, what do you guys wanna do?
I was thinkin' we could check out the movie you guys made.
I kinda wanna see what I look like on the big screen.
Pass! It's probably gonna be lame!
I quite agree! However, hearing
that coming from you really irks me.
Man, those fried noodles weren't enough.
Oh, yeah! Next up's the barbecue
hosted by the Science Club!
You're still hungry?
Before we hit the barbecue, how
'bout we score us some hotties?
Hotties?
That's right, Mr. Kunikida, hotties.
We find a coupla girls dressed casual, kinda like
those two. Then we make with the chit-chat, and it's on.
It's a tactic I developed over years of experience.
What good is your experience
when your success rate is zero?
Thanks, but I'll pass. You guys are on your own.
I think I'll pass, too.
Good luck, and if you find a girl to hang out
with, you can introduce me to one of her friends.
Uh, what? So you guys are just gonna chicken out?!
I'm not a coward.
It's just that if a certain someone saw me hitting
on a girl, it could be a little bit of a problem...
Actually, a big problem.
Look, just try to enjoy the rest of the arts festival.
And do it normally.
Now then, where should I go next?
The wind ensemble's performing in the lecture hall.
Then the Rock Club's hosting a
concert with a bunch of bands.
I guess I'll head over there.
After pulling that all-nighter,
it's the perfect place to rest my sleep-deprived body.
You rock, North High! We are Bandage!
Thank you and good night!
Next up, we have the Rock Club's very own, ENOZ.
Y-You're kidding!
What the hell is she doing?!
♪ Blazing on by ♪
♪ There's nothing more that I can do ♪
♪ I'm sorry that I'll never be with you again ♪
♪ Even though my heavy heart is parched with pain ♪
♪ I know somehow, your sorrow's something I won't see ♪
♪ It's my life ♪
♪ I'm moving on and never going back there ♪
♪ But you just turn away and leave me on the lonely rail ♪
♪ God Knows that I would follow
you if that is what you wanted ♪
♪ Take me into all of your darkest shadows ♪
♪ and you'll see that I'm even
stronger than you could know ♪
♪ God know that I am standing
here and you could disappear ♪
♪ slipping right over the edge of the future ♪
♪ If I had my way, we'd be together forever ♪
♪ Eternally, God bless ♪
♪ The way you're standing there ♪
♪ I feel as though we're almost one again ♪
♪ and yet, we're miles apart in time ♪
♪ Beneath the pale blue moon ♪
♪ I see your eyes are glistening with so much love ♪
♪ It's tearing you apart to be here ♪
♪ You know it ♪
♪ God knows that I would follow
you if that is what you wanted ♪
♪ Take me into all your darkest shadows, ♪
♪ and you'll see that I'm even
stronger than you could know ♪
♪ God knows that I am standing here ♪
♪ and you could disappear ♪
♪ slipping right over the edge of the future ♪
♪ If I had my way, we'd be together forever ♪
♪ Eternally, God bless ♪
Miss Suzumiya's very good.
So is Miss Nagato.
What's up with that outfit you're wearing?
I hurried over here as soon as I heard.
The student council was buzzing with this rumor...
about how Miss Suzumiya was going to be
doing something in the lecture hall today.
This would be that something.
Uh, hi.
Everyone, this is ENOZ.
The name ENOZ comes from using the first
letter of the last name of each of the members:
Enomoto, Nakanishi, Okajima, and Zaizen.
Unfortunately, something happened and Enomoto and
Nakanishi couldn't come up here to perform for you today.
That's Yuki over there.
Well, she and I aren't in the band;
we're just filling in. Sorry!
Let me introduce you to the real members of the band.
On drums, we have Mizuki!
And that's Mai, on bass.
And filling in for Miss Nakanishi on guitar, Yuki!
And I'm filling in for Miss
Enomoto today on guitar and vocals.
I don't know if I can play this thing very well.
In fact, I don't know if I'm doing so hot singing either.
What I'm saying is that I got the sheet music
about an hour ago, so I'm sort of winging it here.
By the way, if there's anyone out
there who wants to hear the real song...
performed with the real vocalist and guitarist,
come see us after the show, okay?
Oh! And if you wanna bring a mini disc,
we'll make a copy of the songs for you for free.
Is that cool?
So that's that.
We're gonna do one more.
I didn't have much time, so I only got two songs down.
This'll be the last one.
Sorry if you were expecting more,
but we're playin' our hearts out up here for you.
You ready?
This is "Lost My Music."
♪ When I look up at the sky ♪
♪ I can't help wonder why ♪
♪ we can't be here together ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ And no matter where you are right now ♪
♪ all I want is to be by your side ♪
♪ Every time I think of you ♪
♪ I wish I were there, too ♪
♪ instead of feeling lonely ♪
♪ Since you took me to the cinema ♪
♪ I can't help it ♪
♪ you're always on my mind ♪
♪ 'Cause, oh boy, our love has gone so far away ♪
♪ and it hurts so much, I almost lost my music ♪
♪ I can't wait to wake up from this endless dream ♪
♪ and be together every day till we say good night ♪
♪ I still, I still, I love you ♪
♪ I'm waiting, waiting forever ♪
♪ and I just can't make it stop ♪
Later, I got the whole story.
I was passing out flyers for our movie, but I ran
out, so I headed back to the club room to get some more.
I was walking by the shoe lockers, and I saw the
band arguing with the Festival Operations Committee.
I guess they weren't going to let them on stage to play.
The lead singer, Miss Enomoto, had to go to the hospital
the night before because she got a case of tonsillitis.
And on the day of the concert, Miss Nakanishi,
the guitarist, tripped and sprained her wrist.
So, neither of them could perform.
Miss Nakanishi's a singer, and
this was her last North High festival.
She wanted to play even if it killed her.
They were going to play new songs,
but in the end, Miss Nakanishi had to
be taken away to get her wrist looked at.
And that's when you decided to
get involved and help the band out?
I can really understand how they felt.
Even if my throat was wrecked and my arm went numb,
I'd be up on that stage playing on willpower alone.
I don't doubt it.
But when I saw Miss Nakanishi,
I figured there wasn't anything they could do.
I mean, if you saw her,
you'd feel bad for the other members of the band, right?
They must've practiced so hard for that show.
So then, this is what I told them:
"Since you guys are in a jam,
you want me to fill in for her?"
I'm kinda surprised that the other
two girls agreed to let you do that.
I told them all I'd do is sing, and
both Miss Okajima and Miss Zaizen said:
"Hey, with you, we just might pull it off!"
After all, I was in the Rock Club for a little
bit, and they probably remember me from back then!
Stories about Haruhi's eccentricity are pretty well-known.
But she's also famous for being a super-utility player.
She can do anything and everything!
I wanted to play all the guitar stuff,
too, but there wasn't enough time to learn it.
I had to go over the sheet music. All
I could do was get the main chords down.
That explains Nagato.
Yeah! I barged in on her fortune-telling
racket, and when I told her what was happening,
she decided to join me! Did you see her play?
I never knew she was dexterous!
She took one look at the music
and then played it perfectly!
I wonder where the heck that girl
learned to play guitar like that.
Probably the moment you brought it up.
Hey, it looks like we have a couple guests.
They wanna see Miss Suzumiya.
Well? Go talk to them.
Okay, but you're coming, too.
Is your throat any better today?
Yeah, that's for asking.
And how's your wrist doing?
It's not 100% yet, so studying
for my exams will be a drag.
I wanted to thank you, Miss Suzumiya.
You won't believe how many we requests we got
for the original songs after the show, it's crazy!
We can't dub our stuff onto mini discs fast enough!
There's so many people who want it!
But really, it's all thanks to you.
Because of what you did for us,
our songs didn't have to go to waste.
And we really appreciate it.
You're something else, Miss Suzumiya!
This festival was gonna be my last memory
with the Rock Club, so I really wanted to play it.
But this was way better than having us back out of it.
Yeah...
Anyway, we want to do something for you in return.
No, it's okay, really.
They were great songs, and I had a blast singing them.
I'd feel bad if you guys went and gave
me something on top of that experience.
Actually, why don't you tell Yuki? I want her to
hear it 'cause I kinda forced her to come along and play.
We already went to her class.
She just nodded once, and then
she pointed us to this classroom.
Hey, we're gonna play a gig somewhere before we
graduate, so if you want, come check us out, okay?
And you can bring... your friend here with you, too.
And after that, Haruhi slipped into one of her moods.
Then when lunchtime came around,
she rushed out of the classroom.
I'm serious! There wasn't a single
decent-looking girl at the arts festival!
You wanna know what I think? I think
this school's built on a bad location.
We'd get a better crowd if it wasn't on this hill.
After lunch, I took a walk.
I figured it would settle my stomach.
And no, there wasn't any other reason.
Hey!
Yeah? What is it?
I didn't have time to practice, so
we had to make them sound simpler.
People wanna listen to the real thing though, don't they?
You're talking about all the people that want mini discs?
Yeah.
That was a heck of a performance
for being on the fly, though.
Don't you think it was good publicity for them?
If I just had one more day to
practice, I could've nailed it.
Part of me's asking, "Was it good
enough? Could it have been better?"
I don't know... How do I explain it?
When I was up on that stage, I felt
like I was really doing something.
This sucks. I mean, why can't
I just forget about it already?
How should I know?
But I do.
It's because you're just not
used to being appreciated by others.
The things you do aren't things
that people usually thank you for.
What is it now?
If you've got something to say,
just say it. Spit it out already!
It's probably something stupid anyway,
but don't just stand there and keep it bottled up!
It's not good for you!
Seriously... It's nothing.
Hey! Do you know how to play any instruments?
I don't...
It doesn't matter 'cause we got a whole year to
practice our butts off for the next arts festival!
Oh, come on...
Our goal is to enter next year's
North High Arts Fest as a real band!
I'll be the lead singer, and Yuki can play guitar!
And we'll have Mikuru shake the tambourine
and be a totally awesome stage decoration!
And of course, we'll have to
make a sequel to our movie, too!
Next year, we'll be super busy.
After all, our goal each year should be to
increase the number of goals we set for ourselves.
Hold on!
Come on, Kyon, let's get moving!
Where are we moving?
We're gonna get some instruments!
First, we'll hit the Rock Club's room.
I know we'll find stuff they're
not using just lying around up there.
Then, we'll ask the ENOZ chicks
to teach us to write music!
Don't sweat it.
I'll write the songs, compose the
music, and I'll do the choreography!
But you don't have to do it right now!
Are you nuts? A year's gonna go by like that!
And what do you mean by choreography?
I thought we were gonna be a band!
We need it! We're gonna create a
new image of what bands should be!
But that's no different from a pop idol!