Okay.
Asking somebody how long they've
believed in Santa Claus is so stupid,
you can't even consider it a
topic suitable for idle conversation.
But if you still wanna know how long I've believe
in some old, fat guy who wears a funky red suit,
I can tell you this:
I've never believed in him... ever.
The Santa that showed up at my
kindergarten Christmas festival?
I knew he was fake.
And I never saw Mommy kissing Santa or anything.
But I have to say that even as a little kid,
I knew better than to believe in some
old man that only worked one day a year.
Now, having said that, it wasn't
until I got older that I realized...
aliens, time travelers, ghosts,
monsters, ESPers, evil syndicates,
and the anime slash manga slash fantasy-flick
heroes that fight said evil syndicates...
... were also fake.
Okay, I guess I always knew those things were bogus,
I just didn't want to admit it.
All I ever wanted was...
... for an alien, time traveler, ghost, monster,
ESPer, evil syndicate or the hero who fought 'em...
to just appear and say, "Hey."
Unfortunately, reality is a hard road indeed.
Yep, you gotta admit, the laws of
physics definitely puts a damper on things.
I even stopped watching those TV
shows about aliens and ghosts and stuff.
Aliens, time travelers, ESPers, 'course they don't exist.
But a little part of me wishes that they did.
I guess I've grown up and realized that I can
think about those things and still accept reality.
But by the time I got out of junior high,
I pretty much outgrew that kinda stuff.
And I guess I got used to the
idea of living in an ordinary world.
And just like that... I was in high school.
And that's when I met her...
I'm Haruhi Suzumiya from East Junior High.
First off, I'm not interested in ordinary people.
But if any of you are aliens, time
travelers, or ESPers, please come see me.
That is all.
Is that supposed to be funny?
There stood before me this amazing, beautiful girl.
O-kay... Next?
I bet everyone thought she was kidding,
but it wasn't a joke.
And it wasn't anything to laugh about.
Haruhi is always dead serious.
And that's how we first met.
Looking back, I wanna believe
that it was just a coincidence.
As long as Haruhi Suzumiya is sitting quietly,
she's just like any other
extremely beautiful high school girl.
And my seat just happens to be in front of her.
I mean, can you blame me for wanting to
exploit this seating arrangement so I could, um...
get to know her better?
Hey, that stuff you were saying when you were
introducing yourself, were you serious about all that?
What about the stuff I was saying?
Well, you know, about aliens and stuff.
Why? Are you an alien or something?
Well, no, but I just...
Well, no, but you just what?
Well, I... Just forget it.
Then why are we even talking right now?
You're wasting my time. Ugh.
Later on,
I found out that quite a few of my new
classmates were from the same junior high as Haruhi.
Look, if you've got the hots for her, take my advice:
Forget it.
After being in the same class as her for three years,
I know her pretty well.
Let's just say she's what you might call beyond eccentric.
Like her introduction?
Yep! In junior high, I can't remember a day
when she wasn't doing something completely wacky.
You ever hear the quad scribbles incident?
No, what's that?
You know that thing that draws
lines on the athletic field?
Agh, what d'ya call that thing again?
Whatever. Well, she used that thing to draw
this big, mysterious symbol on the school quad.
She snuck into the school grounds at night to draw it.
Yeah, I remember reading about that.
I think it was in the local
section of the daily newspaper.
It sorta looked like a botched
version of a Nazca drawing, didn't it?
So, you're telling me she did this all by herself?
No doubt. And she totally admitted doing it.
Oh yeah, and then one morning, I get to class early.
All the desks were shoved out into the hall!
Then there's the time she painted a star on the roof.
And this other time when she plastered these talismans...
What the hell's she doing...?
You know, like the ones you use to reanimate corpses?
I have no idea why.
But all the same, man, she's pretty popular with the guys.
She's not too hard to look at, you know?
And she's freakin' good at sports.
And, on top of that, she gets good grades.
She's a super weirdo.
But if she's standing there quietly, you'd never know.
Somethin' tells me you have more to say about her.
For a while, she was goin' out
with one joker after another.
I think the longest any one guy lasted was about a week.
And the guy that had the shortest relationship with her?
He asked her out, she said okay,
and it ended five minutes later.
I don't have any time to deal with ordinary humans!
Then why the hell'd you say okay?
I mean, that's what I heard, really!
I don't know why, but she never turns a
guy down when he steps up to ask her out.
And so, before you get any
bright ideas, buddy, take my advice:
Forget it.
Forget it? What's to forget when
I haven't even though about it?
If you were me, there's only one girl
in this class to go after. And that's her.
Ryoko Asakura. And I'm telling ya, she's
in the top 3 on the freshman hottie list.
So what, are you telling us that you've
already checked out all the freshman girls?
Heck yeah! I ranked 'em all from A to D，
and I even went so far as to memorize the
full names of all the A-list girls, buddy.
Really? So what ranking did Asakura get?
She gets Double-A plus!
On top of being gorgeous, I
bet her personality is wonderful.
Now, all this was happening when Haruhi
Suzumiya was still acting sorta normal.
For that whole month, even I was feeling pretty good.
However, it should be noted that:
bits and pieces of Haruhi eccentricities
were already starting to make themselves known.
Haruhi Eccentricity number 1:
A different hairstyle everyday.
Monday.
Tuesday.
Wednesday.
Thursday.
Friday.
As the days passed, the number of
places she'd tie off her hair increased.
On Monday, she resets her hair, and then
adds off a tie-off point each day until Friday.
Wonder what her hair looks like on Sunday.
Think I'd like to see that.
Haruhi Eccentricity number 2:
Our PE class is separated into boys and girls.
When changing into uniforms,
girls use the odd numbered classrooms
and boys used the even numbers.
It didn't matter that guys were standing around,
she'd just start changing out of her school uniform.
To Haruhi, guys were pretty
much the same as a bag of potatoes.
Eccentricity number 3:
It was rather irritating that Haruhi joined every team
in every extra-curricular club the school had to offer.
Every single one of the sports clubs
lobbied for her to join their respective teams,
and she'd turned every one of 'em down.
She'd change clubs on a daily basis depending on her mood.
In the end though, she didn't remain
a member of a single one of the clubs.
I mean, what the hell does she wanna do anyway?
And before I knew it, it was the
day after the Golden Week vacation.
What's up?
Hey.
And by the way, Kyon? That's my nickname.
And I really wish people would
stop calling me that already.
Oh. I guess today's Wednesday, isn't it?
And with that thought, something
must've snapped inside me.
I can't think of any reason why...
So, do you change your hairstyle
everyday to ward off alien invaders?
I was talking to Haruhi Suzumiya.
So when did you notice?
Mmm... A while ago.
Oh, I see.
Actually, I have this theory that each day of
the week has its own image with a specific color...
that only goes with that day.
And by colors, I'd say...
It felt almost like we were having a
real conversation for the first time.
And Thursday's green. Friday is gold, and
Saturday is brown. And the color for Sunday is white.
Hey, I kinda understand what she's talking about.
So, if you turn that into numbers,
Monday'd be zero, and Sunday'd be six, right?
Right.
I kinda feel that Monday's more like a one.
I don't think anybody was asking for your opinion.
Oh, is that so?
Have I met you somewhere before? Like,
maybe in the past, or something like that?
Not likely.
Usually, an event is triggered by
something that's considered trivial.
Well, this must've been my trigger.
I was surprised that Haruhi even
replied with a half-decent answer.
I totally thought she'd say something like,
Shut up, loser! Who cares?
I mean, you get the picture...
And so, when Haruhi came to class the
next day with her long hair all chopped off,
I was rather disturbed by it.
I mean, cutting it short like that
the day after I made my comment...
It's a little rash, don't you think?
Not really.
Ever since that day,
talking to Haruhi right before homeroom
started was becoming sort of a ritual.
Is it true you've dumped every guy you've ever dated?
And just what gives you the right
to ask me a question like that?
I don't know about anything you've heard.
Whatever. You wanna believe it? It's probably true.
Well, with all that dating, wasn't there at
least one guy you were even a little serious about?
Absolutely not.
They all took themselves way too seriously,
and not even one of those dorks was an
alien, time traveler, or even an ESPer.
That's how people are normally.
Okay, so what's with most of
them asking me out over the phone?
I mean, shouldn't important stuff like
that be done face-to-face, not phone-to-phone?
Yeah, I mean, if it were me...
I'll just agree with her for now.
Yeah, well, none of that's important anyway!
So what is?
Here's the problem:
So far, the way it looks is that all the
men in this entire universe are pathetic.
I mean, all through junior high, that was
the one thing that irritated me the most.
All right then, so what kind of guy would you
have really have been into? An alien or something?
Yeah! Anything like an alien or
something else along those lines.
Anyway, as long as the person isn't an ordinary human,
I don't care if it's a boy or a girl.
Hang on a sec, what's wrong with being human?
I mean, why do they have to be an alien?
Because that way, life's more interesting.
Hey, Kyon!
You need to tell me what kind of magic spell you're using.
What're you talking about?
I have never seen Suzumiya talk that long before,
and I'm not exaggerating, man!
What the hell'd you say to her?
Huh...
Wonder what I could've said to her.
I think it was all pretty random stuff.
This is a phenomenon.
Kyon's always gone after the strange ones;
The weirder the better.
Little louder, please, so everyone can hear you.
I wanna know how you did it.
No matter how much I've tried to talk to her,
I can't get Haruhi to answer any of my questions.
What do you do to get her to open up?
Do you have any tips for me?
No idea.
Hmm... Still, I think it's a good thing.
I've been sorta worried about her
always being completely alone in our class.
I think it's really great she's
made at least one friend here.
A friend, huh?
Well, just keep doing whatever you're doing,
cause maybe she'll warm up to the rest of us.
I mean, since we're all in the same class,
it'd be really for the best if everyone got a long,
and that's why I'm counting on you.
Easy for you to say.
In fact, from now on, if there's
anything we need to say to her,
we'll just talk to you, and you can tell her for us.
Hey, hang on a sec! What do ya think I am;
Am I supposed to be your spokesperson or something?!
Pretty please?
Kyon, we're buddies, aren't we? We're pals, right?
Everyone's turned into an idiot.
Apparently we're changing seats.
I picked a number out of a cookie tin that gave
me the seat next to the window second from the back.
An awesome seat if I may say so.
Farewell, Haruhi. Forever.
Coincidence?
Hey, I heard you checked out all the clubs at school.
Give me a heads up if you know
about any interesting ones, okay?
Absolutely none.
An instant reply.
Absolutely none!
It seems she likes to use the word "absolutely" a lot.
I thought things would get a little
better when I got into highschool,
but it's the same here as it's been
throughout all these mandatory school years.
Maybe I'm just in the wrong school.
I sorta wonder what her criteria are.
There was a club called the "Mystery Research Club."
Yeah? How was that?
It was hilarious. They told me they've never
had anything they could even remotely call a case.
And the members were a bunch of mystery novel otakus.
Definitely not master detectives.
Well, that figures.
Yeah, well I had high hopes for the
Supernatural Phenomenon Research Club, too,
but that thing was just a bunch of occult freaks.
What do you think of it?
I don't think about it.
Oh man! I'm so bored!
With all these clubs, you'd think they're be
a couple of really strange cool ones out there.
Listen, you can't help it if there aren't any.
Besides, us normal human types, we gotta be happy
with what we're given, you know what I'm saying?
You could look at it this way:
The people who don't like what
they got are the same people
who invent things and make
discoveries and advance civilization.
They made airplanes 'cause they wanted to fly,
and they made cars and trains 'cause
they wanted to go from place to place.
It's as simple as that.
The only reason that we've got
all the things we have now...
is because a certain group of people got together...
and used their talent or imagination or
genius or whatever to make it all possible.
Ordinary people are probably better off living
their ordinary, little lives in an ordinary manner.
Shut up.
Hmm?
Perhaps it was this conversation that sparked the idea...
It happened suddenly.
What's wrong with you?!
I got an idea!
About what?
I can't believe I didn't realize it before!
It's so obvious!
What is?
If it doesn't exist, I should just make it myself!
Make what yourself?
Make a club!
I hear ya, but you gotta calm down, all right?
What's with you?! This is what we're talkin' about!
You should be happy you're about this development.
Well... we're in the middle of class.
You're gonna help.
I feel like I'm being bullied outta my lunch money.
What d'ya need help with?
Starting my new club, that's what!
First, tell me why I'm the one who's gotta help
you set up a club that's your idea in the first place.
And you can let go of the tie, now.
I'll find us a room and some members, and I
want you to personally handle all the paperwork...
She's not listening.
Why don't you tell me what kind of club it's gonna be.
Who cares about that right now?!
We've gotta go make the club first!
You got it? Do all that stuff before school ends today.
I'll find a room for the club by then!
Okie-dokie?
Rules for the creation of a new extra-curricular group...
At least five members, a teacher to supervise,
a name, the name of the person in charge,
the purpose of the organization.
There's nothing for me to do.
It's all in the back of the student handbook.
And I can bet money on this:
Haruhi's little scheme?
Nothing about it's gonna contribute to
making school life more creative or more fun.
Of that I'm positive.
This is going to be our new clubroom!
Hang on, I don't even know where we are right now.
This is the cultural department!
The art club's got the art room,
and the wind ensemble has got the music room, am I right?
Club's that don't need specialized classrooms like
that end up in this wing of the cultural department.
They call it the old building.
This room's for the literary club.
So then it's the literary club's room.
Yeah, I know, I know, but this past spring all the
senior members left, so now the club's got no members.
And if nobody else joins, then that club's gonna be cut.
Oh, and this girl's a new freshman member.
So, the club hasn't been cut then.
It's the same difference.
Besides, she's the only one here.
But what're we gonna do with her?
She told me that she wouldn't mind it.
You sure about that?
When I saw her at lunch, I asked
her if we could use the club room.
She said go ahead. She doesn't really
care as long as she has a place to read.
I guess some folks are just strange like that, you know?
Look who's talking...
Yuki Nagato...
Miss... Nagato, was it?
You understand my colleague here wants to
use this room for some other type of club.
Are you okay with that?
I'm fine.
You are?
O-Okay, but I'm pretty sure we're gonna
end up causing you a lot of trouble though.
No problem.
But someday you might get kicked out of this room.
Go ahead.
Well, there you have it!
From now on, we're gonna meet
here in this room right after school.
And ya better show up, mister, 'cause
if you don't it's the death penalty!
Understood.
I don't wanna die.
We need to find club members.
We're gonna need at least two more people.
What, that means you already have that
literary club girl included in the head count?
Does Haruhi think she comes with
the room like some kind of accessory?
Don't worry, I'll get 'em in no time.
I gotta couple leads on some random people I can bring in.
And so, the next day...
I'll meet ya there!
I guess I had no choice.
I found myself shuffling over to the club room.
So, whatcha readin'?
Is it interesting?
Unique.
So, what part's unique?
All of it.
Huh, you really like books.
A little...
I see...
Can I go home now?
Sorry about that!
I'm a little late today 'cause
it took me forever to catch her.
It was another girl. A really beautiful girl.
Where am I? W-Why did you bring me here?
Who are you people anyway?
Why are you locking the door?!
What do you want from me?!
Just be quiet.
Allow me to introduce Mikuru Asahina.
So much for introductions.
Where did you kidnap her from?
I didn't kidnap anyone, she came here on her own.
Same difference.
I caught this one daydreaming her
brains out in the junior's classroom.
During recess, I make it a point to
walk every inch of the main building.
I remembered seeing her around a
couple of times, and, well, here she is.
So that's why I haven't seen her during recess.
Unbelievable.
Uh, hang on a second, did you say she was a junior?
Well, so what if she is?
Yeah... Um, it's Miss Asahina, wasn't it?
Why pick her of all people then?
What're you, blind? Just look at her!
She's a total little cutie!
Great. Now she sounds like a pervert.
In this situation, moe is an
important concept to keep in mind.
Sorry, what'd you say?
Moe! Moe!
This girl's a prime example of moe.
It's a rule that in stories with strange things going on,
you need to have one moe character.
Someone with glasses or in a maid costume,
or anything fetish-y. It's essential.
And that's just the beginning!
She's tiny, but she's got bigger breasts than me!
I mean, look at these things! They're immense!
This is another important aspect of moe!
Indeed...
Man, these suckers are huge!
It kinda pisses me off.
I mean, she's so cute and her
boobies are ginormous compared to mine.
What're you, an idiot?
But they're totally huge! Really!
You wanna feel 'em for yourself?
I think I'm gonna pass.
So Haruhi, you brought this girl, Miss Asahina,
all the way up here just because she happens
to be cute, tiny, and extremely well-endowed?
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
That's right!
She truly is an idiot.
I figured what the club needs
more than anything is a mascot.
Mikuru, are you a member of
any other school clubs right now?
The calligraphy club...
Oh, you can quit that one.
It'll just get in the way of our club's activities.
Well...
Okay...
I understand...
What did she understand?
I'm going to quit the calligraphy club and join this one.
However, I don't really know what the literary
club does, could you at least tell me that?
We're not the literary club, Mikuru.
We're sorta borrowing this clubroom for now,
and the group you're about to join is
something that Suzumiya is gonna be starting up,
and so far she hasn't figured out a name and has
absolutely no idea what we're gonna be doing here anyway.
Oh, and by the way, the girl siting over there
reading the book is the real literary club member.
Oh...
Okay, I've got it!
I just figured out what we're gonna call ourselves!
Well, spit it out.
May I have your attention please.
The name of the hereto for nameless start up
club has just been decided and its name is...
The SOS Brigade!
The "Spreading Excitement All Over
the World. With Haruhi Suzumiya Brigade".
The SOS Brigade for short.
Yeah... It's okay to laugh now.
Actually, the name should be something like,
"Spreading Excitement All Over the
World With Haruhi Suzumiya Organization",
but we don't have the right to form an organization yet.
And we still don't know what the point of this club is.
Brigade'll have to do then, won't it?
And with that baffling statement,
the name of the club was decided.
Yay...
Just do whatever you want.