The arts festival and its chaotic aftermath were over.
The mountains winds are beginning to whip up, and you
can just hear the footsteps of winter drawing ever closer.
December is almost upon us.
Now this old building, also known as the club
room wing, has been here since the school was built.
And thanks in part to its thin
walls, even though we were inside,
you could still feel the chill right down to your bones.
The SOS Brigade always seems to
get involved with strange things.
Well, actually, I'm the one
getting involved with strange things.
But even so, it's not something weird
has to happen to us on a daily basis.
Besides, if life dropped a crazy bomb on me every
day, my body wouldn't take it. And it'd just crumble.
It would be even worse for my mood.
Still, when Haruhi isn't around, it's really quiet.
It's kinda nice.
Then again, maybe it's a bit too quiet.
Come to think of it, it's been six months since
I first met Haruhi, Miss Asahina, and the others.
We've been through a lot together.
And sure, Haruhi's provoked a lot
of it, but not necessarily all of it.
Well, either way, one thing's for sure.
It was always at times like this when
we were just kicking back and relaxing...
that Haruhi would bust through that door...
Everyone! Listen up!
I've got some really good news!
What? Again?
Whenever Haruhi describes something as being "good,"
news or otherwise, rarely has that ever been the case.
And that's especially true for Miss Asahina and myself.
What is it this time?
I've got everything all set up to get
us a heater for this ice box of a room.
Oh! Your tea!
You know that appliance store that sponsored our movie?
Well, I just got the owner to give us a heater for free!
He called me up and said he had an
extra heater he wanted to get rid of!
It's a model from last year, and it's been
sitting in storage so long, they forgot they had it!
I just can't believe there's an appliance store
owner out there who's both willing and kind enough...
to call Haruhi and offer her anything.
I'm sure she must've forced the deal on him somehow.
Okay, Kyon! I want you to go to the
store and pick it up for us right now.
Right now? Like now-now?
Right. You, now, right now.
Lemme get this straight:
You want me to go down the mountain, the
one I have to climb up and down every morning.
You want me to go down that thing right now to an
appliance store that is two whole train stations away,
pick up a heater, and then lug that thing back here?
That's right! 'Cause if you don't, the guy might
change his mind, and then we're out a free heater!
Don't complain, just hurry up and go!
You're bored anyway, aren't ya?!
Oh, that's great.
Sitting in this room was enough
to label you as being bored, nice.
Aren't you bored? Why don't you do it?
I can't! There's something important
I need to take care of right now.
Koizumi is the deputy chief, and
you're just a rank and file member.
That's the deal in every group I know of.
The grunts always work their butts off.
Naturally, the SOS Brigade totally supports that policy.
Oh, well...
For once, Haruhi's made a reasonable request.
I give up.
Besides, I was just thinking how
this place could use a heater anyway.
If she's going to force Miss
Asahina or Nagato to go, then I'll go.
Hold on!
I heard it's going to be chilly today!
Thank you.
Hurry up and go!
Go on, get going!
Well, now that he's outta the way,
Mikuru, I wanna take a couple of
pictures of you. Do you mind posing?
What are the pictures gonna be for?
It's for the DVD!
I'm gonna make a DVD of "The
Adventures of Mikuru Asahina."
And I still need to shoot a sexy cover for it.
Wha... You mean you're really
going to go through with that?
B-But I thought you said you weren't going to.
I just said that 'cause Kyon was naggin' me about it.
But now that I got rid of him, nothing's gonna stop me.
The first day I had to climb this
hill to get to school, I hated it.
But after walking up and down the thing for
the last six months, I've gotten used to it.
I've gotten used to A., hiking to and
from school, and B., the SOS Brigade.
Funny how that works.
I wonder what Haruhi's doing
right now, since I'm not around.
I just hope she's not bored and treating
Miss Asahina like some kind of toy or something.
Koizumi! Hold the bounce card for me.
Right, got it.
Mikuru, stop spacing out! Pose!
Come on, pose! Pose!
O-Okay...
Come on, smile like you're flirting
with a cute guy. More seductive! Come on!
That's not gonna cut it for the male fans.
Get sultry, girl!
Cool! Costume change!
Put this one on!
Come on, stop stalling!
Mikuru! Come on! Let's go!
No! I can do it myself!
Like I haven't seen it before!
Here, it's faster if I help!
No, not my bra, too!
Well, you're gonna have to take it off anyway.
Mikuru! Wow, those things are
even bigger! You look dynamite, girl!
It's cold!
Hold still!
Oh! That's not good. My tea's gone cold.
Ohh... It's really cold in here!
Could we stop now? This is so embarrassing!
Mikuru... You need to have a
little more confidence in yourself.
You're the best mascot on campus! I wouldn't
have picked you if you didn't have what it takes!
Right, Koizumi?
It's exactly as you say.
Okay, next! Try this!
Again? No!
I can do that myself!
Hurry up!
We have to finish shooting this stuff today!
Come on!
Put this one on next!
But this nurse outfit and that one... Um... I don't
really remember wearing either one of them in the movie.
Are these pictures we're taking
really for the cover of the DVD?
Yeah! Of course they are!
But I just came up with another idea!
With all these photos, we can publish a picture book!
What do you think about that, Koizumi?
I think it's a great idea.
No! Wait!
The DVD needs a bonus features section!
We could put these pictures there!
What do you think about that idea, Koizumi?
I think it's a fantastic idea.
Stick your arm in there!
Looks like we might be in for a
little bit of rain today, doesn't it?
Nice!
It's the funniest thing ever.
You're kidding!
Well, no, not really.
Good! Next outfit!
What?! We've got more outfits?
Just gotta find the zipper...
No! I-I need that!
I want a shot of you flashing some panty at us!
So these have to go! And soon!
This is so fun! Taking all your clothes off!
Well, there's the heater I promised her.
Can you carry it back okay?
Oh, yeah. I think I can manage.
And about the girls, how are those
three cutie pies doin' these days?
Pretty good. The energetic
one's starting to get on my nerves.
The commercial help business any?
Honestly, I haven't seen any difference so far.
Figures.
Putting a commercial in the middle of a
movie showing at a high school arts festival...
isn't what you'd call a stroke of marketing genius.
I'm surprised this guy actually sponsored it.
That reminds me.
When the energetic one called today,
she mentioned something about a sequel.
Is it true? Are you really going to make another movie?
Well, if she says we're making another
movie, we're making another movie.
She asked if I'd want to sponsor it,
and I told her I'd be happy to, so...
So I guess you can consider this heater
my donation to your next cinematic wonder.
So that's how she got it.
Guess I'll head back now.
Thank you very much for the heater.
No worries, take care!
Ameobas are red, a-i-u-e-o!
Little shrimp in floating moss, swimming to and fro!
Persimmon tree, chestnut tree, ka-ki-ku-ke-ko!
A woodpecker pecking at a dead zelkova tree just so!
Pour some vinegar on cow-peas, sa-shi-su-se-so!
I stabbed a fish in a stream that was very, very shallow!
We all stand up when the trumpet blows, ta-chi-tsu-te-to!
When we stood, it flew off with a...
Konk-konk-konk-konk-boom!
A slow crawls very slow, na-ni-nu-ne-no!
Na-ni-nu-ne-no!
Aha! So you are the culprit!
Oh, the red player has picked number 14!
Very well, I wonder how that's
going to affect the game today!
Next question!
Amazing! Just by showing up, she's
changed the atmosphere on the stage!
But she seems completely different, doesn't she?
She's not the same as she was a few minutes ago!
What a terrifying little girl!
Tanmen noodle set!
Fried rice set!
Tempura and cold soba set!
Young man, ace!
Middle aged, ace!
Retirement, ace!
Non-promoted, ace!
Next year, ace!
Unfortunate, ace!
I love it after all, ace!
Why don't you do your best to beat me?!
Bring it on!
What you guys have done is snappy,
crackly, and totally obvious to us!
He looks like a child!
But he's pretty subtle on the inside.
A powerful ally all over town!
Now, now, now, now!
Can you not see this crest that I hold?
Because... I... am the queen of France!
Now that hit a weird spot!
You've still got a way's to go!
Hello! We're the Arctic Sea ice candies!
Bang.
You know, Yuki, you're as sexy as ever!
Where are you lookin', pervert?
I'm callin' the cops.
Starting with a low blow?
I feel like I've been accused of
groping people on a crammed train.
Yeah. By the way, it's winter now.
Right, it's winter.
And speaking of winter...
Baseball's off season.
Cool point there, Yuki. Why, even
the WBC is shaking in their cleats!
I'm really looking forward to
seeing who gets the pink slip.
That's a really dark way of enjoying it.
But okay! Well, you know! It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
I wanna eat a hot pot.
Right!
You can't do without hot pots in winter!
What do you put in your hot pot?
Let's see! Nappa cabbage,
chicken, pork, leeks, natto, tofu!
Well, what about you, Yuki?
Brown bear.
Wow, Yuki! You're a hunter?
Even Masaki would cry and run away!
Yeah, but I think about how the bear feels.
I feel sorry for it and lose my appetite.
Then don't put it into your hot pot to begin with, woman!
I'll play the part of the brown bear.
What? You will?
And you play the pot.
Here it comes, folks!
The worst comedy skit in history! Get ready!
Hey, Kyon!
What are you lurkin' around down here for?
It's obvious, isn't it?
I'm carrying stuff around.
Hah! You sure are a hard worker! You're
running errands for Suzumiya, aren't you?
I guess six months was all it took for my classmates to
fully comprehend the situation I've gotten myself into.
Are you takin' that thing back to school?
Oh, wow! You're a hard worker!
You're telling me.
Well, see ya.
Yeah.
See ya tomorrow!
Damn!
Now it's gonna start raining!
The weather forecast said there
was only a 10% chance of rain today.
Yet another thing that can't be trusted.
I hope it doesn't turn into a downpour.
Looks like it started raining.
I wonder if Kyon's all right.
I've never wanted to be in that room more than I do now.
First thing I'm gonna do is grab myself a
cup of Miss Asahina's tea and warm up my body.
Along with my heart.
Hey, is Mikuru here?
Nagato? Are you the only one here?
I wanna see if she'll trade cleaning
duties with me tomorrow. So I came to ask her.
Do you know where she is?
Oh, she's over there, huh?
Cool, thanks!
To the left!
Right, left, right, left, right, left!
To the right!
Stand in place!
Right, left, right, left, right, left!
Side to side!
Oh, brother.
Hey, Kyon! Were you out running errands again?
Miss Tsuruya!
That's why!
Huh? What do you mean?
Nope, nothing at all!
You hard worker!
Hm... You're soaked to the bone.
Here!
Thank you.
Well, see ya!
Just give my handkerchief to
Mikuru when you return her scarf.
I don't think I'll ever get
what's going on in that girl's head.
She's a nice person though, I'll say that.
Oh, Nagato.
You're the only one here?
So, where's Haruhi and the others?
Yeah! Now that's how you're supposed to land on your butt!
We got it! Moving on!
Ouchie!
I'm in awe of your clumsiness.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Koizumi! Take over for me.
This is how ya do it, like this.
I'm a little worried about where the three
of them are and what they're doing right now.
But schlepping that rotten heater
up that hill really wore me out.
The worst part is, I'm gonna have to go
right back down that hill again when I go home!
How messed up is that?
Come on... Come on, come on.
Man! My hands are so cold.
I'm just so tired...
Oh, Haruhi, it's only you.
Yeah, so? Is that a problem?
No, I don't have a problem with it.
You didn't go and draw something
silly on my face this time, did you?
Of course not! I'm not a little kid, Kyon!
Hey, where's everybody else?
It didn't look like you were gonna wake
up any time soon, so they all went home.
But... you coulda just gone home. Why'd you stay behind?
I couldn't really help it! You were
still sleeping. Whaddya want me to do?
I gotta lock the door before I leave.
Besides, it's still raining out there!
Okay, hand it over.
My cardigan!
Okay... So that one belongs to Haruhi.
But... who does this other sweater belong to?
Whoa, that means that Miss Asahina was changing
clothes right next to me while I was sleeping!
Dammit! Why did I have to fall asleep?!
If I pretended to be asleep, I could've seen...
Well? Everyone left school a while ago.
Come on, let's get outta here.
Okay.
I'm kinda stuck though.
I didn't bring an umbrella with me today.
One'll be enough for the two of us.
Aim that thing over here more.
I'm getting all wet.
But you've got a ton of umbrella over there.
Uh! Oh, nice one. This isn't even yours.
This thing's got "faculty" stenciled on it.
It belongs to the school, so there shouldn't be
anything wrong with a couple of students using it, right?
What? You wanna go home all sopping wet?
Fine! Then I won't let you use it!
Geez... I went to all that
trouble bringing the heater back,
and little miss brigade leader over
there can't even say, "Thank you."
Typical Haruhi.
Hey, wait up!