[ATHENA]
Trance with me...
My dear Yoshichika.
Huh? Why? I don't see
any Foreigners around.
Please kiss me.
[ATHENA]
I want it.
All of your Logic.
[YOSHICHIKA yelps]
Oh, okay. Just a dream.
Is there any chance
that you were dreaming
about the two of us?
[YOSHICHIKA]
How'd you know?
Because to be honest,
I was dreaming about you, too.
That's kinda crazy.
It's quite common, actually.
Now that the two of us
have Tranced together,
we're able to share our Logic.
Yeah, that's right.
So what happened in your dream?
[ATHENA giggles]
That's my little secret.
[JARNO]
This is unexpected.
But I'm honored to
welcome the one-time ace
of the Hong Kong bureau
back to active duty.
Thanks, Sir.
As you already know,
I am ALCA Director
Jarno Utsutsuno.
I'm afraid you're
on a trial period
for the next
couple of days.
Since you're technically
a new member to the chapter,
we have to follow procedure.
Sure. That's fine.
I have high hopes
for you, Yoshichika.
Don't disappoint me.
High hopes?
[OLGA chuckles]
Don't get a big head,
Mr. Hong Kong.
Hey, I didn't see you there.
You're with ALCA?
[OLGA]
Uh-huh, I'm a Logicalist.
My name is Olga Breakchild.
[YOSHICHIKA gasps]
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I came to deliver a message.
My Logic tells me
you will come to great
harm during your trial.
And it's never been wrong.
Not even once.
So what's his problem?
[JARNO laughs]
I wouldn't worry about him.
[VERONICA]
Let's get started.
Today is the beginning
of your trial period.
[CHLOE]
Really?
Why do we have to be here?
[VERONICA] Because it's
a review for everyone.
[CHLOE sighs]
Somebody shoot me.
Now then...
Do you remember everything from
yesterday's lesson, Nanahoshi?
[YUKARI]
Oh, uh, yes, ma'am!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Excuse me, Chief?
I'm pretty sure somebody is
missing from the classroom.
I don't see Olga.
Do not mention that name
in my presence.
Five hundred questions.
Whoever answers
the most incorrectly
will be making dinner for us.
[ALL gasp]
No! I hate these quizzes.
You did study, right?
Let us begin.
First question--
I wouldn't worry.
You'll do just fine.
The world we are currently
on is called Septpia.
But there are many realms
exactly like it
that are inhabited by
powerful gods and dragons.
That said,
which one of these realms has
been attacking Naien lately?
A: Monolium. B: Disfia.
C: Tetra-Heaven.
'Cept for Chloe, correct.
Val, didn't all of you goddesses
come from Tetra-Heaven?
I mean, yeah.
I know! Here!
I've been doing
some research on this.
The archdemons fought
a hundred-year war
against the goddesses
of Tetra-Heaven,
and eventually lost.
After their defeat,
they found and unlocked doorways
which allowed them
to flee to other worlds.
That's why they're trying
to move to Septpia.
[NEMESIS]
More like invade it.
Huh?
Anyway, the goddesses
followed them here,
and ended up joining the ALCA.
Yes. Good.
That was a very
well-phrased summary.
'Cept you missed
the part where you need
a special card to open a gate.
Oh, I didn't realize.
It's true.
That's why we have
to recover the cards
from any Foreigners we fight.
If they lose those, they won't
be able to move between worlds.
And preventing that
is our ultimate goal.
Good to know.
[MANA]
She's eager.
Yes.
Like a happy little worker ant,
trying to make its way
in the world.
That's not a compliment.
Enough with the chit chat.
Let's continue.
[NEMESIS] "What is the name
of the otherworldly area
that forms around
invading Foreigners?" Is it:
A: Paradox Zone.
B: Paradox Area.
Ha! I got this!
Sorry, Blondie. No dice.
Huh?
[NEMESIS] What department
is the ALCA affiliated with?
[NEMESIS]
Everybody's right.
Awesome!
How many ALCA branches
are there throughout the nation?
A: Five. B: 108. Or C: 47.
[VALKYRIE gasps]
[NEMESIS]
Again, everyone but blondie.
You're kidding me!
[NEMESIS]
This one should be easy.
What is the proper terminology
to describe what happens
when a person enters
a Paradox Zone
and gets Trance Jacked
by an invading Foreigner?
Is it:
A: Paradox Sickness.
B: Logical Disease.
C: The Nastybad Trauma.
It's A, right?
[VENUS]
Uh-huh!
Don't help her.
[NEMESIS]
Good job, guys!
Chloe.
I'm counting that one
as a wrong answer.
That's it. Test's over.
Huh? We're done already?
[NEMESIS]
Here are the results.
Blondie's makin' supper.
[VERONICA]
We're done. Class dismissed.
[NEMESIS yawns]
That was exhausting.
[VERONICA]
Tell me about it.
[ATHENA] You got them
all right, Yoshichika!
I'm so proud!
Oh. I'm not the
only one, though.
She scored the same.
[CHLOE]
Ta-da! Dinner's ready!
It's my famous "Diets are
for Chumps" special.
You and your awkward titles.
I never know what I'm
gonna eat till I see it.
It's great. Culinary artwork.
Yeah. It does
look delicious, right?
Sure. But looks
can be deceiving.
Fine, I'll give it a try.
This is great!
Well, duh!
[YOSHICHIKA gagging]
[YOSHICHIKA sighs]
Well the sauce was not good.
You will come to
great harm during your trial.
No way... Couldn't be...
[SHIORI]
I need your help, Brother!
Dad's lost it!
What's wrong with him? Tell me!
It's bad.
He brought a girl home.
Charge!
[WOMAN 2A laughs]
[SHIORI] Do you remember
that lady he had a crush on?
Matador?
[SHIORI] That's the one.
He's lured her home.
Things are getting
pretty uncomfortable.
I don't think mom
would've appreciated it.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Let me talk to Dad.
I'll handle it.
Well...
He's kinda too busy
to talk at the moment.
He's doing a backstroke.
[RENTARO]
I win!
Shiori! What do ya think
of your old man's swimming?
I'm going for the gold!
[WOMAN 2A squeals]
I'm sorry.
I wish I could
be there with you.
[SHIORI]
Oh, don't worry about me.
I shouldn't have called
and bothered you.
I know how busy you must be.
It's cool. Call me
anytime you need to talk.
[SHIORI] Thank you.
Keep working hard over there.
Yup.
[YUKARI]
Yoshichika...
Was that your girlfriend?
No. That was just
my little sister.
I'm still... single.
Oh. So you're available?
What'd you say?
I'm unattached as well,
if you're interested.
Knock it off!
You don't have to throw
yourself at every guy you see.
Why not?
[TAMAKI]
Because!
Goddesses are supposed to bind
with only one person for life.
Isn't that a rule of yours?
[VENUS]
Technically, yes.
Huh. I didn't know that.
[TAMAKI]
Hmph!
What is she mad about?
You blew her off yesterday.
I did what?
Introductions.
[YOSHICHIKA gasps]
I'm the team's leader.
Nice to--
[YOSHICHIKA] Sorry, but could
we pick this up tomorrow?
[TAMAKI gasps]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Forgive me.
I guess I haven't properly
introduced myself
to everyone yet.
No, you haven't.
Oh, me first!
My name's Chloe!
And this pretty redhead
is my Covenanter.
The name's Valkyrie.
It's a real pleasure
to meet you.
I'm Artemis, and this
little one is with me.
My name's Mana.
Oh, and I'm Venus.
Your new best friend.
Um... okay. And she is...?
Her friends call her
Princess Tama.
I never agreed to
that name and you know it.
She's our leader, Tamaki Yurine.
Yurine. Got it.
[TAMAKI] I would like to know
your total Trance time.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Uh...
Because this is mine.
225 hours. Wow.
She became a Logicalist
when she was only 13.
Cool. That's really impressive.
Huh... Let's see what mine is.
2066 hours?!
What? How old are you? Talk!
You're really an old man!
With lots of plastic surgery!
No! I'm only 17!
[TAMAKI gasps]
Wait, but I'm 17 as well.
[ATHENA]
He's talented.
Due to the circumstances
of his past,
his Trance Limit recovery time
is much faster than most.
Right, Yoshichika?
Yeah.
On a good day, all I need is
about five minutes to re-Trance.
[TAMAKI]
For real?
Amazing! You can Trance forever!
Settle down.
Remember you have
your own Covenanter.
Aw, nuts.
Okay. Now change of subject.
Where is that Olga guy?
Why doesn't he eat
with the rest of us?
What?
[AARON]
I heard a rumor about you.
Are you really back with ALCA?
[YOSHICHIKA]
Yep. Can you believe it?
My Logic card
was actually found.
[AARON]
Congratulations, man!
I knew the best of us
would come back someday!
I appreciate it.
But they're treating me
like a newb here.
[GIRL 2A]
I love you, Yoshichika!
Go. Away. Leave.
So what's up?
I know you didn't call
just to chat.
[YOSHICHIKA]
I need something. Info.
On a Logicalist
named Olga Breakchild.
[AARON]
Breakchild?
Never heard of him. Is he new?
No, I don't think so. Just off.
And I'm starting
to feel like the others
are hiding something from me.
[OLGA] Don't worry.
I'm not here to hurt you.
I can help you escape...
my friend.
He's in a perfect position.
Attack!
I'm the one who gives
the orders around here.
Then give them.
[CHLOE]
Stop! You're both wasting time.
Let's get wild on this beast!
[YUKARI] Wasn't this archdemon
already in our custody?
[NEMESIS laughs]
[YUKARI]
What's funny?
You've heard of virtual
reality, haven't you?
[YUKARI]
So it isn't real then?
[NEMESIS]
Keep up, girly girl.
This fake scenario was created
using Foreigner data
and city maps.
It helps prepare
agents for combat.
[YUKARI laughs]
[VERONICA] The control room is
busy collecting tactical data,
which is provided by each
ALCA member's Logigraph.
Okay, Artemis.
Can I pull the trigger on him?
[ARTEMIS]
Yes. Go for it.
[VERONICA]
This gathered intel is crucial.
It determines which tactic
the Logicalists should use
to effectively take out
each Foreigner.
[OLGA]
Relax, I'm just here to watch.
[ARTEMIS] Embrace the
rhythm of your breathing
as you take control
of the target's fate.
[CHLOE]
Excellent! Here we go.
I'm gonna use the
Exercise Supreme.
[VALKYRIE]
Exercise?
How else am I supposed
to wear him down?
[VALKYRIE]
Next time, just say that!
Don't get too close!
I'm not goi--Ah!
[YUKARI gasps]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Don't do anything crazy!
Good job. Help her out.
I'm sorry...
It's just your outfit is a
little on the distracting side,
ya know?
You think I like wearing this?
It's completely impractical.
I hate it!
Venus dresses me up like this
so take it up with her!
[VENUS]
What are you talking about?
My clothes are beautiful!
We'll talk later, okay?
[VENUS]
Fine, fine.
[YUKARI] So Chloe fights
as a center forward,
while Mana is more
like a side back.
And if Tamaki works
as the center back,
then that would leave
Tsurugi as the keeper
of our little team.
Hey, soccer girl, take a break.
[YUKARI] I'm sorry,
but are you talking to me?
[NEMESIS]
No matter how hard you study,
it's pointless
without a Covenanter.
[YUKARI]
Oh. Right.
Well then I'll try harder
to find a Trancing partner.
[NEMESIS]
Uh-huh.
[YUKARI]
Excuse me...
Can I ask you a question, Chief?
Ask away.
Well, I know that
a Trance occurs
when a Logicalist links to a
Covenanter to use their power.
And a Trance Jack
is where a Foreigner
successfully takes control
of an unwilling person's body.
But I'm still not quite sure
what an Over Trance is.
[VERONICA] That's not
something you need to learn.
Why isn't it?
[OLGA]
We're forbidden to use it.
[VERONICA]
Olga...
[OLGA] I'm sure you know
that every living creature
is made up of 1,000 Logic cards.
A Trance occurs
when two partners
combine half of
their Logic cards.
On the other hand,
when every one of their Logic
cards are used to link together,
what's known as an
Over Trance happens.
It's dangerous because
it causes both parties
to contract Paradox Sickness,
destroying their personalities.
How terrible!
[VERONICA]
It can't happen.
The Logigraphs
prevent any Over Trances.
But if for some reason
one is ever needed,
I'm in charge of
giving the go ahead.
[YUKARI]
That's good to know.
[OLGA]
But Mr. Hong Kong pulled it off.
[TAMAKI]
Finish it, Chloe!
Finally!
Valkyrie!
[VALKYRIE]
I'm ready.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Chloe!
[CHLOE]
Huh?
Wait... Asuha has him.
Hear that? Take your shot
whenever you're ready.
[TAMAKI gasps]
Oh, man! No fair.
[MANA]
Copy that.
Moon walk!
[MANA]
Artemis? You ready?
[ARTEMIS]
I am whenever you are, Mana.
[MANA, ARTEMIS]
Start Logic Drive!
[ARTEMIS]
At this moment,
a lovely poem
would soothe my heart
and nourish my spirit.
[MANA]
Here's one.
"Die, beast!"
[ZERA] Tsurugi's Logic influence
dramatically improved
the team's numbers.
Mental and physical levels
were cut in half
from previous trials.
Really?
Hey, good job!
I saw everything.
It really taught me a lot.
[YOSHICHIKA] You're always
lurking around in corners.
Why aren't you training
with the rest of us?
[OLGA] I completed that
simulation ages ago.
I don't need to practice.
So does that mean
you're the ace of this group?
You can call me that
if you want to.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What combat skills do you use?
And I'd love to meet
your Covenanter.
[alarm wailing]
[PIERI] Foreigner presence
detected in Area 08
of the Eastern Naien District.
Paradox Level is at 1.1.
[ALL gasp]
[CHLOE] Seriously?
That's not much of a threat.
[VERONICA] So only one
of you will be needed.
Tsurugi. Head out.
Why me?
[VERONICA]
The girls need to rest.
Yesterday's fight
took a lot out of them.
They are drained both
mentally and physically.
Makes sense.
But I'm still pretty new
around here.
Shouldn't Olga go instead?
Don't question me. Just go.
That's a direct order.
[YOSHICHIKA]
I don't get it.
When is this guy gonna
have to do something?
[NEMESIS]
Technically he is a Logicalist,
but also kinda not one.
Huh? What's that
supposed to mean?
[YOSHICHIKA] He's hiding
something. He must be.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What's the deal with Olga?
[ATHENA] Stop thinking about him
and concentrate on our mission.
[YOSHICHIKA]
You're right.
Let's do this.
[SANDMAN]
Now, children.
Bring me all your candy. Do it!
Unless you want
a face full of sand!
Really, now?
Stop picking on the children.
I'm sorry. Have mercy.
Fine. Just release
your Trance, okay?
[SANDMAN chuckles]
Gotcha!
[SANDMAN]
Huh?
Please cooperate,
little guy. Or else.
[SANDMAN sighs]
You win.
Are you ready to rock?
C'mon. Let's go.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What are you doing here?
Are you gonna answer, or not?
[ATHENA]
Please leave him alone.
It's not what you think.
This is between him and me.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Again...
What are you
planning with Belial?
Just listen!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Huh?
Yes, he's a Logicalist like you,
but he's also not one.
Say what?
It's hard to explain.
He is a Logicalist...
But he hasn't located
his Covenanter yet.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What's his total Trance time?
[ATHENA]
Zero seconds.
The last two days,
Olga has been trying to
convince Belial to join him.
As his Covenanter.
[YOSHICHIKA] So everyone
acts weird around him.
Because... Well...
We feel sorry for him.
It's fine.
One day I'll find the ultimate
Covenanter to Trance with.
But until then,
I'll be more than happy
with what I have.
[OLGA laughing]
[YOSHICHIKA]
What's with this guy?
[YOSHICHIKA] Sorry I'm late.
Please forgive me.
[JARNO] I heard you found out
about Olga's little issue.
I wasn't trying to be nosy.
But he had said earlier that
some kinda "great harm"
was coming to me.
He has a talent
for predicting the future.
So be careful.
He's a fortuneteller?
Yes.
But let's address the
results of your trial.
Well... I'm going
to make some changes.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Hm? Changes?
He's making you the new leader.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Seriously?!
Yes.
[TAMAKI growls]
He's not fit to lead, sir.
He waited to apprehend
the Foreigner.
That was careless!
The Trance Jacked citizens
should have been saved first.
Tsurugi's actions
put human lives at risk.
He shouldn't be giving
orders to anyone.
My apologies, Tamaki.
But as the ALCA director,
I get to make these decisions,
and Yoshichika will
be the new leader.
[TAMAKI]
As you wish, sir.