That was a nice workout.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Missing?
[CHLOE] What are
you guys talking about?
[TAMAKI]
Olga's gone.
[CHLOE gasps]
[TAMAKI] Not only that,
he took his Logigraph.
Without clearance.
[VERONICA]
Status?
[CLAU] We've pinpointed
the location of his Logigraph,
but he's not responding.
He either cut off all
communications with us,
or the Logigraph itself
has been destroyed.
Its coordinates
have changed recently,
so it seems he has it with him.
[CHLOE] No use.
I can't get through to Olga.
[MANA]
I wonder what happened to him.
[QUETZIE laughing]
Stop that!
This is not a laughing
matter, Quetzie.
Maybe not,
but I think I know what
happened to your lost friend.
[CROWD praying]
Our savior is here!
I've been praying for this!
Please, Trance with me, Lucifer!
Me too!
[CROWD begging]
Ready to experience paradise?
[OLGA]
Tell me something.
Honestly. Why did you
have my Logic Card?
[LUCIFER] I took it to help you
realize your full potential.
Simple as that.
Your fellow Logicalists
were treating you unfairly.
It reminded me of
how the other gods
oppressed me during
the Hundred Years War,
causing me to lose
my place in Tetra-Heaven.
[LUCIFER]
In my experience,
shaking off the
whole "evil" label
once it's been attached to your
name is damn near impossible.
And it's difficult to exist
when your own supposed comrades
don't show you the
respect you deserve.
They will never understand
how brilliant of a man
you truly are.
Now why are you here?
Aren't you afraid to be
alone with the devil?
You said...
...that you had
something to show me.
Look at them.
Students. Professionals. Lovers.
They were all
surrounded by people
who took them for granted
and treated them unkindly,
which made them lose sight
of their own Logic.
Sounds familiar,
doesn't it, Olga?
[LUCIFER] I can hear each
and every one of them
crying out to me.
Asking for their
heart's desire, Logic.
And I aim to give it
to all of them.
[OLGA] What kind of Logic
do they ask for?
[YUKARI] Are you sure
this is the place
where Lucifer took Olga?
[QUETZIE] Of course.
My instincts are never wrong.
[YUKARI]
Quetzie, look down there!
[QUETZIE]
Huh?
See? I told ya.
Oh, no.
[VERONICA] You're saying
that Olga is with Lucifer?
We think he may have
been taken prisoner.
[CLAU]
Hey, Chief!
I think I've figured out
who's responsible
for unlocking
the basement cell.
Was it Olga?
No, it wasn't.
The analysis logs
show that it was opened
by the receptionist's terminal.
[ALL gasp]
If memory serves,
the person who
was on duty that day
was the new transfer,
Miki Shinobu.
But why would she do that?
[YOSHICHIKA] I guess this means
Olga wasn't guilty after all.
Okay, so the plan is to
storm into the enemy's camp
and make them
give him back to us!
[VERONICA]
Not yet!
Don't forget
Lucifer's Paradox Level
makes him a
formidable adversary.
We need to know exactly
what he wants with Olga
before we rush into
any rescue mission.
She's right.
An attack would
be too dangerous.
There's got to be
a way to grab Olga
without provoking Lucifer.
[CHLOE]
Let's do this!
Can I have a word with you?
How did you know exactly
where we would find Olga?
[QUETZIE] With my ingenious
instinct, of course.
[VENUS]
Please just tell us the truth.
[VALKYRIE]
If you're hiding anything...
...I will filet you.
Can't you ladies
handle a little joke?
Well, the truth is...
The first thing I did
when I came to Septpia...
...was have a meeting
with Lucifer.
[QUETZIE]
This is great!
I owe you for finding me
a world I can rest in.
Don't thank me yet.
This world has Logicalists
you need to worry about.
[QUETZIE] That's who the
goddesses work with, right?
[laughs]
I think I can handle
a bunch of kids.
You shouldn't
underestimate them.
They may deflate
that ego of yours.
You really think so?
I'll take that bet.
But if do I end up
fighting them and win,
then you have to
hand over your Gate Card.
[laughs]
Of course, if you're
too afraid of losing,
I won't force you.
[humming]
[LUCIFER]
You're on.
[QUETZIE]
That's it.
And thanks to you guys, I ended
up losing that bet after all.
So Lucifer used his Gate Card
to allow you passage into
this world, is that right?
[QUETZIE]
That's what I'm saying.
Then he could have easily
let other archdemons
into Septpia without us knowing.
The question is how many?
What is that sneaky devil up to?
Beats me.
[QUETZIE choking]
[ARTEMIS] Now, what kind
of sides should we make
to compliment Quetzie?
I swear I've already
told you everything I know!
Lucifer just provided a bridge
for me to come to this world
and that's it!
I promise that's all I've got!
[yelling]
I mean it is
possible that Lucifer meant
what he said about living
on our world peacefully.
But why volunteer
to work with ALCA
if that's his intention?
[QUETZIE]
This isn't funny!
I bet Lucifer asked
Shinobu to open the cell door.
[NEMESIS] He does have
a way with the ladies.
If Lucifer was responsible
for the break out,
then there's a high
probability that this was all
an elaborate trap
to get control of Olga.
[LUCIFER]
This Gate Card is the key.
With it I can save the
archdemons from suffering
in Tetra-Heaven's land
of fallen angels.
[OLGA] So then all of this time,
it was you pulling the strings.
[LUCIFER]
I truly never meant any harm.
I was trying to give
the archdemons
a new place to call home.
Nothing more, I swear.
It was not my plan
for them to bring
such destruction
and chaos to this world.
Please forgive me.
[LUCIFER] There's only
one thing I wish for.
A world where gods
and men can co-exist.
Is that really so evil?
I'd like you all
to meet someone.
This man is the former
ace Logicalist of ALCA.
His name's Olga Breakchild.
No, wait--
[LUCIFER]
And now...
He is my Covenanter.
[CROWD cheering]
[WOMAN 10D]
Welcome, Olga Breakchild!
[MAN 10C] It's such an honor
to be in your presence!
We would never be able
to create our paradise
without your charisma.
You're the one these people
have been waiting for.
Me? That's impossible.
Do you really miss the ALCA?
They'll never let me
come back after this.
We welcome you
here with open arms.
[LUCIFER]
If you walk this path with us...
...you'd be the one
leading us into paradise.
--[CROWD cheering]
--[MAN 10D] Leader!
[MAN 10E] We've been
waiting forever for you!
Stay with us!
[cheering continues]
[VALKYRIE]
I kinda feel bad for Olga.
He tried so hard to find
a Covenanter to Trance with.
[NEMESIS] After everything
he's been through,
he must have felt
like Lucifer was sent
from Tetra-Heaven just for him.
[VENUS]
I think he did,
but would he really turn
against the ALCA over it?
[QUETZIE] When a man
is desperate enough,
loyalty and duty become far less
important than his ego.
The need to boost
ones self-esteem
by obtaining the
approval of others.
It's one of the weakest and
most fragile of human Logics.
Even the wind is
in a foul mood today.
It carries many
sorrows with it.
The time is now, Olga.
Show us your
unlimited potential!
I am Olga Breakchild.
And I vow to devote
my Logic to you, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER]
I am Lucifer.
And I vow to devote my Logic
to you and only to you,
Olga Breakchild.
[LOGIGRAPH]
Alliance forged.
Now we Trance.
We're picking up a new
reading in central Naien!
What's the Paradox Level number?
[PIERI]
Sorry, Chief.
It's not a Foreigner.
What do you mean?
It's a Logicalist.
[ALL gasp]
[ATHENA] I don't believe it.
That's Lucifer!
[OLGA] It is time you learned
the truth about the ALCA.
They have been using
the Foreigners they capture
as guinea pigs in a series of
heartless experiments.
What's he doing?
Has Lucifer brainwashed him
or something?
Olga should
consider himself lucky
that he wasn't outright
Trance Jacked.
Chief, please.
Let me go talk to Lucifer.
I wanna try to convince
him to let Olga go.
No one will get hurt that way.
I'd like to go
with him, Chief.
[YOSHICHIKA]
No.
I need to do this by myself.
It'll look like
we're there to fight.
And I really don't
want to provoke him.
I agree.
But I want Athena ready to move
out if your plan turns sour.
[ATHENA]
Understood.
Asuha.
I have a special
assignment for you.
[OLGA] Citizens of Septpia,
hear me, please!
As long as we needlessly
fight other worlds,
casualties will
continue to rise.
We have to stop
this aggression.
Our future is dependent
on the path we choose.
Instead of continuing
this meaningless war,
we must learn to coexist
with our neighbors.
We must come together.
There is no other way!
[alarm blaring]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Everyone get back!
You're not safe here!
Please evacuate the area!
It's about time.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What has he done to you?
Olga!
[YOSHICHIKA] We know you
didn't open the cell.
It was the receptionist.
Miki Shinobu.
[OLGA]
Why should I care?
It means you're
no longer a suspect.
Come back to the base with me.
Before you get hurt.
[OLGA] I'm not going back,
understand?
Tsurugi.
You have no idea
how long I've waited
for the chance to fight you.
[OLGA] If you intend
to stop me, then Trance.
I didn't come here
so I could fight you.
Of course you would
try to make peace.
Too bad.
I'm not giving you
a choice in the matter.
You don't have to do this!
[OLGA]
Evening Star!
[ATHENA]
Yoshichika!
He didn't hit me.
We have to Trance now.
Hold on a sec.
You're not going
to be able to help him
if you get yourself killed.
Come on.
You're right.
Let's Trance.
There you go.
This is about to get fun.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Don't attack!
I just wanna talk to you.
Speak to Evening Star!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Aegis, now!
Olga!
Three Star Strike!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Reflection!
[ATHENA]
Yoshichika!
[OLGA]
Out of the game so soon?
I was hoping you'd
be more of a challenge.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Lucifer has changed you.
There's no denying that.
But he's made you
into a monster.
[OLGA]
He hasn't done anything to me.
I need you to understand...
...that this is me.
[MANA]
Sneak Walk.
So many...
I beg you.
Grant me divine mercy.
[YOUNG MAN 10A]
My prayers have been answered!
[VERONICA]
It's a Logic Card.
[MANA] All the people here are
suffering from Paradox Sickness.
I see. That can
only mean one thing.
[MANA]
You're right.
They're waiting
to be Trance Jacked.
The people discard their
unwanted Logic Cards.
And in exchange, receive
the ones that they desire.
It's known as Voluntary
Logic Card Transplantation.
That's insane!
Unbelievable.
I didn't even know
that was possible.
[VERONICA]
It is.
But I'm not sure what
he's trying to accomplish.
[OLGA]
Coexistence between man and god.
The gods will be allowed to
live peacefully in this world.
In return, the humans
become their ideal selves
through Trance Jacking.
It will be a paradise,
the likes of which have never
been known to either world.
Olga...
My Logic has been
speaking to me often.
It says I should not
protect ALCA or Septpia.
That I should create
a new world where Septpia
and Tetra-Heaven coexist.
A Septa-Heaven!
Lucifer and I will build
this new land together.
And lead the people to paradise.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Nonsense!
Open your eyes!
[OLGA] I don't have time
to argue with you.
Can't you see he's just
using you as his pawn?
[OLGA]
Be quiet!
I alone chose this path,
and I walk it freely.
There's only one way to find out
which of our Logics is correct.
You know it as well as I!
Now it's time to fight!
Attack me!
Or does the thought of
fighting a worthy opponent
frighten you?
I have no choice.
[ATHENA]
Are you sure?
[YOSHICHIKA] He doesn't
understand what I'm trying
to tell him!
So I'll have to teach him
the hard way!
Gravity Star!
Three Star Strike!
[YOSHICHIKA gasps]
Disappointing.
[TAMAKI]
Looks like it's our turn, Venus!
[VENUS] Don't worry, I'll have
you patched up in no time!
[CHLOE] Hope you're ready
for a face-lift, traitor!
You're done here.
Detonate!
Activate Gravity Star!
[NEMESIS]
Not too bad.
[YUKARI]
Everybody...
Watch out!
That mass of darkness
is dangerous!
It acts like a black hole,
devouring anything
that comes close to it.
[OLGA]
Concisely put.
It'll save time if I
take you all at once.
Seven Star Strike!
[VERONICA grunts]
[YOSHICHIKA grunts]
[YUKARI yells]
[YUKARI screams]
[CHLOE screams]
You can't run from me forever!
Seven Star Strike!
Gather around me!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Aegis!
This power...
It must come from Lucifer.
It's both of our
energies combined.
I am the only
person here capable
of mastering Lucifer's
absolute power.
We are a perfect match.
[OLGA]
Fight's over.
Eleven Stars!
[ALL scream]
[CHLOE]
What's his deal?
It feels like he's cheating.
Taking them down
was surprisingly quite easy.
[LUCIFER]
True.
[ZERA] This attack
has caused so much damage.
[alarm blaring]
[PIERI]
Olga's on the move.
Where's he going?
He appears to be heading...
...towards us!
He's here.
And on his way
to the basement cells.
[OLGA]
The time has finally come.
Get ready for the
sweet taste of freedom.
[JARNO] I used to have such
high hopes for you, Olga.
Your intuition in the art of
combat was without parallel.
Please stop what you're doing
and return to ALCA.
[OLGA chuckles]
I promise that you
won't be punished harshly.
But you will have to
leave with me immediately.
You seem to be
misinterpreting this situation.
I will not be returning.
I'm not your soldier anymore,
so stop giving orders.
Or else.
I can't let you turn Septpia
into a new kind of hell.
[OLGA]
I wouldn't dare.
This world will
soon be a heaven.
Now leave.
[JARNO]
I will not.
[OLGA] You'd be a fool to think
ALCA can save this planet.
The savior... is me.
Gods and men will coexist.
Evening Star!
[OLGA]
Five Stars!
You have my deepest gratitude.
Thanks to you,
I was finally awoken.
It was my pleasure.
I need you.
[OLGA] It's time to make
the paradise you prayed for
a reality.
Whoever wishes
to be Trance Jacked,
please come forward.
Pick me! I wanna do it.
Me too!
Please take me to paradise.
Let me Trance!
Foreigners are
popping up everywhere!
Give me a visual.
[gasps]
[CERBERUS growling]
[BELAIL growling]
[OLGA chuckles]