[ZERA]
Clau, are we still unable
to communicate
with Headquarters?
[CLAU]
That's right, sir.
It's the Paradox Zones.
The interference has
crippled their operations.
[PIERI] We're getting
a massive influx of Logic
from the gate to Tetra-Heaven.
[PIERI] The Paradox Zones
are expanding!
[CROWD screaming]
[ALCA RESCUE UNIT 11A]
Come on! Keep moving!
Dad, we gotta hurry!
[RENTARO]
Right! Okay, let's go!
[PIERI] We've evacuated 49%
of the central precinct, sir.
[ZERA]
That's not good enough, Pieri!
Before we know it, all
of Naien will belong to them.
I wonder what that'll be like...
[JARNO]
One hell of a day, huh?
These are the only personnel
who were able to
evacuate Headquarters.
That's awful.
As of this moment,
I'm taking charge
of the command center.
[JARNO] Veronica,
you're needed on the field.
[VERONICA]
Yes, sir.
Nemesis, let's go.
[NEMESIS]
All right.
[JARNO] Have the other
branches responded yet?
They haven't, sir.
We're reading Tetra-Heaven
Foreigners coming from all over.
Looks like every branch
is busy fighting them off.
Then I think we have to assume
we're on our own for now.
Attention Logicalists.
Remember, your first
priority is to ensure
the safety of our civilians.
To that end,
every Foreigner must be
captured and brought in quickly.
Your secondary task
is just as vital.
Close the Gate
over Headquarters.
The rest is in your hands.
Make me proud.
[ALL]
Sir!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Trance!
[VERONICA]
[TAMAKI]
Trance!
[CHLOE]
[MANA]
Trance!
[YUKARI]
[OLGA]
Did you really come alone?
I think I'm being insulted.
[VERONICA] We'll get there
as soon as we can, Tsurugi.
You'll have to
handle him until then.
[ENLIL]
Oh my...
Revenge is going
to taste so sweet.
You'll never learn, will you?
It's obvious what you are.
A masochist.
Just hand over the gate card.
So we can end this
madness peacefully.
We could, but fighting
sounds like much more fun.
Aegis!
[SANDMAN laughing]
There's no way they'll find me!
Now where are you hiding?
[YUKARI]
Gotcha!
[SANDMAN]
Impossible!
[YUKARI]
Here goes.
Hip attack!
[SANDMAN]
Oh, no. This is not good!
[YUKARI, SANDMAN yell]
[YUKARI]
Hold it right there!
[MANA]
Let's do this.
Here we go, Val!
[VALKYRIE]
Acknowledged!
Hey there, small fries!
You get the Quick Kill Blade!
[LOGIGRAPH]
Paradox Level: 8.0.
Okay. Now we gotta deal
with the big daddy.
Little help here, please.
[VENUS]
Don't worry. I'm on it.
[NEMESIS]
Raging fury!
Disgruntled Bombs! In your face!
[OLGA]
Don't fool yourself, Hong Kong.
Taking me on solo
is no cakewalk.
You really think
you're up for it?
I'll never know
unless I try, will I?
Things are about
to get rough, sir.
[JARNO]
Hm?
All the other Foreigners
were brought down
because the Logicalists
worked together.
Only Sandman could
possibly be taken down solo,
but he's going up
against Yukari Nanahoshi.
And she's got
virtually no experience.
Judging by their
elevated Paradox Levels,
these are not
the kind of enemies
one Logicalist can defeat alone.
[ZERA] Please allow our staff
to deal with the fieldwork.
I've stood witness to the
growth of these Logicalists.
Their fearless efforts.
Their passion.
They have earned
my complete confidence.
[PIERI] Unknown Foreigners
are one thing,
but we're familiar
with this group.
We're aware
of their weaknesses.
If we exploit them,
we can take them down.
It isn't numbers that'll
determine the outcome.
It's the strength
of their Logic.
That's correct.
The future of the world is no
longer in our hands.
All we can do now
is trust in the potential
of these extraordinary
young Logicalists.
They will succeed.
I know they will.
[SANDMAN chuckling]
She'll never find me here!
It's perfect!
[YUKARI]
What's new, Pussycat?
[SANDMAN gasps]
[YUKARI yelling]
You wanna play dirty? Fine!
I'm as dirty as you can get.
What are you gonna do?
[QUETZIE]
I'll bet nothing.
I think the little guy
is being uber literal.
[MANA]
Moon Walk!
[MANA] Shooting him at
close range isn't an option.
[ARTEMIS] So we'll be
as the moon in daylight.
[MANA]
Sneak Walk!
[VALKYRIE]
Chloe!
Bondage isn't really my thing!
Sorry, bub!
[VENUS] If we keep
recovering at this rate,
you'll run out of Logic.
[ENLIL laughing]
The weather took a turn
for the worst, didn't it?
[NEMESIS]
He just had to say it.
[ENLIL] A single Logicalist
could never break through
my wind barrier.
Well, if I can't get through...
I'll have to lure you in.
[ENLIL]
No!
It's time for you
to show me the results
of your training.
Activate Logic Drive!
[VERONICA]
Gaia Explosion!
[MANA]
Full blast!
[CHLOE] Time for the
Last Final Finish Sword!
[TAMAKI]
Lover's Dance!
[SANDMAN] Wait...
What does Logic Drive mean?
Uh, should I be scared?
[YUKARI]
Let's see...
[QUETZIE] You should
at least remember that!
[YUKARI]
Stun... Graffiti?
[SANDMAN]
That's super scary!
[QUETZIE]
Sheesh.
[PIERI]
That's Five Foreigners defeated!
[STAFF sighing, cheering]
[JARNO]
It's not over.
The most dangerous one
of all is still out there.
[OLGA]
What a pathetic effort.
Are you even trying?
Come on!
[VERONICA]
The others are out of the way.
However...
[CLAU] Yurine, Chloe,
Asuha, and Nanahoshi
are nearing Trance Limit
and activity threshold!
[VERONICA]
We're all that's left.
It's just you and me.
[YOSHICHIKA]
We'll be enough.
The thing is...
All I'm really doing here
is trying to prevent you
from going to help
the other Foreigners.
[OLGA]
Interesting...
You were playing decoy
and punching bag, then, eh?
So?
Despite your pathetic trickery,
you know that Gate won't close
unless you actually defeat me.
[VERONICA] We don't need
any kind of trickery.
It won't go down
like the last time.
Athena!
[ATHENA]
Right!
[ATHENA, YOSHICHIKA]
Logic Drive!
[YOSHICHIKA[
Rejection!
[ATHENA]
We have to be careful.
Being in this state
consumes a lot of Logic.
We can't sustain it for long.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Yeah.
[OLGA]
Ah...
You have to be careful not
to burn it all up too soon.
I can hear my Logic right now.
The probability that
I will be beaten by you...
...is zero percent.
What's the status?
It isn't good.
[OLGA]
Seven Stars!
Nice.
You've absorbed their power,
have you?
[NEMESIS] Madness!
Intimidation! Hysteric bombs!
Time to get crazy!
Gravity Star!
[OLGA]
Eleven Stars!
Chief, let me handle this one!
Careful!
Trying to change
your shield's attributes
through absorption...
That'll work for a while.
You'll neutralize my attacks
as long as you can keep it up.
So knock yourself out.
You'll just end up
using all your Logic.
No skin off my back.
[ATHENA]
Time is running out.
We're about to reach
the Trance Limit!
[NEMESIS] We're not getting
anywhere this way.
Wait...
I think I've discovered
what his weakness is.
[VERONICA]
Hm?
[YOSHICHIKA]
Olga can only use his spear
to do one thing at a time.
Attack or defend.
Good observation.
Here's the plan.
We'll wait for him to attack,
then we'll make our move.
I can get him
to direct it my way.
Right.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Aegis!
[NEMESIS]
Now!
[OLGA]
You're finished.
Eleven Stars!
[NEMESIS, VERONICA]
Logic Drive!
[VERONICA]
Star Mine... Insanity!
Lucifer...
[LUCIFER]
So much for the side show.
[LUCIFER, OLGA]
Logic Drive!
Activate Twin Evaworld!
[OLGA]
Gravity Star!
That is so not cool.
[OLGA]
Your aim was dead-on.
Too bad I was expecting it.
Now I can attack and defend.
Twin Eleven Stars!
[LOGIGRAPH]
Trance Limit reached.
[YOSHICHIKA]
No!
What do we do?
Chief, look out!
They've been hit!
Are they all right?
[OLGA]
Do you get it now, little guy?
You misread the situation.
This was never a real fight.
Your options aren't
winning or losing.
Your future's far
more bleak than that.
More like despair.
Or destruction.
So which one?
I'll give you some time
to let it sink in.
I know you aren't
used to failure yet.
I can hardly wait to hear
your decision, kids.
[HQ STAFF 11A]
Director...
According to reports,
every branch in the country
has been overtaken
by Foreigners.
[ZERA grunts]
We've gotta close that Gate!
Otherwise, their power
only increases!
So it's come to this.
We're the last line of defense.
Damn...
If only I could've done
something to help her.
[TAMAKI]
It's not your fault.
Our opponent is just too strong.
[CLAU] Tsurugi, please report to
the simulation room immediately.
We heard the news
about what happened.
I'm so sorry, son.
I was worried.
You okay?
I'm fine.
[BOY 11A]
Look! A Logicalist!
That is super cool!
Totally!
Good luck, sir!
[CROWD chattering]
[BOY 11D]
Here. You can borrow this!
Thanks, big guy.
But you know what?
I think you should keep it.
It'll help you to
look after your family.
'Kay.
Hey, Brother...
[YOSHICHIKA]
I don't want you to worry.
I plan to keep my promise.
You better be the
stereotypical lead character
who always wins, understand?
If you lose,
I'll never forgive you!
[YOSHICHIKA]
I'm gonna blow this guy away.
Exactly like a stereotypical
lead character should.
You'll see.
My son. Make me proud.
[RENTARO]
And once you've won,
we'll celebrate
with a guys night out
at a strip club together,
just like you've always wanted.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Actually, Dad,
I think it that was
your idea, not mine.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Athena, we need to talk.
Sure.
[YUKARI]
Chief!
Olga... What happened?
How are Yoshichika and Athena?
[VALKYRIE]
They're safe. Thanks to you two!
Good.
You can't, you need
to get some rest!
I'm sorry. But there's no time.
[PIERI] The Paradox Zones
are expanding
at the same rate as before!
[ZERA]
I guess this is the end.
[door opens]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Director. I have a proposal.
[inaudible]
[ZERA]
Tsurugi! You can't!
[YOSHICHIKA]
There's no other option, sir!
You realize what
that means, don't you?
[ATHENA] Yes, and we're
willing to take the risk.
[CHLOE] But you know they
can't go up against him
without backup!
[TAMAKI] He's already proven
that they're no match for him!
We have a plan.
[ALL gasp]
You don't mean...
But it's too dangerous.
[OLGA]
Have you brought me an answer?
Despair or destruction.
Which will it be?
[YOSHICHIKA]
Neither one, thanks.
[OLGA]
How cliché.
Ever the heroic leading man,
aren't you?
If you think you
can get through this
based on guts and courage alone,
you're in for a rude awakening.
[YOSHICHIKA]
That's not our plan.
Sir. Permission to Over Trance?
He's joking, right?
No, wait!
There has to be another way!
[JARNO] Permission to
Over Trance is granted.
[TAMAKI]
Director! Please, don't!
[JARNO] This is a path they
willingly chose to take.
[LOGIGRAPH] Confirmed.
Executing Over Trance.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Ready?
[ATHENA]
Yes.
[YOSHICHIKA, ATHENA]
Over Trance!
[LUCIFER]
It's all come to this.
Despair or destruction.
If we aren't careful,
we'll be the ones
who are forced
to make that choice.
Let's see what they're
made of, shall we?
Logic Drive!
Twin Evaworld!
Twin Eleven Stars!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Benediction!
I don't know if this
gamble is going to pay off.
[OLGA chuckling]
Don't let that
give you any false hope.
I hear my Logic.
The probability of
my losing to you...
...is zero percent.
[OLGA]
Lucifer.
[LUCIFER]
Yes. Let's do it.
All for the sake of Paradise!
Stop them, now!
Over Trance!
Olga!
[ALL screaming]
[OLGA]
Now, we begin our journey.
To the very edge of our Logic!