[YOSHICHIKA grunts]
[OPERATOR 1A]
The Paradox Zone is expanding!
[YOSHICHIKA gasps]
It blows my mind that people
are still talking about this.
[SHIORI]
Big bro! Breakfast is ready!
I'll be down in a second!
[yawns]
You stayed up again?
And what are you always
watching that's such a secret?
Nothing. Just cat videos.
I have my doubts.
[ATHENA]
One day, the truth was revealed.
[ATHENA] There is a concept that
transcends even the atoms
that form the basis
of all matter.
A force governing emotions,
memories, abilities,
and all other intangible things.
We call it Logic.
It was through the discovery
of otherworldly Logic
that the existence of gods
became common knowledge
in this world.
Though some gods are peaceful,
there are those with ill intent.
A battle for the sake of
all worlds looms near.
[SHIORI] He stayed up
all night again!
Come on, Dad.
You need to do
something about this.
Oh? Do I?
I know what
you've been up to.
[YOSHICHIKA gasps]
You've been looking at dirty
websites and don't you deny it.
No, I wasn't.
Okay. So...?
I, uh...
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Well, he's becoming
a man, after all.
I met the girl
of my dreams long ago.
The mood was right,
and all was going well.
Suddenly, I lost control
and things got super spicy.
I don't understand.
What was spicy?
Knock it off!
I asked her if she
would be my matador!
And then I--
Some of us are
trying eat here, Dad!
Do you mind?
I still don't get it.
Hmph. So how's middle school
treating you, Shiori?
Are you settling in?
[SHIORI gasps]
Yeah, pretty much.
I just wish that you could have
gone to high school too.
Mom would have wanted
the same thing for you,
no doubt about it.
[siren wailing]
[PIERI]
Evacuation alert.
Paradox level 3.7 detected.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Hurry!
Cover your heads and
get under the table!
[RENTARO, SHIORI]
Huh?
[PIERI] An otherworldly
Foreigner has just appeared
in Naien.
Please be careful,
and do whatever you can to avoid
entering the Paradox Zone.
Jeez bro, overreact much?
It's a 3.7.
No, I'm just preparing for
the worst case scen--Ow!
[YOSHICHIKA groans]
[SHIORI]
You okay?
I'm a little more
worried that you're gonna
tear up the place
before that thing does.
[TAMAKI]
Mana!
Do it, Venus.
Don't worry, I'll have
her healed up in no time!
[TAMAKI gasps]
[CERBERUS 1A growls]
[CERBERUS 1A growling]
[CHLOE]
Nice one!
Valkyrie! Let's nail him!
[VALKYRIE]
Roger!
[CHLOE, VALKYRIE]
Logic Drive Go!
[CHLOE]
Final Finish Sword!
Don'tcha think "Final Finish"
is a little redundant?
Who cares?
It still sounds cool!
[CHLOE yells]
[CERBERUS 1A growls]
[CERBERUS 1A growling]
It just kinda seems like
a waste of time to me.
You worry too much.
Just go with it.
[RENTARO]
My compliments to the chef.
[SHIORI]
Bye, Dad!
Well, I guess
I should... pass out.
[SHIORI]
Hey, wait a minute!
Don't tell me you
forgot about today.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Uh...
[YOSHICHIKA] So find whatever
you think Dad would want
for his birthday.
He's easy, right?
[SHIORI] He'd be happier
if we both picked it out.
That's what Momma would
have thought, anyway.
[YOSHICHIKA]
I just want to sleep.
[SHIORI]
That's your own fault.
So what's with the getup?
We don't want anyone
knowing it's me, do we?
I don't think
that'll be a problem.
I mean in this city,
you're pretty much
just another Villager A.
Gee, thanks for the compliment.
[WOMAN 1A]
I've never seen one!
[MAN 1A]
Awesome vintage, man.
[WOMAN B]
Is that an ALCA scout?
I can't really talk right now.
I have club stuff to do.
[ESCORT 1A]
What?
I'm the manager
of the girls' soccer club
over at my school.
We actually have a
tournament coming up soon.
She's got important stuff to do!
So leave her alone
and get outta here!
I'm terribly sorry,
but this is mandatory, madam.
Your responsibility
is quite clear.
World Federated Self-Defense
Act, Article Six. Now...
[CROWD gasping, chattering]
[FRIEND 1C]
Yukari! Come back!
Let's go.
You thinkin' about
the glory days?
Not at all.
Protecting you and Dad
is my mission now.
Right, and we're
grateful for that.
Just make sure to keep
an eye out for tables, 'kay?
[YOSHICHIKA grunts]
Uh... Sorry about that.
Seriously?
See?
[VERONICA]
I'm Veronica.
Chief of this bureau.
Yukari Nanahoshi.
[YUKARI]
Yes?
[VERONICA] You are something
of a rarity in the world.
Someone who's realized
their powers.
Hey! Are we getting a new girl?
Yeah. Guess so.
[CHLOE] Aw, that braid
is the cutest thing ever.
Don't you wanna
watch with us, Mana-Mana?
[MANA]
Pass.
Why did I even ask?
No doubt your abilities
will begin to blossom,
though it's hard to tell when.
We've yet to determine
the exact cause of this.
But without exception,
it happens during
one's adolescence,
and degrades after
reaching adulthood.
So then, does--
Does that mean that you've
already lost your powers, Chief?
[VERONICA] Is that your way
of saying I look old, Cadet?
[YUKARI]
Oh no, not old, just mature!
[NEMESIS giggling]
[laughing]
Nemesis!
So uh... Who is she?
She is my Covenanter.
Wait, what does that mean?
[VERONICA] In any case, those
who have become conscious
of their abilities must protect
this city and join our forces
as a member of the special
police agency, ALCA.
Me too, then?
[siren wailing]
[PIERI] Detecting a Foreigner
in the Central Area.
Paradox Level registers as 7.2.
[NEMESIS giggles]
Sounds like you have
your work cut out for you.
[YOSHICHIKA] Aren't these...
a little tacky?
[SHIORI]
Huh?
I dunno, they look cute to me.
[siren wailing]
[PIERI]
Evacuation alert.
Paradox Level 7.2 detected.
[YOSHICHIKA]
7.2?
[PIERI] Please take shelter
so as not to be caught
in the Paradox Zone.
[YOSHICHIKA, SHIORI gasp]
[CROWD yelling]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Get away from the Zone!
If it touches you, you're dead!
[CROWD screaming]
[YOSHICHIKA]
You okay?
[SHIORI]
Hurry up!
Get outta here, Shiori.
[SHIORI]
Not without you!
Move it!
You'll be fine. You're strong.
Now, go to that girl,
understand?
[YOSHICHIKA] Shiori, take him
to the evacuation area!
I'll deal with this thing
until you can get away!
Come with us, Yoshichika,
you're not a hero anymore,
don't be stupid!
Just get going!
Come on, kid.
Over here, you stupid bull!
[ATHENA]
This way!
I'm so sorry!
Let's go!
Before we get swallowed
by the Paradox Zone.
We have to be quick!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Hey!
[CHLOE]
Here, Toro!
Ow!
Are Foreigners over seven
supposed to be this tough?
[TAMAKI]
Its Logic is still at full.
[MANA]
We could be killed.
Hey, that's part of the job.
It's running away!
What'd you do?
[CHLOE]
Ugh! We lost it!
I'm sorry.
The target got away.
[VERONICA] Return once you've
closed the gate, then.
Understood, Chief.
[LOGIGRAPH]
Gate card downloading.
Standing by.
Closing the gate now.
[PIERI] The Central Area
evacuation alert
has been lifted.
However, the Foreigner
has not yet been secured.
Please continue to use caution.
[MOTHER 1A]
Thank you so much.
--[RENTARO] Shiori!
--[SHIORI] Bye, take care!
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
But I can't find
Yoshichika anywhere.
[YOSHICHIKA]
So I'm gonna go out on a limb
and guess that you're
not from this world.
[ATHENA]
I'm impressed.
You certainly do know your
stuff, Yoshichika Tsurugi.
[YOSHICHIKA]
How do you know who I am?
My name is Athena.
I came all this way to see you.
Logicalists.
People with a special ability
that is found
only in this world.
They are able to comprehend
otherworldly Logic
and to invoke it at will.
I know you're one of them,
and I want to protect this world
from the gods of evil.
Let me be your Covenanter.
What are you talking about?
I'm a regular--
As long as you have this,
you can fight.
No, that couldn't be...
[ATHENA]
It is.
Your lost Logic Card.
Please, take it.
Hold on...
Why do you have my card?
I was looking for it.
Now we can fight side by side.
[RENTARO]
Yoshichika!
[SHIORI]
There you are!
I was so worried about you.
It's part of who you are.
Please, take it, I beg you.
Who is this girl?
She a friend of yours?
And what is that card?
This card contains a part
of your son's character
that he'd lost.
His Logicalist power
rests inside.
She can keep it,
don't listen to her!
So what are you gonna do?
Come on, we should go home now.
Just Let the Logicalists
handle the Foreigner.
'Kay?
I can't do that.
ALCA needs all the
help they can get,
because if that Foreigner
decides to attack again,
there will definitely
be civilian casualties.
Stop talking as if
you're a lead character!
You're "Villager A" now,
remember?
Start acting like it!
I know that's what
Momma would say, too!
I'm not so sure.
[SHIORI]
I've had enough.
I don't want you
to suffer anymore.
You said it yourself, Brother,
the only mission you have now
is protecting our family!
I did.
And I said that because
that's the only thing
I could do before, Shiori.
But now...
Since I have this back...
I can do a whole lot more.
[siren wailing]
[PIERI]
Evacuation alert.
Paradox level 7.2 detected.
Please take shelter at once
so as not to be caught
in the Paradox Zone.
I'm ready.
Big brother, you can't!
[YOSHICHIKA]
I'm doing this!
If I save even one
innocent life, it's worth it.
I'll make sure that he's safe.
Please try
to understand, Shiori.
Not everybody
gets a second chance.
He just wants to make
the most of his.
There's one thing
I'd like to know.
Why would you choose me
as your partner?
Hong Kong, two years ago.
[HONG KONG CHIEF]
There's nothing you can do.
Get out of there!
[YOSHICHIKA] Chief,
permission to Over Trance!
[HONG KONG CHIEF]
Are you out of your mind?
You know what could happen!
Of course I do, but it
also goes with my Logic!
[ATHENA]
You never forsake any life.
No matter what.
Even if the life belongs
to an otherworldly foe.
I am convinced
that if you had to,
you would even be
willing to sacrifice
your own personality
if it would save another.
That's why I found your card.
Please, let me work with you.
Okay.
I want you to
Covenant with me, Athena.
Right.
[ATHENA]
This is your Logigraph.
[LOGIGRAPH]
Judge your Logic.
Yoshichika Tsurugi, I, Athena,
vow to devote my Logic to you
as your faithful Covenanter.
[YOSHICHIKA]
My faithful Athena.
I, Yoshichika Tsurugi,
make a solemn vow
to devote my Logic to you.
Trance with me.
Yes.
Here we go!
This ugly cow isn't
making it easy for us.
[TAMAKI]
Oh no!
We're almost at
our Trance Limit!
What? So soon?
It was obviously trying
to run down the clock all along.
[CHLOE gasps]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Aegis!
Are you all right?
Where'd you come from?
[YOSHICHIKA] It's using up
a great deal of Logic
on this heavy attack.
It's gonna have to switch
to another medium soon.
[YOSHICHIKA]
We'll only have a moment.
Don't miss this opportunity!
Who died and left you
in charge, huh?
[ATHENA, YOSHICHIKA]
Logic Drive!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Reflection!
Go now!
[CHLOE]
I'm all over it!
Cover me, Mana!
Are you ready, Valkyrie?
[VALKYRIE]
Copy!
[CHLOE, VALKYRIE]
Logic Drive go!
[CHLOE]
Last Final Finish Sword!
[LOGIGRAPH]
Trance Limit reached.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Trance release.
Athena?
Is that gentleman
your Covenanter, Athena?
[ATHENA]
Yes, he is.
[VALKYRIE]
You went with a boy?
Didn't see that one coming.
[VENUS]
Lovely!
I want one too!
[giggles]
Who is this guy?
An ALCA recruit?
Beats me.
He sure knew his way
around a fight, though.
[SHIORI] My brother's done
enough for you creeps.
Leave him alone!
You aren't welcome here, so go!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Shiori... wait!
I promise...
I'm not gonna do anything crazy.
Yeah, you'd better not.
I'm not gonna do anything
to worry you, either.
It's too late for that.
But this is
something I gotta do.
To protect you
and everybody else.
Make sure you do.
You better be the
stereotypical lead character
who always wins, understand?
If you lose,
I'll never forgive you!
Shiori...
I want our viewers to be bored
from how unkillable you are!
Me too.
Go get 'em, kiddo,
and visit when you can.
I will, Dad.
[JARNO]
Well...
I certainly admire your
single-minded devotion.
Though, I must admit that I
never would have guessed
you'd Covenant with him.
I'm really glad that I did.
No regrets.
[JARNO]
Indeed.
My image of him has
grown as well. Greatly.
[CHLOE] He was in Hong Kong
two years ago?
That's right.
He's also the only person
among the currently
active Logicalists
who has successfully performed
the prohibited Over Trance.
Is there like an
employee handbook?
Speak of the devil...
Let's welcome the newest member
of the ALCA, Yoshichika Tsurugi.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm looking forward
to working with you.
[VERONICA]
I'm sure you are.
This is Tamaki.
I'm the team's leader.
Nice to--
[YOSHICHIKA]
Sorry.
But could we pick
this up tomorrow?
I haven't slept since yesterday.
[yawns]
My Logic is begging me
to hit the sack.
Are you really
blowing off introductions?
Your room is this way.
Great. Thank you.
Unbelievable.
--[ATHENA chuckles]
--[door closes]
I think that one's occupied!
Didn't anyone tell you?
Living with your Covenanter
is mandatory around here.
It's proven quite effective
at improving our bonds.
I'm looking forward to it.
It should be fun!
[OLGA] You chose the wrong path,
didn't you, Yoshichika Tsurugi.
I can hear my
Logic loud and clear.
It tells me the odds
you'll meet the same fate
you did in Hong Kong are...
One hundred percent.