[SOCCER PLAYERS yelling]
I wanna see some
hustle out there!
The left side's open!
[CHLOE]
Pass it, Yukari!
Hurry it up!
But I'm just
the team manager.
You're the player.
The heck are you waiting for?
Would you please
stop yelling at me?
I shouldn't even be on the
field. Someone call time out!
Just kick the ball, will you?
Okay, fine!
Coming your way!
Take that!
[YUKARI groans]
Please no cleats.
Good morning, Yukari.
Good morning, Chloe.
Sorry about before.
That was an awful pass.
I'm embarrassed.
Uh... What pass?
Oh it's nothing, never mind.
Hope you enjoy your morning run!
[CHLOE]
Bye.
Chloe works so hard.
All of them do.
I really need to step up
my game. And quick.
[YUKARI]
First thing...
...is to prove I'm ready
to join their team.
[YUKARI sighs]
You run every day?
I really admire that.
Thanks, Yukari.
Uh... What is this stuff?
Cola! Not too hydrating,
but it's good!
Seems kinda weird to
drink it warm like this.
Hey. It's actually pretty tasty.
A hot drink
for a chilly morning.
[CHLOE] Mmm!
That's a wonderful idea!
I try.
[giggles]
Oh, yeah!
[KITAOKA]
Cold...
[beeping noise]
Hi. Can I come in?
Aren't you kinda
chilly in here?
Oh, I'm fine.
But winter's always been
my favorite season, anyway.
Now where is Gordo hiding?
This weather irritates
his lower back,
so he decided
to stay home today.
I guess that means
you're in charge now.
Yep!
Man, this looks good. For me?
Yeah. I made extra
just for you.
You need to stay
sharp for us, Kitaoka.
Think this'll help.
I can't believe that
you remembered my name.
[crying]
That's so sweet.
[KITAOKA]
You made this?
--[QUETZIE] I'm cold.
--[KITAOKA] Hits the spot.
This is torture, and you aren't
even asking me questions!
Pay attention to me!
I'm gonna freeze to death
in here, you dumb human!
--And it'll be your fault!
--[KITAOKA] The power's out.
There's nothing I can do.
[QUETZIE]
Liar!
There's steam coming from your--
So that's the
feared Quetzalcoatl.
He is always complaining.
And he caused this
to begin with.
Ya know...
If I were a Logicalist,
power would still be on.
I'd have knocked him flat
with one punch to the kisser!
Yeah...
Sorry you have to
deal with all of this.
I'm not trying to say
you should've stopped him.
I'm just really upset that
Hoshimi Akatsuki's concert
was cancelled because of it.
She's an angel.
Sent from the heavens
to bless us with her voice.
[YUKARI laughs nervously]
What is that you're carrying?
Exotic chocolates that came
with Hoshimi collector cards.
Apparently the guard Kitaoka
is a huge fan of hers.
I'm gonna put on
a kettle of tea, okay?
[YUKARI] I've got mango
juice for Venus...
Some coffee for Valkyrie...
And last but not least...
I'd like warm droplets
of amber-colored moonlight
in a ceramic vessel.
Tea for Artemis.
Straight from Darjeeling
to your cup.
[VENUS]
Mmm! Heavenly.
The perfect combination
of sweet and tangy.
[VALKYRIE] The chocolate
compliments the coffee well.
You seem to be in an
especially good mood today.
I am.
It's because of Mana, isn't it?
Correct.
That one is a wounded spirit.
But she's tough.
And protects herself
at all costs.
She can be as sharp and
cold as a sword made of ice.
And yet...
She's fragile, which is
the reason I chose
to serve her in the first place.
I've been a good
Covenanter for her,
but I've failed to
bring her any peace.
You're not giving
yourself enough credit.
Your support has truly
changed her. I know it.
I hope you're right about that.
This is hard for me to admit.
But I'm slightly jealous
that Yoshichika was the one
who connected with
Mana instead of me.
You're the type of person
who notices the little things.
Yeah. Like with your finger.
It's just a habit, I guess.
I tend to twirl it
when I'm writing poetry.
Though, lately,
it seems to happen
when I'm in a pleasant mood.
I didn't even notice it.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. It's a good thing.
You take the time to observe
what makes everybody else happy.
Oh, I do? Can't help it.
[beeping noise]
[VERONICA]
Olga. Nanahoshi.
Report to the training room.
Okay, I'm ready.
Let's get started.
[YUKARI]
Right.
[LOGIGRAPH]
Trance Session.
That's good, Nanahoshi.
Now focus on sharing
your Logic with her.
[beeping noise]
[LOGIGRAPH]
Crashed.
Step back and watch a pro.
[LOGIGRAPH]
Trance Session.
Let's go.
[LOGIGRAPH]
Crashed.
[OLGA groaning]
[laughing]
My Logic informs me
that not even a goddess
of Athena's talent
could possibly handle
my kind of power.
I'll try to get over it.
[YUKARI]
Athena.
Is there a trick to
Trancing successfully?
Let me think.
Perhaps you should
try connecting
to the other person more.
Connecting in what way?
Well...
Personally, I try to predict
what Yoshichika is feeling
in any situation
and then act upon it.
That makes sense.
Kinda like you're tapping
into his emotions, right?
[VERONICA]
Not all partners work that way.
So what are some other methods?
Just think about
Chloe and Valkyrie.
They don't employ
that type of strategy.
Yes.
It seems like Valkyrie
and Chloe always focus
on different objectives
when they Trance.
But what works for them might
not work so well for others.
A solid observation.
Every duo finds their
own method, eventually.
You're right about that.
Don't worry.
You'll discover your own
Trancing technique soon enough.
First I'll need a
Covenanter. But who?
[OLGA]
Why wait, newbie?
All you need is to Trance
with yours truly,
and let my genius
take care of you!
Like you have any.
I think Olga is pretty amazing.
I've always really
admired people
who have that much
confidence in themselves.
All of the top soccer players
on the team I managed
were the same way.
They believed their
dreams would come true.
And I did too.
[OLGA] I'm happy that you
can recognize my talent.
Gives me faith that you're
going to do well here.
I really hope you're right.
I want to be the
best Logicalist I can.
Maybe I should take a page out
of the others' Trancing books.
Tsurugi's strength
comes from his empathy
and reasoning skills.
That won't work.
I'm not nearly
as smart as he is.
Chloe relies on her instincts.
Still, no go.
[YUKARI] I wouldn't
be able to approach it
with Tamaki's tenacity.
And I'm definitely not
as level-headed as Mana.
I wish the answer
would come to me.
[YUKARI] A little pepper
should do the trick.
That's good!
Maybe thinking like a manager
isn't going to help
in this case.
[LITTLE QUETZIE]
Hey! Listen to me!
I'm cold! So very icy cold!
Put a cork in it, will ya?
[LITTLE QUETZIE]
Why are you so cruel to me?
I'm freezing in here.
[KITAOKA]
We all are! What a pest.
Okay, I hear you!
The heat will be back on
later this afternoon,
so just hold on till then, okay?
[KITAOKA]
I'm putting in for a transfer.
Hey, I have something for you!
[gasps]
[KITAOKA]
This can't be happening!
Don't you die on me!
Hey!
Please wake up, little guy.
[LITTLE QUETZIE growls]
[YUKARI]
Just a little farther.
But I know Kitaoka would
appreciate some warm stew.
[YUKARI]
What's happening?
[YUKARI panting]
[YUKARI screams]
You're free?!
[QUETZIE] That dumb guard
unlocked the door for me
while I was getting
a little shut eye.
Kitaoka?
You have to release him!
Please...
You can't keep him Trance Jacked
for very much longer.
The results could be deadly!
[QUETZIE] You think I care what
happens to a pathetic human?
His name is Kitaoka
and he'd nev--
[QUETZIE]
I've never seen you before.
But I can tell by your outfit
that you're a Logicalist.
Yes. But I'm just
in training right now.
[QUETZIE] You need to be trained
to keep your mouth closed.
Unless you have a death wish.
No... I don't.
All I want to do is
protect innocent civilians
from Foreigners like you.
[QUETZIE]
Hmm... You're a very brave girl.
I bet you taste good!
My name is Yukari!
I'm not food!
But you're in luck.
How about some stew?
[VERONICA] This situation
is extremely dire.
So what do we do?
We have to take him out,
obviously.
Clau, Pieri, I need you
to begin the evacuation.
[PIERI, CLAU]
Right!
Chloe and Yurine
are still tending to Asuha.
So it's up to the four of us
to handle this situation.
[gasps]
[OLGA]
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think you'd
forgotten about me.
[VERONICA sighs]
Okay, then the five
of us will handle this.
[YUKARI]
Before I started training,
I was the manager of a girls'
high school soccer team.
Which means...
I looked after
all of the players.
I made sure they had
everything they need--
[QUETZIE]
What are you rambling about?
I don't care about
your boring life, human!
Get to the point or die!
Okay!
Well, basically my job was
to take care of people
that I looked up to.
[QUETZIE] You could have said
that from the beginning.
I believe I
understand what you are.
You're like a priestess
living to serve
the god she worships.
The actual title is "manager."
[QUETZIE] These "managers"
seem slightly less useless
than the rest of you humans.
As you can see,
he's holding Nanahoshi prisoner.
Yeah.
So how are we
handling negotiation?
We won't be.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Huh?
No time for that.
If he extends his Paradox Zone,
then this entire branch
will be demolished.
[NEMESIS]
It's true.
Then he can release as many
Foreigners as he wants.
What are you thinking?
We'll destroy the floor.
Some well-timed blasts will
drop them into the lower levels.
Are you just
assuming she's gonna
magically survive
that kinda fall?
It's your job to
make sure she does.
My job?
Do whatever is necessary
to keep her from harm.
Are we clear?
Crystal.
[OLGA] Hey.
What do you need me to do?
[VERONICA] Oh, I have a very
important job for you, Olga.
Oh?
You will be the one giving
Nanahoshi her instructions.
Sure, I can talk her
through it, no problem.
Hold on.
It won't be from there.
[YUKARI] There's been an
increase of Foreigners
coming to our world
and causing chaos.
Why is that?
[QUETZIE] The denizens of
this world have forgotten
how to worship.
They praise only
their own progress
and attempt to bind
their betters.
That is what
causes us to rampage.
What about you,
little trainee?
Do you show reverence?
Yes. I do.
[QUETZIE]
Finally, a sensible human.
[YUKARI laughs nervously]
[OLGA] "We're carrying out
a rescue operation!
Buy us some time!"
[QUETZIE] Little girl...
Are you listening to me?
Yes, of course.
Hurry up!
We're running low on time!
It would be a lot faster just
to blow up the ceiling.
That is not an option.
Do you want them
to be buried alive?
Two more minutes and
we'll be ready to go, Chief.
[QUETZIE] Humans have lost sight
of their place in this world.
They need to devote themselves
to the gods through worship.
[YUKARI]
True.
[QUETZIE] If you agree
to serve me loyally,
you shall be greatly rewarded.
However, I do not hesitate to
punish any unfaithful followers.
[OLGA] "We will blast from
below and bring you both down."
That sounds a bit dangerous.
[QUETZIE]
Why would I care?
All humans are expendable.
[OLGA]
"There is no other way."
That seems like it may kill us!
And I really don't
want us to die.
[QUETZIE]
Quiet!
How dare a priestess
talk back to her god?
[OLGA]
"Draw this out!"
Please, forgive my rudeness.
I swear...
I will worship and pay
tribute to you, Master.
And then you won't
need to punish me, right?
[QUETZIE]
I would not...
If you were speaking honestly!
You have the audacity to think
that you could distract me?!
[OLGA]
Huh?
No! Get out of there!
[OLGA yelling]
[QUETZIE]
Insolent whelp!
Did you think me a fool?
You've been plotting
against me this whole time.
[YUKARI whimpers]
No... I haven't.
[QUETZIE]
You lie.
[roars]
Sorry, Quetzalcoatl.
We're out of time.
[YUKARI screams]
[QUETZIE roaring]
You okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
[rumbling noise]
[QUETZIE]
Who are you?
[QUETZIE roaring]
Nice. Don't worry,
you're safe now.
Stay right where you are and
let us take care of this beast.
Wait, don't kill him!
[QUETZIE yelping]
No one should die here.
Not even him.
This is it.
Say goodbye.
Wait!
This isn't over, Chief.
I haven't had my turn yet!
Watch out, Quetzalcoatl!
I'm calling for a time out!
Nanahoshi!
Here goes nothing!
Aegis!
[QUETZIE]
You...
Why did you protect me?
Because... it's part of my job.
A good manager always...
protects her team.
[QUETZIE]
What? You make no sense.
What reason is that
to risk your life?
I didn't want someone to die.
Even you.
So I stepped in.
For my teammate.
Rescue team, stat!
[VERONICA]
You all right?
Don't worry about me.
Go check on Kitaoka.
Yes. He's fine.
Strange...
Logicalists aren't
such pushovers.
How intriguing.
I'll accept defeat
this time, Lucifer.
[YUKARI laughing]
Hey, little girl.
Are you really a trainee?
Yes, I wasn't lying about that.
All right,
that settles it then.
I'll allow you to
be my priestess.
Are you ready?
[LOGIGRAPH]
Trance Session.
Activation.
[YUKARI laughing]
Whoa!
Way to go, girl,
you're doing awesome!
So, uh...
What happened while
we were at the hospital?
It's kind of a long story.
[YUKARI laughing]
Well, my Logic was right.
It said she'd pull it off
and she did just that.
But her potential
is still nothing
compared to the power
that I possess.
[CHLOE]
Mm-hmm.
Now you just
have to apply yourself.
So...
How do you feel... about them?
It's sorta like one's the brakes
and the other's the gas pedal.
I actually think they
complement each other well.
Do you honestly believe
we can trust Quetzalcoatl?
[YOSHICHIKA]
I'm not sure about that.
But they get along,
so that's a start.
That's true.
I believe they'll do just fine.
[YUKARI]
Look at me! I'm flying!
[QUETZIE]
You aren't flying.
You're getting carried!
And I really appreciate
you doing that!
Thanks, Quetzie!
[QUETZIE]
Huh?
Is everything okay, Quetzie?
[QUETZIE] Call me Quetzie again
and I'll drop you like that!
But it's so adorable!
I think it's perfect for you!
[giggles]
[QUETZIE]
I'm not adorable!
I'm a God!
[YUKARI]
Well I like it!
[QUETZIE]
I don't care!
[YUKARI laughing]
She'll always
be a manager, huh?
Now acting as a
priestess serving her god.
I never would
have thought of it,
but it really is the
perfect path for her.
Can't let them
show us up, can we?
Right!
[QUETZIE]
Hey! Stop!
[YUKARI laughing]
[QUETZIE]
I'm tired!