[helicopter blades whirring]
[crash]
[siren wailing]
[ZERA] The Sapporo precinct
has had multiple
simultaneous
Foreigner incursions.
[VERONICA]
The ice belva. It's back.
[NEMESIS]
This is awkward.
Did they move him or something?
[CHLOE groans]
This skirt's gotten so tight!
Well, yeah, you ate
seven slices of pizza.
Being a Logicalist
is a test of strength.
I should've eaten
ten more slices, at least!
[QUETZIE]
Can't... move...
I... I ate way too much.
You ate the rest of it?!
I want my pizza back,
you bottomless pit!
[QUETZIE wretching]
[CLAU] Hakodate is
requesting assistance.
[ZERA]
Put our members on standby.
[CLAU]
Yes, sir.
[JARNO] Have Yoshichika
brought to me. Now.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Wait, is this...?
Resignation?
It's such an
old-fashioned gesture,
not to mention problematic.
Let's talk.
We have a lab in Hakodate,
in the Sapporo Precinct.
Four years ago, Veronica
was being trained there
by a man named Ash Paxton.
That man was later Trance Jacked
by a Foreigner from Monolium,
an ice belva, to be precise.
This destroyed his personality.
His Paradox Sickness was severe,
and the higher-ups decided
he should be quarantined.
So they stuck him
in the basement
of the Central Hospital.
They found him easier
to forget about that way.
That's harsh.
It was out of my hands, but I
tried to make the most of it.
Veronica's wellbeing
was my top concern.
I decided she would
be better off here.
Three days ago,
a team from headquarters
started a follow-up
investigation.
And that same day,
Ash was moved back to the lab,
despite his condition.
When he arrived,
the ice belva,
which was under
tight containment,
reportedly started going wild.
I find that rather odd.
Don't you?
Bring her back. For me.
[QUETZIE] I don't get why I'm
being forced to go on this trip!
I brought plenty of things for
us to snack on for the ride!
And Sapporo is pretty famous
for its tasty morsels!
Oh my word,
they all look so yummy!
You know that I have
no interest in human food.
There's gotta be something
there that you'll like, Quetzie.
Like what?
Let's see...
Well, Marimo moss balls
might work.
Marimo, huh?
Well is it still alive,
at least?
Yeah, uh... Probably.
Good! I'll take them.
All of them!
Marimo! Marimo!
Are you all right?
Sorry. What was that?
Tsurugi, relax.
Your eyebrows could
get stuck like that.
You're worried about
Veronica, aren't you?
I mean, for her to leave
without saying a word...
It has to be
something pretty major.
It's formidable.
The ice belva.
I'm well aware of that.
[AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER 8A]
We have you on approach
and will guide you in.
[BELVA growling]
Monster.
Veronica?
What're you doing here?
Oh, just taking care
of your belva problem.
You must be her Covenanter.
I bet it's tough having such
a difficult partner, huh?
Nah, that's what makes it
such a good time.
Where have you
taken Instructor Ash?
He was in no condition
to be moved!
Well... He's not far from here.
Show her, please.
[STAFF MEMBER 8A]
Yes, sir.
[VERONICA]
What is this?
Look.
We finally located
Ash's Logic Cards.
[VERONICA] I'm going to
need your help, Nemesis.
I'll be ready.
Do you think we could
have our next mission
somewhere slightly less frozen?
Things'll heat up soon enough.
Oh, yeah!
[VERONICA]
Trance!
[YUKARI] I have to admit,
I'm kinda surprised
we were called in just for this.
[QUETZIE]
This is so boring!
There's nothing but snow
in any direction!
I'm over it!
Yeah, well, I don't know
what to tell ya.
[yelps]
Okay, how's this?
We can play the word
chain game, Quetzie!
We'll limit it to food.
I'll start with "banana"!
[QUETZIE]
Asparagus.
[YUKARI]
Hmm. "S." Shrimp!
[QUETZIE]
Possum.
Only he would eat those.
Um... Oh, marimo!
[QUETZIE]
Oyster.
Raspberry!
You've got "y." Go.
[QUETZIE]
Yawn.
[YUKARI]
Uh-oh, you lose, Quetzie!
Quetzie?
Both of us'll fall if you
go to sleep right now!
Come on.
If you doze off,
we'll plummet head first!
You gotta stay awake for me!
[QUETZIE]
I'm not sleepy. Totally awake.
[QUETZIE snoring]
[YUKARI gasps]
Quetzie!
[YUKARI screams]
[PIERI] Foreigner suppression
rate is at 30 percent.
[CHLOE]
I can't watch this!
Zera. I've gotta go to Sapporo!
Yeah, me too.
We all want to go.
But if we leave here,
who's going to protect Naien?
We can't neglect our duty!
Sorry, but you just missed them.
Veronica and her Covenanter are
already headed to the lab tower.
[YUKARI]
Oh, no...
Okay, it's time to get to work.
Right.
[YUKARI]
As soon as Quetzie wakes up,
we'll be right behind you.
[BELVA roaring]
[VERONICA]
Do you remember me, ice belva?
Ash Paxton was my teacher.
No, much more than that.
He was like my brother--
Someone I could always count on!
But you took him away from me!
Because of you, I lost something
that can never be returned!
[NEMESIS]
Raging fury!
Disgruntled bombs!
[VERONICA]
By the time I'm done,
you'll be nothing
but a pile of embers!
Quetzie?
Thank goodness! You're awake!
Yukari?
[stomach growling]
[YUKARI laughs]
I bet you're hungry.
I'll get you a snack!
Marimo! Gimme Marimo!
Oh! All right.
Just give me a second, okay?
[YOSHICHIKA] So the chief's
at the top of this tower, huh?
Let's think.
We have to find a way up there.
[ATHENA]
Okay.
Not if I have anything
to say about it, you won't.
What're those?
[YOSHICHIKA]
Run!
[ATHENA]
Right!
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, no!
[ATHENA]
Why are they after us?
[YOSHICHIKA]
I don't know.
But I won't let them
get near you.
[ATHENA]
On your left! Look out!
[ATHENA screams]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Athena!
[ATHENA screaming]
[YOSHICHIKA]
Trance!
[ATHENA]
Are you okay?
[YOSHICHIKA]
Uh... Yeah.
[ATHENA]
That was a pretty nasty fall.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What about you? You okay?
[ATHENA]
I am.
[crashing noise]
[ATHENA]
What is this?
[YOSHICHIKA]
They're all dead.
Terrible.
Yeah.
Pieri, can you do it?
Sir...
No matter how tight the Hakodate
Lab's security might be,
it'll be nothing compared
to Central Bank's
underground vault.
How would you know that?
Last one.
This secret lab is about
to be a lot less secret!
[BELVA growling]
[LAB STAFF 8A]
This is not good!
[LAB STAFF 8B] Chief Orlov, the
Belva's rejected the Trancing!
Performing an Over Trance
at this point
would kill him for sure!
[ORLOV]
Keep going!
If you won't do it
for all mankind,
then at least
follow my damn orders!
[LAB STAFF 8C]
We have to shut it down!
Do not interfere!
I can do it.
If anyone can, it's me.
I'll control.
Over Trance.
I'll protect us. I promise.
This is for our future!
He's gone?
Well, his humanity is.
He went too far and now
all that's left of him...
...is tragedy.
You mean the Belva was...
[ZERA]
You saw what happened.
I need you to rendezvous
with Tsurugi and Athena ASAP.
[YUKARI]
Yes sir.
Quetzie, the chief's in danger!
This is no time for you
to have a leisurely meal!
[QUETZIE choking]
We have to hurry!
Choke it down!
[ATHENA] Does Chief Veronica
know about what happened?
She's cut off all
communications with us.
[ZERA] I've dispatched
Nanahoshi and Quetzalcoatl.
Once you're all together,
you'll have to inform
the chief of the situation.
Right.
[JARNO]
Listen.
You're the only ones with
a shot at reaching her before...
...she does something
she'll regret.
Yes, sir!
[YUKARI, QUETZIE screaming]
[QUETZIE] I'm getting dizzy
and freezing to death
at the same time!
[YUKARI]
Hang on! You can do it!
[YUKARI screaming]
Where are the others?
I don't see them!
[screaming continues]
This is about to go bad!
[YUKARI, QUETZIE screaming]
[crash]
[YUKARI]
That coulda gone better.
Quetzie, you still in one piece?
[QUETZIE groans]
[ATHENA]
Yukari?
Wow, I can't believe
we actually found you!
Thank goodness you're both okay!
[YUKARI gasps]
[ATHENA]
Are you all right?
[YUKARI]
Uh-huh!
Hold on.
These Foreigners...
It looks like they're all dead!
[YUKARI]
Quetzie!
[QUETZIE]
Huh?
How long do you
plan to lie there?
We have to go stop
Chief Veronica!
[YUKARI]
Here we go!
[BELVA growling]
[VERONICA]
I will avenge you.
[BELVA growling]
[VERONICA]
You won't leave alive, Belva!
Nemesis!
[NEMESIS]
Madness! Fury! Intimidation!
[YUKARI]
Gotta go faster!
The tower won't hold!
[YOSHICHIKA]
We have to split up.
I'll find the chief
and tell her the truth.
You go on and look for
the missing Logic Cards!
[YUKARI]
You got it.
[YOSHICHIKA]
Now!
[YUKARI] Please make sure
she doesn't do anything
she'll regret!
[YOSHICHIKA]
I will! Don't worry!
[YUKARI] I'm gonna find
those Cards no matter what!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Counting on it!
Oh, no!
Damn it!
Nemesis.
Let's hit him hard! Now!
[NEMESIS]
Prepare to be exterminated!
Jealousy, Trepidation, and
refreshments at no extra charge!
[VERONICA]
Take this!
[NEMESIS]
All-Star Bombs!
Even more!
Give it your all!
[VERONICA]
Tsurugi?
Chief, don't do it!
You have to stand down!
[VERONICA]
Get out of the way!
That thing destroyed Ash's mind!
[YOSHICHIKA]
No!
The belva is the real victim!
It was Ash and the lab chief,
Orlov, who destroyed its mind!
[VERONICA]
Like I'd ever believe that.
Even if you saw it
with your own eyes?
Do not interfere!
I can do it!
If anyone can, it's me!
[VERONICA]
What is this?
It's impossible!
[YOSHICHIKA]
We gotta go!
[VERONICA]
Ash!
Instructor!
[ORLOV chuckles]
Perfect.
All the evidence
goes up in smoke.
[VERONICA]
Thank goodness.
[YOSHICHIKA]
No, Chief! Don't!
Orlov and Ash were experimenting
with some kind of
artificial Over Trance
and they took it way too far!
The belva isn't the enemy!
Chief, stop!
[NEMESIS]
Yoshichika!
That's enough.
I'm with you. Let's end this.
When I was all alone,
Ash took me under his wing
and he never abandoned me.
He saved my life!
[ASH]
Veronica...
Together, we're going to bring
an end to this otherworldly war.
He instilled me with a new
sense of hope for the future.
He told me we were going
to save the world together.
He promised me!
[VERONICA]
And this monster!
No, please! Don't do this!
[NEMESIS]
Veronica.
[VERONICA]
Damn it!
The victim's... you?
Oh, Chief...
[YUKARI]
I'm here!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Nanahoshi!
[YUKARI]
I'm sorry I took so long.
Instructor Ash...
Forgive me.
Stop!
[VERONICA]
Stay back, Tsurugi!
[YOSHICHIKA]
I said I'd protect you!
And that's what I'm gonna do!
No matter what it takes!
I'm so sorry.
I could only find
one of his Logic Cards.
[YOSHICHIKA]
It's over now.
[ORLOV]
What are you doing?
I'm the chief of this lab,
you morons!
[JARNO]
Don't worry. They know that.
[ORLOV]
Director. What is this?
Orlov Tunguska...
You're hereby under arrest.
This is a serious
violation of the Accords
on the Treatment of
Otherworldly Detainees.
The courts will not be lenient.
[CHLOE]
Yay, you're okay!
I was so worried!
Hey, Chloe!
[QUETZIE yells]
I'm glad you
brought her home safe.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I hope we didn't
worry you too much.
Not at all.
[JARNO]
Hey...
There was no doubt in my mind
that you'd be back.
Director.
We have to talk about...
Something tells me that you
won't be needing this anymore.
Yes, I will.
I committed a major
disciplinary breach.
Staying is
out of the question.
What breach?
The way I see it, you went to
back up the Sapporo branch.
There's no reason you--
I tried to kill
an innocent Foreigner
and I almost succeeded!
[JARNO]
The belva will be heading back
to his own world shortly.
You aren't guilty.
I'll re-submit my
letter of resignation.
[ZERA]
Chief!
I'm sorry to bring this up now,
but it's time to conduct
member evaluations.
[CHLOE]
Me first!
I ate a ridiculous
amount of pizza today.
My clothes don't fit!
As a Logicalist, I need
to learn to respect my body!
She's such a disgrace.
[TAMAKI]
My turn!
I write really long letters
to my sister in Kyoto
every single day.
And because of that,
the Naien postal workers
can't take any time off.
Letters really are best
when written by hand, though.
[MANA]
Guys...
I snuck out,
in the middle of the night.
And I ate some... ramen.
Hey, Chief!
I'll write an apology.
I'll clean toilets.
Really! Whatever you want!
Me too!
I'm, uh... really sorry
for something!
What are you doing?
Are you still determined to go?
I can't.
See you later!
[VERONICA]
Tsurugi...
--Thank you--
--[CHLOE] I'll take KP!
All pizza, all the time, baby!
[TAMAKI] Ya know, I don't
think that's how it works.
[CHLOE]
What do you mean by that, huh?
[VERONICA laughs]
Yurine, Asuha,
and Nanahoshi, you're on KP.
Chloe, you're cleaning
bathrooms for a whole week.
[CHLOE] Knew I
shouldn't have said that.
[VERONICA] I think the two young
men should clean my office.
What? Aw, man...
I wasn't supposed
to be here today.
Victim of fate.
This sucks.
[ZERA] You need to learn not
to sweat the small stuff, kid.
Lighten up!
[YOSHICHIKA]
Yeah, I'll try.
[ZERA] Now, I wanna hear
every detail about Sapporo!
Fly, fly away peaceful birds.
[YOSHICHIKA]
What's she saying?
Give us hope that we too
may soar far above our burdens.
Majestic and free.
Unencumbered by doubt.
In a sea of clouds
unafraid of falling.
You know what?
If the chief needs me,
I'm glad to help out.
[NEMESIS]
They might not be geniuses,
and they screw up a lot, but
they're really not a bad bunch.
They're exactly as stubborn
as they are resourceful.
And maybe that's
just what you need.
They're your comrades
and your children.
Yeah. They really are.