And now, a very special preview.
Something's happened...
And I need your help.
Will they live...?
Or will they die?
I bet they're hiding in here.
Let's stay close...
They have one more than we do.
Not anymore they don't.
The Otogi Bank
Chosen Team versus
the Three Tonda Brothers--the
Stink Terrorists...
It's going to be a
fierce, brutal battle.
Bring back the Gourmet Club
or we will refusing to bathing
and pass gassing
whenever you walk bying!
Unbelievable word endings.
If you want to win this battle,
then listen up good...!
First you must defeat
me in Twister-ee!
Really unbelievable.
We've been waiting for you.
The third one is normal.
Ryoko Okami.
Ryoshi Morino.
Ringo Akai.
In...
Okami-san and the Three Pigs.
I'm okay...
I just got a little in my
lungs, but you carry on.
Ringo!
That preview before the opening
song threw you didn't it?
Just trying to keep
you on your toes!
Now back to our usual beginning!
A bride request?
Seriously?
Yes but it's not from
anyone at this school.
In fact... I think it
would be very convenient
to have a favor
owed from this person.
From the way you're talking,
I assume this is someone
who's either very
powerful or very rich?
Yep...
He's an heir to the
House of Nezumi.
I think I've heard of them...
Their company has industrial
real-estate commercials
on television,
isn't that right ?
The point here is that
this guy is a big deal.
He doesn't really need
help finding a bride.
He's just lazy and
trying to buy one.
If he's as powerful and
as wealthy as you say,
there are probably plenty of
girls who want to be with him.
This is true.
Money is quite the aphrodisiac.
I think it's because he's not
every woman's physical type.
But I trust you'll help him out.
We appreciate your help.
This is Master Chutaro Nezumi...
...no need to genuflect.
I am Harmel,
his butler--honorable
by association.
Whoa, wait a minute...
I'm a little confused...
He's the one
looking for a bride?
No girl is going to say "yes"
to him dressed like that!
It's so small.
Is this a peasant's
house or something?
It's an office, sir, but
I do understand the confusion.
Let me smack him...
Rude little jerk.
Come on now, he's just a kid.
Anyone thirsty?
Then the maid-girl enters.
Um, may I ask what
your name is, sir?
Yes, I suppose
you could do that.
Okay.
If I may be so bold.
It's Harmel, though I've always
felt more like a Sebastian.
Wow! I love that name!
A butler named "Sebastian,"
that's original.
I do too.
It just feels right, doesn't it?
And what's your name miss?
Oh my goodness.
I'm so sorry.
How rude of me.
I'm Otsuu Tsurugaya.
Ah, and here I would
have guessed Mabel...
Just by virtue of
your ensemble...
I would also assume you
have a very clean house.
And a dirty mind.
Perhaps you assume too much!
Well that was
awkward for no reason.
Can someone explain
what just happened here?
Not it!
You're on your own.
So what you're saying is...
...as the Nezumi heir,
it is customary for
Chutaro to select a bride
before his twelfth birthday
and he hasn't been able to
find one yet, is that correct?
You've understood me perfectly.
Married by twelve?
And we're okay with this?
We will need to get
started straight away.
We're running out of time...
His birthday is
one week from today.
But you've known about it
for almost twelve years now.
Shouldn't something
have been arranged earlier?
He does have a good point there.
Um, yeah.
Kid...!
You don't have any little
friends that you could marry?
No...
I really don't...
If I did, I wouldn't be here.
It wasn't easy to
lower myself like this.
It's not easy for me to
watch this--you're eleven!
No, we understand...
so let's say we were to search
for prospects at our school...
what would we look
for--preferences, conditions...?
I haven't thought about it much.
I know I want a
woman who'll be able
to help me run the Nezumi
House in the future.
So maybe that's what
you could look for--
someone who's smart and who
seems like they'd work hard.
Someone who's smart.
And who'll work hard for you.
We're looking for a girl, right?
Do you already have
someone in mind for him?
Maybe someone perfect
is about to walk in.
No, just making
sure we got it right.
Pardon me...
Sorry, but the
President sent me here
to see how things were going.
What have we here?
Is this the girl?
She does seem
like a possibility.
Just wait until I get
my hands on that pansy...
...ugh!
I can't believe he's
setting Alice up like this...
The nerve!
Believe it...!
This is, in fact,
the President's doing!
He even provided that file
of information in advance.
It says that you're
beautiful, intelligent
and a competent worker.
Exactly what we're looking for.
Gee, thanks a lot...
You're one smooth
talker, y'know that?
Strange isn't on here.
It does say you're a bit rigid,
but that might be a good quality
for a servant-wife to have.
At least we know you're clean.
Excellent!
Will you please accept
my hand in marriage?
Right to the chase!
Wha?!!
Hold on.
Rigid is sometimes a nice way
of calling someone
a control freak.
And control freak is a nice way
of saying this woman
would ruin your life.
I don't know why we
didn't notice it earlier...
Just look at the deep
creases between the eyebrows.
Those are frown lines and
proof that she becomes angry
and hysterical quite often.
That tight miniskirt will soon
be replaced with sweat pants,
she'll wear chains
on her glasses
and spend all her free
time watching soap operas.
Yes, I think I understand...
and those are some
deep lines, I mean...
wow...
Plus, I don't like soap operas.
At least he let her down easily.
It's not like I have
wrinkles on my face
because it's fashionable!
And I don't like soap operas!
Sorry.
Something tells me she
wouldn't have been able
to handle the job.
That wasn't her fault.
They're the ones who made
her freak out like that!
Idiots.
Anyone would react
the way Alice did
if you criticized
them that much.
We'll have to apologize
to her for this later.
Who's that?
What did you see?
Is something wrong?
I don't know.
I thought I saw something that
looked kinda like a house gnome.
Or... maybe not?
Okay, I know it's early
but that is such a
perfect place to break.
So suspenseful!
See you in a bit!
We're back!
The wolf is on the
hunt for a child bride...
or a bride for a child.
Now that I think about it,
Ami already has a boy
that she's in love with,
so perhaps this
isn't a good idea.
Well, "in love" doesn't
mean that she's married.
She's not, but...
...there's another side to her
that isn't listed in that book.
Well, it doesn't matter
if she has a boyfriend.
I'm extremely good looking...
She'll be much happier with me.
Do your best not to hate
him because he's beautiful.
Or a mini-dork--take your pick.
Comes with being a
wealthy scion, I guess.
That's Inuzuka.
You may remember him
from earlier as part of
Momoko's entourage...
He's also on the baseball
team as Jin's assistant.
'So... Where is she?
She's right over there.
I see a tree and a bush.
Is that who I think it is?
Hello, how are you today?
What?! Nothing!
Yep!
That's Ami Jizou.
She's supporting Jin in
her usual maniacal way.
Of course not...!
I'm just secretly watching
over him from a distance...
not that it's any
of your business.
Wouldn't it make more
sense for you to go in
and watch from the sidelines
like a normal person?
You are dating him, right?
I can't do something like that!
It might creep him out!
That might creep him out?
You're wearing a stalker poncho
and spying on him
from the bushes.
And I imagine it
gets hot in that thing.
Pardon me.
Is your name Ami Jizou?
According to my records,
you're the serious type,
but a very good house keeper.
It also says you're
physically frustrated
but you're choosing
to keep quiet about it.
"Physically frustrated"?
Is that his attempt
at being subtle?
It didn't work.
It's still awkward.
I believe you would
be very good at looking
after the Nezumi House.
Most beautiful lady,
will you marry me?
What?!
Are you kidding?!
Not just yet!
If she's as repressed
as that book says she is,
this could be bad news.
She could blow her top
like an emotional land mine.
Is he really doing this again?
And another thing...
She clearly has
stalker-like tendencies.
Pretty soon your
pets will go missing
and you'll wake up to find her
undergarments in your mailbox.
Now he's just being tacky.
Where does he get this stuff?
I'm sorry, but that's
coming on way too strong.
Mailing unmentionables
would be a bit forward,
but aren't we
jumping the gun a bit?
Too crazy...?
Emotional land mine...? Stalker?
Ami, don't go!
She'll be all right.
Just remind me to take
an apology gift
basket over to Jin's.
Good idea...
Although that means
they'll have to tell him
where they found her and
that could be a little awkward.
Oh look, there she is again...!
It's the house gnome
girl from earlier.
Wish they'd explain who she is.
The next stop on their search
is the gym class storage area.
You know, you're from
a very high class family...
You should make sure
that the bride you
choose is of equal caliber
or else things could
become quite unbalanced.
That's a good point,
Harmel, thank you.
So...
We need to find a girl
from a higher class family.
Can you think of anyone?
Yes...
In fact, the one we're
looking for qualifies.
According to the
student network,
this is where Taro Urashima
tends to hide out.
So if we can find Taro, Otohime
will either be with him already
or close behind, right?
Ah. That makes more sense.
Man, I could learn
something from her.
The way she has Taro follow her
around like that is pure genius.
Oh really?
What technique is it, precisely,
that you would be
interested in acquiring?
Um, yeah.
It's just a misunderstanding!
I was yawning and "request"
just sounded like "breast...!"
I promise I wasn't
hitting on her!
We were working, I swear!
I knew it!
I'm getting good at this.
Since when does that
involve holding hands
and whispering sweet nothings
into someone else's ear?!
We always seem
to find them like this.
Right in front of the child!
This can't be good...
We could always
say it's educational,
but what if it scars him?
Or, no, wait, I guess he's fine.
I'm told you come from
a high-class family.
I would be so honored
if you'd be my bride.
I'm very sorry but,
I have to say no...
I've already found the one
I'm going to marry in
the future and he's...
Ringo and Ryoko...!
So good to see you...
scrumptious as always.
Thanks, though that's
highly inappropriate.
I have no response to that.
You're as hard to
please as ever I see.
That's all right; I enjoy
a challenge--it's exciting.
Taro, get over here...!
There is a refined gentleman
proposing to me right now
and not only are you
completely oblivious
but you're throwing yourself
at all these girls
right in front of me!
How can you be so cruel?!
Wait, that's not a gentleman.
He's still just a kid.
That's not the point!
Tell me the truth.
Do you still love me?
Of course I do, Otohime.
My eyes may look at other women,
but the only one
my heart sees is you.
Sold! He's so good at that!
Thank you, Taro.
Oh crap!
Here we go. Get it girl!
Hey kid, I'm sorry.
I know you wanted
to be with her,
but let me explain
something to you...
that kind of libido can
be pretty exhausting.
You know, I'm not saying don't
ever do it, cause well...
That would be painful.
But moderation is your friend.
Remember that!
I'm not sure I understand what
you mean by that, but okay.
It was nice of
him to try though.
Maybe we can make this
into an instructional video.
I don't know much about girls,
but they're sure enthusiastic.
Look who has an opinion.
Great. Now he's going to think
all women are just like her.
It's not that
Otohime's a bad person,
but I know what you mean.
All right then...
Let's move on to
the next, shall we?
Yes, because they're
clearly ready to go.
Hi!
I'm Mimi Usami!
It's so nice to meet you!
Aw...!
She's so cute!
Careful young master.
It's often the cutest ones who
have the blackest of hearts.
Why don't you come and say
that to my fist, you jerk...?!
I dare you!
Hi, I'm Suzume Shitagiri...
Suzume with the broadcast club!
We like her!
Oh! She has such a
pretty voice, too!
Yet she would chat about the
most boring subjects all day.
You'd feel like you were
living with a broken radio.
And you are about to live
with a broken face, turd-liver!
Remember Gretel?
The student council secretary?
The Nezumi House
would be international!
You don't want a girl
with a brother complex.
The love my brother
and I share is sacred
and none of your business!
Kizaki! Shiratori! Tanuki!
Aisaka! Kushieda! Kawashima!
Misaka! Shirai!
Saten! Hatsuharu!
They look so exhausted.
You showed us a lot,
but none of them worked--
they all had something
wrong with them.
No you just kept
looking for their flaws.
You're never going to find
anyone if you keep that up.
Young master...
If I may, please allow me to add
one more important condition
to your bridal criteria.
What's that, Harmel?
Make sure she has
a huge bra size.
Where did that come from?!
What the hell is
wrong with this guy?
Yet another prejudiced
generalization.
The size is important?
Yes...
I know you don't
understand it now, sir,
but someday they will be
the only joy you have left.
Observe!
A prime example!
It's the famous
Otogi double dumplings!
Wow, Harmel! You're right!
Those are incredible!
That they are indeed, sir...
Every man's folly
and wildest fantasy,
wrapped up in
two perfect bundles.
I'm not exactly sure what
you mean, but thank you!
There's too much
awkward happening here.
By the way, Ryoshi?
What's wrong with Ryoko
and her little friend?
They're not comfortable
talking about breast size.
You know, just stuff...
You know how girls can be.
I like you!
Will you do me the
honor of being my wife...
Wait just a moment, sir!
Oh no! Not again!
I was so blinded
by their beauty,
I forgot to remind you that
there is gravity here on earth.
Yeah, I know that, so what?
It's a curse sir...
One day that perky shelf
will fall down to here.
Life as you knew
it will be over...
Shape, a distant memory.
Hey...!
What the heck are
you talking about...?
I will never let that happen.
Gravity has no effect on me!
It feels that way...
Believe me, I wish
it could be true,
but give it ten years
and you'll see it isn't so.
So passionate about
something so absurd!
What a waste.
That's gonna be rough.
Have fun keeping those
things off the ground.
It's the attack of
the angry flat girls.
I'm sorry you skipped
puberty but insulting me
is not going to make
your chest pimples grow!
Harmel...
...if gravity is so powerful,
does that mean eventually
every size breast will fall?
No sir.
Fortunately there
are some miracle sizes
that can defy the
laws of gravity.
For example...
Tiny ones like those
two are smuggling!
He's just asking for it!
These miniature
morsels are majestic!
They rest on towering,
curveless figures acting
as shields unyielding to the
wind and refusing to back down!
I think I get the idea.
If there's nothing for
anyone to grab on to,
then gravity will
never be an issue.
His parents must be so proud.
Absolutely.
Because of their limited
handling over time,
they do tend to
hold up quite well.
I'm gonna kill you!
Lemme at him.
You have to calm down now.
We're still
fulfilling a request!
Little Red is impressively
calm, considering.
Well...
I guess that leaves
me with these two
and they're both about
the same size up there,
so which one should
I pick, do you think?
The younger one, sir.
She'll be physically
attractive longer
and have more
energy for housework.
All right...
Then I choose that one.
What are you talking about?
On the other hand, master;
she may look young and firm,
but I can see through her.
She is well past expiration.
No he did not!
Uncalled for!
What did you just say?!
That's it, butler...!
It's on!
Just hang in there, Ryoshi...!
You've got to keep them
back or it's going to get ugly!
Gotta keep them back.
Just ignore the pain!
I've always found it
impressive how butlers
can remain completely stoic
in situations like this.
It's interesting, isn't it?
All the things we look for
when trying to find
the perfect bride?
Women only look for
one thing, you know,
it doesn't matter
how much money you have
or how powerful
you'll be in the future.
They want what you
give without really noticing.
What's that?
Friendship...
one that's genuine
and lasts a lifetime.
Look at that...
It's like we're in a
completely different story.
Tell me something, young master,
why did you decide to go looking
for a bride at this
particular time?
Because it's the custom.
You know that.
That's not the real reason...
Be honest, now...
Wasn't it for her?
Hey!
It's the little
gnome girl again!
I'd know that
shaggy bob anywhere!
Is that Uika?
Chutaro!
I don't understand why
are you looking for a bride?
Is it because you
don't like me anymore?!
No! Of course it isn't!
It's just that I was
hearing these rumors...
They said you'd found
a boy you really liked
and that you were happy.
I didn't!
They're lying!
There's only one person
in this whole world
that I like in that way...
And that's you, Chutaro!
Thanks, Uika.
It's a common mistake, sir,
but hopefully now you can see
that it is dangerous
to believe rumors,
rather than going
straight to the source.
There was never any need
to search for someone
to complete your life.
Everything you were looking for
was right beside
you the entire time.
You're right.
This was certainly unexpected.
Looks like they were
thinking the same thing.
Ah!
What great story!
So his long journey led
him to find the treasure
that he'd always had beside him.
You should be
proud of yourselves.
Because of all your hard work,
the love between a young boy
and girl was finally realized!
Very good work, all of you!
Notice that the President
is the only one laughing.
Oh don't look at me like that.
I don't think it's
very funny either.
Guess who...?!
I'm sure you've forgotten
all about it by now,
but we're gonna go
back to that random story
we started in the beginning.
We take you now to the climax!
The Otogi Bank Team
has broken into the hideout
of the three terrorist brothers.
Although it was dangerous,
Red insisted they
go through with it.
It's because of her that they
were able to force these pigs
to drop their deadliest
weapon--their stench.
There's only one
thing left to do...
The entire future of the school
and humanity rests on
one game of Double Dare...!
Who will survive?
I'll make the
first dare... so...
Number one has
to kiss number two!
So if I'm number one then...
Hey look!
A fan service shot!
What the crap do you
think you're doing, Ringo?!
Don't be angry, it was a dare.
I had to do it...
I hope you took notes!
Because next time, we will
be passing out the dares.
So pucker up!
I hope you're all
ready for that.
Oh yuck!
I don't want to watch
those pigs make out!
Hey!
What just happened...?
I was watching that!
No reason to continue from here.
I'm surprised that Ringo would
even make a movie like this.
Whoa!
So that whole thing was
a movie that Ringo made?!
What a fun plot-twist!
I wonder where Otohime
and the others ran off to.
Oh! Sorry...!
Meanwhile...
I want that... oh,
and come to think of it...
Tonight every single girl
in this story is here.
I'll have one of everything
on this front row, please.
Give me the top five most
expensive items you have.
I want one of these and two
of those things over there.
I'll have whatever's
in here, please.
I'll have what's in
there, two of these,
one of those, and
that entire front row.
On second thought,
I'll have three of everything.
Change my order
to four of everything!
Stop trying to be better than
me you ugly brat and ex-turtle!
And just who are you
calling an ex-turtle?!
I don't know why
you dress like that.
Everyone knows
you're an old hag!
I'm adorable!
I can't decide!
It all looks so delicious!
It's certainly hard
to choose, isn't it?
Oh come on, stop
worrying about that
and pick something yummy!
Wow what a turn-out.
I didn't expect this.
There seem to be people here
that didn't even show up today.
I guess that's true.
Mojolika wasn't involved,
but that's the only one I see.
Since you're here, Ryoshi...
My wallet seems to be
getting thinner and thinner
and I don't know that I'll
be able to cover all this.
Do you think I could borrow
just a little bit of cash?
Of course, but
I don't have that much.
And then a few
other things happened.
But in the end, all
anger and heartache
was snuffed out by delicious,
yet expensive, pastries...
and with the exception
of the President's wallet...
...all's well that ends well!
Now what do those
two girls holding hands
have to do with that title?