We're from the Otogi Bank.
Nowhere to run...
So just give it up.
Your days of stalking
that scared girl end now.
'Cause if it happens again...
I have several pictures for the
police and your parents; uh oh!
That's too bad,
because she's mine!
Ringo, take a hike.
My pleasure.
You're just a girl!
A girl who kicked your ass!
That was splendid Ryoko.
I was able to capture
the entire event.
Always so formal.
Ringo, did you see something?
No, what do you mean?
Nothing... It doesn't matter.
A long time ago in
a faraway village...
Well, actually not that long ago
and more of a suburb really...
There was a town
called Otogibana City
whose jewel of a school in
which the children did rule
was the Otogi Academy.
This angry girl is Ryoko Okami.
She's a first year student
also known as Okamisan,
which means "the Wolf."
And the red haired classmate
of Ryoko's is Ringo Akai
also known as
Little Red Riding Hood.
Unfortunately, the flat-chested
Wolf and Little Red Riding Twerp
are this story's
eye candy... heroines.
The place they're headed
is the Otogi Academy Mutual
Student Aid Association--
but most people around school
know it as the Otogi Bank.
It's like a yearbook
club but a little different.
Together, with
some other freaky--
uhhh, unique?--special
upperclassmen,
they have "activities"
almost every single day.
Welcome back, ladies.
So... how was your assignment?
This is Lizst Kiriki...
He's the club's President...
...and she is the President's
cousin, Alice Kiriki...
I appreciate that.
It is strange that he
fought back, though...
Most students tend to give up
as soon as they hear our name.
The pretty young maid
is Otsuu Tsurugaya.
It still bothers
me that our women
always have to do all
the dirty work around here.
On that note, I've been thinking
about adding another guy
to our little group
to round things out.
What do you think?
Don't you think Taro is
enough guy for all of us?
Well, yes but...
Taro, wait!
What you're hearing
are the voices
of two first year
students Taro and Otohime.
I'll leave what
Otohime is trying
to do up to your imagination.
I swear...
See? Keep the antics of
our other male member
in mind in case you
find someone new.
After club
activities are finished,
Okamisan usually
trains at the local gym.
As you've seen,
Otogi Bank requests
can be a little intense.
Ryoko...
That's enough for today.
Kay...
I have to apologize...
With that chest this is
actually Fan Disservice.
Okamisan... I love you!
That's weird...
Is somebody here?
Okamisan... I love you!
Hey! How 'bout you go--!
Who... are you?
Uhh me...? I'm Ryoshi Morino.
I'm in your class.
Okay, whatever dude.
You don't remember him
at all, do you Okamisan?
He really is in your class.
Please don't stare at me.
Oh great...
D'you wanna tell
me what's wrong?
Ah, well...
Come on, spit it out already.
Okay... Here goes...
I love you.
That's sweet I guess but dating
really is not my thing at all.
So, excuse me.
You can't just walk
away like that...
I'm throwing
my heart at your feet,
the least give me a
chance to prove myself.
Okay fine!
Let go of me and
I'll give you a chance.
So tell me, kid...
What exactly is it that
you 'love' about me?
Well... you know... stuff...
Oh okay, I got it;
I got it, chill...
Hold on... I love
the strength you have...
I love your style...
That you're dignified...
You're never
afraid of anything...
You're kinda like a guy but
hotter... really, it's your--
Never court a lady
by calling her a hot guy.
Later on that evening...
...in the student dorm rooms.
Oh my goodness!
Did he really say he
was in love with you?
This is the Wolf and
Little Red's room...
They've lived together
since middle school.
Well... yeah,
I mean... he did his best...
I knew the day would
finally come when someone
noticed how beautiful
and adorable you are Ryoko!
So, who is it?
Tell me! Who? Who? Who is it?
He's a classmate...
His name's Ryoshi Morino.
Ryoshi?
Important note here,
both these girls are in the
same class with this guy...
For some reason they
have no idea who he is.
Guess that's him...
So what does it say?
Someone's curious.
Nevermind! I don't
need to know anything...
He does nothing for me.
I already like one
thing about this guy...
He's the first boy
intelligent enough
to fall in love with
you at first sight,
but I shall be the
judge of whether or not
he is worthy of my
best friend's affections.
She sounds like
my mother-in-law.
Whoa, no reason to
go all psycho on me,
and besides, I completely
shot him down on the spot.
You just leave this to me.
So... the next day...
Ryoshi Morino is a first
year student in group F.
Everything about him,
grades, height, weight,
is all the national average.
Socially, he doesn't
mix with others
and he tends to
stick to the sidelines.
It's not that he's
isolated, though.
It's more like he vanishes
from peoples' memories
because he doesn't stand out.
His talent for blending
in without appearing
out of place seems to
have been passed down
from a grandfather on
one side of his family.
This stealth ability
could be very useful...
Just think about
how it could help
with our surveillance needs...!
So you see, that is why...
I've invited him
to join us here!
Impressive.
Hah! Sounds like a
bunch of malarky to me.
Stare...
Stare.
Stare!
Please stop staring at me!
His upbringing in
a very small town
has given him a case
of ophthalmophobia...
A fear of being
stared at by others.
This grows more
fascinating by the minute.
Scared of being looked at?
Doesn't that just
make him worthless?
And that snaps
him back every time.
Don't you get it, silly?
Even with this horrid
fear of standing out...
He still told Ryoko
he was in love with her.
Ringo, gah--talk much?
Stop looking at me!
True courage acts
through the fear.
So when did the
love overtake you
and compel this act of daring?
Well... it just
happened last week.
Don't freak...
...but I secretly followed
you around most of last week
trying to find the right moment.
But, I just couldn't
bring myself to speak...
Oh, great...
So he's a stalker.
...until yesterday
We've been looking
to bring in another guy.
No objections, I trust?
Well that didn't
take much thought.
That's that. What do you think?
Uh, yes sir!
If you'll have me, I mean...
He's just thinking about
being near Okamisan...
Look at that smile!
I don't like it.
You're saying...
You were watching when
I was attacked the other day?
Is that right?
That's right.
Okamisan, wait...
You chose to hide
when the one you say
you love was in danger...
I would never trust a dude
like that to watch my back.
I guess she's
right about that...
Even when Okamisan was being
attacked, I completely froze...
I kept my head down
and stayed out of sight.
Pathetic.
It's a new client.
I'll be back in a bit.
You still might have a chance.
If you were able
to redeem yourself...
It's possible that Ryoko
would accept you, right?
It's all up to you now, Ryoshi.
Yeah-- Yes sir!
I'll try... I know I can do it!
So now that the President's gone
to work on poor,
pathetic, little Ryoshi...
Do you think he'll
actually become
one of Okamisan's companions?
Let's get back
to that new client
and see what her deal is...
My name is Kakari Haibara...
I needed to help
this really sweet guy
I like on the tennis team.
Are you familiar
with our system, right?
I take a loan out,
in the form of a favor,
and then I pay back the
favor when it's asked of me.
Right.
The Otogi Bank helps out
students who request assistance,
and in doing so, creates
debts with said students,
which are
forcibly repaid later...
...kind of like
paying it forward
except you don't have a choice.
Well, go ahead.
Tell us what you need.
Okay...
There's this guy on
the tennis team named Ohji
who got hurt and
won't be able to compete
for a couple of months.
I heard.
It sucks to have
our best player out.
I used to play tennis.
I was forced to quit and
it bothers me to this day
that I never went back to it.
I would watch their practices
and dream about playing again...
Hey... you wanna grab a racquet?
This is Ohji.
You can think of him as
the Prince of this story...
or at least of the tennis team.
Thanks.
I'd love to but
I'm afraid I just can't
Look, I won't push
you but... at least smile.
Later.
Hey...
Do you mind if I come
watch you play once in awhile?
Yeah... cool.
Ever since that,
I go to the court
and watch him play when I can...
Seeing him at it made me feel
like I could do it again...
Hormones are more
powerful than reason.
But then someone told me that
he was quitting the tennis team,
and he stopped showing up
at the courts everyday...
Wow...
It must be his injury...
He's afraid he'll never
play like he used to.
He could still stay on the team
but only if he doesn't
give up his spot.
I know he'll regret it if he
doesn't try to follow his dream.
He helped me so I want
to help him this time!
Please!
A favor? You're
returning a favor?
That is so wonderful!
Otsuu has an obsession
with returning favors.
You can't let him turn
in that withdrawal slip...
You have to stop him.
Please don't let him quit.
A withdrawal slip is
a not a simple form.
After you fill it out,
it has to get stamped
by the club captain,
advisor, and homeroom teacher,
before being submitted
to the Athletics Assembly.
Only then is the
withdrawal complete.
The assembly's tomorrow
at five o'clock...
If he doesn't submit his
withdrawal by that time...
...then his next chance to do
it won't be for another week.
Here's what I think, kids...
We can figure out the right time
and try to steal the slip...
...or we can try to
stop the captain
and all of the others from
seeing it in the first place.
If that's the case,
I think it would be prudent
to maintain constant
surveillance on him.
You can count on me, I guess.
Now, we're supposed to be
evaluating Ryoshi's abilities
on this one so no fair helping
him out, is that understood?
And that is how Ryoshi
got his very first mission.
Look at him.
He could have been following
you around like that for weeks,
and you never
would have noticed.
Nice! That image is
gonna make me puke...
Besides, what are we doing
stalking the guy who stalked me.
For my research...
I must determine if
Ryoshi is suitable for you.
That's not really your
choice to make is i--
Come on, let's go.
Here ya go, here's your change.
A bathhouse?
I hope he's not stuck in a
cheap dorm without showers.
But since we're already here,
we might as well
go in and take a bath.
Sorry. But they'd be
waste to show anyway.
Where's that withdrawal slip?
This is his big chance!
If he can steal it
right now, he's done.
We're contractually obligated
to say that stealing is wrong.
Stealing is wrong.
I wasn't doing
anything, I promise.
Stare...
Look at Mr. Subtle,
playing it cool.
Hey, wait!
You've got the wrong idea.
It's not what you think.
Get back here.
Stop!
Okamisan, Ringo!
Thank goodness you're here,
I need some help
explaining to him...
You...!
Getting punched
while naked must suck.
Withdrawal slips require stamps
from the club captain, advisor,
and homeroom teacher.
You have to stop him
before he gets them all.
Ryoshi must stop him before--
If only... he could...
But... no.
Time zips by in a flash
and suddenly class is over.
What...? How did you lose him?
I'm really sorry.
We're running out of time.
You know as the
president of the club
this should be
making you nervous.
Looks like he's already headed
for the assembly, you guys.
Five minutes until it starts.
That's it...
We'll just have to stop
him by force, won't we?
How?
Even if we ran as
fast as we could
we'd never make it in time.
Well, I was afraid something
like this might happen,
...so I asked Majolika to help.
Behold the power.
What I have to show
you will blow your mind.
It's the Pumpkin Bicycle!.
It's just like the
coach Cinderella
got to use 'cept it's a bike.
I'm in a skirt.
Oh that is awkward.
I'll drive you Miss!
I've done nothing except
cause trouble up to now.
I want to prove my love,
so I can't sit back
and watch what happens...
I've got to do this.
Right!
Well then, big boy...
I hope you don't flip
out riding that thing,
cause everyone is
going to be staring.
I've got an idea.
Keep going, it's straight ahead!
Okay!
Okay, that mask makes
him look like a space frog.
Take a right up there.
Got it!
He's here!
Ryoshi... you have to stop!
Okay, sure!
Where are the brakes?
Way to go, Majolika!
She probably never thought
about making it stop.
Don't stare at me!
Olympics here she comes!
Oh no... that bell probably
means its too late...
Oh wait... there's
his withdrawal slip.
Withdrawn!
Looks like Kakari left
behind one of her shoes.
The mission was a
success, more or less.
Yeah, except the whole
kicked in the face part.
Poor girl...
she was pretty upset.
It's all because that jerk
can't handle the pressure...
He's not getting in.
Hey, over here!
He came back.
With reinforcements.
Man!
His stupidity
makes him persistent.
No kidding!
It's time for some payback.
Ringo? Why don't
you take a hike.
As you wish, milady.
Incidentally,
these kitty knuckles
were also made by Majolika.
Get 'er!
You're dead!
You little!
Okamisan, look out!
Oh great.
That does it!
Hey, are you okay...?
What were you doing, anyway?
I was being your shield.
A shield?
You're nuts...
I wanted to apologize to you
for all the problems
I caused so I followed you...
Then...
I thought I could impress
you if I took them out...
but I guess I was just
too scared to move...
Being a shield was
all I could manage...
That was a pretty
nice move, man...
Thanks. I think.
Isn't this much better?
Finally, I can deem thee worthy
of protecting Ryoko's back.
Welcome to our
humble group, Ryoshi!
Okamisan, I look forward
to working with you!
Screw up like this again and
you'll be out on your butt...
..till then... it's Ryoko...
And I'll stop calling
you "dude" Ryoshi.
That's great.
Way to go, Ryoshi!
So... what do we do with them?
For the moment, we let them be
embarrassed by their failure.
Then if necessary strangle
them with silk scarves...
That's funny.
And that's how Ryoshi
became Okamisan's shield
and one of her companions
at the Otogi Bank.
After that, the prince
felt he was destined
for the princess who
kicked his face in...
...so he held tryouts.
I might get to go out
with the Prince of Tennis!
Every girl in
the school lined up.
Kick me!
Nope. Next!
Nope. Next one!
Kick me!
Yes sir!
That's it...!
Please, kick me some more!
Awesome!
More!
Harder! Oh yeah!
Is anyone else kinda
creeped out by this perv?
You're the strongest
girl I've ever met...
I'll do anything
to be with you...
Let's play tennis together!
Yes... my prince!
Thus, the Prince found a
new purpose in life,
coaching Cinderella.
And they all lived
happily ever after.
Dirty tricks and
Tricky Dicks next time.