It all started back when Otohime
was just in grade school...
Back when she was fat.
Hey... Where are
the other students?
They... went home I guess.
And left you here to
clean up all by yourself?
Man, what a mess.
They should know better than to
treat girls like slaves, jerks.
No, it's okay... um...
I'm the one who's slow and
always ruins everything.
What does that have
to do with anything...?
You don't need to do
everyone else's work.
Um... I'm, really sorry.
Why are you
apologizing, Otohime?
How do you know my real name?
It's a talent I guess.
I remember all girls'
names for some reason...
Can't say the same for guys.
No, I mean no one
ever uses my name.
They just call me
turtle or turtle girl.
What? Why?!
They say it's because I'm clumsy
and stupid and
really fat like one.
Well, let's take
a look at you...
Naww...!
I've never seen a turtle with
long legs and a pretty face...
Those eyes are especially nice.
You're pretty cute, ya know.
And just wait til you
lose your baby fat...
Oh man...
That'll show them, huh?
Thanks a lot Taro.
So yeah, you could say her
looks've changed a bit.
Long, long ago...
Yadda yadda yadda
something redundant
and on to the interesting part.
Ryoko made your lunch
today, didn't she, Ringo...?
You're so lucky.
You are correct
on both accounts!
Best omelets in the world
and they're all mine!
I shall make you a deal...
Spin around three times,
barking like a dog
and the lunch is yours.
Okay...! One, two three...!
Woof! Woof!
The hero of our story,
ladies and gentlemen...!
Could he be more pathetic?
That hurt.
Hey!! Move...!
Save me, Ryoko!
And I'm saved, thank you.
Get off of me...!
You're such a pervert!
Is something wrong, Taro?
Yeah, that.
Oh my!
Is there a fight
going on? Drama!
I recognize the one wearing
the little girl clothes...
I think that's Mimi Usami.
She's a second year.
Is she famous or something?
She's popular,
because she dresses
and behaves like a
child to get attention.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, would you, Ringo?
'Kay... Well, it
looked pretty intense.
Any idea why she would
have been staring down
Otohime earlier today?
Well, there's a history there.
The three of us were in
elementary school together.
Otohime and I both ended up
staying back a year...
So I had no idea Mimi Usami
went to this school.
He also had no idea that
while he stayed behind
to pursue knowledge, Otohime
stayed behind to pursue him.
It's sweet, really.
I'm sorry, Miss...!
Are you okay?!
Let me help you up.
Is that you Taro?
Yes, who... Oh wow!
Mimi, hello!
It's been so long...!
Look how pretty you are!
It's great to see you!
I can't believe we're
at the same school...!
How have I not run
into you before?
Did you just transfer?
Well... I decided I wanted
to study abroad for a year...
So after I came back,
I had to start in school
as a first year student.
And now here we are running
into each other again...!
Literally!
This can't just
be a coincidence.
We need to catch up soon.
But not now.
I'm trying to avoid
being followed.
Taro!
Mimi... Is that you?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, have we met before?
I'm not surprised
you don't remember...
It's been a long time, we went
to grade school together.
I'm Otohime Ryugu.
Oto... hime...
Wait! Turtle Girl?!
Wow, that name brings back
a lot of memories for sure.
You look amazing!
Didn't even recognize you!
What's your secret?!
You got a little nip-tuck there?
Maybe some shnoz-scaping?
No, no. I didn't
spend any money.
I just started eating
right, exercising,
and doing things that make
me feel good about myself.
So how I look is just
kind of a reflection
of how I feel on the inside.
'Kay... Ready to go, Taro?
Maybe...
By the way...
Taro mentioned to me that he
was trying to avoid someone...
Was he talking
about you, Turtle Girl?
Maybe he was joking...
Guess you didn't know we're in a
serious, committed relationship.
Also... As you can see,
I'm no longer
the clumsy little fat kid
you used to make fun of.
So I'd appreciate it if
you'd stop calling me names.
You certainly talk a lot
more than you used to,
that's for sure.
Look, I'll make you a deal...
Why don't we settle this at
the Miss Otogi Academy pageant
they're holding next week.
It'll be like a game.
And when I take
first place over you
then I get to keep
calling you Turtle Girl
and you can't complain...
Sound good to you?
It sounds silly...
but easy enough.
So if I win this
thing then you have
to stop calling me Turtle
Girl permanently, right?
Turtle!
Yep...!
That is the game!
Rabbit!
And with that, the race
between the tortoise
and the hare had begun!
To be honest...
Otohime is way hotter
and I'm pretty sure she could
win the whole thing, but...
I suspect Mimi not calling her
names anymore won't be enough.
I have a request!
I need you to make sure
that I win first place
in the Miss Otogi
Academy pageant!
If I can beat Mimi Usami
and show everyone
I'm the one who
ended up with Taro,
then that should get rid
of the Turtle girl image!
Makes sense, but you realize
even though you are a member,
it still counts as a request...?
Are you sure about this?
Absolutely.
And I will repay
my debt in full...
Please! I'm begging you!
She's begging!
And so, the very next day...
Entering the Miss Otogi Academy
Pageant won't be a problem.
The nomination process
is a total sham.
It's set up to accept anyone...
...but the winner is determined
by the number of male votes
and that could be a bit tricky.
One vote per person.
Obviously.
What do you mean?
You've got some
stiff competition.
Momo from the morals
committee is entering
and so is Shirayuki...
...not to mention the
mysterious beautiful girl
who won last year.
I'm here...! And right on cue!
Who called for a
mysterious beautiful girl?
I thought people outside of
the club couldn't get in here!
Really...?
Guess that makes me speci--
Geez,you have got to quit that.
How can you be so inhumane
to a sweet young thing like me?
Ahem.
Happy...?
Wow... You must not
know your own strength.
That's... the president?
Yes, he's often in drag...
It helps him gain access
into numerous places
for information
gathering purposes.
He can also completely
change his voice!
...and brought back juicy deets.
Turns out that for every one
who adores Mimi Usami--and
there are quite a bit--
there's another who finds
her cutesy act disgusting.
A whole camp, in fact,
dedicated to hating her,
so it's pretty evenly divided.
Does not surprise me at all.
Hello, Kettle?
This is Ringo.
You're black.
Otohime's popularity
seems pretty consistent
all the way around...
She's absolutely stunning--which
is always a plus--
but I think being with Taro will
really help her stand out here.
Might help her stand out, sure,
but I don't know
that guys will vote
for a girl who has a boyfriend.
He's got a point.
So it's looking like we have
a fifty-fifty chance here.
No! I'm going to win this!
And I don't care what it takes.
I'm going to come in
first no matter what.
Tell me--what's the
first thing I need to do?
Oh no...
You made a full-fledged
request this time,
so the only thing you need to
do is let us handle everything.
If we need you, we'll call.
Okay.
Great. Then let's get started.
The one who controls
the media controls
the way the vote swings!
It's true, but in
which direction
are you wanting them to swing?
I figure it will take
about a week.
We'll release all
her dirty laundry
and if she doesn't
have any, we'll create it!
This is also a great
opportunity for us to show
what the Otogi Bank
is capable of.
That's the dirty laundry
you came up with?!
That's mortifying!
What is all this?!
It's gonna be okay!
Lies...! They're all lies!
You can't let them see you cry!
You guys are the best...
Thank you.
Think you're so smooth,
don't you Turtle Girl?
Not you too!
Suspicion slash awareness
of Mimi being paid
for dates has
exceeded fifty percent.
Unfortunately, she's
now spreading rumors
that Otohime
is sleeping around
and this belief is closing in
at about fifty percent as well.
The good news is,
if they didn't know who she
was before, they sure do now.
I think it would be a good time
to do a little wardrobe change
and start some more rumors.
Ta ta!
Make sure you don't talk to
her entourage by mistake!
Those wastrels stuffed trash
in Otohime's shoes earlier.
Trash smash!
I say we put
lizards in their shoes!
I guess that means
we're going reptile hunting?
This is getting out of hand.
It seems like this
is more about messing
with each other
than the pageant.
Yep.
And I really don't have
time for that childish crap.
What the hell is going on?!
Why does it say
I entered this thing?!
I thought everyone should enter!
It looked like so much fun!
What a brilliant idea, Majo.
Ryoko is prettier than
Mimi but not Otohime--
which will make
Otohime look even better!
Three days passed
in much the same way.
Oh, hi.
How are you doing today?
Hello. It's nice to see
you haven't completely
forgotten your manners.
Isn't that the girl
that charges for dates?!
But the other one's
easy and she's free!
I hope they're happy.
It appears the rumors
are spreading quickly!
Well, everyone knows who she is.
Yeah because of bad rumors.
This isn't good.
I can't wait to see how they
pull themselves out of this one!
It's going perfectly!
The president is never
bothered by anything...
She's slipping.
How's she supposed to get votes
when people think
she's a you-know-what?
Don't worry your
pretty little heads.
I've got this covered.
I'm cashing in
favors as we speak.
But perhaps I should
give them an extra push...
Oh Ringo, my dear?
What can you do to entice
Miss Mimi's voters away?
So hot!
Keep it in your pants, boys!
Do I have to watch this?
Disturbing, yes,
but fascinating!
Hey! Look this way for a sec!
You sick jerk!
Put that thing away!
Wow!
An angry chick!
It doesn't take
much to impress them.
Do you really think this is
going to help us to get votes?
I'm hoping to get the
attention of the culture club.
It'll be grand if we can
get them to vote for us.
Oh I see...
'cause then we'd get
their followers votes.
Yes, that, and because
they're all pedophiles
who worship Mimi...
The president said it
would be very easy and all
we would have to do is dress in
baby clothing the way she does.
He said we wouldn't
have to act at all...
Not sure what he meant by that.
The boy was just being honest!
Um, what are you doing in here?
I knew it.
There's no way this
was going to get past her.
We were just here on a
job for the Otogi Bank...
There was a request
made to have a photo-shoot
with beautiful models.
Oh sure there was.
You're so pathetic.
You think I don't
know you came in here
to steal my votes
you cheating pig?!
Wow, you are worried
about your votes.
It must be hard to be you.
The hardest part is
trying to talk to a baby!
What did I just hear you say?!
You don't get to
talk to me like that!
I'm the only one
who can start fights!
Then bring it on,
you dumb [Bleep]!
You can both go [Bleep]
yourselves and the Otogi Bank!
Now get out of here!
Oh my!
You should really take these
dirty things you're saying
and shove them up your
filthy [Bleep]
where they belong.
And speaking of your [Bleep]
Where's that smell coming from?
Oh say that again
you [Bleeping bleep]!
That's it.
We're going straight to DVD.
There's no way this
is suitable for TV.
I can't believe someone
as sweet as our Mimi
would say things like that.
Someone's losing votes!
OMG.
I'm sorry; I can no
longer respect you.
And with that she
lost her entourage!
No! No, wait!
You will rue this day!
Does this mean I won?
Boy are you naïve.
I'm the narrator!
Blah!
There is way too much
going on in this scene.
And now we come to the day
before the Miss Otogi
Academy pageant!
This is perfect!
Otohime's popularity
has jumped significantly!
And would you look at that,
Little Miss Nutjob's appears
to be dropping
right on schedule.
You're doing an excellent job!
How is that?
Otohime's votes jumped
but they're still not as
good as they could be.
No! No, it's fine!
Oh, and Ryoshi...
you're not allowed to
vote for Otohime tomorrow.
Huh?
Um... Why not?
She still needs votes,
doesn't she?
Oh, just trust me
and enjoy the show.
I can always tell when
he's up to something!
The first contest tomorrow will
be the swimsuit competition.
This one's kind of...
I bet Mimi will wear one even
smaller just to intimidate me.
Want me to walk you home, Mimi?
No, let's go to the new arcade!
I wish I could but I'm
on cleaning duty today.
The Turtle Girl
will clean it for you...
Right, Turtle Girl?
Yeah, it's okay. Don't worry.
I can handle it by myself.
See! Turtle Girl wants to do it!
Well if you're sure...
Thank you!
They're right. I am a turtle.
Otohime?
It was that moment that
changed me into who I am today.
That's when it clicked...
I had to become pretty...
I wanted him to
look at me someday...
...and be proud.
Oh hi it's you.
Have you not been home yet?
I promise you...
I am going to win this!
I'll win first place
and prove to you
and everyone that
we belong together!
Please... just say
you believe in me!
You shouldn't be
so hard on yourself.
'Kay.
It's finally here!
The day of the pageant!
Well hello there, gentlemen...!
It's so good to see
you on this exciting day!
This is Suzume Shitagiri...
She's Otogi Academy's
very cheerful emcee.
...for your votes and
for your enjoyment!
Wow... this is so amazing.
What do you say
we get right to it
and bring out our
lovely contestants...?!
Ladies!
Let the competition begin!
Our first battle lays
out our girls' pride
and modesty on the line.
No way! Swimsuits?!
I love today!
You haven't seen
anything yet, my friend.
Oh please...
Oh please, don't tell me.
She's the heroine in the story--
it's hard to get
them to show skin.
That figures... You know,
it's too bad Alice couldn't
be here to see all this.
Okay, let's meet our
lovely contestants!
Isn't she adorable?
This is Mimi Usami!
She's here to prove fierce
things come in tiny packages!
Our little red riding hood has
a basket of treats in one hand
and a poisonous
apple in the other!
This is Ringo Akai!
Next we have Majolika
le Fey being quite strange
and wearing swirly
glasses! Oh my!
Good thing she brought
her maid to service her!
Please welcome Otsuu Tsurugaya!
Some just don't have
to play by the rules!
Give it up for our
not-as-tough-as-she-seems girl,
Ryoko Okami!
And finally, the one you've
all been waiting to see--
a lady by day, a vixen by night
and Taro Urashima's number
one fan, Otohime Ryugu!
This is it. I can't lose.
I am going to win first place...
...for me and for Taro.
Oh my goodness!
This is not what I meant by
sparks flying on the stage!
And on that note...
...it's time to cast
your votes, people!
You can turn in your ballots
as soon as you're done,
and remember--only
one vote per person!
Are you guys ready
to see some results?
Let's do it!
This Miss Otogi thing
is freakishly efficient.
They count votes the same day
and can show
results immediately.
Otsuu placed? Really?
The maid costume placed.
It has very loyal fans.
Now let's get to
the real winners.
Let's see our top three!
In third place...
Mei Uozumi with two
hundred and forty-nine votes!
Second place...
Momoko Kibitsu with three
hundred and forty two votes!
And the title of
Miss Otogi goes to...
You remember what'll
happen when I win, right?
You're gonna be so embarrassing
when you have
to eat those words.
Himeno Shirayuki...!
Four hundred and
thirty three votes!
Congratulations to
all of our winners...!
Is this some kind of joke...?
How is it that the creepy maid
made the top ten and not me?
There she sat, mortified
and overcome with shame...
Well, you reap what
you sow, I suppose!
I kept waiting for you to
win first place as you said,
but as it turns out,
you're all talk.
This is all your fault...!
You copied my act
and stole my votes you
ugly cheating knock-off!
How dare you?
You'll pay for that,
you blithering Black
Bunny Freak Show!
Is that a threat, Little
Red Snapper Crotch?!
What the hell are
you all staring at?!
I said... what are
you staring at?!
It's too soon to be
depressed, my dear.
Right there. One vote.
Now... who could
it have come from.
What does this mean?
You won...
You're the winner of
this contest, Otohime.
No I'm not.
I was supposed
to take first place.
You wanted to win...
...but it wasn't first place
you were truly interested in...
...it was about
getting the attention--
or in this case, the
vote--of the one you love...
...but you got so wrapped up in
erasing your past, you forgot.
We lowered both your
and Mimi's scores
so it wouldn't be about
popularity anymore.
That way, you would
recognize the importance
of the vote you did get.
Though I guess
I owe you an apology
for not fulfilling
your precise request.
I'm sorry.
All of your hard work
has paid off, Otohime...
You're beautiful
both inside and out.
There's no need to worry
about your past now...
what other people think of
you doesn't matter anyway.
It's what I think
that's important.
Oh Taro... Thank you...
I don't know what to say...
I can't stop crying...!
Thank you so much!
You deserve it, Otohime.
And so the fight
between the tortoise
and the hare finally ended...
And Otohime became...
Well, the Otohime she
is today... Beautiful.
Kendo club, photography,
and swim team
cleared the account.
Art, track and
crafts created a debt.
Why would...
He will take out a loan
for anything at any time
and not think twice about it!
But that's our
President for you!
...complicated
business, you know...
...and worth it.
Just look how well things
are going for the two of them.
No Otohime! Not there!
Anywhere but there!
There's no need for
me to narrate here!
And we shouldn't be
listening to this anyway!
That was such a stupid pageant.
I still don't understand
why you dragged
me into that circus.
What were you thinking?
See for yourself.
Each of the contest scores...
This is yours.
And just a marginal inch
away from the top...
Isn't that right, Ryoshi?
Yeah, it's true...
Ryoko will always be number
one to me no matter what.
Dear Ryoko, tell me
what it's like to be loved!
Wolves have an interesting way
of hiding their embarrassment.
As you can see, a lot happened.
And yet the Otogi Bank was
as peaceful as it always was.
All's well that
ends well, right?
Now they're advertising favors?
Dirty. I'm sure
I'll see you there!