Hello, everybody!
Welcome back
to Otogibana City...
Every time I see this
scenery I feel so zen...
Oh, look! It's our
trio of misfits!
Okamisan, Red, and our
favorite screw up, Ryoshi!
Do you have any idea
what the president wants?
No, but I do know this is
not your average meeting;
he doesn't normally
get everyone together.
It sounds like there
might be an emergency.
There she goes with
that fantasy again.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine,
all right, jerk...?!
Why don't you mind
your own business?!
Funny how one little dream
can make her so moody...
Such a delicate flower.
I'm sorry... I think?
Okamisan is no fairy
tale damsel in distress.
Here we are, at the Otogi Bank.
I'd like you to take
a quick look at this.
The Otogi group is corrupt,
and they charge
ridiculous interest for
virtually no assistance...
What the hell is this crap?
Um... It's kind of accurate
if you think about it...
...but someone
managed to scatter
these papers all around town.
On top of that,
baseless criticism
has been showing up
on internet forums.
Come to think of it,
there must be a lot of people
who're holding something
against us, right?
He's correct...
Which begs the question,
we have been denounced before,
so why is this
time more important?
Well...
it's more than just criticism...
Things have taken a bit of
a turn for the dramatic...
This is an article in today's
Otogi Newspaper.
It can't be!
They found out where our
secret basement room is?
No, no. It hasn't
gone that far, yet.
The newspaper gave us
a call about this article;
apparently they received an
anonymous tip a few days ago...
They actually asked if
we would mind commenting
on a story about us.
So we gave them our secrets?
No way.
I just showed them my
workshop and gave 'em a tour.
See?
Majorica's workshop
is also in the basement,
so they weren't exactly lying.
I gave them sucker
souvenirs, too!
Don't worry, no one
knows where we are.
The door to this
room is triggered
to be hidden in case
of emergencies...
We have a lot of personal
data stored in here,
so we've taken
extra precautions.
That's comforting.
I suppose we need
to figure out just
who was responsible
for that anonymous tip.
Hold on--you're not implying
one of us did it, are you?
Of course not; no one here
would do something like that...
...but someone somewhere has an
awful lot of information on us.
Any idea who it might be?
I think it's most likely
the student council president
of Onigashima High School.
Shiro...? Seriously?
Of course.
Shiro Hitsujikai...
In Onigashima High School...
...he is the thug president.
...to figure that part out.
Okay... so what do we do?
The only thing we can do;
we'll just continue
to monitor the situation.
There's a high probability
he's waiting for us
to make the next move.
In the meantime, I thought
it would be a good idea
if we were more proactive
about taking requests.
Someone obviously
knows how to prioritize...
Right now, all requests
are thirty percent off.
Requests are thirty
percent off? Weird.
It wouldn't be a bad idea
to go ahead and stock up
on some favors in
case we need them.
So, let's get out there
and take some requests!
Hit up the school
and wherever else people
might need some help...
You can do it!
It says requests
are thirty percent off.
What does that even mean?
I don't get it...
So what do you think?
There's probably no difference,
to tell you the truth.
Oh well. It worked.
And we're ready; who's next?
What exactly would you
like us to do for you?
I'd love it if you
would fetch my balls!
Oh, no! The pain, the pain!
Could you clean
the swimming pool?
The unbelievable sorrow!!!
Would you feed
the animals for me?
The horr-- Oh, wait.
She likes doing this.
Alice is a request
handling superstar.
Okay, is everyone listening?
Move your tongue like this.
Otohime is holding
a beauty class...
Or, maybe a kissing class...
I'm not sure.
Otsuu is being her typical
sweeping maid self.
La la la la laaa!
Three days nonstop--I'm
freakin' exhausted.
Me too.
I feel like a handyman.
And we still have to help
out the manga club, don't we?
I don't like their room;
it always smells like
stinky feet and sour milk.
Oh... you leaving?
Yeah, we've got a request.
I can help you
out if you want...
I'm done with all
mine for the day.
No thanks... We'll be fine.
This show
should be called
Okamisan and Her
Complicated Heart...
Poor Ryoshi doesn't
stand a chance.
Yea, I'm fine,
all right, jerk...?
Mind your own business!
No thanks... We'll be fine.
Maybe it was something I said.
Ryoshi senses
another presence...
Not bad!
You knew I was here
before I called out...!
You really must be
descended from hunters.
So...
You are...?
My name is Saburo Nekomiya;
I'm a senior at Otogi Academy.
You can just call
me Neko, though...
Everybody does.
Oh my... He's certainly
a handsome young man.
Well, then...
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, okay; it's nice to
meet you too--I'm uh...
You are a first year member
of the infamous Otogi Bank...
You're Ryoshi Moreno...
You boldly confessed
your love to Okamisan...
..only to be rejected.
This one is clearly
a fan of the show.
That fancy little
club of yours gets
an awful lot of attention...
Guess what else I know?
Staaare.
Please don't look at me!
I really hate being stared at!
Oh, yeah, you got it bad...
That's ophthalmophobia.
What do you want
from me, anyway?
Do you have a request
or something like that?
No, no... I was hoping
you'd let me give you a hand.
What?
See I'm a big fan of
helping people out...
I like to offer assistance
to others whenever I can.
Uh, this sounds
extremely shady to me.
Relax, man.
You're not gonna
have to repay me...
It's totally free!
And now, the whole
thing's even shadier.
I'm sorry, but I can't think of
anything I would
need to ask you for.
Thanks anyway though...
See ya later.
So you don't want to
protect the girl you love?
Come on now, don't
act so surprised...
You've gotta know the way
things are going between you,
it won't work out.
Don't worry; I've
got your back, friend.
Stop freaking out and
put your faith in me.
I will turn you
into the perfect man...
One Ryoko Okami won't
be able to resist.
Interested?
Now, we can begin
your training tomorrow...
...sound good?
Heh, well, Neko
may be Puss In Boots,
but I think we know
who the real puss is...
Yes, sir!
I'm so worn out!
I'll go draw a bath for you.
Whoa. Who's that?
Please... Help me.
Oh, how awful!
That's an Onigashima
High uniform, isn't it?
Who cares?
Let's just get her inside.
Hey there, sleepy, welcome back.
What? Where am I?
The Otogi Academy girls' dorm.
You collapsed right
outside the front door.
You didn't have to
take care of me-- Ow!
Just try to relax, okay?
Thank you...
You're both very kind.
My name is Reiko Kokonoh.
Some jerks from my high
school were after me so I ran...
I didn't mean to bother you;
I was just trying
to find a place
where I could hide from them.
That's weird.
Why were they chasing
you in the first place?
Do you know Shiro Hitsujikai?
He's the Onigashima
student council president.
Yes, we've heard of him.
Why do you ask?
He's my; well, I used
to be his girlfriend...
...but I guess he didn't
want to be with me anymore.
So he tried to sell me.
I was waiting to talk to him,
but those thugs
showed up instead...
They said Shiro told them
they could do whatever
they wanted to me.
That bastard!
He will pay!
What are you going to do?
What do you think...?
I'm gonna go see him!
Don't be ridiculous.
You know you can't!
She's right!
It's much too dangerous.
Please don't!
The important thing is
I was able to get away
from those guys...
Trust me--that's enough for me.
I'll help you get out of there.
We can get you transferred
from Onigashima.
Are you serious?
I think it's do-able...
Don't you, Ringo?
Yeah.
You can stay here until
the paperwork is finished.
Are you sure?
Yes.
And don't worry;
we'll protect you... Cool?
Thank you so much.
Ringo, you're fine
with this, right?
Yeah... Sure thing...
To be continued
in the second half.
The day after
Okamisan rescued Reiko.
Well, congrats; you all
did a lot of work today.
Fifty requests were completed,
and even at a discount
a return favor is
still a favor, isn't it?
Sure would've been nice if
you woulda done some of them.
She's right--you've
been a bump on a log.
I'm not gonna disagree.
Don't you worry; I'm doing a
bit on my end of things, too.
I know you're all tired,
but we need you to
keep up the hard work...
Just think, only
two more days to go.
'Kay.
It's like a Hell Week
for requests.
Oh... I have to go now.
I'll see you guys later.
What was that all about?
Are you saying you're curious?
No, gah... We should
be heading back, too.
I have some business
I need to take care of...
But by all means,
you go on ahead without me.
Seriously, you too?
See ya later, then.
I have something important
I need to discuss with you.
So, um...
what kind of training is this?
The kind that'll
help you in a fight.
I guess Ryoshi decided to
take Neko up on his offer.
Now...
I heard when you
went to Onigashima
to bring those
juvie losers down,
you used a slingshot,
is that true?
Yeah, that's right.
That's cool and all,
but you're only backing
her up not saving her butt...
If she got into a tight spot
and needed some real help...
you'd have to step it up
and fight, wouldn't you?
Yes, of course he would.
Don't you want to get ready
for when she truly needs you?
The most important thing
to remember in a fight
is to keep your cool.
If you snap,
you've lost control,
which means you'll likely
lose the upper hand as well.
You need to learn to maintain
your calm no matter what.
Brace yourself for your
first challenge, Ryoshi!
Wait...!
Can I ask you something?
Sure, what?
Why are you helping me?
What is all this about?
I have been wondering
the same thing.
All you need to worry
about is keeping up...
Now get ready!
Hey! What was that for?
Ha! For your own good.
My boots are steel-toed,
so it's really gonna hurt
if you don't dodge them.
He's quite strict for
such an adorable boy.
Yes, sir.
Okay... Here we go!
Yes, sir!
I'm home.
Hey, I made dinner.
Holy crap...
You mean you did all of this?
Yes; I figured it was
the least I could do...
I went ahead and folded
all the laundry as well.
And straightened up a bit.
Get out. Well, thank you, Reiko.
Sure thing.
So it's a girl from
Onigashima High School?
Yes.
I'm not saying there's
anything suspicious going on...
I just feel...
That it's better
to be safe than sorry.
Yes.
Hey...! I think I found her.
She has good grades.
Although it does appear
that her personality changes
drastically depending on the
guy she's dating at the time...
She's at Onigashima because one
of her boyfriends influenced her
to shoplift, and so she had
a run in with the police.
That's so sad.
Ringo...
why don't you monitor the
situation for right now...?
If her story is true, then we'll
probably be receiving a visit
from a few of those
guys who were chasing her.
No problem.
In case the worst happens
and those boys do show up,
it might be a good idea to pair
an additional person with her.
My instinct would
be to send Ryoshi...
...but he seems to be
busy somewhere else.
Finally, I'm back you guys!
It's a good thing
I left the curtains open.
This is fun...!
I love stakeouts!
True... but there's no need
to get overly excited about it.
All you need to
do is tell someone
if anything bad
happens to Ryoko, okay?
I won't let you down!
I'm like a hawk!
She is in total stakeout mode.
So?
Did you find anything out?
What makes you
think I could get info
the great Otogi Bank
president couldn't?
That's what I was afraid of.
You know... we're
assuming Shiro was the one
who was trying
to frame the bank,
but what exactly
is in it for him...?
I mean he's gotta have some
sort of motive, doesn't he?
Guess I've got no choice.
Thanks for all
your help... See ya!
And so... Time passed...
Slower for some
than for others...
And now it's the last day
of the thirty percent
off request campaign.
Don't tell me you
have another request?
In just a few days,
Otohime became the go-to beauty
guru (and kissing expert).
All right. Have fun!
The last day of the sale and
Litzy decides to disappear...
Isn't that just perfect.
Wait, did she just call
the president Litzy?
Huh... well that's odd.
Mimi is visiting the Bank,
which is pretty odd...
so we'll deal with Litzy later.
What can we help you with, Mimi?
Well, is Otohime here?
She's out on a request right
now, but can I help you?
Oh, yes, of course...!
One of my friends who
goes to Anderson asked me
to come up here for her;
she has a request.
You mean Anderson
Academy for Girls?
The academy they're speaking
of is basically a school
for the richiest
of rich girls...
which I'm sure
piques Alice's interest.
Yeah, I could do that.
So where are we going?
You need to learn
to concentrate...
If you're scared
of being looked at,
then your fear will distract
you from avoiding my kicks.
Thank you for fixing my window.
You're so sweet!
Taro has just
finished a request.
Now then, how would you like
to join me for a cup of tea?
Is something the matter?
No, no... I'm fine;
something just seems off.
Without Otohime showing
up out of the blue,
he looks kind of ridiculous.
Your girlfriend's
not coming, Urashima.
This is for you.
This is Otohime's purse.
You're gonna want to
come with us I think, pal.
Who are you!
Alice and Mimi have
come to meet the student
from Anderson Academy for Girls.
That was so easy!
It would've been
more fun with Otohime,
but as long as I get everyone
out of the Bank, I'm good...
I wonder what they're
gonna do to the place...
I can't wait to find out!
Is something the matter, Mimi?
Oh, no... I'm... just great.
Hey.
What the heck is
wrong with you guys?
Nice work.
You should leave now.
You're part of the Otogi Bank,
aren't you, four eyes...?
Get up, 'cause you're
coming with us.
You set this entire thing
up for them, didn't you?
They set me up, too!
Come on!
Damn it!
Get 'em!
And we're back with the girls...
They're making a
quick trip to the store
on the way to another request.
I'll just run in
and give this to Reiko
before we head out, kay?
I'll wait for you here.
Blocked caller...?
Yes? This is Ringo.
Ringo Akai.
Is that correct?
And who is this?!
Were you aware that Himeno
Shirayuki has seven siblings...?
What do you think she would do
if they disappeared one by one?
What...?! What are
you talking about...?
Ryoko, I...
Himeno Shirayuki's house...
She's Ringo's older sister
and has seven little siblings.
Coming!
Ringo, it's good to see you...!
How's it going?
Did you come to
play with the kids?
Himeno!
Is everyone okay?
Yes, they're fine...
See.
Thank goodness!
They're all safe.
Thank goodness.
Oh, no!
Reiko, I'm home...
I got that stuff you
asked me to bring you!
Wonderful, you're just in time.
How's it been?
Anything weird
happen around here?
No... Not yet.
Well, that's a relief...
I was planning on talking
to the school director
about your transfer tomorrow...
...so... it shouldn't
be much longer on that.
You're so nice.
"Ryoko Okami is nothing if
not a decent human being...
She's also extremely gullible."
You're just like
Shiro said you would be.
You lied!
I'm back, Alice!
Hello? Where'd Alice go?
Out on a request, maybe...?
I don't know; I just got
back from filling one myself.
Lizst!
What's wrong, Ringo?
It's... I think Ryoko and
Reiko have disappeared...
and Otsuu is missing, too!
I found this on the
floor of our room.
The Otogi Bank
has been scattered.
What will become of them now?!
Hey! Ryoshi!
What are you doing?!
Your friends need you!
The Otogi Bank is in
its greatest peril yet!
To be continued.
You're never going
to know what happens
unless you watch
the next episode.