A long, long time ago...
Actually, we're just
picking up the story
from the last episode...
Neko and Ryoshi
are still training.
Don't tell me
that's all you've got.
No sir!
Hello? Yeah, of course...
Ryoko? What do you mean?
The Otogi Bank's greatest
challenge continues!
Good, you're awake.
Reiko, how's tricks?
Sorry about all these lies,
but Shiro really wanted
me to bring you here.
Must be nice... all this love.
I can't say I'm not jealous.
Don't forget to be gentle
with our guest, Reiko.
This is the
Onigashima High School
student council president...
Shiro Hitsujikai.
No need to fret, my sweet.
I'm not quite ready for you.
What're you trying to prove?
Merely that I enjoy watching
the misery of others.
In addition to abducting you...
I thought it might be
fun to play with everyone
from the Otogi Bank
for a little while.
Though I did think that
it would be harder than this.
Go to hell.
Now we just have
to wait for Ryoshi.
The fun is just beginning.
Nobody else has the
motive and capability.
From what I can tell the only
logical conclusion is that
Shiro's the one
conducting this operation.
He knew exactly how
we'd react at every turn
and we just let him take them!
It's time to call in some of
those favors we banked
the past couple of days.
If he's smart he'll be
holding each of our people
in different locations.
So let's get to work.
Move it! Come on!
It's a dead end...
This way!
Hey!
Damn it!
Where could they have gone?
Well don't just stand there.
Look around for them!
Let's go.
It looks like we
finally lost them.
This is all my fault, Alice.
I'm really sorry.
They just made it
seem so innocent...
How can I make this right?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's just that you're
surprisingly honest.
There is nothing
surprising about it.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Now are you sure that
Ryoko's in Onigashima?
Shiro had her taken
to try to lure us out...
That's gotta be it.
So now... he'll be waiting for
us somewhere he knows I'd look.
Inside!
Taro got snagged by them too.
Taro, thank goodness!
Otohime!
Lucky for her all
they did was tie her up.
I hope you guys are ready
for what's coming next.
Easy Champ, we're not the
ones you should worry about.
A bikini ambush!
Cut to a creepy abandoned
factory somewhere
on the outskirts of town.
You're stuck here girlie.
This should be fun.
Where you going?
I've got a surprise for you.
Ta dah!
No.. I won't do it!
A maid would never
wear a nurse's uniform!
It's like Otsuu's
own personal hell!
Oh please, let us
touch you, Taro...
You're soooo adorable!
Is Taro actually blushing?
Oh boy... it's hard to choose...
You're all so darn beautiful.
Taro I'm here...
If Taro doesn't love
me like he used to
then I don't have anything
left to live for anyway...
They can kill me...
That'd be a waste of the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen.
You know I never mean
to make you worry...
...my sweet...
Oh my Taro...
I thought these chicks
were gonna break him!
Let's get him!
That's my boy.
Heh... looks fun...
I should help.
A woman's jealousy is blacker
than the deepest ocean chasm.
You may all begin screaming now.
Okay... never make
Otohime angry.
You've been warned.
Meanwhile, Otsuu is
facing fashion torture!
Will she be forced to
shed her maid costume?
Will she? Will she?
That's enough!
Oh yeah? And who
the hell are you?
Pee-ons don't get
to know my name.
Otsuu.
Let's go!
Thank you so much
for coming to save me.
I need you to put these on.
Majolika, not you too?!
No... Come on!
And so Otsuu's fashion
nightmare continues.
Back to Alice and Mimi who
are not out of the woods yet.
Alice is more of a tech nerd so
running isn't really her thing.
Can you still walk?
I don't know.
You do know it's
over now, right?
Good... now sleep tight.
Huh...? Wait, who are you?
Aw, geez...
Sure took you
long enough, Litzy!
Whoa, did you just say 'Litzy'?!
I mean... sure took you
long enough, President!
Yes, sorry about that.
Takes awhile for me
to get into character.
Plus, I couldn't take
them all on at once
so I had to pick my moments.
If they figured
me out I'd be dead.
Where's your help?
Didn't anyone
else come with you?
They've all got their own
problems to deal with...
But Ryoshi...
Well...
He's running out of time
and he's got quite a
battle ahead of him.
In the next half,
we'll storm the fortress!
I hope you know...
you'll be toast
after this little stunt.
And do you think
I care about that?
It's worth it if
I get to watch you
and all your friends
get torn into pieces.
My bonus is seeing all your
hopes dying in front of you...
Well, well, now
what do we have here?
It seems your Prince has come.
That's a big crowd.
Prudence suggests we
wait for reinforcements.
Don't be such a wuss.
I know that sexy voice.
It's Momoko and her pack
of wild breastlings...
Which now includes
the Tonda brothers!
What are you guys doing here?
We made a lot of requests on
that thirty percent off week--
better start paying you back.
We'll lend our helpiness.
Helpiness?
Debts repaidified!
Repaidified?
Just leave it to us!
That third guy is normal.
Whatever Momo asks...
Even through fire
and damnation...
It doesn't matter!
We'll repay her
for her dumplings!
Is dumplings too subtle
a metaphor? Breasts!
Things are really
starting to heat up now.
That's right.
You still got nothin'!
Let's get 'em!
Yeah!
So that thirty percent
off sale seems like
a real bargain about now.
It's like the President knew
they were going
to need the back up.
Look at the doors!
We're the holdingest
brothers in the world!
Hurryupitude!
I can't take them seriously
when they talk like that.
Time to save Okamisan, Ryoshi!
Yes, sir!
Yeah... just your
normal triplets.
Not so fast!
I'll cut through all the fat.
I don't think so.
Sorry we're a
little late, my friends.
And as for all the rest
of you Oni delinquents...
Heh... better run.
Uhhh!
Ah, yes. Taro in gentleman mode.
I'm sure he and Otohime had
quite the make-up session
after being trapped together.
Jeez. I can't beat up
boys twice my size.
Stop that! Get your
hands off of me!
Wow Mimi... Nice job there.
Yeah, well don't
you get all mushy.
Running away would
be totally spineless.
I didn't want to ruin
my reputation, that's all.
Right.
Now boys, go get 'em!
Yeah!
Ow, my spleen.
Ryoshi, you'll have to go
find Okamisan on your own.
Right!
Ryoshi...
do you remember when you asked
me why I wanted to train you?
I can tell you now.
Three years ago, I had
a chance to save a girl,
but I ran away instead.
There were some people after
me and she tried to stop them.
But I abandoned her...
and I never looked back.
After that... I felt
like such a complete jerk.
But how could I waste
her sacrifice like that?
She gave everything to save me.
I decided right then
and there that I needed
to hone my fighting skills
so maybe one day
I could defend her honor.
All my training has
led up to this moment...
...but none of
it matters anymore.
Because of you.
Because you're the one
who has to save her.
Ryoko...
Get out of here, Ryoshi!
My name's Neko, and trust me,
after today you won't forget it.
I think completely
destroying you
one by one is the purrfect way
to spend a little time,
wouldn't you agree?
Exterminate!
Let's do this!
Get out of here...!
You have to save Okamisan...!
Go!
Ryoko!
Ryoshi!
Ah, we've been waiting
for you Ryoshi...
Though I did expect you to
arrive much sooner than this.
I'm here!
He's blinded by his anger.
Shiro don't!
Hey, it's no fun if I let
you use your little toy.
Yep, only one way to show me
how far you're willing to go
for the girl you claim to love.
Oh I'll show you all right.
I'd do anything for her...
Oh wow... That is just adorable!
Ryoshi!
How does it feel?
Must be awful to be humiliated
in front of the girl you love...
...just awful.
I'm sorry...
You're the one
who has to save her.
You've never given up...
...even when you were
surrounded on all sides...
...nothing was going to tear
you away from protecting her.
You were able to see
what Okamisan needed
and then you did it
without taking credit...
While the best that
I could do was abandon her.
You're saying the
girl you left was...
It was Okamisan.
But I figured there
was no possible way
you could protect her
without somebody's help...
So I decided to train you.
Ryoshi, I need you to
think about the reason
you want to protect Okamisan.
My reason?
That's it...
...connecting to those
feelings will give you
the strength you need
to protect her from
absolutely anything.
I know you can do it.
Okamisan needs you!
No!
Come on, you're not giving
up on me already are you?
Leave him alone.
You...
You can't...
...stop me from...
...protecting Ryoko!
The most important thing in
a fight is to keep your cool.
You need to learn to maintain
your calm, no matter what.
I can't believe
you actually hurt me.
Now it's time to make you pay
for your insolence, little boy.
Can't we all just get along?
You're okay!
Yeah...
You certainly have put us
through the wringer today
but don't worry;
your punishment will
be swift and thorough.
Are you attempting
to threaten me?
You know, for a club of
your considerable reputation,
I would think bringing adults
into this was beneath you...
Such a pity.
Don't be silly, we seem
to be fine on our own.
You made the decision
to pick this fight
with the Otogi Bank...
And we'll be sure
to make you pay.
You'd best be ready.
Right, and on that little note.
Wait a sec!
We're going.
That is such a drag.
I had so many fun things
that I wanted to do to her.
Don't you worry.
The more they enjoy it now,
the more it will hurt
when I finally destroy them.
That will just make it
so much more delicious
when I tear them
away from each other.
Now I know today wasn't easy.
But your support made all
the difference in the world,
and I want to thank you.
I'm sorry you got
dragged into this.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
You can't handle
everything by yourself.
Isn't that the reason for the
Otogi Bank in the first place?
Our motto is "help those who
need it without any question."
Thank you.
Right, that's it
for today, then!
Very good work everyone!
Yeah! Congratulations!
Mimi, I just wanted
to say thank you
for lending a hand
the way you did.
You certainly came
through for us in the end.
Well, I started off by
making things worse for you
so I figured I had
to make up for it.
I'm really sorry
for how I was before.
I don't know why I was
acting rude to everyone...
But it was totally beyond
wrong, I know that...!
I hope you'll forgive me.
Of course.
I wasn't the nicest
person to be around
during the beauty
pageant either if I recall.
I apologize as well.
Then let's call it even, okay?
I love it when people
learn to get along.
I would say your
assistance was invaluable.
Thank you so much.
It's nothingIt helped
me more than you know...
In fact, I feel like
I can sleep peacefully now.
Don't be modest, Neko.
Thanks a lot for
coming back for me.
M'lady.
Good for you... Puss in Boots.
Well, I guess I might as
well get in some exercise
on the way home...
Goodbye, all.
Take care.
Yeah.
See you later.
Well, Ryoshi...
I didn't run away.
Not this time.
And neither did you.
Boy somebody we know sure did
a lot of saving
today, didn't they.
Not really.
It was mostly Neko
and everyone else.
You should think about giving
your hero a little reward...
Maybe you could put on some
fluffy wolf ears and a tail,
and give a sexy howl for him!
I will never do that, got it?
How about showing him
your undergarments?
Rejected.
Okay, maybe just a bikini, then?
In his dreams.
Very well, a one piece
but you have to be wet.
Now you're just being stupid.
I'll take whatever...
You'd look good
in anything Ryoko.
And the three of them go home,
happy as they've ever been.
Later that night...
Alice has fallen fast asleep,
exhausted from all her running.
Good night to you,
my dear cousin Alice.
Sweet dreams.
You know Ryoshi said he
was training this whole time.
What?
Neko helped him
with his fighting skills
because he wanted to be strong.
Strong enough to protect you.
Maybe you could do
some training in order
to get stronger
for him in return.
Okay... Well then let me
get your opinion on something.
Oh what a beautiful day.
Oh wow... I feel
great this morning!
You know that
spending time with you
is all the reward
Ryoshi needs, Ryoko.
I know...
surprisingly wolves sometimes
take the advice
of their friends...
so she went on a walk
with him and the dogs.
You okay?
Yes, I'm perfectly fine.
Well... that's good.
It seemed like you'd
been avoiding me
more than usual lately.
It's like a dream being able
to hang out with you like this.
I want you to know I'll
always be here to protect you.
Uh, Ryoshi...?
The whole getting
kidnapped thing...
I mean...
For a wolf, this is
unusually forthright... But...
Don't look at me!
Nothing ever changes.
Keep talking Ryoko...
...you were about to say
something weren't you?
Once again, you have totally
blown the mood you screw-up!
On that note, all's
well that ends well...
Oh, I should let you know
that our next
episode is the last one.
It's about a sad little girl...
...a sad little match girl.