A long time ago in
a faraway village...
Okay, it wasn't
really that long ago
and more of a suburb really...
Anyway... town
called Otogibana City
and school called
Otogi Academy, here we go...
The Academy director
was a raunchy old coot
named Ranpu Aragami...
He was also a member
of the Aragami Family,
which calls the shots in town.
He created a club called the
Otogi Academy Mutual
Student Aid Association.
Also known as the Otogi Bank.
The purpose of this club
is to help out students
who need assistance,
in return for favors which
are to be repaid later...
And that is where
our story begins...
So, Ryoshi...
how are things going?
It's been a week now, hasn't it?
Oh, uh... yes, sir.
You know you have gotten so
much better at being looked at.
Thanks; it's been hard,
but I think I'm at least used
to you guys looking at me...
...well... for the most part.
Staaaaare.
Please don't stare!!
Ryoshi has a condition
called ophthalmophobia.
It's a hilarious fear
of being stared at.
Nice going Alice!
She's used to
dealing with Majolika.
It looks like he's just as
much of a screw up as ever.
Seriously.
Now don't forget about
yesterday's request.
He did do a pretty
good job of shielding you.
You have to admit... Didn't he?
Yeah.
True... I suppose
that didn't totally suck.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
No. I'm fine.
I'm just sorry
I couldn't help any more.
He's kind of a delicate shield,
but I guess it's better
than no shield at all.
Just so you know,
you would make things
a whole lot more
interesting for me
if you'd consider Ryoshi
as a potential love match.
No way!
Sorry, Ringo... but...
It's not gonna happen.
How utterly disappointing.
It's okay. I'm still happy.
Your companion,
your shield,
I'm good with being
whatever it takes...
Just as long as I get
to be close to you, Ryoko.
Kay.
I'm off to the gym...
See ya later.
Good job today.
Have a great workout!
'Kay, I guess I'll
see you tomorrow, Ringo.
Um...
Wait, do you have a minute?
It's not a big deal...
There's just something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Oh... Sure.
Ask away.
What is it about Ryoko
that caught your fancy?
Oh... well... uh...
I, um...
Please tell me; I'm begging you.
Okay.
Well she's cool and
she's good at boxing
and she's kinda got
this wild girl thing
going on which is nice.
I think you should know
that "wild thing" part
isn't very flattering
to say to a girl.
Oh... No, I guess it
wouldn't be, would it...?
But, to be honest, there is one
other thing that caught my eye.
I'd already been watching her
a while before I noticed it.
It's when she's acting tough
even though she's scared...
...or is strong and
weak at the same time.
There's like this
sense of disconnection
between her appearance
and what she's feeling.
It's almost like I'm getting
to see a bit of the real Ryoko.
There's more...
She's always striving
to be so strong.
I can't help but appreciate
that part about her, too.
Well, that's delightful,
though I feel a bit
embarrassed for asking.
What...?
Oh... I'm sorry--I
didn't mean to.
On the other hand,
at least I can relax now.
What do you mean by that?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
Ringo take a hike.
You're just a girl!
Yes, I see now.
This could come in handy.
The president is
unusually serious...
How disconcerting.
Look at the little
Akita puppies!
Aren't they adorable?!
Apparently, someone
doesn't want anyone else
to see her loving
on some puppies.
I won't hurt you... see?
Aww, she's a sucker
for dumb animals!
Speaking of...
Oh, but you're a
good puppy too, huh?
Ryoko...
What are you doing here?
I was picking up groceries.
They belong to you?
Ryoshi brought these
two lovely ladies
with him from the countryside...
Not that it matters,
but his uncle named them.
This is Elizabeth and Francoise.
I've never seen them take
to someone like that before.
They're hunting dogs,
so they're not very social...
You must like dogs, huh?
No, they were just acting like
they wanted to be pets, so...
I mean, so.
I think they know there's
something in the air.
You see what I mean?
Still though;
they never do that!
Yeah, whatever...
I'll see you tomorrow.
Right, okay!
I'll see you tomorrow!
He's so cute...
Look at him smiling...
He's not used to seeing a sweet
side to our little Wolfie-poo.
Later that night...
You'll never guess
what dear Ryoshi told me
on the way home
from school today.
What's that?
He told me what it was about you
that he found so
terribly attractive.
Did you ask him that?
He said it took a
while to figure out,
but eventually he
sensed the disconnection
between how you
act and how you feel.
And then he told me he
liked you because of how hard
you work to try to
appear strong all the time.
If you ask me,
he's fairly sharp.
Night.
And the next day, after class...
Shopping?
Yes...
The President had
a sudden inspiration...
...something about
improving our equipment.
Incidentally, the club funding
comes from the director,
meaning the Otogi Bank
is quite well off financially.
Why would he want to come along
when he can just
have us go for him?
I'm kind of worried...
I left Ryoshi in charge of the
public office... with Taro.
If you ask me,
they could both stand
to have a little more
testosterone in their lives.
His name is Taro Urashima.
You'll remember him
from a brief appearance
in the last episode...
That said, he's actually
a year older than Ryoshi
and the other club members.
Um... so, uh...
You, uh... transferred
here early this semester?
I mean, that's what I heard...
So was there a reason for that?
Oh yeah... a couple of 'em.
Oh... okay.
Yaoi fans, this
one's not into men.
Sorry.
Oh...! It looks like
someone's come to visit!
Here; this is for you.
Thank you so much.
It's just some tea.
Aw, lil' Ryoshi...
You're still not used to
dealing with people, are you?
Is Okamisan here by chance?
She's out shopping right now,
but, if you want me to,
I don't mind calling
her if you want me to.
Uhh... No, um...
You are simply
enchanting, my dear...
For someone as
beautiful as you...
I would listen to
requests all day long.
Unlike men, when it
comes to "the ladies,"
Taro finds himself
simply spellbound...
However...
Taro?
I'm curious; what
exactly are you doing?
This always ends up happening.
No. You don't understand.
She needs help.
If you're feeling lonely,
darling, I can cure you.
No! Let me go...! Come on...!
Can't we talk
about this? Please!
This way... Hurry up!
As I said before...
I'll leave what they're
doing up to your imagination.
...call Ryoko for you.
Ryoshi decided
that was a good time
to go ahead and call Okamisan...
Everyone else is
still out shopping.
So... What exactly
is your request?
I, uh...
I was sorta hoping...
Well, I hear you're really
good at tough requests...
So I came to ask you...
My ex-boyfriend was always
pretty violent towards me...
In fact, that's the
reason I broke up
with him in the first place--
but he keeps trying
to get back together
So this is about love?
Requests like this
are pretty common;
we get them all the time.
He said if I... met with
him... he'd let me go.
This is where he wanted to meet.
Triangle Park, in
the southern district.
I think he might try to force
me to go out with him again...
I'm scared.
What do you want to do?
Only one thing to do...
We need to head over to the Park
and see if we can figure
out what he's planning.
Thank you!
You don't know how
much help that will be!
I promise I'll repay my debt!
Do you wanna come with us?
Totally up to you.
No... I don't really
want to see him again...
I'll just let you
handle it, if that's okay.
That's fine...
We'll contact you
when we're done.
Thanks; I appreciate it.
He should be here somewhere.
Well, I don't
see anybody around.
Hey...
You're that
Okamisan, aren't you?
This is bad...
They're from Onigashima.
Ryoshi and Okamisan are
surrounded by delinquents...!
What will become of them?!
These guys are thugs from
Onigashima High School...
You may not know this,
but the Oni part of Onigashima
technically means demon.
An accurate description.
You know this isn't
Onigashima territory.
Why are you here?
In Otogibana City, schools
have associated territories.
In Otogi Academy territory,
you don't normally find
these kinds of punk kids.
Go back to the office, Ryoshi...
You need to hurry; you're only
gonna get in my way here...
Against this many people,
you won't be able to
shield me from much...
Now's your last chance. Go.
No way!
Get out of here, now!
No...
I won't...
I'm not gonna leave
you behind, okay?!
No!
You should have listened
to your little girlfriend
instead of acting
like you could hang--
Go to hell!
Hey!
You'll pay for this!
Let go of me you son of a bitch!
Meanwhile, at the Otogi Bank...
They're taking forever.
All the shoppers
have finally returned.
If they were just meeting
with some typical stalker guy,
don't you think they'd
have come back by now?
They have, I saw
the requestor earlier
and she said they'd both
come back together...
Perhaps Ryoko
had to go out again?
Ryoshi!
They've got Ryoko.
Hey.
Why do you lie to everyone?
I don't.
That's not true; your
being strong is a lie.
I am not lying about
that--I am strong!
No. You're simply a wolf in
wolf's clothing, aren't you?
You have to face it...
You've been lying
ever since that day,
pretending you'll be
fine all on your own.
I'm not pretending anything.
The truth is you really
do want to rely on someone.
Rely on someone?
I can't afford to do that.
Otherwise the same
thing will happen again.
It would seem she's tied up
in an abandoned factory...
My guess is they're
in Onigashima Territory.
Look who's finally awake.
Man.
You really did a
number on us... huh?
Don't get mad; I was just trying
to beat some of the ugly out--
What did you just say?
Bitch... Say it again.
Calm down.
Don't hurt her too much,
or you know the boss
is gonna hurt you, too.
You're pathetic.
Spineless cowards who
can only obey their master.
This is a wolf, desperately
wearing wolf's clothing.
Howl while you can...
...the boss'll be
here soon enough.
Yes... Right...
Thank you for the information.
The requestor was being
threatened the whole time...
They sent her here to find
a way to lure Ryoko out
where they could
get control of her.
Does she have any idea
where Ryoko was taken?
No, she doesn't know.
Good work on this, Alice.
Now, why don't we gather
everyone together quickly
so we can split up
and start looking for her.
No, wait!
I think I can take care of this.
I'll be fine. I can get away.
Stay calm... just stay calm.
You're wasting your time.
Ooooh, the Onigashima
boss has appeared.
So, it turns out the
mighty Okamisan
isn't all that mighty after all.
What kind of guys
gang up on a girl...?
Seems to me the Onigashima boss
isn't that concerned
about having a fair fight.
I'm scared.
Yeah, that's only
'cause someone told me
you were too tough to
beat in a normal fight...
He was right, too,
but I think getting our hands
on you made it all worthwhile...
Don't you?
Someone?
Like who, because, surprise,
I don't know any of
your loser friends.
Believe it or not, Princess
Ryoko, you are awfully famous...
Now, if you don't
give me any trouble,
I promise not to hurt you.
The wolf's clothing is on
the verge of being torn off!
Someone... save me!
Hey!
Got it, boss.
Yeah, hello?
Is Ryoko safe?
Safe? Who the hell are you?
I'm the one asking
if Ryoko is safe.
Gimme that.
Sorry to interrupt,
but we were just about
to have a little fun here...
Feel free to listen in,
or, if you want,
maybe I can send you
some pictures later.
No need. You won't get that far.
If you want I can
send some pictures
of what your stupid
faces look like.
Ryoshi.
Guys...
Heads up!
They're shooting something!
Ryoko!
You stuck it out pretty well.
Ringo...
You found me!
I had nothing to do with it.
Hey, girls; when
did you get here?
They're the ones
who led us to you;
they picked up on your scent.
Thank you...!
So what's gotten into Ryoshi?
He took us all by
surprise, actually.
And you know something,
I don't think he's
quite the weakling
we all took him for at first.
Damn it! Where the
hell is this guy??
Ryoshi is holding
pachinko balls.
Together with his slingshot,
they make quite the
fearsome hunting weapon.
They're also
useful for attacking
from hard to see places.
A perfect fit for
our darling screw up.
The President's
the one who saw it...
He noticed something
when he was reviewing
the video of you
and that stalker guy...
Apparently, Ryoshi has
been using a slingshot
since he was a boy
and is quite skilled with it.
Whoa.
You mean that was him?
Incidentally,
in the first episode,
he was using a wad of gum
he found in his pants.
Yes, that was Ryoshi, but
because he didn't come out
from hiding to try and help you,
he didn't think it
was worth mentioning.
Isn't it funny;
he assumed it didn't matter!
Pretty funny. Yeah...
Well... might as well join in.
I figured you might say that...
Here you go!
Custom Made Kitty Knuckles!
Allow me to explain...
These Custom Made Kitty
Knuckles have a mechanism
which functions like a stun gun,
delivering an electric current
when they punch something.
Now she'll huff and she'll puff
and she'll knock
those jerks down!
Okamisan in the front!
Ryoshi covering the back!
What a magnificently
coordinated play!
My body is light...
I can move easily...
I can rely on someone
covering my back...
I could get used to this.
Oh my goodness, I just hate
it when things get violent.
The rest of the
Otogi Bank staff appears!
Don't you tell anyone
I touched a man.
The sophisticated,
yet rather conceited Taro.
And, Otohime is
spellbound, of course.
Adorable!
They look like they're
in a little fight relay...
They work like a
well oiled machine.
That kinda tickled.
He's terrifying...
And on top of that, he's huge!
Would you stay still
for a damn second?
I'll kill you!
Now!
Ding. Ding. Ding. Knockout.
Great job as usual.
Thanks... but it
wasn't just me... Right?
Amazing coordination!
Oh no. I think that was love.
Tale as old as time!
True as it can be!
That isn't it at all!
Someone doth protest too much.
Ryoko!
Get off of me!
I just love strong girls.
I knew you had to
be the one for me.
Hey!
You better let her go right now.
Let her go
Ryoshi!
I'll protect her...
No matter what.
You wanna do this man to man?
Sounds like fun.
Ryoko!
Nice...
You're not too bad, kid.
Are we done yet?
Little bastard!
I'll teach you to mess with me!
No way... I'm a hunter!
I told you to
stay away from her.
Oh, Ryoshi...
Who's a strong little fighter?
Wow, he actually
pulled off cool there
for just a second, didn't he?
Yeah...
Uh... I mean; just
forget what I just said.
My stars, there's no
reason to be embarrassed.
Whatever; I'm not.
All right, kids...
I think it's time to go.
I wonder...
Why on earth were
Onigashima students
targeting Ryoko
in the first place?
Good question.
I believe this may call
for some additional research.
I see more troubles
in their future.
Oh, you're such good
puppies; yes you are!
I'm so proud of you both,
you did such a
great job today...
You're my little heroes.
You are so amazing.
Stop staring!
He's still everybody's
favorite screw up, isn't he?
Back to normal already.
Yes, and it's such a shame, too.
They're perfect for each other.
Geez, he could at least
try to not be pathetic.
Ryoko...
Aren't you going to reward
him for putting his life
on the line like that?
Hell nah.
It looks like it's
going to be a long time
before Okamisan takes off
that wolf clothing of hers...
I suppose I'll just let today's
story end on that note...
Alls well that ends well.
Next time... an epic race...
Look out for
hot chicks in swimsuits!