A long, long time ago...
I don't have to say that
part again after today, do I?
Machiko Himura is
delivering newspapers.
She's like the Little Match Girl
without the grandmother...
...and hopefully without
the dying at the end.
We'll see!
Okay, I'm finished...
So all I gotta do now is head
home and make dad a bento box...
I guess I can just
skip lunch today...
it's been slim this month.
Come on girls... Let's go.
Wait! You're not
supposed to walk me!
Hey, I think that
guy is in my class...
What's his name?
Ryoshi's classmates never
can remember him, can they?
What does that say about him?
Look at that house...
Ugh... dumb bourgeoisie.
Wait a sec.
Expensive looking
dogs and a big mansion?
That's a good girl;
I bet you want a good
girl treat don't you?
I wonder...
Could he be my meal ticket...?
That's brilliant!
Oh, take me with you!
Later, on a day when Machiko's
destiny hung in the balance...
I'm late! I'm late!
Well, that was on purpose.
Oh no; I just
tripped everywhere!
She's got her
name on her panties!
You saw?
Well, I guess
you could say that;
I didn't really have a
choice about it, though.
Naughty.
I don't think she's
right in the head.
I totally made the
perfect first impression...!
Get ready world!
I'm gonna be happy
and worry free!
Do you think she realizes
everyone's staring at her?
Hi Ryoshi!
How are you this morning?
Hey, what's up
with the long face...?
You screw up again?
You know Machiko?
She was running and yelling
about how she was late
and then she tried to tackle me.
Wow, talk about a
cliché dating move...
Next comes the skirt flip...
Let me guess, you saw her
panties, and she acted coy?
Yeah...
How did you know that;
it was so weird.
Oh my gosh!
I ran into you earlier...!
It must be destiny that
brought us together once again!
Well... That or we're
just in the same class...?
Whaddaya think?
Odd.
Look, I'm not good at
being subtle, okay...?
So no more beating
around the damn bush!
Ryoshi Morino!
Um, yes?
I've decided we should
eventually get married!
Well, that's not subtle.
Please stop looking at me!
Nice job.
A little bit unexpected.
Mostly because you
do already have Ryoko.
What are you talking about?
What's your relationship
with my one true love?
Your what?
My one true love; hello, we're
gonna get married eventually...
Duh... like I said,
what are you to him?
We're, uh...
We're just friends, that's all.
She says while not
making eye contact.
Wonderful!
Now I don't have to worry
about your heart being broken.
Babe... we are free
to fall thoroughly
and madly in love
with each other!
Wait, what?
Hey, hold on a second...!
I'm sorry, but I think
you might be moving
a little to fast for me.
You know what they say,
babe; "love happens fast"!
Nobody says that!
Isn't this an interesting
development?
Looks like Little Red
is plotting, as always.
Well...
You're quite the ladies
man, aren't you Ryoshi?
Yeah.
Who would have expected
two people in this world
to have such commendable taste?
I mean.
Why, Ryoshi...?
He's such a weirdo.
Yes, thank you
for pointing that out.
Oh, look. Speak of the devil.
Please you guys!
Tell her I'm not here!
How may we assist you, Machiko?
I want the bank
to lend me Ryoshi
for the entire day tomorrow!
And would you mind
if I asked you what for?
To go out on a date...!
This is the only
way I can think of
to get my future hubby
to go out with me!
Ryoko, what do you
think I should do?
Who cares--do what you want.
I think Ryoshi will go.
How does he always
get dragged into this stuff?
Your request is accepted.
Yeah? Hooray!
Tell him to meet me at
9AM in the park tomorrow!
Because... I love you,
more than anything
else in the world, Ryoko.
I'll always be here
to protect you, okay?
Get out of my damn head!
Ryoko... violence
is never the answer.
I've got a meal ticket.
Dad, I'm home!
I guess he hasn't made
it back yet tonight.
Wow. Looks like she's got
it rougher than I thought.
She is thoroughly twitterpated!
I bet she doesn't even realize
why she's upset right now...
Love is so mysterious.
And Ringo is so ridiculous...
She's loving the
Ryoko suffering thing.
Situation?
Machiko's obsession...
She hasn't spoken a word
to Ryoshi before and now,
out of the blue, she's
suddenly in love with him?
It sounds suspicious;
I think something else
must be going on here.
Perhaps you should check
it out, as a friend, I mean.
I don't really have a choice...
I'll follow them
around tomorrow.
Look, a passive aggressive wolf
helping out a friend in need...
It's sweet, isn't it?
The following day...
Apparently, Otogi only
has one dating park...
She doesn't seem
like a bad person, but...
Okay, babe...
Tell me all about yourself;
I wanna know everything.
We barely know each other,
and that needs to change stat.
Yeah.
I mean, like, what kind
of house do you live in?
Is it way big and full
of expensive furniture?
Better yet, tell me how
much you make in a year.
I'm sorry I wasn't lis---
Word to the wise:
for a first date,
that question is
highly inappropriate.
Okay... now to make sure he
can't help but fall for me!
Boy, it sure is hot today.
Golly... She is so forward!!
Does she put her name
on all of her underwear?
Something the matter?
Yes, No. I mean nothing, no.
No man can resist the girls!
Here it is!
My deluxe bento!
Dig in, babe;
I made it all for you.
Ryoshi is understandably
on guard.
However, I doubt
this apple's poisoned.
Oh, my...!
She made him a
lunch all by herself.
That girl knows how to
impress a guy, doesn't she?
Anybody can make a stupid bento.
I spent a lot of
money making this thing.
I can't let any
of it go to waste.
Machiko actually
skipped dinner yesterday
so she'd have enough money
to make the bento for Ryoshi...
Now she's closing in on
her patented "ah" attack...
How will he defend himself
against such strategy?!
I'm good!
Damn it!
He's a tough nut to crack.
But I'm not done yet!
So, when were done here,
let's go on a boat ride!
We won't be able to
hear what they're saying
from this far away...
Do you want to watch or shall I?
You can look...
I don't really care
what's going on anyway.
She obviously cares...
Why does she keep denying it?
I'll tell you exactly
what's happening...
Okay, here we go,
they're both getting
onto the boat right now...
My stars, they're
passionately embracing!
Gimmie that!
It's rocking! Help me, baby!
Love me! Marry me!
Everyone realizes she's
doing that on purpose, right?
You have to sit down first,
and then it'll stop
rocking, I swear!
I'd say she's controlling
this date quite well.
Ryoshi's surprisingly easy
for her to push around...
Do you think he'll make out
with her if she requests it?
And who's rocking
the boat now, Red?
So, you grew up in the
country, is that right?
That's right...
I was around a lot
of elderly people,
and I didn't really have
any friends my own age.
That's how I developed
ophthalmophobia.
Oh.
But Ryoko's been a big help...
I mean the whole
Otogi Bank has helped me
get so much better
than I used to be.
He won't talk about another girl
in front of the one he's with...
He's surprisingly sensitive!
Your turn--where do you live?
What's your home like?
Mine?
Yeah.
I'm over the boat!
Let's go somewhere else!
Keep an eye out;
Machiko might be planning
to make her any moment now...
Sure you're still
okay with this?
So what's up,
where are we headed now?
Let me worry about that.
My apartment might
be a little cramped,
but I'm sure I'll be able
to get some sort of action
inducing mood going.
She is determined
to seal the deal!
A large white house,
a large white puppy,
champagne by the pool...
Someone has delusions
about being rich.
This is it!
I deserve to be happy!
Are you okay?
I am so sorry to
do this to you, babe;
but something just came up.
Don't worry though, okay?
I'll make it up to you;
swearsey... See ya!
Yeah, all right then...
See ya later.
Well that was... weird.
Hey!
Uh oh...
Looks like
Machiko's in danger...
To be continued
in the second half!
What gives...?
Dad got this month's
payment from me,
so you should have
your money by now.
Yeah, about dear old dad...
He uh, never did show up today.
I bet he took the money and ran.
No... He couldn't.
Which is why we came
here looking for you...
Somebody's gotta
pay what he owes...
Cough it up, little girl.
Yeah, or else...
They do not sound like
very nice gentlemen.
A normal life.
Is that really
too much to ask for?
What the hell?
Let's go, now!
What was that?
I dunno, but let's
go after them!
For the moment at least,
Machiko and Ryoshi have escaped.
We should be okay here for
at least a little bit longer.
Those guys seemed pretty
scary back there, huh?
What, did I come at a bad time?
No. Not at all; you saved me.
Thanks a lot, baby.
I'll have to find
a way to repay you.
Nah, don't worry about it.
My pleasure.
I know...
You could be my first...!
I mean, if you wanted.
Highly inappropriate!
Did, you, mean...?
Yes, of course I did...
Actually, my plan this
whole time was to find a way
to seal the proverbial
deal with you so we'd be able
to get married because you
are the perfect meal ticket.
I know that sounds
pretty terrible...
But see, my dad owes those
loan shark guys a lot of money.
He took the cash I earned
for this month's
payment and ran off...
It seems like my entire life
I've been repaying his debts.
I thought if I could get close
to you, then I'd be safe...
I'm so sorry.
You've gotta be so mad at me...
I lied to you and got you
involved in my stupid problems.
I just don't know how
I'm gonna find the money
to make this payment again...
What do you think
I should do, Ryoshi?
Are you saying you want my help?
I'm asking you if
you want me to help.
You're mad...
I can't blame you...
What do you want me to say?
I'm mad... but not mad at you...
Hello...? I need a favor, so
I'm making a formal request...
It has to be immediate,
like today...
If someone asks,
this concerns Machiko.
Okay, I can email
you the details...
Yes... Yes, if you could,
please; thanks a lot.
Um, who were you talking to?
We'll talk later.
Hey, punk; do you
know who we are?
We're not the guys
you wanna mess with!
I'll try to remember
that this time.
Oh! Ryoshi is armed with
his pachinko balls...!
I don't think those mobsters
know what they're in for!
Ryoko?
Alright you dirtbags,
who wants a piece of me?
Take this!
Okamisan!
Ryoshi has always fought from
behind the scenes up until now.
He's getting brave!
They're amazing.
Ryoko and Ryoshi have
been fighting together
for quite a while now,
so it's no surprise that
they make a fairly good team.
They sure do.
He's so awesome.
I was so scared;
I didn't know what to do...
The bad men came from out
of nowhere and attacked us!
Little Red Dramatic Hood.
Um... Okamisan...? Thank you.
Yeah, sure thing.
So, what exactly were you
guys doing out here anyway?
Nothing. We were just
in the neighborhood!
Certainly can't tell them
you were following them.
Yes, hello?
That's perfect...
We'll be right there...
Good news!
Everything's been taken care of!
Here we are at Okashi Manor.
And everyone's out in
full force to support Machiko!
All right, then!
Let's give a warm
welcome to Okashi Manor's
newest resident
Machiko Himura...!
Cheers, you guys!
Cheers!
I want to thank you for
everything you've done...
I can't believe
you paid the debt
and gave me a place to live.
Please, don't worry about it.
After all, our motto is
something about helping people.
Besides we'll ask you
to repay the favor one day.
Delicious!
Hey, babe...
Can I talk to you
for a minute... please?
Yeah, sure.
I wonder what that's all about.
Who cares...?
It's not like it's
any of my business.
Hey, where are you going?
To the bathroom.
She just lied to me!
Yes, I think she did.
Thank you...
I just wanted to
make sure I said that.
I didn't do it all
by myself, you know...
You had a whole lot of
great people in your corner.
Well, nothing against them,
but if you hadn't tried to help
first, no one else would have.
It's you who deserves
all the credit in my book.
Well... you're welcome
then, I guess.
You were really unbelievable
to watch today, too, babe.
Listen... about us...
Um, Ryoko is amazing, so...
Sure she looks
tough on the outside...
but that's all just for show...
She's actually so vulnerable
she can hardly stand it...
But, that doesn't stop
her from anything...
When I watch her, I can't
help but get the feeling
there might be some
hope for me, as well...
And you know what's funny...
...the stronger she acts,
the stronger it makes
me want to be, for her...
In fact I am the man
I am today because of it...
She's the reason...
It's all because of Ryoko.
Does that, make sense?
Agh! I was rejected
before I even had a chance!
I--yeah, sorry about that.
Ryoshi...! Get back in here
and get us some drinks!
Coming!
Did you get all of that, Ryoko?
So then... how do
you feel about Ryoshi?
Yeah, he might be
a screw up sometimes,
but he's sweet,
and if you need him,
he will always
be there for you...
You have to at least
appreciate that much about him.
I uh...
I need you to give
me a straight answer...
Because if you don't, I'll
never be able to let go of him.
Do you like him or don't you?
Which is it?
I... I don't not.
Okay... fine.
Don't let anyone else
take him away, then.
Hey Ryoko?
Come on! We're setting
off some fireworks.
So pretty.
Yeah.
Seriously, how cute
are Otohime and Taro...?
They've been through
so much together.
Majolika, please stop it!
Come back, Otsuu; it's fun!
How nice.
Otsuu and Majolika are
getting along as usual.
Look, the president and Alice.
Close as two cousins can be.
Yukime and Wakato are so sweet
for gathering everyone
together like this.
Cheer up. It isn't that bad.
Machiko the Rejected...
Ringo the Consoler.
And, these two.
They're pretty, aren't they?
Can I tell you something?
Yeah, what's on your mind?
You know...
One of these days...
Ryoko?
You have to believe me...
No matter what
may happen to us...
I will always love you, Ryoko!
What the crap, man?!
Zoom!
Ta daa!
Until the day comes
when Ryoko is willing
to shed that wolf's
clothing of hers...
The tale of Ryoshi
and Okamisan...
Will simply have...
to be continued...
Alls well that ends well.