I know this is quite sudden.
But please. Would you...
Would you play us in two days?
Okay. So... this is nuts.
Here's the thing, Coach.
The team we were supposed
to play was forced
to cancel on us at
the very last minute.
Looks like too many of
their guys were injured
in the previous match.
So they had to bow out.
I know this is a long shot.
But we'd be honored to
compete against your team.
We accept.
[YOSHIDA, IWASHIMIZU gasp]
Wait. Are you serious?
[MINAMOTO] You'll be playing
our second string, though.
I already promised my starters
they'd get the rest
of the week off.
Call me later and we'll
discuss the details.
Thanks for the opportunity.
[MINAMOTO]
Let's go.
[YOSHIDA] Evidently, Ryoin's
coach accepted our challenge.
I hope I haven't made
a terrible mistake.
You didn't make a
mistake at all, Yoshida.
You just saved the day!
Huh. Yeah, thanks.
Crazy.
This is your fault.
If you hadn't started
talking to them,
this never would've happened.
Yeah. True.
You can thank me later.
[IWASHIMIZU]
I'm scared.
What's the matter
with you today?
You should all be over the moon.
Second string or not.
Ryoin has ruled
Kanagawa 15 years.
And now we get to play them.
So watch and learn.
And steal what ya can.
We have another match today.
So, men, make it count.
[JINKO TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[JINKO TEAM, WAKIMACHI
TEAM yelling]
Matsuo!
A-Ah...
[whistle blows]
[KAMO]
What's wrong with you, man?!
Matsu, get off the field.
Oharano, you're up, son.
[OHARANO sighs]
Here. Your jersey.
Well. I'm tired.
You take it from here, Oharano.
[flatly] Hurray.
Ah...
[KASUGA growls]
[whistle blows]
[panting]
Just great! We lost!
[HYOSU]
What happened out there?
People were flying
by you today, Gion.
[GION growls]
Hey, Kasuga, why did we lose?
I don't get it. I tried
as hard as I could
almost the entire time
and we still didn't--
[yelps]
[KASUGA]
'Cause of you, jerk!
--[GION yelling]
--Kasuga!
[groaning]
Why did he hit me, too?
[KASUGA] I can't believe you
idiots threw that game away.
My lineup won our
match this morning.
[HYOSU] Hey, three and two
is still a winning record.
I have somethin' to ask--
please don' t hit me!
What?
So, do you have any clue
why we lost today?
--[KASUGA] Stop asking that!
--[HYOSU] Don't kill him.
--Noob.
--[GION yelling]
--You know, we are
--[GION] Dude! Chill!
--playing Ryoin soon.
--Maybe you oughtta give the kid
--Please stop!
--a real answer.
What?
This might be the toughest
team we've seen yet.
Even though we're going up
against their second string
and the Kirishima brothers
won't be playing at all,
the guys we will
face are players
who go up against the twins
day in and day out.
It's not just Gion.
If we wanna win,
we're all gonna have to
step up our game and go all out.
Here. Let's do some work.
Gion. Come over here.
Okay.
Your low tackles are
some of the strongest
I've ever seen.
It's fun to watch!
When I see you go low
out on the field of play,
I know the other guy
is in for a world of hurt.
But your positioning
is still dead wrong.
[GION]
It is?
[HYOSU] Yeah, let me show you
what I'm talkin' about.
Ya see where my
right shoulder is?
That's where yours
should be, too, brah.
I'm gonna move and
I want you to keep
your shoulder in sync
with mine, okay?
[GION]
Yeah.
Hup.
All right.
[GION gasps]
[yelps]
[GION grunts]
[HYOSU laughs]
You've got zero
feel for this, Gion!
Anytime you find yourself
directly across
from your opponent,
do whatever you can to stay
with them, step for step.
Just keep your
shoulders squared away
and you'll be in good position.
Listen.
You're in a scrum and the
other team has possession.
In this case, let's say
the first thing they do
is pass it to their number 10.
If that's their first move,
they're most likely
gonna keep passing
the ball to the outside,
so we wanna get in there
and disrupt them right away.
[GION]
Mm-hm.
Now you can see
the space between
each of the position players
and their counterparts.
But look here.
The first big gap
is between the scrum
and the other team's fly
half and this is the one
that counts the most.
Right.
And which player is
supposed to cover
this massive gaping hole?
The flanker, of course!
Whoa!
But when you enter
this space without
proper positioning, you leave
the backdoor wide open
and all they have to do
is step on through.
Go in too deep and, well,
game over, dude.
[gasps]
In rugby, that's what we
flankers call an inside break.
Number 15's the only
one behind you,
so where does that leave us?
Basically screwed!
Yeah.
We have to guard the line
between our opponent's
right shoulder and our own.
You can't let the line break.
You have to maintain
it at all costs.
As long as you can
keep this position,
whether he darts right
or jukes to the left,
you'll always be in the play.
Yeah. I got it!
--Ah--
--[KASUGA] In other words,
no matter what happens
out on the field,
your job is to protect
your own turf.
Right.
Hey! Instead of just talking,
let's give it a try!
Yo!
[ISE]
U-Uh...
[HYOSU]
You can stop hiding now, Ise.
I know you're there.
What are you doing
lurking behind that tree?
Do you wanna be a
flanker or something?
Uh... Yeah.
[KASUGA]
Okay. Gion, you're up first.
I'll be on offense.
For the sake of the drill,
let's pretend there're backs
lined up over there to my left.
Now remember, whatever you do,
do not let me break the plane
and get past you, all right?
Always keep your body
squared up against mine.
Bend those knees!
Okay, let's say the ball
is coming out of a scrum!
Sweet!
Booyah!
All right!
[yelps]
Keep your shoulders
square! Go, Ise!
[ISE]
Oh! 'Kay!
[gasps]
[groans]
Do you wanna know why
you just got laid out?
Your body's not facing forward.
You won't be able
to make a tackle
till you clean up your posture!
Right!
[KASUGA]
Gion! You're next!
Damn!
[KASUGA]
Watch my movements closely!
Whatever you do, do not
forget to bend those knees!
[GION]
Got it!
Ise!
--[ISE] Sir, yes, sir!
--[HYOSU] Huh.
[ISE groans]
[KASUGA]
All wrong!
[GION panting]
[panting]
Come on, you're not done!
That really all you got?
[KASUGA]
Trust me on this!
If you give up that easily,
the Kirishima brothers are
gonna haunt your dreams!
[BOTH gasp]
[KASUGA]
So are you done?
[ISE, GION]
No!
[GION grunts]
[KASUGA]
Too weak! Ise!
[ISE]
Right!
[ISE groans]
[HYOSU]
That's enough for one day!
[panting]
[HYOSU]
Well, guys? Good work.
[ISE, GION]
Thank you.
But, technically,
Kasuga ran twice as much.
Don't worry about me.
I'm just getting warmed up.
Show off.
[HACHIOJI]
Hey!
I thought I might
find you guys out here
workin' over time! I figured
you'd be hungry, too.
So I made you some
homemade rice balls!
You're the best!
Thanks, Mommy!
[HACHIOJI] Who're you
callin' "Mommy," weirdo?
[ISE, GION]
These rock!
You're awesome, man.
How'd you know you'd be
able to find us out here?
Because I noticed all
three of our flankers
were missing in action.
Ise.
So what's the deal? Do you
wanna be a flanker now, too?
Yeah, kinda.
But, I-I'd like
to be a forward, too.
Wow, I'm glad to hear
you say that, Ise.
If you really do take
over as a forward,
then Kasuga or I can go
back to being a center.
[GION]
No way! You were backs?
Sir?
[HYOSU] Well. Originally, yes,
and I started playing
as a forward this year.
We were worried
because we didn't have
a lot of experienced backs.
That's true.
Yeah.
You're definitely helping by
training the flankers, Kasuga!
[HYOSU]
Huh? Kasuga?
[HACHIOJI chuckles] Looks like
Kasuga got the lucky rice ball!
[HYOSU]
Uh?
[HACHIOJI] I packed one of 'em
full of extra hot wasabi!
It's not that hot.
Liar.
[KASUGA] It's got nothing
to do with these rice balls.
But I'm gonna punch
you later, Hachi!
Here. If your mouth's burning,
have a sip of this.
[KASUGA]
It's not!
[HYOSU]
Just admit it already, Kasuga!
[KASUGA]
I'm fine!
[HYOSU]
Yeah, yeah.
[JINKO TEAM yelling, shouting]
Kamo, what in the heck
are you doing, man?
[SHINSHI] Way to bring
home the win, big man!
Dude! We lost the
rock-paper-scissors
tournament again!
Now those idiots get to
take their baths first!
This is awful!
By the time it's our turn,
it's just gonna be
a half-empty bath filled
with dirty sludge and hair!
No fair!
Why do we have to bathe
in their nasty filth again?
'Cause Kamo sucks at games!
You told us rock-paper-
scissors was your jam!
[SEKIZAN]
Hm. Let's go, forwards.
[OHARANO]
Now wait just a damn minute.
[SHINSHI]
O-Oharano, what's up?
Please. I can't take this.
[HACHIOJI]
Wait, you can't take what?
Look. Cut me some slack.
Just give me two minutes
in there so I can bathe alone
and get properly clean
and then it's all yours.
Not gonna happen, freshman!
[OHARANO] Then can you
at least tell the big guys
to stop romping around in there?
They're getting water
all over the floor.
It's so annoying.
[KAMO]
Wow. He's brave.
And how come the water looks
like backed up sewage?
I know you guys are dirty,
but that's gross.
Oh, so we're gross now?
[OHARANO]
On second thought,
I think "gross" is
putting it too mildly.
Ha. I think you're vile.
That bath water smells like
a bowl of sulfuric ramen
made by a demon...
[MARODO]
Somebody stop him, quick!
In fact, I think you
opened a portal
to the fiery abyss
with your stink.
[KIBI]
It's no use, guys!
The stress from that bath water
has made him lose his mind!
Come on!
Look at what you've done to him!
Have mercy on us and let
us take a bath first!
No way, backs!
You knew what was it stake
when you played the game.
We bathe first!
You've awakened the
bathing giant, my friends--
me and the other forwards are
gonna sweat in that bath
till it's dingy as
the day is long!
No! Anything but that, sir!
Captain! Please!
Won't you do something?
A deal's a deal, right?
No!
E tu , Captain? You Brutus, you!
[KAMO sobs]
We should've known.
If there's one thing Seki loves,
it's a long, warm,
relaxing bath!
[NOKA]
Man. I remember warm baths.
They're like a distant dream.
I wanna go home,
I wanna go home, I wanna
go home, I wanna go home,
I wanna go home...
Boys, are you heading
down to the baths?
[sputters] Hey, Coach!
If that's the case.
I thought I'd join you,
After the day I've just had,
I could use a little R&amp;R.
U-Um...
Is that all right?
Yes, sir. Of course.
And I think we should
invite the backs to join us,
don't you?
They say the team that bathes
together wins together!
I couldn't agree more, Coach.
[FORWARDS]
Captain?
[JINKO TEAM
chattering, laughing]
[HYOSU]
Don't make me drop the soap!
[NOKA yelping]
You're getting soap in my eye!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Help me!
It sure is cramped.
Do you guys really
squeeze in here every day?
Yes...
Yep.
There's nothing better than
a big spacious bathtub.
[NOKA screams]
This sucks! I've had enough!
I'm gonna go get
in the girl's bath!
[UMENO]
Huh?
[door opens]
[UMENO]
Get the hell outta here!
[MARODO laughs]
Are you serious?
Yeah, she kicked me
in the frickin' face.
[MARODO]
Ah, that's hilarious.
[SUMIYOSHI laughs] Hey, maybe
she should stop managing,
and join the team instead.
[OHARANO]
Hm?
Huh?
[SUWA]
Yo.
[OHARANO]
What?
Tell me, so how long you
been playin' rugby, man?
Since fourth grade.
Why are you asking me that?
What made you wanna start?
[OHARANO] My brother started
playing. So I did, too.
That's interesting. And how'd
you choose your position?
I don't know.
Someone put me there.
So I decided I might
as well give it a go.
[OHARANO]
What about you?
No offense, but you seem
more like the bookworm type.
Oh, shut up!
[panting]
Cool?
Uh, yeah. I'm good.
I'm sorry I just can't
stand it when people
say things like that.
[OHARANO]
I'm sorry, too.
[SUWA]
You're one of the lucky ones.
You don't even have to try,
and you're still one
of our best players.
I wish the same thing
were true for me.
What? I work my ass off!
Oh, yeah?
Then don't go around saying you
play fly-half just because!
And be grateful when
you get game time!
You got to play today
and yesterday, too!
But I had to sit on the bench.
Do you know what that's like?
Ugh.
[SUWA]
'Course you don't.
You don't have a freaking clue.
You have no idea how it feels
to fight every single day
just to make the cut!
You're right, I don't know.
But honestly, I don't care
how other people feel!
[growls]
You know something?
You're nothing but
an arrogant prick!
Why are you yelling at me, man?
What the hell did I do to you?
Thing is...
Ever since I was born,
I've had awful eyes.
I've always been a skinny,
athletically challenged dork.
A nerd. But still,
I wanted to play sports.
So bad.
So I forced my way
onto a couple of teams,
and I trained my butt off.
But I couldn't get stronger.
No matter how much I ate,
I couldn't gain weight
and I still can't! Not even now!
I hate them all.
The guys who don't
try very hard.
The guys who can naturally
do anything they want.
Even the guys whose hard
work gets them somewhere.
Jerks, I hate 'em!
[gasps]
[SUWA] Why did I have
to be born like this?
It sucks. Big time.
And it's not fair!
I wish I was someone else.
[OHARANO]
Stop it already!
[pants]
[OHARANO]
I-I'm sorry.
But I really hate it
when people do that.
Whaddaya' mean?
[sighs]
Just scoot over!
Uh. 'Kay?
Suwa. You watch
professional rugby?
What? Yeah.
[OHARANO]
Here. Check out Red's number 14.
Their right wing?
He's the head captain of
the Japanese National Team.
See the way he runs?
The guy's not
exceptionally fast.
Doesn't matter though.
He's had an awesome career
at the highest level.
But, he doesn't do
things by the book.
Just look at him.
He's always in the ruck,
almost every play.
It's like he doesn't even care
what a wing is supposed to do,
he just does whatever he can
to help his team win.
[gasps]
Be like 14.
Don't worry about what
other people think.
And don't compare yourself
to your teammates.
Being the strongest
doesn't make you
a good teammate, not by far.
The best player on the
field can be the reason
his teammates can't succeed.
A guy can outrun
everyone he plays
and still lose the game.
If he's too selfish
on the rugby field,
talent won't matter.
Yeah, well, so says
the fastest guy
with all the natural ability.
I'm good. But I'm
not that good yet.
[SUWA]
Now that's a power tackle.
That'll hurt in the morning!
Yikes.
That thing you wished
about a moment ago?
[SUWA]
Mm?
My brother used to tell
me that all the time.
[OHARANO'S BROTHER]
You're lucky.
When it comes to sports,
you can do anything you want.
But no matter how hard I try,
I'll never get any better.
He said something
I'll never forget.
"If we're brothers, and if
we have the same blood,
why did I end up like this?"
But from my perspective,
my brother's life sucks
way less than mine.
He's got 100 times
as many friends as I do.
[laughs]
Do you have a pic?
Pic?
Yeah, a picture of your brother.
I do.
Say anything weird and
I'll smack ya. Here.
Wow. Look, you guys
have the same eyes.
That's weird. Now I'm
gonna smack ya.
You goin' to sleep?
[SUWA]
Time for my run.
I may not be the fastest,
but I'm still gonna try.
[OHARANO]
See ya later.
[SUWA panting]
[EBUMI panting]
[GION] Next time:
"My Friend Taught Me."