Hey, Matsuo.
[MATSUO]
Hm?
[KASHIMA]
Come with me.
[MATSUO]
'Kay.
Listen, we brought you here
because there's something
we need to discuss.
[HIROTA growls]
It's your game play.
It's been way off.
Why are you messing
around out there?
[HIROTA growls] Look, I don't
know what's going on,
but you gotta get your
head outta your ass!
You haven't been trying
hard in practice.
In yesterday's match,
the second you didn't
have to play anymore,
you were smiling when you
got taken out of the game!
[MATSUO]
Yeah. I have been slacking off.
[ALL gasp]
What is this--some kind
of stupid joke to you?
[HIROTA] You better have
a good explanation
for why you've been
acting this way!
Sorry. But I don't.
Damn you!
[MATSUO]
Even if I did explain myself,
I highly doubt you
would understand.
We deserve to know!
All right.
Let me ask you something first.
I know this team has a
goal to get to Hanazono.
But how many of you
are 100 percent sure
we'll actually make it that far?
[ALL gasp]
I mean.
Don't get me wrong, I know
you wanna make it there,
otherwise you wouldn't
be busting your butts
every single day of the week.
Hard work's important.
But I'm sorry to say I don't
think it's gonna be enough.
Coach Komori's made
a big difference,
and it's true, we've
gotten a lot better.
But, do you really think
we've gotten strong enough
to beat Ryoin? Because I don't.
[MATSUO]
Don't get me wrong,
I think we'll get
there eventually.
The young guys
seem hungry for it.
We have a really solid
class of first years.
That's definitely a recipe
for future success.
But, I'm sorry,
guys, the truth is,
I think it's too late for me.
What does that have to do with
you half-assing
practice, Matsuo?
What you just said
makes no sense.
Kashi.
I'm not backing off this.
So, you're saying you've
been slackin' off
'cause you don't think this
team can win. Is that it?
When I see the young guys
busting their asses,
it makes me wanna work harder.
Why doesn't it for you, too?
You're the one who
said you always
wanted to follow
Sekizan's example.
So, own up to it!
[MATSUO]
Sorry.
[MATSUO] I'm gettin'
a drink. I'm thirsty.
Screw that!
You said we'd go
to college together!
You said we'd play rugby
and hang out all the time!
What are you going to
do if you walk away
from rugby, Matsuo?
Ah...
I shoulda told you sooner.
But I can't go to college
with you anymore, Taku.
[gasps]
[MATSUO]
Sorry.
In a few months from now,
I'll be done with rugby
for good. It is what it is.
No sense worrying about me.
It's pointless.
Focus your energy on
the youngsters instead.
[MATSUO]
Like that Oharano kid.
He's a million times better
than me and you all know it.
You should be thinking
ahead to players like him.
If he gets enough game time,
he'll be able to develop
into a powerful player.
You'll go far with
him next year.
Is that seriously your attitude?
So you were lying
when you said you wanted
to be like Sekizan.
All those years of playing
rugby--what were they to you?
Just a massive waste of time?
No. It's just...
[MATSUO] I still wanna
be like you. But I'm not.
I'm sorry. I am.
With all of my heart.
But no matter what any of
you say, the fact remains...
I can't take it
seriously anymore!
[MATSUO] If I could snap
my fingers and be like you,
I would, and we wouldn't
be in this situation.
I'm sorry.
[SIDELINE CROWD cheering]
[REF 23A]
Crouch. Bind. Set!
[KAMO]
Oharano!
Got it!
[OHARANO]
Huh. I think a kick is in order.
Heads up, man!
[yelps]
Let's see what you can do
one more time, Kibi!
Now, Kibi. Kick it
as hard as you can!
[whistle blows]
It went out of bounds!
The ball's gone into touch!
That's what I'm
talkin' about, guys!
Awesome kick, Kibi! Way to go!
Heck of a play, man!
Just don't surprise me
like that, 'kay?
It's not cool.
I'm not sure if
you realize this,
but you're a lot
stronger than me.
But your control
could use some work.
[laughs] I'll work
on it for sure.
No. It was a fake out!
Ya fell for that one!
[gasps] Keep me up!
[HIROTA yelling]
[KASHIMA grunts]
Kashi, awesome pass!
Dammit, you guys!
I'm open!
Keep it moving forward, guys!
Ryoin's crazy fast!
Yeah, and the worst part is,
they make our passes
look super slow.
All right then.
Let's see what you got!
[RYOIN NUMBER 13 yells]
[UMENO] He just threaded his
way through the forwards!
Get 'em, Oharano!
Nice moves, dude!
[MIKADO yells]
Ya think you can
make it past me?
Go ahead and try, pretty boy.
[MIKADO yells]
[OHARANO]
He's fast.
I'm counting on you.
Go get 'em.
[MIKADO, ATSUTA, NOKA,
HIRANO, SUMIYOSHI] Suwa!
Whoa!
Run! Suwa!
[SUMIYOSHI]
Go!
[NOKA]
Score us a try, Suwa!
[SUWA, KAIJA grunting]
[SUWA yells]
--[whistle blows]
--[SUWA, KAIJA panting]
[SIDELINE CROWD cheers]
[ALL panting]
[OHARANO]
Good job, Suwa.
Is this all we got?
Of course, not.
I'll have to chew
them out later.
So, they learn their lesson.
Wow. This is incredible!
We just scored the first
try against Ryoin.
Can you believe it?
Yeah!
I do hate to admit it,
but that was a
pretty decent try.
Yeah. I know.
That's enough gloating.
I gotta make this
conversion, so move it.
[OHARANO]
A-Ah...
Uh-oh!
[OHARANO]
This is your fault, man!
You should've scored
closer to center field!
Too bad you're not
in the game Kifune,
you would've made
that kick for sure.
Oh. I don't know.
It was pretty tough.
Let's shake it off, Jinko!
Yeah! Bad break!
[KAMO]
Hey, Captain?
Sekki. The thing is,
I don't like how
we're treating Matsuo.
Everyone's mad at him
and it's not okay.
[KAMO] I've played scrum-half
since the beginning.
Ever since Matsuo started
playing fly-half.
Your job was to get the
ball out of the scrum.
Mine was to grab the ball,
and pass it to Matsuo.
It was simple. But it worked.
Matsuo sucked at first, but,
then again, so did we.
We could barely play.
So, we practiced
over and over again.
We worked hard.
And eventually, we all got
a lot better, even Matsuo.
But, why did we
do all that work?
We did it to win games.
We did it for days like today.
I don't know about you,
but I don't want everything
we've done to be for nothing.
[KAMO]
He needs our help.
Let's wake him up.
Let's beat the ever-loving crap
out of Ryoin in this game
and snap him out of this
stupid funk he's in!
[BOTH panting]
[KAMO]
Matsuo!
You gotta work on
your positioning, man!
Our opponents are gonna
be really close to us,
which means you need
to get in tighter, too!
Right. Sorry about that.
[OLDER PLAYER 23A]
Hey, Kamo, relax, okay?
Not everybody's played
before like you.
He's a newbie. Give him time.
[gasps]
[OLDER PLAYER 23B]
Don't worry about him, Matsuo,
just do your best.
That's all we can ask
anyone to do, right?
[OLDER PLAYER 23A]
And as for you, the only person
you need to worry about
is yourself, kid.
You're not in
middle school anymore.
Uh...
[OLDER PLAYER 23A]
Let's put Sekizan
in the starting
lineup next time.
He sucks right now,
but he's got potential.
And he's huge, too.
[OLDER PLAYER 23B] Plus,
no matter what we make him do,
he never complains.
[OLDER PLAYER 23A]
All right, everyone!
Get in position for a scrum!
Raita!
[MATSUO]
I'll work on my positioning.
I promise.
[KAMO]
He sucked at rugby.
But he was always good at
getting the upperclassmen
on his side. He wasn't
a bad guy or anything.
[KAMO]
But even so.
I didn't like him
enough to protect him.
[HACHIOJI]
Raita!
[gasps]
[KAMO yelps]
[UMENO]
Uh-oh! An interception!
He's so fast!
Come on, man.
Stop daydreamin' and
get in the game!
My bad!
Get him!
Let's go!
Don't just stand there,
Matsuo, make some noise!
[KIBI]
Gion! Get him!
[yelling]
[yelps]
[RYOIN PLAYERS groan]
[gasps] Sekki!
Get off the damned ground, kid!
All right! Nice tackle, Captain!
[grunts]
Number 8's unbelievable
out there.
That's Sekizan,
their team captain.
He took out two guys like
it was nothing. He's good.
[HIRANO]
All right!
[MIKAMI] Come on! Let's
win the ball back, guys!
We're doing a good job
of making tackles
and staying with them.
None of it will matter if
we can't get the ball back.
They're playing well.
But they're not coming
together as a unit.
They're all caught up in
making individual plays,
without thinking of
how to win the game.
Looks to me like they
have the basics down,
they're just not sure
how to apply them yet.
But even so, they're
giving our backups
a run for their money. It's
way too close for comfort.
You're right about that.
[yelling]
[grunting]
[GION gasps]
[HIRANO] Whoa! He lifted
him off the ground!
[MIKAMI]
Keep going, Iwashi!
[SHINSHI]
It's a maul!
[NISHI]
Get it out! Fast!
Hang on!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Right!
[whistle blows]
Pile up!
Ryoin players didn't release
the ball from the maul.
Jinko's ball, form a scrum!
[HIROTA, GION]
Yeah!
All right! It's a scrum!
There's just under
ten minutes left
in the first half!
We have a chance to
extend our lead, guys!
Now!
We just gotta put the pressure
on and stay on our game!
[REF 23A]
Crouch. Bind. Set!
[JINKO TEAM,
RYOIN TEAM grunting]
[KOMORI]
The boys are playin' well today.
But, somethin's not right,
I'm just not sure what.
Come on, Second
String. Fight back!
[ALL panting]
[KAMO grunts]
[SHINSHI yelps]
Crap! They got the ball back!
Nice hustle!
Take it down a notch, will ya?
[HIROTA] What the hell's
the matter with you, Shinshi?
[SHINSHI]
Sorry, guys! Ah! Damnit!
[KOMORI]
The third years.
[GODAI]
Focus up!
[KUROSE] Don't let them
move another inch!
[MIKADO]
What the hell is happening?
This is bad.
If we don't turn
this game around,
they're gonna think we
don't have what it takes
to beat these losers!
I need to do something fast!
Heads up!
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[MIKADO yells]
[SEKIZAN, MIKADO grunting]
[MIKADO]
It's mine!
[whistle blows]
Ryoin failed to
release the ball!
[MIKADO]
What?
Mikado, come on, man!
Ya jerk!
[pants]
[HACHIOJI]
Sekizan.
Stop looking over
at the sidelines.
Listen to me.
I'm not saying I'm not
worried about Matsuo.
And I'm not saying I wanna
abandon him, either.
But still.
This is no time to be looking
at the bench, Sekizan!
Look at the score board.
We're five points
ahead of a team
we wouldn't of dreamed of
being able to compete with!
Do you wanna make those guys
remember who we are, or not?
Yeah.
Sorry.
[whistle blows]
[HACHIOJI]
Come on. Let's get focused.
I got an idea I think
you're gonna like.
[SEKIZAN]
What is it?
[HACHIOJI]
Bait and switch.
[NOKA]
That was a really good kick!
[KIFUNE] It's a little
less than ten meters
to Ryoin's goal line.
All right. C'mon guys.
Let's win this!
Check it out, Jinko's Number 8
is in the scrum-half position.
They're gonna go for a maul.
We got a maul, you guys!
We need to push 'em back!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Captain!
Damn! I can't believe
they fooled us!
Go get 'em.
[yells]
[ALL gasping]
That's, that.
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A]
Try!
[SIDELINE CROWD cheers]
[MIKI]
We scored!
Hachi!
--You did it! You scored!
--[GION] You're the man, Hachi!
I know!
[SEKIZAN]
Way to go!
Sekki! We totally
tricked those guys!
[KAMO]
That ruled!
The play worked, brother.
[laughs]
--[whistle blows]
--[SIDELINE CROWD cheers]
[UMENO]
Nice kick, Oharano!
[MIKI]
It's 12 to nothing!
[sighs]
Whoa!
Coach. We're kicking their ass!
Jinko's on a roll now!
[sighs]
You finally awake? Good for you.
[ZANBA grunts]
[ZANBA]
I've been awake the whole time.
[TSUKINAKA]
Don't lie!
[sighs]
Well...
[GION]
Next time:
[JINKO TEAM]
"All Out!"