[GION]
All right!
[grunts]
Gion! Hey!
What are you doing?
Stop! Let go!
[IWASHIMIZU yells]
[GION]
Try!
[IWASHIMIZU]
That hurt.
Why in the world did
you just spike my head?
[GION murmuring]
I really... I really did it.
An Ultra Super Try.
That's 20 points in one play.
I'm the best player of all time.
An Ultra Super Try
isn't a thing.
You're just having a dream.
[IWASHIMIZU grunts]
[ALL snoring]
[IWASHIMIZU]
That's weird.
I can't believe that
didn't wake them up.
[MATSUO]
What's goin' on?
You cool?
Yeah. I just need the bathroom.
[door clicking]
[RUGBY TEAM] [GION]
[whispering] Hey, Matsuo.
Is that Ebumi?
Shh.
I wonder why he's
dressed like that.
Where's he going?
[YUMI]
Where do you think you're going?
[KOMORI]
Huh?
[YUMI] Yesterday, you left
at the crack of dawn
and didn't come back
till well after dark.
I thought the whole
point of you retiring
was so you could give
yourself a break.
[KOMORI]
I've got places to be.
[YUMI]
What?
Some rugby kids.
I'm gonna have to put
'em through the ringer.
[GION] Last night, I dreamed
I'd been doing some
secret late-night training
to prepare for a big game.
Then we won 'cause
I scored an amazing try!
Yeah, yeah. Good for you, Gion.
Maybe I should do
some secret training.
Hey! Tree trunk.
What do you think?
[growls]
[IWASHIMIZU] It wouldn't
be much of a secret now.
You've already told
everyone about it.
[GION]
Crap! You're right!
I gotta say, being here
on break isn't so bad!
You know what I heard, dude?
For Golden Week, my classmates
are goin' to Hawaii.
Aw, that sucks!
Do you know what club
they're a part of?
No idea. Maybe the Soccer Club?
They'll be chillin' in
paradise with hot girls
while we're here
workin' our butts off!
There won't be a
single bikini in sight!
If you would rather
chase girls in Hawaii,
then go and knock
yourself out, son.
Let's go!
It's only the second
day of camp, men.
So no screwin' around.
Since you haven't
warmed up, go do ten laps.
What?
[GION]
All right!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Huh?
[yells]
What's his deal, is he stupid?
[KOMORI]
Get goin' already!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[RUGBY TEAM panting]
[growls]
All right, backs, let's
practice attacking the line.
Work on your passes.
[EBUMI]
Got it!
'Cause your team is
on the small side,
you'll need to
perfect this to win.
Skip one.
[MATSUO]
Here!
[yelps]
Way to hang on, Noka!
[growls]
[NOKA grunts]
[NOKA gasps]
Aw, jeez.
[EBUMI] That wasn't
a knock-on, you know!
It bounced backwards, you idiot,
which means the ball's
still in play!
So why in the hell
aren't you hustlin', man?
Uh... Sorry.
It won't happen again.
[growls]
[MATSUO]
Okay! Get ready!
Catch it!
[grunts]
Hey. Nice catch, Gion.
[GION]
Thanks.
Next time, just relax
your hands a little.
[GION]
Gotcha.
[EBUMI] What the hell
is wrong with you?!
[growls]
How many times do I
have to tell you, moron?
If you're not up for the job,
then step aside, you piss stain!
Ebumi's at it again.
All right, fine.
But you don't have
to be such a jerk.
Who in the hell do you
think you are anyway?
[growls]
Dude. You missed practice
for an entire week.
Just worry about yourself.
[EBUMI]
You wanna know why I missed?
'Cause I don't wanna
waste my precious time
practicing next to a
bunch of losers like you!
For all I know,
your suck is contagious!
[SUWA]
Stop! That's enough of that!
Hey.
If you're gonna act like this,
then we don't want you.
What?
[SUWA] Look at how many
guys we have here.
We're small, but we
can do a lot!
I don't care how
talented you are--
if you wanna do it all yourself,
join the guys in
track and field.
You snuck off somewhere
last night--I saw you.
What was that about?
Do you wanna tell us?
[EBUMI gasps]
[SUWA]
Come on, man.
What are you doing out so late
when you should be
getting rest for practice?
Ya know what? Screw you.
[KOMORI] How long are you
guys gonna keep fighting?
Ten laps. I think you
need to cool off.
You'd better get started.
[KOMORI]
That means everyone.
What's with Ebumi?
He hates our guts.
Why doesn't he
just quit already?
[KOMORI]
That's all for today.
Go home and try
to get some rest.
[ALL panting]
Hey, you.
Come talk to me.
Right.
Captain.
Tell me--no--all of you tell me.
Every team has one major
goal, so what's yours?
[gasps]
[SEKIZAN]
Well, it's uh--
Ah.
You should be able to answer
that without blinking an eye.
[gasps] Hanazono, sir.
[GION]
Hold on.
I've never heard of a Hanazono.
Wait. Gion.
You're joking, right?
Do you really not know
what Hanazono is?
Nope. No clue.
It's a huge arena, Gion.
Like the rugby equivalent
of Koshien Stadium.
It's where the
National High School
Rugby Tournament takes place.
Whoa! For real?
I didn't know that place
existed! I wanna go!
[KAMO]
That's easier said than done.
[HACHIOJI]
Everybody wants to go, Gion.
[KOMORI] Sorry, but you
won't make it that far.
[RUGBY TEAM gasps]
Just look. Your
equipment's falling apart.
Plus, the second things
get tough in practice,
you start complaining,
whining and fighting
with each other.
You're just a joke.
Get some rest.
And clean yourselves up.
[GION] Don't go! Help us!
We'll do whatever it takes!
We need your help, Coach!
[ALL gasp]
[KOMORI] If you wanna have
a snow ball's chance in hell
of makin' it that far,
then starting tomorrow,
practice is gonna get
a heck of a lot harder.
Hey! That's fine by me!
[MATSUO grunts]
[footsteps]
[panting]
[EBUMI] Why are you
out of bed? It's late.
I hope you're not thinkin'
about joining the Track Team.
[panting]
[EBUMI]
No. Are you nuts?
Since you're already up.
You mind takin' a
ride on this thing?
[MATSUO]
What?
I don't know about this,
I'm pretty heavy.
[EBUMI grunts]
[EBUMI grunting]
[EBUMI panting]
[EBUMI groans]
[panting]
[MATSUO]
Ha... Look at you.
I've never seen you
this exhausted before!
[MATSUO]
Your stamina's off the charts.
I'm guessing these secret runs
didn't start last
night, did they?
Not much of a talker, are you?
You work hard,
but you're way too rough
on the other guys.
[EBUMI]
It's not about them at all.
[MATSUO]
Hm?
Thing is, I really
can't stand to lose.
I love to win.
And my competitive drive has
gotten me into a lot of trouble.
Well, well, well.
This one's got a mouth.
I guess no one taught you
to respect your elders?
Well, that's a shame.
Why don't we teach
him a lesson, boys?
Ya see, you're just a freshman.
We're seniors,
so we run this place--
[THUGS gasp]
[EBUMI]
Before I came to Jinko,
I'd never been in a club before.
And honestly, I didn't
expect that to change.
[EBUMI]
But then, one day...
Hey there, fellas.
You wanna play rugby?
[EBUMI]
When Hachi asked me to join,
I said, "yes"
without hesitating.
[EBUMI grunts]
[BOTH laughing]
[JINKO TEAM]
Let's go, Jinko!
[EBUMI grunts]
--[whistle blows]
--[EBUMI] Try!
[EBUMI laughs]
[EBUMI] I couldn't believe
a sport like rugby
actually existed.
[EBUMI]
It was too good to be true.
Then I remembered a line I'd
heard on TV a long time ago.
"Rugby is nothing more than
legal, organized brawling."
I'd been getting in trouble
for fighting my entire life.
And here was a sport
that actually rewarded me
for doing what I was good at.
[EBUMI growls] But if I'm
gonna get into a brawl,
I'm gonna do it to win!
Huh?
[EBUMI] I couldn't stand
the upperclassmen last year.
They never cared
whether we won or lost.
They were always joking around.
And this year's backs are
no better than they were.
[MATSUO] I know exactly
what you mean, Ebumi.
When I was a freshman,
our team was the same way.
Huh?
Truth is, I don't
remember too much
about the older guys.
But I do remember Taku.
[MATSUO] He was the hardest
working player I'd ever seen.
[MATSUO]
Every time we lost,
he was covered in mud,
sweat and tears.
[MATSUO]
Earlier, when I saw you out here
givin' it your all,
it really reminded me of him.
[grunts]
It's the truth.
And It makes me feel worthless.
That's 'cause you are!
You sat there while
Oharano took your spot!
[laughs]
You're right.
In the past, seniority
trumped talent.
And a green freshman
like Oharano
wouldn't be given a chance.
He'd ride the pine till
the season was over.
But the team's changed
from what it was.
And so, I've gotta
change with it, too.
[MATSUO] I'm glad we
got a chance to talk.
Hey. If you're goin' for a
run tomorrow, I'd love to come.
[EBUMI] Wow. I couldn't
stand to be sidelined.
Run with me if you want,
hope you can keep up.
No fair! A secret practice?
[BOTH]
Huh?
This was my idea--
why you guys
stealin' my thunder?
[EBUMI]
Nobody's stealing anything.
Don't even act like
you didn't know about
my secret training plan.
[MATSUO]
Shh. Keep your voice down, Gion!
Ebumi, why're you out here
practicing all on your own?
Do you mind if we join you, man?
[SUWA] I thought you were
just out messing around.
I guess you thought
wrong. Ya jerk.
[SUWA]
Hmph.
[SUWA] If you throw us
off our groove again,
I'll kick you out.
[EBUMI]
Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Hey! Who's up for a scrimmage?
[RUGBY TEAM]
Yeah!
[SEKIZAN]
What are you doing out here?
[SEKIZAN growling]
[RUGBY TEAM gasping]
Go to sleep!
[RUGBY TEAM yelping]
Let's start with two
hours of passing drills.
But two hours of drills
is a lot, Coach.
[KOMORI]
You're right it is "a lot,"
but so is gettin' to Hanazono.
Yeah. Let's do what
the coach says!
Kid.
I don't think you're takin'
this seriously enough.
Just think, if this
was an actual game,
they'd have the ball now.
[KETA panting]
[BOTH panting]
--[ALL panting]
--[NOKA] I can't...
[ALL panting]
[SEKIZAN] If you guys have the
energy to complain, then run!
Being tired is no excuse!
You have to give it
everything you've got!
[GION panting]
[GION]
Get ready to rumble, Koshien!
Because, you're mine!
It's Hanazono, you idiot!
[gasps]
Look, of course we wanna
make it that far!
But, Coach, we can't just
walk around saying that!
We're not good enough.
Not with that attitude.
[ALL panting]
[ALL yell]
[yelling]
[KOMORI]
All right. Take a breather.
[ALL panting]
I'm dead!
[KOMORI]
Tell me, men.
Do you know what it
means to go "all out?"
[RUGBY TEAM]
Huh?
[KOMORI]
It's simple.
It's what your
captain said earlier.
[KOMORI] "Giving it
everything you've got."
Look, you don't
have the strength
or talent you need to win.
But if you're prepared
to go "all in,"
day in and day out,
no matter the cost...
If you steel yourself to
battle through the pain,
through the sweat and tears...
...you guys might
go the distance.
[gasps]
[KOMORI]
I don't have children of my own.
So there are some things
I don't understand.
In a lot of ways,
I don't know how
to talk to 'em yet.
And I don't know how
to inspire 'em either.
This might turn out
to be the hardest job
I've ever had in my life.
[GION]
Hanazono here we come!
[KOMORI] It seems some
of you still have energy.
Let's keep runnin'
for another hour.
[NOKA]
Gion, come on, man!
[KIBI]
Keep your mouth shut, you idiot!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Next time:
"I Want to Be Able
to Do Everything!"