[door opens]
You guys, it's late. What are
you two still doing here?
Aren't you tired?
[GION]
No way, this rocks!
I'm studyin' how
to play flanker!
Studying's good,
but I'd start by
learning the rules.
Uh...
Gion, look!
You should read this one!
There's some good info on how a
flanker moves out on the field.
[GION]
What? Let me see that!
[IWASHIMIZU]
It's right here.
You know somethin'?
He reminds me of you
back in the day.
[GION]
Wait. I remind you of him?
You guys have been
playing together
since middle school, right?
No.
Seki didn't start
till high school.
[IWASHIMIZU]
What? Are you serious?
[GION] If you didn't do rugby,
then what club were you in?
Was it baseball or soccer or...?
The Go Home Club.
Oh, gross. That doesn't
sound fun at all, dude.
[SEKIZAN]
What was that?
[yelps]
I'm curious to know.
Since you got a late start,
what made you play?
[GION]
Don't get mad!
But I totally wanna
hear that story, too!
[SEKIZAN sighs]
[HACHIOJI chuckles]
He joined the team
because I convinced him!
[HACHIOJI]
This doesn't make any sense.
I coulda sworn Jinko was
supposed to have a rugby team.
Hm...
Hey! There it is!
Jeez. The sign looks kinda old.
Well, why not?
I'll check it ou--
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[HACHIOJI]
Sorry! Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
--[SEKIZAN] What?
--Uh...
I'm Hachioji Mutsumi.
If you're a freshman, too,
then I have a great idea.
We should join the Rugby Team!
No thanks.
You made that decision fast.
Quick thinking is the
key to rugby, you know.
Hey! What's your name?
I don't know you at all, dude,
and I don't just give
my name to strangers.
But you already know my name.
Remember? I'm Hachioji!
I have one younger sister
and two older brothers.
And my favorite food is curry!
There anything else?
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you're kinda weird.
I don't need a club, okay?
Ask someone else.
[HACHIOJI] I may be weird,
but I'm also stubborn.
And I'm not moving an inch
until you tell me your name!
Yeah, I can see you won't.
I'm Sekizan. Sekizan Takuya.
[HACHIOJI]
Nice to meet ya.
Well, Sekizan...
Since you decided to
tell me what your name is,
that must mean you're
interested in playing rugby!
Let's sign up together!
[SEKIZAN] How you came to
that conclusion makes no sense.
You're insane.
[HACHIOJI giggles]
[GIRL 13A] Look at him.
What is he doing?
[GIRL 13B]
Just keep walking.
He should be coming this
way any moment now.
[gasps] Jackpot!
♪ Well, hello, best friend! ♪
Wait. Don't go!
Have we met?
Ha, funny joke!
I'm Hachi, from the Rugby Team?
Oh, come on, man,
you remember me, right?
What's up?
Look, Sekizan.
I know you said "no," but you
should totally reconsider!
Because...
That penetrating gaze!
Those shoulders!
Your impressive quadricepts!
It's just my humble opinion,
but I think you were
born to play rugby!
[SEKIZAN] Listen! I've never
even watched a rugby game,
much less played one!
[HACHIOJI] There's no time
like the present!
When you slam against
your opponents in a scrum,
or fight your way
to the goal line
to score a game-winning try...
Or when you make a perfect
tackle, I promise you,
there's no better feeling
in the whole world!
The friends you'll
make playing rugby
will be your friends for life!
Building friendships through
contact sports is critical
to become a man.
A man of true integrity. You--
I'm sorry.
But I'm not interested
in sports, okay?
The upperclassmen'll
buy you nice meals!
But I already get free
meals from my mom.
All of the cheerleaders
will wanna make out with you!
[SEKIZAN]
So, that's why you play rugby?
For free meals and
hot girls? No thanks.
I almost forgot--a lot
of local businesses
sponsor the team,
which means they give us
some really cool stuff
for free sometimes--
we even get taiyaki !
[gasps]
[HACHIOJI]
Hey. You reacted.
So you like sweets, huh?
[SEKIZAN]
No!
[HACHIOJI] Well. Okay,
if you say so, buddy.
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[HACHIOJI] Anyway, you really do
have an impressive build.
With a frame like yours,
if you put in a little work,
you'll bulk up so fast you wont
even know what hit you!
With you on the team, we'll
be a shoo-in for Hanazono!
Oh! Hanazono is sorta like
Koshien for baseball!
It's a big deal!
[SEKIZAN] How many guys
are on a rugby squad?
Uh, 15. Why?
[SEKIZAN]
That's a lot.
So how come you're the only
one trying to recruit me?
Maybe there's a reason for that.
[HACHIOJI]
Well, the upperclassmen
are just busy with practice.
[SEKIZAN]
Later.
[sighs]
[HACHIOJI]
He's surprisingly astute.
But even so, I'm not
gonna give up!
Wait. I thought you said
you didn't like sweets?
I was telling a lie.
Not to be rude,
but it sounds like you
were kind of a loner.
And maybe a bit of a jerk.
You would've acted
the exact same way
if you were being stalked,
I guarantee it.
Burn!
[IWASHIMIZU laughs]
I'm confused.
Why were you focusing
on just one recruit?
Why not widen the
search a little?
Gion! You don't
understand a thing!
Recruiting's an art!
And for a successful
rugby team, it's essential!
And it's not for
the feint of heart!
[GION]
Hm.
[HACHIOJI] Rugby teams
at schools like Jinko,
schools that don't get
sports recommendations,
are almost entirely
made up of newbies.
And the sad truth is,
most people have never even
heard of rugby before.
[IWASHIMIZU]
You were like that, Gion.
[GION]
Yeah, I was.
[HACHIOJI]
Think about it.
Rugby's played with 15 guys.
If you only have a few players,
then you can't really
practice the game.
But if you just try to
go after large groups,
well, good luck.
So instead, I focus my
efforts on prospects
who really have what it takes!
Wow, you must've really liked
what you saw in the captain.
[HACHIOJI]
Well, I knew he'd be good.
And I knew the team
would be stronger
and more successful
if I could somehow
convince Sekizan to sign up.
[HACHIOJI]
You just made my day, my friend!
I'm so glad you finally decided
to give rugby a shot!
[SEKIZAN] Well, anything's
better than having you
follow me around all day
like a complete psycho.
Be honest.
You're kind of
interested, aren't you?
Come on, let's see what you got!
Throw the ball over here to me!
But I don't know how.
Hey, don't sweat
the small stuff.
Just throw!
[HACHIOJI]
Wh-Whoa!
What? What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
But just for the record,
this is actually the first time
you've ever played rugby, right?
Yeah?
You never even tried it in PE?
Nope.
And you've never seen it on TV?
[grunting] You're a genius!
Huh?
For a first pass,
that was great!
I knew I was right
about you, man!
Any newbie can throw the ball,
hard or otherwise--
but not with accuracy!
After all, the rugby ball
has a peculiar shape to it.
Most people really
struggle. But not you!
[SEKIZAN] What, are you
trying to win me over
with compliments or something?
Look, I've never even seen
a game and even I know I suck.
What? No way.
I bet you always hit home runs
when you played baseball.
In fact, I bet you
only hit home runs.
[SEKIZAN sighs]
[loud thud]
[SEKIZAN] They called me
"The Strike-out King."
[HACHIOJI] Well, I'm sure
you scored a lot of goals
when you played soccer!
[SEKIZAN]
I was the keeper.
[HACHIOJI] But I bet you know
how to dunk a basketball!
[SEKIZAN]
Not exactly.
[HACHIOJI sighs]
You're overestimating
my athleticism--trust me.
[HACHIOJI]
Hm. Hey. You're green!
But with a body like
that, it'd be a crime
not to at least try out!
I know my weaknesses, okay?
And I'm not a good athlete.
If I have a strength...
...it's sumo.
Wait. Sumo?
[SEKIZAN] Since sumo
wrestling doesn't involve
any equipment like balls,
I think I'd be decent at it.
Hey. Why don't we start
a sumo club together?
You'd make a really
good sumo wrestler.
[HACHIOJI] Yeah. People have
been tellin' me I have the build
of a sumo wrestler ever
since I was a little kid.
[gasps]
[SEKIZAN]
Let's go to Ryogoku together.
[gasps]
[SEKIZAN]
Well? Are you in?
Wait. You're for real?
Aw! That was a close one!
I almost joined your club, man!
That was a joke.
[HACHIOJI]
Sekizan, hold on!
I really think you should
give rugby a try!
I don't understand,
why does it have to be me?
There are other
prospects out there.
Yeah, there might be others.
And it's absolutely true
that you have to have
15 players to make up
a complete rugby team.
But if you wanna hear the truth,
I don't care about any of them.
If you'll just give me a chance,
then I'll show you how
awesome rugby really is!
"How awesome rugby is"?
[HACHIOJI] It's a truly one of
a kind sport, if you ask me.
It's a game you play
with your whole body.
But a good team
needs strong guys,
agile guys, and
guys who can kick.
It takes every kind of athlete
you can imagine,
all working together to
achieve a common goal.
It may not be an
individual sport,
but you need all kinds of
individuals to succeed.
Whatever your
unique strength is,
it'll be helpful to the team.
My strength? But what is it?
[HACHIOJI] Even if you've never
played sports in your life,
rugby can help you
answer that question.
Just, please!
[HACHIOJI] Join! I know
you won't regret it!
[gasps]
If you'll try!
[sighs] All right, count me in.
Wait! For real?
Awesome! I'll bring you an
application form right away!
Cool. Thanks.
[JINKO RUGBY TEAM laughs]
[SEKIZAN]
Wait a sec.
Aren't those guys your
team's upperclassmen?
What guys?
[JINKO RUGBY TEAM laughs]
[SEKIZAN]
Why are they going home?
It's not even dusk yet.
[HACHIOJI]
Oh, uh, I guess they're just--
[SEKIZAN] They look like they
haven't even broken a sweat.
Looks to me like they're
a bunch of jokers.
Are you the only one
on the team who cares?
Maybe.
But if someone like you joins
the team maybe they'll change.
Maybe they'll work harder!
[SEKIZAN]
That's too many "maybe's."
I'm sorry, but if you're just
trying to fill up a roster,
then thanks, but no thanks.
I'm not interested.
Later.
You can count me out.
I refuse to waste my time
on a team like that!
[HACHIOJI] You can walk away,
but I'll never give up!
No matter how much I annoy you,
I'm never gonna stop
asking until you say yes!
[GION] Wow, Hachi you were
pretty stubborn, weren't you?
But then again,
Captain, so were you.
You said it, Gion.
[GION] Were you that
desperate to lounge around
in the "Go Home Club"?
I don't know.
[HACHIOJI] The way I see it,
Sekizan's more than just
a regular guy, he's
like a giant locomotive.
[BOTH]
A locomotive?
[HACHIOJI] A train engine!
It's not that he doesn't care.
It just takes him more
than a little bit of fuel
to get him moving in
the right direction.
But once he starts goin',
look out, cause he won't
stop for anything.
That's just the kinda guy he is!
Cool.
Go!
[whistle blows]
[HACHIOJI] Wow! You're like
a train engine, man!
I think it'd be
a terrible mistake
for you to stay in
the "Go Home Club."
I don't have anything
against exercise.
If anything, I kinda
like working out.
Well, that's good news!
[SEKIZAN] The track and field
team invited me to join them.
Huh?
[SEKIZAN] In track,
whether you win or lose,
it all depends on your
individual performance.
Seems simple.
[HACHIOJI] I think you'd be
making a big mistake!
Team sports are way more fun!
They offer you things
you can never achieve
playin' a sport all on your own!
It's like I told
you before! Remember?
There's nothing better than
a bunch of individuals
coming together as a team
to achieve a goal!
The feeling you'll
get from learning
from your teammates is awesome!
It's the greatest gift there is!
[SEKIZAN]
Yeah well, not for me.
Here's the deal.
I'd never play on a rugby team
like the one at Jinko.
[HACHIOJI]
I don't understand.
I'm sorry, but I can't
stand half-assing things.
I talked to all of the
track and field guys.
And they told me
who your team is.
They haven't even won a practice
match in how many years?
Although, I guess
that's not surprising,
considering what I witnessed.
But that's because--
Are you really
satisfied with that?
Half-assing practice?
[gasps]
I'm not half-assing
anything! Do you hear me?
I may not know much
about rugby yet,
but I know this much is true.
Those guys are a bunch of losers
failing at a loser's sport.
Listen to me! Rugby is
not a loser's sport.
You can underestimate me,
and you can
underestimate the team!
But don't underestimate rugby!
[GION]
Oh, man.
You guys totally almost
went fist-a-cuffs?
[IWASHIMIZU]
So tell us, what happened next?
Jeez, this story is
a real nail biter!
[laughs]
To be honest, I still can't
believe things turned out
the way they did after
that letter you got, can you?
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[GROUP]
Huh?
[SEKIZAN] Are you really gonna
tell them about that?!
[CAT meows]
[gasps]
[SEKIZAN gasps]
U-Uh...
[running footsteps]
[LETTER GIRL 13A]
"Dear Sekizan,
Since the moment
I first saw you,
my heart hasn't
stopped pounding.
You may think a letter is little
on the old-fashioned side,
but I had to tell you how I feel
or I knew I would
always regret it.
I think you'd make
a great athlete.
Hey, you should play a sport!
Like rugby, for example.
And when you do decide to play,
I'll be there cheering you on.
Love, Mutsumi"
Mutsumi?
I'm Hachioji Mutsumi.
That jerk!
How did I do?
Really good. Here. Your payment.
[LETTER GIRL 13A]
Yipee!
[HACHIOJI chuckles]
[GION, IWASHIMIZU laugh]
[GION]
Wow, Hachi, you're no joke.
[SEKIZAN]
What is wrong with you?!
How could you tell
the freshman that story?
[HACHIOJI] But you joined
the team because of it,
so no harm no foul, right?
[SEKIZAN]
What?!
Oh, come on, Seki,
you don't you remember
the bit at the end?
[SEKIZAN]
No way!
--[HACHIOJI yelps]
--[thud]
'Course I don't,
I tore it up immediately!
That's not true, I was
watchin' you, man!
[HACHIOJI] "By the way,
I have a message for you--
it's from your best friend
in the world Hachioji."
You have got to
be kidding me!
[HACHIOJI]
"The current upperclassmen
may not be motivated
like you are,
but we can change that.
We can transform the whole team.
If we work together, by the
time we're upperclassmen,
it'll be all ours!"
Wow. So is that what
pushed you over the edge
and made you join, Captain?
Yeah, right.
If anything, that just made me
wanna tell you "hell no."
Wait, for real?
[SEKIZAN]
Yeah. For real.
A rugby team is
made up of 15 players.
Having a couple of motivated
guys on the team means nothing.
Sit around waiting for
the upperclassmen to retire,
and your own retirement'll
sneak up on ya.
It'll be staring you in
the face before you know it.
Sorry, buddy. I did not
have that kinda time.
What? But you came back
to the club room!
Yeah, I did, but honestly,
I came so I could turn you down.
[knocking]
[SEKIZAN]
Anybody around?
Nobody's here.
Why am I not surprised?
[HACHIOJI grunts]
[HACHIOJI panting]
I need to practice getting
lower when I make a hit.
[HACHIOJI yells, grunts]
[HACHIOJI panting]
[SEKIZAN]
Hey.
Uh. Ah!
[HACHIOJI]
Sekizan!
How come you're just
standing there like that?
That was a pass
from a genius, right?
The note--I wrote it.
Yeah. It was kinda obvious.
[HACHIOJI chuckles]
[SEKIZAN] You told me not to
underestimate rugby, didn't you?
Yeah.
Then teach me how to play.
Would you be willing to?
Uh...
[HACHIOJI chuckles]
[HACHIOJI]
That's it!
Next time you throw it,
put a little spin on it, okay?
Use your wrist!
[SEKIZAN]
Like that?
[HACHIOJI]
Yeah, just like that!
Did you notice how the ball flew
a lot straighter that time?
[SEKIZAN]
Yeah.
[HACHIOJI]
Now! Let's try catching!
It's a piece of cake,
just get under the ball and
bring it to your chest!
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[HACHIOJI]
You got it, Seki! Good job!
[SEKIZAN]
This is pretty fun!
[HACHIOJI] Oh, we're just
getting started, pal!
This isn't rugby yet!
Guys. I'm feeling
very emotional!
Yeah! That story rules!
I'm fired up!
Hey, come! Let's practice,
Wait. What? Right now?
[GION]
Move it or lose it, tree trunk!
Hey, if you wanna practice,
you have to wait for me, Gion!
Excuse me!
Hey, try not to work too hard!
As far as the newbie's go,
I think we did pretty
darn well this year.
Yeah. I'm looking forward
to training camp.
Ya know, this is it.
Our last summer.
[SEKIZAN]
Next time: "X Day."