This was a great contest.
It's been a long time since a
game got our guys that fired up.
[WADA]
Thank you.
Let's do it again.
[HIROTA]
Hey!
Dude. What's wrong?
You seem down in the dumps.
He's been like
this all day long.
Well that's okay.
There's nothing wrong
with getting emotional.
--[SEKIZAN growls]
--[HACHIOJI gasps]
Don't you see?
Guys. If we played
at the beginning
like we played them
at the end, we--
We coulda...
We coulda won it all!
Like I said, all day.
That's unfortunate.
But he's not far off.
We may be getting
a little better,
but a loss is still a loss.
We're not good enough yet.
We gotta get stronger.
If we don't,
we're never gonna win.
[SEKIZAN]
It was that moment!
That damn scrum at the end!
Now that's enough, buddy.
Chill.
Boys, we're going to the beach.
[RUGBY TEAM]
The beach?
Whoa. That sounds fun!
Yeah, totally. When do we go?
I need some
new swim trunks!
Get ready, gentlemen,
because we're meeting
there in one hour.
It's about six kilometers
to the Arukimizu coast,
the closest beach to Jinko.
I'm heading there now in my car.
You guys'll be getting
there on foot.
Huh?
[KOMORI]
Better get moving.
You're joking, right?
He's for real.
[RUGBY TEAM]
What?!
[UMENO]
All right, Coach.
So far it's been 40 minutes.
[EBUMI panting]
[UMENO] Nice, Ebumi.
You made it in first.
[EBUMI panting]
[KOMORI] Hey. Don't stop moving.
You'll get cramps.
[UMENO]
Here they come, Coach!
[HIROTA panting]
[UMENO]
Hey! Hirota!
The hour's up,
but don't stop now!
All right.
Now we're gonna pair up
and do wheelbarrows.
Ten 50-meter laps each, boys.
[SUMIYOSHI] Seriously?
We just ran for freakin' ever.
[NOKA] Whatever,
at least it's nice out.
[KOMORI]
Begin!
[NOKA]
All right, Coach!
[yelps]
[NOKA]
This sucks, big time!
[RUGBY TEAM grunting]
[UMENO] Come on, guys!
You're doing great!
[KOMORI]
Hey.
How much longer you
gonna lay there, chubs?
[HIROTA]
Hey, shut up!
Don't make fun of
fatty's problems!
[KOMORI]
Build a bridge and get over it.
Coach.
[RUGBY TEAM]
We're all done!
[KOMORI]
Good work.
Now carry each other
for 20 laps. Go!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Huh?!
[KOMORI]
Now!
[RUGBY TEAM grunting]
[GION]
Just how heavy are you, dude?
[KAMO grunts]
[KAMO]
Gion!
[grunting]
Not bad, man.
Hey. Thanks, but
this is nothing.
Nothing at all, my friend.
[EBUMI grunting]
[yelling]
Stupid crab! Damn you!
Nice catch.
Like I said, man. It's nothing.
[HACHIOJI grunting]
You're heavy.
We're not newlyweds, so stop
clasping your hands like that.
What?
[HIRANO]
You guys...
I need a partner;
does somebody wanna pair up?
[HIROTA]
How about me?
No, thank you.
Well. Good job, boys.
It's time for the next
exercise. Miss Manager?
[UMENO]
Yes, Coach!
Shovels?
[KOMORI]
Start digging.
[KIBI, SHINSHI, ISE]
Huh?
Trust me on this one.
Digging holes uses almost
every muscle in your body.
Besides, it's good anytime
you have to dig in your heels.
Back at school, we
don't have the necessary
equipment for
proper weight training.
But public beaches are free.
[RUGBY TEAM]
What?!
Time to get to work, boys.
[NOKA]
Man, this sucks!
[KIFUNE] And it has nothing
to do with rugby!
[MATSUO]
Oh, come on!
I've never dug a
hole before, have you?
It's gonna build up muscles
we don't even realize we have.
If this'll help us get stronger,
then it'll help us
win games, too!
[SEKIZAN grunting]
Whoa, dude.
Holy moly! Sekizan's going hard!
Once you're done digging,
you can fill 'em back up.
[RUGBY TEAM]
What?!
[UMENO laughs]
[RUGBY TEAM]
We're all finished, Coach!
[KOMORI]
Okay. That's enough.
[RUGBY TEAM chattering]
All right, forwards.
Gather 'round.
Let's see how
you boys sumo wrestle.
Wait. Sumo?
Oh, right.
You're bummed 'cause the
May Natsu Bosho Tournament
just ended.
I don't give
a damn about sumo;
what I care about is
winning rugby matches.
Get in position.
All right, gentlemen. Begin!
[SHINSHI grunts]
[HACHIOJI laughs]
Nice takedown!
What's happening here?
[HACHIOJI]
No one can beat Hirota
in a head-to-head competition!
[KOMORI]
One more time.
Wait. Are you serious, Coach?
Do you see, gentlemen?
That's it. That's the
stance, my friends.
It's called ruck posture.
Generally speaking,
the lower player wins in a ruck.
If you start from that
position, you'll prevail.
[BOTH grunting]
[KOMORI]
Push your opponent up diagonally
and when he gives,
flip him over.
[SHINSHI grunts]
[SHINSHI]
All right!
That's how you do it, kid.
It'll work every single time.
Plus, the sand is soft.
It'll help you improve your
balance and footing.
If you practice this move,
you will see results.
That look super fun!
Can I join in? Hirota, fight me!
All right, then.
Come and get me, squirt.
Get ready, gentlemen.
[KAMO] If I win, you owe
me some fried chicken!
[HIROTA gasps]
I just remembered.
He ate the fried chicken in
my lunch box the other day,
that sneaky little jerk wad!
--[KOMORI] Begin!
--[KAMO] Take this!
[HIROTA] Take this and this
and this and this and this!
That's what you get
for eating my food!
[laughing]
Did they just...
...vanish?
Oh!
We forgot to fill
a hole over there!
Guys! Are you okay?
[HACHIOJI]
Hey, Kamo! Where are you?
Quick! Somebody!
Go get a shovel!
[SHINSHI sighs]
That was rough!
[HYOSU]
I'm dying!
[HACHIOJI]
Are you okay, buddy?
I'm dead...
Do you know how many days
there are till the prelims?
One hundred forty-seven,
to be exact.
If we practice two hours
a day, that's 294 hours.
Less than 13 days.
That's not a lot of time.
But it's up to you
how you spend it.
If you wanna win,
then you have to work.
Wait. Only 13 days?
Crap. That's not enough time.
At this rate,
we're totally screwed.
[SUMIYOSHI]
Captain?
No. We're not screwed.
Let's double up.
We'll do morning practices here.
Well. Get yourselves
ready, then.
[NOKA groans]
[HIROTA]
Sekizan, you idiot!
Why the hell did
you say that, man?
[MAROUDO]
This sucks.
Well, I'm gonna have a
little fun while I still can!
Let's go swimming, everyone!
[KIBI]
Hey! What about your clothes?
[MAROUDO] I don't care.
Just leave 'em there, Kibi!
[SUMIYOSHI]
Oh, man! It's freezing!
[TAKEBE] I kinda wanna try
playing the number 8 role.
I dunno, maybe it's too hard.
Oh, I think I'd
rather be a back!
[IWASHIMIZU]
It's fun, but it's really hard.
We have some pretty good ones.
Hey, you'll play prop, right?
[MIKAMI]
Why, 'cause 'a how I look?
[HIRANO]
Yeah! Totally!
[GROUP laughing]
[TAKEBE] I just hope we're
assigned positions soon.
That way we can play!
[HIRANO]
Yeah!
[GION] Hey. I wanna
talk to you for a sec.
Hey. I didn't ask
you to sit. Beat it.
No way.
I overheard the freshmen
talking just now.
They were all gossiping
about what positions
they might wanna play.
I have a question
I wanna ask you.
So... do you think I'd
make a decent wing?
Or is there another spot
that would suit me better?
How did you make your decision?
[OHARANO]
I dunno.
I was playing fly-half before
I knew what was what.
Probably because I was the best
player at my rugby school.
[groans]
Dammit!
I freakin' hate being small.
I wish I was my brother!
He's almost as tall
as the captain is!
You have a big
brother? For real?
Yeah. Do you?
A younger one, yeah.
He invited me to Rugby School.
A long time ago.
Whoa.
That's cool that your
brother plays rugby.
[GION] I guess my brother
should probably play, too.
He's got the size,
that's for sure.
He's the opposite of me.
I'm small and I can't pass or
catch the ball to save my life.
You're lucky, dude.
You can do everything.
[OHARANO'S LITTLE BROTHER]
You're lucky.
You can do everything.
[OHARANO'S LITTLE BROTHER]
You're lucky.
You can do everything.
[OHARANO'S LITTLE BROTHER]
The best player on the team
always plays fly-half.
Come on. That's not true.
[COACH 10A]
Oharano! Oharano! Come here!
Go on. Coach is calling!
[OHARANO] Hey. He could
be calling for you.
Right?
Please. Get real.
[OHARANO'S LITTLE BROTHER]
When the coach calls out
our last name,
he's always calling for you.
[OHARANO]
Hey, Gion. Do you like rugby?
[GION]
Hm?
Hm...
[OHARANO]
I hate it.
[GION]
Well, as a matter of fact--
I don't know if
I'm sure anymore.
I pretty much suck ass!
I can barely play at all!
And I didn't even get a chance
to go in the game the other day.
I wouldn't exactly
say I'm having fun.
Why're you still
digging? Moron.
Oh, shut up!
[OHARANO yells]
[spitting]
Hey, what was that for?!
Because you're a moron, too!
If you hate it
so much, why play?
[OHARANO growls]
Shut up!
--[GION yells]
--[OHARANO] Shut up!
[GION]
Hey! Timeout, okay?
My brother!
Till my brother plays
again, I won't quit!
There! Are ya happy? Jerk!
He loved it so much.
Way more than I ever did.
It was his favorite sport.
[OHARANO]
It was all he ever wanted.
It's his everything.
[OHARANO]
For years,
he sat there and
was forced to watch.
And he never complained!
Even when he couldn't
do something
he still had a
positive attitude!
[GION]
I wasn't serious!
It doesn't matter
if I'm facing hot shots
like you or Ebumi.
Or big guys like
Hirota and Iwashi!
I'll take you all down
no matter what it takes!
I'll show you idiots
how strong I am!
I'll show you
I have what it takes!
Good luck with that, jerk.
Jerk?!
You just wait and see, man!
[OHARANO]
You're delusional!
Delusional? I'm not!
[OHARANO]
Yes, you are!
[GION]
No, I'm not!
[OHARANO]
Yes, you are!
[GION]
No, I'm not, jerk!
--[GION] You're an ass!
--[OHARANO] You are!
--[OHARANO] Don't tell me!
--[GION] Shut your damn mouth!
[OHARANO]
You shut yours!
[GION]
You throw sand like a woman!
[OHARANO]
No!
[GION]
You like that, butthead?
[BOTH panting]
[GION]
I can't lift my arms anymore.
This kinda practice
is good for you.
It'll make you a strong tackler.
Keep trying. And you'll improve.
Yeah. Well...
I don't really understand
rugby, to be totally honest.
But I do like tackling.
I think you'd
like playing forward.
It's suited for cocky idiots.
[OHARANO]
Then again, playing flanker
might be more your style, Gion.
'Cause you get
to hit the big guys.
[GION]
Which one is the flanker again?
[OHARANO] Maybe rugby
isn't for you after all.
[GION]
Give me a minute! I'll remember!
[ALL groaning]
[NOKA]
Our clothes... they're gone!
Idiots.
[school bell ringing]
Wait, you want to be
a flanker? For real?
For real.
The only problem is
I'm not 100 percent sure
what that position entails.
I'm hoping someone
will show me the ropes.
You as a flanker?
That might not be a bad idea!
You know what?
We don't have
practice this Sunday.
Okay, I got a
great idea, Gion.
[GION]
Hm?
[KAMO]
You and I should go and spy
on the champions of Kanagawa!
[GION]
Ryoin?
[KAMO]
That's right!
[KAMO] They've made it to
Nationals 15 years in a row now.
Ryoin Gakuen is the strongest
team in Kanagawa by far.
[KAMO]
Don't mind us!
We're just a couple of average
middle school kids here
to take a tour of your campus!
Do you really think anyone's
gonna believe that story?
Instead of me explaining
to you what a flanker does,
I figure it makes way
more sense for you
to watch Kanagawa's best
flanker live and in the flesh.
[GION]
Right.
[KAMO] Today, they're
playing Kanto Gakuen.
They made the Kanagawa
quarter finals last year.
It should be a pretty good game.
[GION groans]
[KAMO] To say it in the simple
words of Old Man Komori,
[KOMORI]
"Steal it."
[GION]
Steal what?
[KAMO]
Uh... His technique, I guess?
[GIRLS cheering]
[KAMO] Uh-oh. Looks like
they've already started.
[GIRLS cheering]
[GIRL 10A]
Let's go, Sekito! You got this!
[cheering continues]
Gion, do you wanna
watch from over there?
Yeah. Sure.
[KAMO] Seems like a
good enough spot to me.
Let's see, now.
Where's the flanker?
Be on the lookout for
number 6 or number 7
on the blue team.
Right.
[KOKUTO grunts]
Whoa! Talk about a perfect hit!
[GION]
Number 7! That's him!
He's huge!
So that's the best flanker
in all of Kanagawa?
[KAMO laughs]
Well, second best.
[GION]
Huh?
Ha! I don't care
how big you are!
Or how good you are at tackling!
It doesn't matter if you miss!
That was so low!
Thanks.
Look alive!
Number 6!
[KANTO 10B]
Dammit! Get the ball back, guys!
Sekito!
[SEKITO]
Got it!
[KANTO 10B]
Surround him! We'll crush him!
Whoa!
[GION]
He just dove through their legs!
[GIRLS cheering]
[whistle blows]
That, my dear friend,
is Kanagawa's best flanker.
Number 7's good,
but he's better.
His name's Sekito.
Nice pass, bro.
Nice try.
[KAMO] And number 7, that
gigantopithicus right there,
is his twin brother Kokuto.
[GION]
Damn. He's good.
He's better than good.
He might be the best rugby
player I've ever seen.
Craziest part is
he's not even the biggest
guy on their team.
But his spot's secure.
Because of his low form,
quickness, and tremendous build.
[GION]
So cool.
[KAMO] Make sure you're
paying attention, Gion!
[GION]
Gotcha!
[GION] Wow! Can you believe
how fast that guy is?
[KAMO]
I know, right?
[ZANBA]
What are you two doing here?
[GION]
What?
We're spying on them, of course!
You think you'll
learn anything good?
[GION]
Holy crap!
Who the hell are you, man?
[KAMO gasps]
[KAMO]
Huh? A Ryoin jersey?
Wait. How come you're
here and not out there?
Because I'm running late today.
I ate way too much shaved
ice before the game started.
Now I have a bad tummy ache.
[ZANBA] Next time: "You Have
No Feel for the Game."