[RYOIN NUMBER 10 grunts]
Halftime's close. Really close.
[KASUGA grunts]
[JINKO TEAM,
RYOIN TEAM grunting]
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A]
Pile up!
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A] That's the end
of the first half!
[UMENO]
Jinko has the lead!
We're up 12 to nothing!
All right!
[HACHIOJI]
Hey, guys, wait up!
I'm sorry we kept
screwin' things up
during the first half!
Hey, at least we're
winning, right?
That was a sweet try,
by the way!
[HACHIOJI]
Lucky is what it was.
Let's focus on the second half!
[ISE]
Right!
[KOMORI]
Sounds like they're aware
of their own performance.
[KOMORI]
In that case,
there's nothin' for
me to say to 'em.
What's gotten into
you guys today?
I barely recognize
you out there.
You're givin' your
best every play
and leaving it all on the field.
There's no doubt, they're
a more athletic squad,
and they're faster, too.
But you boys are
stayin' with 'em.
Excellent work.
But, don't let it go to
your heads, all right?
They're gonna step up their
game in the second half.
If you keep the focus you had
in the first part of the game,
we'll win.
Let's give 'em
everything we've got!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yes, sir!
There's not much to say.
Your passes are much faster,
your skills and techniques
are far more advanced,
and as far as experience goes,
you've got the edge
in that category, too.
So does someone
wanna tell me why
you let them score two tries?
Because, Coach.
We underestimated their players.
We assumed Jinko was nothing
but a joke of a team.
But we were wrong.
And they made us pay for it.
That's right. They sure did.
But now it's your turn,
men. Let's pay them back.
Win the game.
[MINAMOTO]
One more thing.
Regardless of the outcome,
every single one of you
is running laps,
first and second string.
--[RYOIN TEAM] Right!
--Not fair!
The second half
starts right now!
Let's go!
[yelling]
[MIKADO]
Yes!
Hey, Coach.
To be completely honest,
I was surprised you
wanted to play Jinko.
It's fine. It's just
a little strange is all.
It's our second string.
Those boys have
a long way to go.
I thought they could use
a kick in the rear.
Sometimes, when a
player wins too much,
they get too cocky.
I'm no exception.
And neither are you.
The truth is,
I knew Jinko wasn't gonna
come out here and lay down.
But I had no idea
their coach used to play
for the national team and
I had no idea he'd be able
to coach them up to the level
they're competing at today.
[TSUKINAKA]
Apparently, he keeps a blog.
[MINAMOTO]
I saw it.
He says he's been
putting them through
a bunch of old school,
outdated exercises.
But I guess it's working
all right so far.
The drills he runs
are nothing special.
Just your basic training.
Agility and strength.
But what is special is how hard
his players are willing to work.
How badly they wanna win.
[KASUGA grunts]
[MINAMOTO] For them,
this isn't a scrimmage at all.
It's the real deal.
And they don't care that
we're better than them either.
They're gonna give us
everything they've got
till the bitter end.
Giving our guys the "what for"
is only gonna build
their confidence level.
And with the Kanagawa
prelims coming up,
nothing could be worse for us.
[MINAMOTO] A team's mental
toughness can be
the difference between
them advancing
and getting knocked out.
[MINAMOTO]
The question is:
what are we gonna do about it?
[yelling]
Jinko!
[panting]
[MIKADO, SEKIZAN grunt]
Sekizan!
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A] Jinko failed
to release the ball!
Yeah. We paid 'em back!
[HACHIOJI]
Shake it off, Sekizan!
[whistle blows]
It's Ryoin's line-out!
Come on, you guys,
stop 'em right here!
[HIROTA] They're leaving
a pretty big gap open.
But which way will they go?
Look behind!
[gasps]
I'm comin' through!
[KIBI gasps]
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A]
Try!
Nice job! Way to go, dude!
Stay on the attack, guys!
Let's kill 'em!
[whistle blows]
Aw, crap. They made it!
It's 12 to seven now!
Come on. Fight back!
You got this, guys!
[MINAMOTO]
Tch.
Hm?
What do you want?
I'm not letting you
out of laps, kid.
Their failure is your failure.
[gasps]
[MINAMOTO]
Hey, Ref!
Ryoin would like to make
a substitution! At Number 8!
Tosa's coming out--
Zanba's going in!
Hey, Coach. You sure?
Yeah.
Look, we don't wanna show
them all of our cards.
But a few is fine.
We probably could've beat them
without Ryujin in the game.
But, hey, what the hell?
I wanna trample on
their confidence
till there's none left.
[SUMIYOSHI]
You've gotta be kidding me!
I thought we were just playing
their second string!
Check it out, tree trunk,
the Giant of Ryoin!
Are you ready to knock
him off his block?
No, but I am ready
to pee in my pants.
Well, well.
Ryoin's coach must
be pretty worried,
putting him in the game.
[MINAMOTO] If we let Jinko's
morale getting any higher,
it could come back
to bite us hard.
Besides, with the way our
second string's been playing,
I think they could use a
little inspiration, don't you?
Then I'd say you've put in
the right player then, Coach.
He's inspiring, all right.
If there's one player
built to break a team's
spirit, it's him.
[IWASHIMIZU]
With the big guy in the game,
we can't let them get
possession of the ball.
We have to stay on the attack.
Make a move downfield!
[IWASHIMIZU gasps]
[IWASHIMIZU grunts]
[SHINSHI]
Iwashimizu!
[KASHIMA]
Zanba's coming!
[SHINSHI]
Stop him!
[KASHIMA grunts]
[SHINSHI groans]
[yells]
Suck on this!
[yelps]
[HIROTA groans]
Ya big freak! You're goin' down!
[GION, KASUGA yell]
[ZANBA]
Hm. Not bad.
[KASUGA yelps]
[EBUMI, GION groan]
[BOTH gasp]
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A]
Try!
I like you guys.
Your team goes all out.
That's a good sign. You have
to want to kill your opponent.
I feel the exact
same way about you.
I wanna kill you all
and eat you for dinner.
[ZANBA] Ya know what
makes this sport fun?
The violence.
[ZANBA laughs]
Make the kick or else.
[MARODO]
Jeez. You see that play?
That can't be legal!
[NOKA] The second he
stepped onto the field,
the momentum flipped!
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[SEKIZAN]
Coach. What is it?
[KOMORI] Why do you look so
down in the dumps, Captain?
Up until a few moments ago,
you boys were all smiles.
There you just caught
that pass didn't you?
And I'm a former
national player!
I know you boys have
a lotta fight left in you.
So use it.
Get out there and battle 'em
until the last whistle blows!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[KASUGA grunts]
I don't like how he plays.
It's just not fair.
Look, I work hard for this.
Harder than anyone else
on this team by far.
I don't have a choice,
'cause I'm the smallest guy.
[whistle blows]
[SEKITO] But watching him
barrel down the field so easily
makes it all seem pointless.
The guy's like an animal.
He devours everything
in his path.
What's wrong with you, kid?
You upset I didn't put
you in the game, too?
Not at all, Coach. I'm fine
just stayin' right where I am
[BOTH panting]
It's not over. Not unless
we stop fighting back!
[whistle blows]
[BOTH panting]
Not good.
[BOTH gasping]
[gasping]
[UMENO]
We're running out of time!
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[SEKIZAN yells]
[gasps]
[whistle blows]
[UMENO]
That's it. Game's over.
[KOMORI]
Thank you, Coach and good match.
That was incredibly
informative for us.
--No, no. Thank you, Coach.
--[TSUKINAKA] Come on, guys.
--We learned a lot today, too.
--Time to run some laps!
--[RYOIN TEAM] Right.
Guess what? Next time,
you're goin' down!
We're gonna kick your butt!
Get real, nerd!
We'd never lose to a
bunch of jerks like you.
Bet that!
Sekki. Are you okay, man?
Yeah.
[ZANBA]
Hey.
That was an awesome game.
You know something?
You're cool. I like you.
You guys went all out
till the very end.
Uh... Thank you, man.
[ZANBA] I don't think a good
rugby player is someone
who's really fast, or
someone who's super strong,
or someone with
perfect technique.
It's the guy who gets people
excited when he plays.
The guy who, the moment
he steps on the field,
has the crowd right
in the palm of his hand.
Someone whose love and passion
for the game is infectious.
I'm not sure how to
explain it exactly,
but you guys have it.
[ZANBA]
And that made our game worth it.
It made it fun.
I can't wait to play you again.
See you at the prelims, Jinko.
[TSUKINAKA]
Ryujin! Hurry up, will ya?
[ZANBA]
Yeah, yeah.
[TSUKINAKA] Wha-- Hey!
Not cool! Stop it! Ryujin!
[ZANBA]
Stop squirming, Captain.
[TSUKINAKA]
Put me down, now!
[GION]
I can't believe we lost.
Where're we goin' now?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Davos Hill.
The seniors said something
about it being a tradition.
[GION] Wait, Davos Hill?
What The heck is that?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Who knows?
All I know is the older guys
said they go every year.
[GION laughs]
So this is it!
Sweet!
This place is so cool!
Are we gonna camp out here?
Well, they're having
fun. Too much.
If they think this
is a camping trip,
they're gonna be bummed.
Last year, the hike
was totally brutal.
[NOKA]
Yeah, and that was before Coach.
We've worked hard.
We've all learned a lot, too.
But there's one more
hurdle left to cross.
And that's the conquering
of Davos Hill.
Sprint to the peak.
Move it, men!
[JINKO TEAM]
What?
We're screwed.
Totally. How far is it
to the very top?
I don't know!
This sucks!
Hey, Gramps. Are you
comin' along?
Yeah, I am.
I'll do my best, but I'm not
sure I can make it to the top.
But the Captain can handle
the conversation up there.
Hey! Don't call him
"Gramps," Gion!
[JINKO TEAM panting]
[panting] This is
a pretty steep hill.
[groans] I hate Davos so much!
There's way too much grass,
and it's muddy, too!
Did you come here with
your middle school
squad back in the day?
Yeah, and it sucked then, too.
Everybody who comes to
Sugadaira ends up on this hill!
I think I'm gonna die!
Huh?
[HIROTA panting]
[HIRANO]
Come on, Hirota! You can do it!
Hey, check it out, guys!
Ebumi's all the way
out in front.
Damn!
Come on.
Let's see if we can
catch up to him!
[NOKA] Damn it! Ebumi's
not gonna beat me!
Hey, Gion. Be careful.
It's really steep!
[GION yelps]
[HACHIOJI laughs]
This brings back memories!
Remember when we came
here as freshman?
It rained all morning long.
The entire hill was
like a mudslide!
Oh, yeah!
Hirota fell and rolled
all the way down!
[laughs] Man, forgot about that!
[HIROTA]
Hey!
[GROUP]
Huh?
Ya jerks!
Are you talking shit
about me again?
[OHIE]
How did you even hear us?
[HACHIOJI] No, we weren't
talkin' smack. Swear!
Man. This sucks, bad.
This's our last run.
We better make it count.
[HYOSU, KASUGA panting]
[BOTH panting]
[HIROTA yelps]
[KAMO] You guys! Hirota
tripped and fell again!
[OHIE]
Hirota! Don't roll down, buddy!
[HIROTA]
Shut up! Stop lookin' at me!
[JINKO TEAM laughs]
[UMENO]
Hey, Coach!
[MIKI]
Sorry we're late!
[UMENO]
You're really out of shape!
Well, look who it is
and with a pretty gal
hangin' on each
of your arms, too.
You're too kind, Coach!
What are you talking about?
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
For takin' our stuff to the inn.
That was a a big load off
and I know you were there
to lend a hand, too, Miss Ikita.
Uh. Well. I was.
But it was my pleasure, really.
At first, my uncle made a big
fuss about going to the game.
But he was pumped after.
He said, "Get 'em next time!
And visit real soon!"
If it weren't for you, Coach,
we wouldn't've stood a chance.
Oh, I don't know.
The boys deserve the credit.
All I did was stand there.
They're the ones who
fought the fight.
They're the reason Ryoin
put in a first stringer.
It was all them.
What they did today
was incredible. Truly.
If you wanna give some praise.
Give it to those kids,
'cause they gave it their all.
Besides, I'm all washed up.
Like a moldy pile of leaves.
[laughs] Moldy. Ha!
So what does that make me,
Coach? The water?
Huh. I don't know,
let's see here.
Maybe a worm.
[UMENO] What? I don't wanna
be a worm--that's gross!
[KOMORI] Then I suppose
that leaves you, Yoshida?
I've got a good one for you.
I think you're the earth.
[MARODO]
Guys! They're finally here!
[JINKO TEAM panting]
--[UMENO] Gosh, that hill is
--[ISE] Whoa!
--way too high.
--Are you gonna be okay, Coach?
I'm fine.
I used to be able to run laps
up and down this stupid hill!
Hey, you guys.
I think he might need some help!
Get up, Teach.
You look like a ratty old cloth!
[KOMORI]
Well.
I haven't been up
here in a long time.
Tell me, freshman. What do
you think of the view?
Huh?
This is so awesome. Ha, ha.
Well, I've completely forgotten
what I was gonna
say to you, boys.
[KOMORI]
Screw it. Meeting's over.
[JINKO TEAM]
Wha...?!
Captain? You're up.
Say somethin' inspirational.
Uh. Right. Sure.
We finally won a game or two.
Then, when we went
up against Ryoin,
we gave it our best shot.
And even though we still lost,
I'm so proud. 'Cause
we all learned a lot.
And we're a better team.
I've never worked
this hard before,
but it was worth
every drop of sweat.
[KOMORI] You're talkin'
about yourself? Wow.
What? Oh. No. I just--
I feel the same way!
Me, too. The captain's right!
He always is!
I know I gave it
my all. Every day.
Yep.
This fatty gave it
his all, Coach!
We worked so hard.
And we ate a heck
of a lotta food!
It's true. The food was awesome.
We did work our butts off!
I'm really glad we
came to this camp!
You worked hard, too, Ebumi.
You're a super creep.
We did our best!
Yeah, I guess.
I'm proud of us!
Yeah. Me, too!
Know what? We should
all be proud!
We gave it everything we had!
Like Zanba said. All... Uh...
All about?
No. All out!
All about! That's the
only way Jinko plays!
[GROUP]
No! All out!
Yeah, I went "all out," too!
And, guys--woo!
It was so kick ass!
Sure was!
Ha! Good. That's great to hear.
We have two hours
before we leave, boys.
Your time's your own.
[JINKO TEAM]
Yes, sir!
Guys!
We got some balls to play!
[GION]
Sweet! Let's run a few drills!
Hanazono, here we come!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yeah!