[KOMORI] It's important
to watch high-level games.
It's even more important
to play in high-level games
against high-level opponents.
But the most important
thing of all is to learn
from one another
through your experiences:
to let your teammates
be your guide.
If you wanna be a great player,
there's nothing more effective.
[KOMORI]
So, no matter what,
make sure you're always
teaching each other.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
It's a real pleasure
to meet you.
The name's Haijima Yuji.
I'm the coach of
the Keijo Rugby Team.
I think this joint practice
session is a great idea--
I know we're both
gonna learn a whole lot.
Pleasure's ours.
We just watched the video
of your game against Sagami.
They've whipped us pretty good
a couple of times before.
But I gotta say,
I was very impressed,
your guys really held their
own in the second half.
What a game.
And then I heard the Jinko team
had a brave new leader,
so I reached out right away.
I figured my boys could learn
a thing or two from you, Coach.
The way I see it, the more
opportunities we have to work
with other players,
the better off we'll be.
Thanks for the invite.
We're just glad
to be here, Coach.
[gasping] Komori's a legend!
He was a member of
the national team!
What should I do, Iwashi?
[IWASHIMIZU yelps] Stop digging
your claws into me, man,
you're gonna draw blood!
Sekizan! Oh, man!
That game! You were so great!
[laughs] I love watching...
You guys really
gave it your all!
Thanks man, but don't
you think we outta
do something about them?
[OGI]
It's good to see you, Oharano.
Hey! It's me, Ogi!
All right, you morons!
Shut your damn mouths!
Move your sorry butts and
get warmed up right now!
[RUGBY PLAYERS shriek]
Sorry, Coach.
But if you give
those boys an inch,
they'll take a mile
and then some.
Please, I'm in the same
exact boat with my team.
I think you and I are gonna
get along just fine, Coach.
[HAIJIMA] I was thinkin' that
since we have so many players
to contend with,
it might be a good idea
to split up into
forwards and backs.
[KOMORI]
Sounds like a plan.
Hey, what're you doin'?
Backs are over there, Gion.
I'm right where
I need to be then.
Yeah?
Because starting today...
...I'm playin' flanker!
[SEKIZAN, HACHIOJI]
Uh...
Hey oh! The little guy's
found his voice!
Welcome to the big
leagues, tiny mite!
So he's a flanker now?
Is this a joke?
What? So Gion and Iwashi
are both over there?
[SEKIZAN]
Well, this is news.
[GION]
The thing is...
See, Kanagwa's number 1--
[TAIRA] We should be
friends, you and me!
[GION] I mean, Kanagawa's
number 2 flanker told me
I'd excel in that role!
[HACHIOJI] Wait, did you
talk to the twin brothers
who play for Ryoin?
--[blow lands]
--[TAIRA yelps]
[SEKIZAN] Truth is, we don't
have enough forwards
coming through
the ranks right now.
Might as well see how it goes.
Since we're practicing
together today,
how 'bout we form a scrum?
Sweet.
Scrum? Awesome! I'm in!
Uh...
Scrums are cool.
They're radical, man!
And I wanna learn how to do 'em!
Well! He's got taste!
In that case, get ready, kid!
If you really wanna join our
scrum, we need a flanker.
[GION]
I'm just your guy!
[HACHIOJI]
You're really nice. Thank you.
Listen up.
A scrum is made up of
three rows of forwards.
Number 1 to number 3
are the front row.
Number 4 and number 5
make up the second row.
And number 6 to number 8
are the back row.
Right.
[HISAKAWA] Hey, kid.
You ever done the turtle?
Yeah. A lot!
That's the basic posture.
Try to push my backside
with your shoulder, okay?
Yeah. Cool.
The name is Taira
Tadakazu, gentlemen!
I'm the best hooker
in the league!
So, are you ready to
get started, kid?
[GION]
Okay.
[HISAKAWA]
Here's the deal.
Some flankers just
pretend to push
since they're on the
outside edge of the pack.
But there're no free rides
in a Keijo scrum,
I can promise you that.
So push as hard as you can.
[MASA]
Crouch. Bind. Set!
[yells]
[RUGBY PLAYERS
grunting, yelling]
[GION grunts]
Push back harder, kid!
Get even lower!
Straighten up your back!
Come on, dig deeper!
[GION grunts]
All right.
[grunts]
[HISAKAWA]
That was piss poor.
But, it was your first time.
You must've felt it
during the Sagami game.
When a team gives
everything they've got,
day in and day out,
that combined effort
becomes the foundation
for creating a winning mindset.
It's not just in games.
It starts with how you practice.
[GION]
Damnit!
That sucked. I sucked.
More scrums! From this
moment forward,
I wanna be in every scrum I can!
[KOMORI] Your kids keep
a positive attitude
during practice. I admire that.
[HAIJIMA]
Thank you, Coach.
I feel the exact same
way about yours.
But I gotta say, your team's
demeanor has changed completely
from when we played
them a month ago.
Tell me your secret--
what are you
feedin' them, Coach?
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you,
but if I told you that,
I'm afraid I'd have to
kill you right here.
Touché!
You almost ready?
Boys. Take a water break!
Drink up, because
when you're done,
we're playing a scrimmage!
Well, you heard the Coach,
spilt into teams A and B!
Come and get your
uniforms, guys!
[MIYUKI] Iwashi. Since
we're on the same team,
maybe I won't get
hurt this time!
Ha. Very funny, man.
[MIYUKI chuckles]
[GION growls]
[HIRANO] Wow. This line-up
really rocks, you guys!
[HAIJIMA]
This may be a practice game,
but you better not hold back!
[KOMORI] Every chance to play
is a chance to get better.
Oh, man.
They're so lucky they
get to be on a line-up
with players from Keijo.
I just wish I could
be out there with 'em.
It looks so fun.
[HAIJIMA]
Team B will kick off! Begin!
[whistle blows]
Sekizan!
Holy crap. They're
already goin' all out!
[TANASHI groans]
[HISAKAWA grunts]
[KANAI]
An interception! Aw, crap.
Get that ball!
[IWASHIMIZU] Hey, Miyuki,
watch their number 8.
Whenever he's about
to be tackled,
he'll get rid of the ball.
[MIYUKI] I watched the video
of the Jinko Sagami game.
I studied his moves.
He waits until he's
tackled to pass.
Almost every single
time, without fail.
Iwashi was spot on.
[IWASHIMIZU] Since Sekizan's
so powerful and strong,
he can always keep the ball
in play, even after he's hit.
But it's become
a habit for him.
I bet he hasn't even
realized it himself.
[IWASHIMIZU]
Neither has anyone else.
[SHINSHI]
You're not going anywhere!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Except me.
I took note of it.
Damn right.
[KANAI yells]
[KANAI grunts]
[yells]
[MIYUKI grunts]
[whistle blows]
Wow.
That number 10 is the best
fly-half I've ever seen!
Yeah. He's got
some serious game.
But don't you think
Iwashi's play seems
a little different than normal?
[HACHIOJI]
I forgot that about him.
I remember it now though.
Iwashi's good,
but he gets even better
when he's side by side
with really excellent players.
[HACHIOJI]
They make a terrifying tandem,
that's for sure.
[EBUMI]
Hey, Matsuo!
[MATSUO]
Hm?
[EBUMI]
Aren't you stoked about this?
After all, we didn't get to play
in the last match against Keijo.
I mean, I know this is
technically a scrimmage,
but a game is still
a game, right?
Plus, this gives us a chance
to jack up these d-bags!
[cackles]
Ebumi's kinda scary.
And he's really quick.
We shouldn't let him
get the ball.
Huh? I wouldn't worry
about Ebumi too much.
After all, he's going
toe to toe with Ogi Yoichi,
Keijo's fastest runner.
You still worried?
[IWASHIMIZU sighs]
Maybe.
[MIYUKI]
Understood.
Hey, centers! Come here!
[TAKEBE, ISE]
Huh?
It's a good match so far.
Though I'm a little disappointed
in some of my players--
they're a bit off
their game out there.
They're young players.
At this age, they
haven't settled into
their own style
of play just yet.
As a result, when they see
somethin' new, they emulate it.
Heh. 'Course that's why
they're so much fun to coach.
[KIBI, FUSHIMI grunt]
Team A intercepted it!
[HONKAWA]
They're movin' the play outside!
Give me the freakin'
ball, come on!
--[KANAI grunts]
--[EBUMI] Dammit, dude!
[growls]
[MATSUO]
I have to change my plan.
I wanted to use Ebumi
to shift the momentum...
[EBUMI]
Matsuo! Just give me the ball!
[FUSHIMI grunts]
[MATSUO]
...but they're onto us.
[BOTH grunt]
[MIYUKI] Jinko's fly-half...
He's an interesting one.
[MIYUKI]
He's not particularly fast.
And he's not that strong either.
He may be on the big side...
[MIYUKI]
...but I can take him.
[MATSUO] Well, let's try
this one on for size.
[gasps]
Wow! Something's coming my way!
Oh, man. What a kick!
[gasps]
Yoichi! Faster!
Huh?
[EBUMI]
Heh!
[gasps]
[HONKAWA] The kick made
it to the end goal!
Run, Ogi!
[whistle blows]
Oh, yeah!
--[MUSASHI] Ogi!
--[yelps]
How could you let him
smoke you like that?
I'm sorry!
In my whole life, nobody's ever
beat me in a foot race before!
Ah! It was an accident, I swear!
Please don't be mad at me!
[MATSUO] That was lucky, but
I know I can't kick the ball
every time and rely on
Ebumi's speed to score.
This game's startin'
to get interesting, guys.
That's a good thing.
'Cause I'm all fired up now!
[NOKA]
That's one try for each side.
[SUMIYOSHI]
Talk about an awesome game.
[footsteps]
[GION]
Uh?
We're gonna make a substitution.
[KOMORI]
These three are goin' in.
Noka's subbin' in for Suwa
as team A's number 14.
Ohie's subbin' in for
Shinshi at number 1.
And finally, uh...
Gion's in for Masa.
Ahh!
All right! This is the
greatest day ever!
Good for you! Go get 'em, man!
[GION] Hell yeah! I'm gonna
dominate every last...
The little guy's sure
full of beans, isn't he?
Yeah, well.
I'm sorry you're facin'
him as a flanker,
but he needs all
the work he can get.
Don't be sorry, Coach.
The more passionate a player is,
the more I want him to learn.
I've never seen
anybody that serious
about taking notes before.
That's good prep.
But can he apply it?
Whoa. So you're
playin' flanker, eh?
Betcher ass!
Yeah. That's the spirit, kiddo!
It's Gion!
[HAIJIMA] Play will resume.
Team B will kick off!
Hey!
You up to speed on
your positioning, Gion?
All over it.
Huh?
[GION, SHIMOI grunt]
Team A sure is making a lot
of mistakes out there today.
Although, being a mixed team,
I suppose that's to
be expected, isn't it?
You're right.
On the other hand,
team B seems to be
movin' the ball around
pretty darn well.
[MIYUKI]
Move up, wing!
That fly-half of yours
is dominating the game
on every single front.
[HAIJIMA] You mean Miyuki?
He's a freshman.
Is that a fact?
For a rookie,
he's really terrifying.
He knows the game well.
His head is on a swivel.
He sees the whole field.
Musashi, catch!
[MUSASHI]
One of the subs.
He looks a little green to me.
I can just side step him.
What the hell?!
[SEKIZAN, IWASHIMIZU grunt]
Damn.
Kid may be rough
around the edges,
but I gotta admit,
he moves pretty darn well.
[yells]
[GION grunts]
[MIYUKI]
Oh, man. His energy is amazing.
But he's not where
a flanker should be.
He only has eyes for the ball.
But...
Gion!
I know you're excited,
but are you positive
you know how to play flanker?
I'm all over it.
[GION]
What does a flanker do exactly?
Everything.
Whether it's attacking
or defending,
we're first on the
scene every time.
[GION] My problem is, I still
suck at handling the ball.
[SEKITO]
That's why it's so much fun.
Because we always
get there first.
[HYOSU, GION grunt]
[GION]
But I know how to hit people!
[MIYUKI] I'll give you this:
you're all over the field, Gion!
If you really wanna stop me,
you're gonna need
more than energy!
Trust me!
[MIYUKI]
What is he looking at?
[MIYUKI gasps]
[GION]
[HACHIOJI]
Get the ball out! Quick!
[GION]
Damnit!
[MIYUKI]
Huh?
Getting the freakin' ball
back is really hard!
Oh. Uh, hi, Miyuki.
[MIYUKI] Where in the
heck was he looking
when he tackled me just then?
[MIYUKI]
Wait...
That's it!
[MIYUKI]
The belly button!
[KASUGA, KAMO grunt]
[MIYUKI]
You can always move your feet.
Or juke with your upper body.
But you can't move your torso.
So that's what he's aiming for
when he goes low
to make a tackle!
[MIYUKI laughs]
He's not a slouch anymore!
Gion, the belly button, really!
Yep! It's easy to locate,
and it makes tackling
big guys a piece of cake!
Besides, when I go for the legs,
it hurts too bad when
they kick me back!
This works like a charm!
Coach.
For a small guy, his movement
in space is pretty effective.
[KOMORI]
Hm...
True, but if he doesn't
start usin' his brain,
it won't matter one bit.
Here!
[gasps]
Huh?
That was a forward pass.
You're not stopping me!
[laughs]
[whistle blows]
[HAIJIMA]
Team B! Throw forward! Game off!
Huh?!
--[thud]
--[GION] Ow!
Wha...?
[HAIJIMA] Game's over,
everyone! Gather 'round!
What? The game's not done!
That is weak sauce, bro!
Watch it, dude!
[HISAKAWA] I forgot we
were just practicing.
This was fun.
I wish we could play with
you guys all day long.
[TAIRA]
Yeah, let's do it!
Come on, Coach!
Can't we just play
a little bit longer?
[HAIJIMA] Shut up, Miyuki.
There's no whining in rugby!
Sorry. Can we play
tomorrow maybe?
[HAIJIMA]
Men.
We're very proud of the way
our teams played today.
And from where
we're standing,
it certainly looked
like you learned
some valuable lessons out there.
It was a good match.
And you all fought hard
till the bitter end.
Good work, everyone!
We're making rice balls,
so everybody help
yourselves, okay?
Not the rice balls again.
They taste like dirt.
As far as I'm concerned,
Kanai, you can just starve!
[JINKO RUGBY TEAM]
Awesome, we love rice balls!
[RIE] I think you could
learn a thing or two
from the Jinko squad, ya jerk.
Making these balls is a
lot harder than it looks.
How are you so good
at this stuff, Rie?
[RIE] Because I make 'em for
the guys after every game.
You wouldn't be able to
make enough for your team
by yourself, would you, Umeno?
I really hope I end up
with Rie's balls.
As long as Ume doesn't
make mine, I'm good.
[MIYUKI wails]
No fair!
I wanted to keep on
playing the game!
Will you shut up, dude?
I'm tryin' to eat my balls.
These look really good.
I wanted to play, Iwashi!
Miyuki, you should
eat your balls.
Thanks man, I really am starved.
So what's the deal, has
he always been like this?
Yeah, more or less.
Oh, I meant to ask
you something...
[MIYUKI]
Huh?
...about Sagami.
You remember Hanadate, right?
[MIYUKI]
Hanadate? Oh!
Isn't he the guy that
tried to get into your head
during your last game?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Uh-- Yeah.
Yep. Of course
I remember Hanadate.
The first time I faced him,
we played Asakura Middle School
in the semi-finals years back.
He sat on the bench
the whole time.
[gasps]
[MIYUKI] The thing I
remember most about him
is that he stared
down every person
who stepped on the field
with an evil glare.
[sighs]
So what did he say to you?
He was being mean.
I'll leave it at that.
Oh, man.
I forget how sensitive
you are sometimes!
[SEKIZAN]
Iwashimizu.
[IWASHIMIZU yelps]
Uh... Yes, sir?
You played through his taunting.
I was really
impressed by that.
[GION]
Captain!
Did I do a pretty
awesome job today?
I ran around a lot and tackled
a lot of guys--did you see?
I was amazing, right?
[GION whines]
You didn't even touch
the ball, Gion!
You just ran around like
a maniac and dove into
people's bellies
with reckless abandon!
You're not where
you need to be yet!
You've got lots to learn!
Well, Coach.
What are we going
to do now? Practice?
Yeah. What else?
[HAIJIMA]
Jinko learned a lot today--
I just hope we didn't
teach 'em too much.
[HAIJIMA] Things are about
to get interesting.
[SEKIZAN] Next time:
"Let's Go to Ryogoku Together."