[SEKIZAN]
You guys.
We can win. We can do this.
Once we're done
eating our snacks,
let's get back to work!
What is up with these weirdoes?
Well...
Looks like these losers have a
little bit of pep in their step.
Let's slow 'em down.
[HYOSU]
Get that ball!
Renpei, you're playin' so well--
the balls are soarin' off your
cleat today! Jinko doesn't...
Why don't ya stop
running your mouth,
and get your head
in the game, Suna?
[HIROTA yells]
[KAMO yelps]
[yells]
[BOTH]
Nice job, you guys!
[SHINSHI] All right! The sumo
drill is totally helping!
Good.
[GION]
We got the ball back!
[UMENO]
All right, Jinko, let's go!
Move the ball outside, guys!
[SAKURA]
Come on, let's pick up the pace!
Not on my watch!
[gasps]
[KIBI]
What a hit!
--[GION, MIKI gasp]
--[UMENO] Suwa!
Whoa.
Looks to me like Jinko's
about to score a try.
[SAKURA]
You're dead meat.
[SUWA, SAKURA grunt]
[KAMO yells]
Oh, come on!
You're a waste of
space! Ya jackass!
[TSUKUBA gasps]
Don't call me a jackass!
If anyone's a jackass
it's you, jackass!
Hey, now. Don't fight, you guys.
Why can't you both
be jackasses?
[TSUKUBA]
Stay out of it!
Damn you!
[sighs]
They made it past
their 22-meter line
pretty easily.
But Tenjiku's D got to them.
And quickly, too.
[HORIKAWA] Scoring a try
won't be an easy feat.
Let's go, you guys!
Get the damn ball
outside already!
[KAMO]
Matsuo!
[MATSUO] No. Takin' it
outside is no good.
The backs won't stand a chance.
[BOTH gasp]
Look at him go!
Captain!
[GION]
All right!
[SEKI]
Sorry, dude. This ends now!
[SEKIZAN, SEKI grunting]
He just stopped Sekizan cold.
Wow.
I thought he would've had
the advantage for sure.
[SEKI, SEKIZAN grunting]
[ISE]
Captain!
Pass it!
Ise!
Get some!
[ALL yelling]
Help out Ise!
[ALL yelling, grunting]
[GOSHOZOME]
Let's go, Jinko!
[ALL growling]
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Try!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL cheer]
All right!
[KIBI, GION]
Ise!
[HACHIOJI]
Natsuki! Way to go, man!
Hey, thanks a lot!
Ise! What are you, a forward?
Nice!
[laughs]
That was excellent. Great job.
Thank you!
[HYOSU]
All right!
Kifune.
You're gonna go for
the conversion, okay?
Huh? Uh-- Right!
[MATSUYAMA]
Unbelievable!
I didn't see that one
coming, that's for sure!
I underestimated them.
Those guys don't suck.
Not at all.
[SEKI]
Jinko's number 8 is pretty good.
We should really
watch out for that guy.
Agreed, but why are you
rubbing on my stomach?
Oh, it helps me relax.
[SANO growls] You guys. It's
time to get serious out there!
[whistle blows]
Good job, Kifune! Nice kick!
It's a tie game!
[SAKURA] They really
are useless. Totally.
They suck. All of 'em.
[UMENO] Ten minutes left
in the first half!
Let's keep the pressure
on them, Jinko!
[grunts]
Nice catch!
Matsuo!
Use the backs in the
next play, all right?
'Kay. Jeez.
Hey, maybe they can
score another try!
Jinko had better
represent for Kanagawa.
I don't want those Osaka d-bags
thinkin' they're
better than we are!
[KAMO]
Look alive!
[KIFUNE]
We're inside the 22-meter line!
We need to claim more territory!
Dude.
Is he putting the ball in touch?
[WADA]
Man. That was a quick pass, wow.
Hold on.
Wait a sec, I thought the ball
went over the line, right?
It's not against
the rules, Gion.
Sometimes, a player can
make a quick "throw in"
even if the ball
has gone into touch.
Ah! Ah...
Renpei! Pass it!
God. You're annoying.
[SAKURA]
You're all annoying--
every last one of you pricks!
Suck on that, losers!
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Drop goal!
How in the hell did
he make that kick?
That's completely nuts!
Damn, dude. That guy
sure can boot it.
That kick was well
over 50 meters.
[SANO]
Renpei!
Why did you go for
the drop goal?
Three points doesn't
do us any good!
They just put up seven on a try
they crammed down
on our throats!
Stop being such a selfish
player and pass the ball
for once in your life!
[SAKURA] I wouldn't have
to be a selfish player
if you guys would
make a damn play
and stop messing around!
Until you put up some points,
do everyone a favor
and shut your damn mouth!
--[TAKEBE, KIFUNE gasp]
--[EBUMI] Hm?
No, I won't. Who do
you think you are?
[OSAKA]
Renpei! Take it easy!
Don't talk to your
teammates like that.
It's not okay. And, Cap'.
Three points is better
than no points, right?
Remember, we're all
on the same team here.
[SANO growls]
Hey, why are they fighting?
That's weird. They just
scored a drop goal.
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
All right, break it up!
[laughs]
Tenjiku's an amusing
bunch, aren't they?
I'd love to take
a crack at these guys.
We could sit back, relax,
and watch them
implode from within.
[laughs]
[KOMORI]
No tradition. Not at all.
[HOSOTANI]
Hold up!
Why do you defend him, dude?
Can't you see he's
tearing this team apart?
[OSAKA] We've been friends
for almost 12 years now.
I can always tell what's
goin' on in his head.
He isn't a bad guy. I swear.
If you say so. Some friend.
[KOMORI]
Tenjiku's playin' well.
[KOMORI] There's no doubt
they're a talented
group of kids.
But in spite of their talent,
they have a lot of weaknesses.
Not the least of which:
they lack tradition.
Tradition is what colors
a team's character--
it's what gives them identity.
And even more importantly,
tradition can dictate the
way a team plays the game
on the field of battle.
It can be a blessing or a curse.
Tenjiku doesn't know
who they are yet.
You can see it in the way
they treat one another.
They're constantly at
each other's throats
instead of focusin' on the game.
They have no tradition
to speak of.
No identity either.
[KOMORI] They're a group
of individuals. Not a team.
[SAKURA]
Come on, Buckteeth!
[OSAKA]
Hoso!
[SEKI]
Pass it!
[grunts]
Those guys sure need to
work on their passing.
You suck.
[HOSOTANI]
Renpei!
What, were you not
paying attention
when the captain told you
to stop kicking the ball?
How'm I s'posed to catch that?
Shut up.
Huh?
[SAKURA]
Are you seriously blaming me
because you're not fast enough?
No. I just, I--
[SAKURA]
You bucktoothed--
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A] That's the end
of the first half!
We're three points behind!
Hell yeah! We got this!
Come on. Let's go.
[SAKURA]
Whatever.
[OSAKA] Relax, we're
still winning, guys!
Let's try to build on that
lead in the second half!
[OSAKA]
Renp--
[HOSOTANI]
Hey, Sunao.
I can't deal with him.
I really have tried.
But I just can't.
Listen. All this infighting
is unacceptable.
I don't care who started it.
[FUTAMI]
You got it?
Ugh.
No more of your bickering.
I wan't men out there,
not a bunch of skirts.
Do you understand?
Captain.
I think the first half could've
gone a whole lot worse.
Don't let this inexperienced
team give you trouble.
Turn it around.
Right.
[MATSUYAMA] That was the
worst halftime speech
in the history of rugby.
[SEKI] It's not cool
the way he put everything
on the captain's shoulders.
Talk about pressure, eh?
I don't suppose there's any way
I can get you to
stop doing that,
Look, guys. Screw the coach.
We don't need him.
Besides, I like being able to
do whatever the hell I want--
that's why I transferred to
this school in the first place.
[SANO]
Ugh. Hang on!
Uh. What's up?
I need to know whose side
you're on right now.
Huh? Listen, Cap. I'm on
the team's side. Always.
Then do somethin' about Renpei!
Huh?
[SANO]
Come on.
You two have been friends
since you were little kids.
He's singlehandedly destroying
my squad and you know it!
I'm the captain of this team.
Make him listen to me
or you're both gone!
With all due respect,
I don't think that's something
a captain should say!
[gasps]
[OSAKA] You heard what
the coach just said.
The first half went pretty well,
all things considered.
Let's keep up the good work!
[OSAKA]
Listen.
I know Renpei can be a little
rough around the edges.
But it's only because
he really wants to win!
So, let's cut him
a little slack.
[SANO]
I'm done with those two.
They're hopeless.
Well, men? The game
is far from over.
[JINKO TEAM panting]
[KOMORI]
But that was one hell of a half.
[KOMORI] Watching you guys
play lit a fire inside me.
And it made me
incredibly proud of you.
Keep it up in the second half.
Got it?
[JINKO TEAM]
Right!
[KOMORI] But remember.
This is still just a scrimmage.
I want as many of our guys
as possible to go up against
Osaka's quarterfinalist
offering.
And so, I'm gonna make
some substitutions.
[gasps]
[REF 17A] The second half
will begin shortly!
[GION]
This is it!
Dude, do you have to
scream all the time?
It drives me freakin' nuts?
Gion? You sure?
Yeah. Why not?
Hey. Your call.
I'm very curious to see
how this turns out.
Come on, it's the uncertainty
that makes it so much damn fun.
Nice work out there, Hyosu!
[HYOSU]
Thanks, Kibi!
Man, it sucks you don't
get to play though.
[KIBI]
Yeah, I know.
But, hey, there's a heck
of a lot I can learn
by watching the game
from the sidelines.
[HYOSU]
You're a good teammate, brah.
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Begin the second half!
[SANO]
I'm pissed off.
The forwards are gonna
score this time around!
[grunts]
[groans]
[yells]
[panting]
The kid moves.
[KIBI] I gotta give it to him.
His sweeps are fast.
When a player's
tackled to the ground,
his opponents always swoop
in to take the ball, right?
Getting those guys out of
the way is called sweeping.
The faster the
sweep, the better.
That way you can get
the ball out quickly.
So you have to
think on your feet.
If you spend too much
time in a ruck,
not only is it more
likely that the ball
will be taken from you,
but more and more players
will gather until their defense
has you right where
they want you.
To be effective in
the middle of a ruck,
ya have to get as low
to the ground as you can.
The lower the better.
It might be the
perfect job for Gion.
Ah!
[grunts]
[KOMORI]
Gion.
You only have one job
to do out there today.
Whenever your
teammates get tackled,
help 'em out.
Be the first one to the ball.
The first one!
Yes, sir!
[HORIKAWA]
The kid with the speed--
he didn't play
in their last game.
[HORIKAWA]
Huh.
Ya know what?
If they keep this up,
they just might get a W today.
Here's hoping. Right?
[whistle blows]
[HIROTA]
Dude, look.
Gion seems calmer
than normal, doesn't he?
Sure does.
[KOMORI]
Help your teammates.
Be the first one to the ball.
Gion.
It doesn't matter
how talented you are,
you won't be able to
save everyone, everytime.
Uh?
But be ready, and you'll
make a huge impact.
If you see one of your
teammates get wrapped up,
push him forward
as hard as you can.
If you're far away, but you
think you can get there,
then go. Just be smart about it.
The key is not to
waste all your energy.
Stay focused.
Trust your instincts.
The faster you get there,
the faster we'll be able to
drive the ball down the field.
Remember, every second counts,
so stay on your toes.
Keep an eye out for patterns
in the other team's movements
so you can get a jump on 'em.
Examine your opponents.
Feel the flow of the game.
Always be lookin' for a chance
to learn somethin' new.
Study.
[gasps]
[GION]
But, I don't have my notebook!
Gion! You're out
of position, man!
[growls]
[SAKURA]
Forwards, stop screwin' around
and get the ball back!
Do you wanna win this game
or not, ya losers?
[gasps]
[OSAKA]
Team morale is low!
We need to widen our lead,
or this one might
slip away from us!
I gotta get the ball
back into our hands!
[MATSUO]
If I pass it...
...their defense will crush us!
[gasps]
[ADACHIHARA] A kick?
Did he panic or something?
Bad move either way.
Their wings dominate high punts.
[SAKURA]
I got it!
[OSHIMA]
No. This one's mine!
Look out!
Huh?
--[SEKIZAN grunts]
--[OSHIMA groans]
[grunts]
--[HYOSU] Run!
--[KIBI] Come on, Captain!
[MATSUO]
Taku!
[SEKIZAN grunts]
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Try!
[ALL cheer]
[panting]
Yes!
[GION] Captain, that was
so amazing! Wow!
[MATSUO]
Taku!
[SEKIZAN]
Nice kick, bro!
[MATSUO]
I only chanced it because
I knew you'd be there!
Kifune.
Uh--
Ya think you'll be
able to handle
the change in position?
[KIFUNE]
Yes! Of course!
Cap', my bad, I'm sorry.
It's not your fault, man,
so don't apologize.
[SAKURA]
Then whose fault is it, Captain?
Do ya know what
you two losers are?
You're both weak.
[OSHIMA]
I'm sorry?
Don't you say that to him!
Let's go.
[whistle blows]
[GION]
Next time: "I'm Not Crying."