[GION]
Big bro! You wanna play?
No.
[GION]
Uh--
Go home, Gion.
I'm not gonna play with you--
you're just a kid!
[RUGBY TEAM snoring]
Wake up!
[SHINSHI]
Ugh... My body hurts.
[HYOSU]
My soul hurts.
[GION]
Come on, guys, get up!
[MAROUDO]
Too tired.
[GION]
Let's go!
Well, you're extra
pumped up today.
Why's that?
I've never done anything
like this before!
Rugby's awesome by itself,
but training with
you guys is the best.
It's like I gained
a bunch of brothers!
[yelps]
Gion!
[EBUMI]
So "rugby's awesome," huh?
[GION]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Tell me just how awesome it is
when you learn to catch.
'Cause right now, you suck!
[groans]
[EBUMI] I don't have time
to teach you everything,
you little turd!
Whoa. Come on, man. Chill.
He's doin' his best!
Well, kid, you tried.
Don't worry, I'll teach you.
[GION growls]
Dumb jerk!
I'll get him back
when we start tackling!
[RUGBY TEAM panting]
[KOMORI]
Okay. Break for lunch.
Let's meet back here at 2:30.
[SEKIZAN]
Right!
We're gonna run a Gewalt, men.
[gasps]
[KOMORI]
Oh. That's right.
You kids don't call it that.
These days, I guess you'd
call it an intrasquad scrimmage.
[KOMORI]
Come on, get in line.
We'll play 12 on 12.
[gasps]
[KOMORI]
The starters will be team A.
The reserve players
will be team B.
Team A?
Wait. He starts?
[GION] I'm a freakin'
starter, you guys!
Ugh! Well, let's
destroy these losers!
Men, team A kicks off.
Begin!
[HIRANO] Hm...
I'm confused. I didn't think
rugby could be played 12 on 12.
It's 'cause we don't
have enough guys.
Each of the mock teams
is missing two forwards
and one back.
[laughs] I'll show these jerks!
They don't know
how good I--
[yelps]
Damnit!
[BOTH gasping]
[NOKA]
That sucked.
[GION]
All right!
Hey, Gion! Ball is life, get it!
[OHARANO]
I'll say this much about him.
He's rough around the edges,
but he sure knows how to tackle.
[GION chuckles]
[GION yells]
You're mine!
Gion, wait! One behind you!
[EBUMI] Don't you realize
there's a hell of a lot more
to rugby than making
tackles, pip' squeek?
No good! It's Ebumi!
Wow. He's fast!
Damn it!
[whistle blows]
[EBUMI laughs]
Suck on that!
[growls]
Gion!
[yelps]
[ALL gasp]
[whistle blows]
It's a knock-on.
[OHARANO] He can tackle,
but he still can't catch a pass.
[KAMO]
Still? Oh, man.
[RUGBY PLAYERS grunting]
[ISE]
All right!
[grunts]
Ise dropped the ball!
Let's get it back!
[BOTH grunt]
[whistle blows]
[OHARANO] Hey, Gion!
You're too far forward!
The little shrimp--
he's the weak link.
[whistle blows]
[KOMORI]
Fourteen to nothing.
Team B is leading
after the first half.
And there's only one reason
team A is struggling.
You.
Come on. It's not
all me, is it?
Five tackles.
And only two of 'em
have been successful.
On the other three, you
completely missed your target.
And as for passes?
Catches?
Zero.
You're right, bad half.
But don't worry about me.
I'll tackle those losers
so hard in the second half
they won't know what hit 'em!
Just watch!
[KOMORI sighs]
Is tackling all
you wanna do, kid?
While your forwards get
covered in the mud and muck,
and your backs are
fighting tooth and nail
to get your team the ball,
what are you gonna do?
Let the ball bobble on the deck
so you can make a tackle?
Tell me. Have you played
organized sports before?
[GION]
No.
Yeah. Thought not.
You'll never make it anywhere
'cause you only
play for yourself.
Sorry. But I'm subbing
you out, kid.
Suck it up.
Let's get the
second half underway.
[GION]
When I was a little kid,
my big brother never
let me play with him.
[GION] But all I wanted
was to be part of a team.
Sports aren't fun when you have
to play them by yourself.
I think you better
go home, dude.
Sorry, but you're way
too little to play for us.
[STUDENT 7B]
You suck big time!
[STUDENT 7C]
You're in the way, short stuff!
I won't be small forever.
I'll grow. Just you
wait and see!
[STUDENT 7B]
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
[STUDENT 7C] Let's go play
with those guys over there.
[GION]
But I knew I wouldn't give up.
No offense, but you're
pretty little.
You sure you wanna try out
for the Basketball Team?
[GION yells]
[GION]
They were right.
I was definitely a small kid.
But, so was everyone else.
Especially when I was in
elementary and middle school.
[GION] But they got to play.
So why couldn't I?
[GION]
And so...
...I blamed myself for it.
[GION]
I suck.
[gasps]
[whistle blows]
Well, that's time.
Team B is the winner: 21 to 12.
[ALL]
Yeah!
[KOMORI]
The losing team gets to practice
tackling for a full hour.
[TEAM A groans]
[KOMORI]
Team B, go home.
[KAMO]
All right!
[HYOSU]
Let's go get some ice cream!
[SEKIZAN]
Again!
[yelps]
Come on, Iwashimizu.
Fight through the pain!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Y-Yes, sir.
[pants]
I've never done anything
like this before!
[SEKIZAN]
Team A. Wrap up.
[SEKIZAN] We'll start
again tomorrow at five.
Get plenty of rest tonight.
[TEAM A]
Yes, sir!
I don't understand, Coach.
How come you were
so hard on Gion?
He's green.
He only started playing
rugby a month ago.
No.
[gasps]
You mean the
little fella, right?
He hasn't even
begun to play yet.
[IWASHIMIZU gasps]
[HYOSU]
Hey!
Have you seen Gion?
We can't find him anywhere!
Huh?
I wouldn't worry
if I were you--
he'll show up once
he gets hungry again.
[MATSUO] Hey! If you're
there, say somethin'!
Gion! Are you there, buddy?
[KAMO]
Gion?
There's no way he'd
fit in there, Kamo.
[OHARANO sighs]
He is such a pain in the ass.
[IWASHIMIZU panting]
[HACHIOJI]
Well. His things are still here.
[HYOSU] He's probably pissed
off and hiding somewhere.
[KAMO]
Let's leave him be for a while.
[pants]
[IWASHIMIZU panting]
[KOMORI] He hasn't even
begun to play yet.
[sighs]
Listen, just for a sec.
I know tackling is your
favorite part of the game.
But tell me this:
what's the real reason
you love it so much?
'Cause you wanna win?
Or cause you're taking
your frustrations out
on the bigger guys?
Because of all the awful
things they've said about you?
The things they say
about both of us.
[gasps]
Uh! L-Look...
Don't get me wrong, okay,
I'm not telling you
tackling is a bad thing!
But... Well...
Take me, as an example.
I'm good at catching the ball,
but I can't scrum
to save my life.
I'm not good at kicking
the ball either.
And sometimes I'm
not very smart.
I'm not quick or
fast like Ebumi.
Or big and strong
like the captain.
And I can't do those low tackles
you're so good at either, Gion.
[IWASHIMIZU]
But...
I wanna be able
to do everything.
That's why I work
so hard in practice.
Because... if I give it my all,
day in and day out...
...then maybe I'll get better.
And maybe we can win.
That's our ball he's got!
Are you gonna let him
take it from you?
[IWASHIMIZU] When we
scrimmaged against Keijo,
the truth is,
I was still hanging onto my
baggage from middle school.
But because of you,
I was able to let that all go.
And for the first time,
I was a full-on member
of the Jinko Rugby Team.
[panting]
[KOMORI]
Okay. That's it for the morning.
[KOMORI] Grab a break,
grab some breakfast,
and we'll get started
on weight training.
And get ready, everyone,
because this afternoon,
we do another scrimmage.
For real?
What?
I mean, I guess I'll be
starting again, right?
I was in the lineup
when we played Keijo.
If anything, I don't understand
why he was a starter yesterday.
[whistle blows]
[TEAM A, TEAM B
shouting, grunting]
[KOMORI]
Kid.
Don't just sit there and stare.
Make yourself useful
and put those balls away.
[HYOSU, SHINSHI grunt]
[gasps]
[grunts]
Well done.
Listen to me, kid: don't get
so down on yourself next time.
You're goin' in.
[gasps]
[KOMORI]
Just for the last five minutes,
so you better make it count.
[whistle blows]
We're up six points now, Gion.
Finish strong, all right?
[grunts]
[KAMO] Let's get one
more try, you guys!
[yelps]
[OHARANO]
They stole the ball!
[KAMO gasps]
It's wide open!
[MAROUDO] If they score a try
now, we're in big trouble!
[GION]
The ball!
Gion!
[GION] When I tackled Sekizan,
it was the first time
someone told me I was
amazing at anything.
Of course I want them
to keep saying that.
[GION]
But I have to earn it...
...every single play.
[ALL gasp]
[grunts]
That's my ball, kid.
Cough it up now!
[growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[KAMO]
Gion--Gion!
Here, pass the ball!
[whistle blows]
[gasps]
[growls]
[whistle blows]
[KAMO]
Way to go, Gion!
We won!
[GION]
What?
We were six points ahead, man.
If Ebumi had managed
to score a try,
and if they'd made
the point after,
they would've stolen the game
right out of our hands.
That was super close!
[IWASHIMIZU] You saved the game
with that pick-up, Gion.
You protected the ball.
So we won.
[IWASHIMIZU grunts]
[IWASHIMIZU coughs]
[KOMORI]
Gather round, men.
[KOMORI] You guys still
have a whole lot to learn.
That said, your fundamentals
are getting stronger
every single day.
You're small,
but what you lack in height
you make up for in quickness.
And trust me, being able
to move the ball around
is no small feat.
But, gentlemen, if you're
just playing for yourself,
then none of it'll
matter in the end.
[KOMORI] You have to learn
to play for your teammates.
Whether it's tackling,
scrums, or tries,
you have to do it for the team.
So, guys, I have a feeling we
gained a new member today.
[yelps]
Hey. You jerk!
Yep! That's you, Gion. Congrats!
Way to go.
Hey. Guys!
Don't! For real, guys! Stop it!
Wait! Coach! I got a great idea!
To celebrate my success,
how 'bout you buy
us dinner tonight?
[SHINSHI]
Gion!
[KOMORI]
You know what? You're on!
If you can all be ready
by five o'clock, that is.
[NOKA]
We only have 15 minutes!
[KAMO]
Hurry up!
[HYOSU]
There's no time to get changed!
[MAROUDO]
Nice job today, Gion!
[KOMORI]
Next time: "Ball Games."