[GION]
'Kay, I've got my practice kit.
I've got my underwear.
I've got my socks.
My toiletries are ready to go.
I've got my rule book.
I've got my healthy
snacks for the bus
and most importantly,
my secret notebook.
All right! That's everything!
[GION sighs]
I'm so pumped.
I'm so ready to get going,
I can't even relax!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Today, we'll be featuring
some of the world's
most popular
vacation destinations.
[applause]
[WOMAN 16A]
So we're dying to know.
Tell us: how do the two
of you spend your time off?
[CELEB 16A]
Well, I think it's silly.
But he likes to eat
parfaits at a dog café
--[phone vibrating]
--with his Chihuahua.
--And that's not all.
--[phone vibrating]
--Wait till you hear this.
He takes the dog for walks
in a stroller of all things!
Yeah? What's goin' on?
[GION]
Hey, tree trunk! Are awake yet?
[IWASHIMIZU]
G-Gion?
[GION] Have you finished
packing for camp?
[IWASHIMIZU] No. We don't
leave till tomorrow.
I was gonna pack first
thing in the morning.
[GION]
Well, I'm already packed!
I'm really antsy right now
and I don't have
anything else going on,
so I figured I'd
give you a call.
Wanna practice?
Now?!
[GION]
I'll meet you at the station!
--No. Gion, wait!
--[phone beeps]
[IWASHIMIZU groans]
He's the worst.
[UMENO]
It's way smarter to shop here
than it is in Sugadaira!
Yeah, and it's way cheaper, too!
You're a really thrifty
shopper, you know that?
These bags are heavy.
If we were smart,
we would've brought
some of the boys to
help us carry them.
Why not put those
muscles to good use?
[laughs] Yeah, but, they are
about to go to training camp.
They need a day off.
It's good we let them
rest, don't you think?
I think you're way too nice.
Ah.
[RIE]
What's the matter, Ume?
[UMENO] Our two captain's
just walked by. That's weird.
[BOTH laugh]
[SEKIZAN]
Hm...
You wanna give him
something as a gift?
I think that's a really
nice gesture, Sekizan.
[SEKIZAN]
Oh, man, these look so good.
Which would you go with, Hachi?
Strawberry or mango?
Or wait--maybe Japanese
sweets would be better.
I dunno, man.
I think he'd prefer crackers
over somethin' sweet.
Do you think they're
shopping for training camp?
Fancy department store
sweets for training camp?
There's not a chance.
You're probably right.
Well, if not that...
[UMENO]
...then what?
There's only one explanation:
they're shopping for presents
for their girlfriends!
[BOTH squeal]
[RIE]
This's for you.
You must be outta your mind!
There's no way it's for me!
Umeno, what's goin' on?
[BOTH scream]
[HACHIOJI]
Aren't you Keijo's manager?
Yes. I am.
[UMENO] You're going to
Coach Komori's house?
[HACHIOJI] Yep. For a
pre-training camp meeting.
So you were
shopping for something
to bring with you as a gift?
That's right.
He invited us over for lunch,
but I thought it would
be very impolite
to come empty handed.
So, I bought these.
It's a small way of thanking
Coach for the invitation.
[GION]
Lunch with Coach?
Hey, man. Not cool!
I like lunch. Can I come, too?
That only seems fair!
That's pretty rude.
You can't just invite
yourself to stuff.
But we just finished practice.
I'm so hungry I
could eat a horse.
Wait, you were practicing?
[GION]
Sort of.
I wanted to do
some field drills,
but tree trunk said no.
He said we needed
rest so we read
rugby books in the library.
[UMENO]
You're a good boy.
Hey!
[UMENO laughs]
[GION]
Anyway, I'm totally starving.
Using my brain makes
me really hungry.
I'll come along.
Lunch with the old man
sounds super fun!
I can't give you
special treatment, Gion.
What kinda message
would that send
to the rest of the team?
Who cares about them?
I need food now!
[SEKIZAN growls]
Sorry.
Don't be so selfish, okay?
I'll buy you some
lunch another day.
And, guys?
You'd better be there
on time tomorrow.
See ya then!
Hey, Gion.
Since we're not invited,
do you wanna go grab
a burger or something?
[growling]
Oh.
No way.
Man, I'm starved.
You don't usually practice
on your own, Sumiyoshi.
Are you sure you're
feelin' all right today?
[SUMIYOSHI]
Very funny.
[MIKAMI]
And Noka's not with you either,
which is a bit out
of the ordinary.
[SUMIYOSHI]
I invited him,
but he said he wanted to
stay home and get some rest.
Apparently, he overdid it
in practice yesterday.
And what do you mean
by that comment anyway?
Its not like we're
attached at the hip.
[YOSHIDA]
Gentlemen.
Don't forget to lock up, okay?
[KITAMACHI]
Yes, sir!
I know you're just our advisor,
but it means a lot to me
and the guys that
you practiced with us!
Hey. What's up?
Of course. Now, boys,
please go straight home.
What?! We'll be there ASAP, man!
[ALL gasp]
[HYOSU]
Dude! I studied my butt off!
My brain is so freakin'
tired right now!
How the heck am I supposed
to kick butt at rugby
when they make me
take extra classes
the day before we
leave for camp?
Takebe! Whoa, you
had class today?
Yeah, and I'm guessing
that's why you're here, too?
[HYOSU]
Totes!
If you don't get your act
together you're gonna fail,
and then you'll hafta retake
all your classes, man!
Hey I know! I'll be your tutor!
[TAKEBE]
Uh, no thanks.
I'll be all right.
[HYOSU]
Hey, it's no sweat, buddy!
We may be stupid,
but we're old timers,
which means we've seen
this kinda crap before.
[screams]
Kasuga.
Maybe you should tutor him.
You're the one who
offered to help out.
You do it.
[HYOSU] You're 3 whole ranks
above me in our grade
which means you're way smarter!
I'm at 212 and you're
at 207, ya dummy!
That's four ranks,
not three, you idiot!
What, you can't
even do subtraction?
Uh-- You guys, it's cool.
I really don't need your help.
I already have a tutor lined up.
Marodo's found someone
who's going to help me.
[phone vibrates]
Actually, I bet
that's him right now.
What? Gion?
[BOTH]
Oh. I'm sorry.
Ah!
Wow. Huh. You shop here, too?
So what if I do, you perv?
Please don't hurt me.
[phone vibrates]
[EBUMI] Ugh. It's that
stupid little turd.
[KAMO]
And now, my sleeping beauty,
I must wake you with
a princely kiss.
--[phone vibrates]
--[gasps]
[claps]
[phone vibrates]
[KIFUNE]
Hello?
[ATSUTA]
What? Right now?
Uh. All right then.
What now, you guys?
[OHIE]
We just ordered triple helpings.
And a dozen orders
of pot stickers, too.
[HIROTA growls] There's no
turning back now, gentlemen!
We finish our food first!
All right?
[SHINSHI, ATSUTA, OHIE]
Let's dig in, boys!
[WOMAN 16A] Here are four plates
of fried rice on the house!
[HIROTA, OHIE, ATSUTA,
SHINSHI groan]
Well, guys? All done.
Everybody'll be there!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Gion, wait.
Hm?
What about Oharano?
What?
Uh! Chill. I tried him
but he's not answering.
I called his home line, too,
but his brother
picked up the phone.
There's no reason
to be concerned,
he said he's out taking
their dog for a walk.
[GION]
Hmph! We're droppin' by!
Uh...
[panting]
What's wrong?
Are you tired already, Pom?
You're hopeless,
did you know that?
But you're pretty
darn cute, though.
--[GION] Found him!
--Uh-- Ugh.
Gion.
[GION] We've been lookin'
for you everywhere, man!
I thought you were supposed
to be walking your dog.
Why're you carrying it?
[POMEKICHI growls]
It's a he and Pomekichi
gets tired very easily.
[GION]
Hm? Pome-what?
Pomekichi is his name.
Anyway, whadda you want from us?
Right. Good news.
We're all goin' to eat lunch
at Coach Komori's place--
do you wanna come with us?
No. Tell the guys I said hello.
Wait! Hold on!
You have to come, man--
the captain said I can't go
unless the whole team goes!
Besides, doesn't
hanging with the guys
sound like fun?
I think we have different
ideas of what "fun" is.
Come on!
Don't you wanna eat some
lunch at Coach's place?
--[phone vibrates]
--No, I'm not even hungry.
[GION] Yeah, well, I am,
so suck it up, dude!
Hey!
You have your freakin'
phone with you!
How come you didn't pick up
when we called earlier?
Huh?
Because I didn't want to.
[screams]
--Let me go, tree trunk!
--How'd you find me anyway?
[OHARANO] You must've been out
here looking for a long while.
[GION]
I'm gonna kill him!
[OHARANO]
Oh.
[GION]
I'm gonna rip him...
Right.
[GION] I'm gonna make him cry
like the little girl he is!
[GION]
Don't forget about us!
[BOTH gasp]
[RUGBY TEAM]
All right! It's time for lunch!
I brought everybody, Captain.
Now it doesn't count as
special treatment, does it?
Huh?
[KOMORI]
What's goin' on here, fellas?
[laughs]
We're all havin' lunch
at your place, Coach!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Yeah!
[SEKIZAN] I'm so sorry.
Gion overheard us talking.
Come on, guys, I don't
have enough food here
to feed the whole team. I--
Sorry, but it looks like
the entire team has shown up.
I'm sendin' 'em home.
I'm off. Gotta go buy more food!
[KOMORI]
Yumi!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Don't worry 'bout us!
Oh my goodness. My, my, my!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Thanks for havin' us!
Nice to meet you!
There're so many
young men here, dear.
What on earth are we to do?
Who cares?
[SEKIZAN] I'm really very
sorry about this, ma'am.
Ah! Oh, my, look at that hair!
My name is Sekizan.
And, um, what should
I call you, ma'am?
Oh.
Mrs. Yumi's fine.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Coach.
We all pitched in a few bucks
and bought a ton of meat
and veggies at the
supermarket around the corner
so we don't put you
and your wife out!
We just need to borrow
stuff to cook with!
Oh, my!
The hot plate should be
somewhere upstairs, darling.
Go get it!
Huh?
We'll do it for you, Mrs. Yumi!
It's fine--after all,
you're our guests!
Get the hot plate, darling!
The damn thing's as big as I am!
Hey, come on. Help me.
Okay.
[YUMI]
My, my, you're all so strong!
You're not as big as
the rest of these boys,
are you, cutie pie?
--Eh...
--[SHINSHI laughs]
Coach and I, we've
always wanted kids.
Yeah but, if you did,
your kids wouldn't look like me.
They'd look more like him.
Hi. I'm Yoshida.
The team's advisor.
[KASHIMA]
She does not like him.
Here we go, you guys!
[ALL grunt]
Does it need more sauce?
Or do you think I put
enough on there?
It's fine. So are we
supposed to boil the corn?
No, you idiot!
Don't you know corn
is meant to be grilled
with the leaves on?
Chill, dude.
Hey! Watch the flames, will ya?
Sure thing!
Ah...
No! Don't touch the meat--
it needs 20 seconds more!
Okay! Sorry!
--Cook...
--[KASHIMA] He's a pro.
[KAMO]
Yeah, it's true--
the guy really knows
how he likes his meat.
Just a touch longer. Good.
[KAMO yells]
That's what you get
for blowing bubbles
while I'm cooking, you jerk!
Atsuta! You need
more training!
Five years of prep!
Eight years of grilling!
[ATSUTA]
Yes, Master!
Wow. I can't believe Hirota's
been grilling for 12 years!
Fourteen, dude!
It's 13, actually.
Gosh, I hope there's
enough rice for everybody.
There's not, is there?
This is a disaster.
[UMENO]
Look.
Don't worry. We brought
a buncha microwavables.
And if that's not enough,
we can feed 'em this cabbage!
Oh, my. You're so smart!
Thanks. Can I borrow
your microwave?
Yes. Please!
Uh-oh. They're gonna
feed us cabbage.
That's gross.
[MARODO moans, laughs]
Here, Hachi! It's ready!
Ha! Aw, thanks, man.
So your brother let you come?
Yep.
Hey, lame ass.
Make me up a plate, too!
Shut up. Make your
own plate! Dick!
Nice!
It's delicious, even after
a triple helping of ramen!
There's always room for food!
Put on a triple helping of meat!
Right! Yes, sir!
[ALL]
Ah...
And a triple helping
of that cabbage, too!
Yes! Sir!
[ALL]
Ah...
Hey.
This cabbage isn't half bad when
you put a little salt on it!
Yeah, this is the bomb!
You guys are nuts!
Cabbage is disgusting!
I'm so sorry. I shouldn't've
let this happen.
I hate that we've intruded
on your lovely home
on your day off.
I should've stopped them, Coach.
Relax. I'm not upset.
Not at all.
The truth is, I
haven't seen my wife
this happy in a
really long time.
Just look at her.
Mrs. Yumi, may I have
some more rice, please?
Well, of course!
Oh! I'll make yours extra large!
I was surprised
to see them here.
And you as well.
[YOSHIDA]
Yeah, me, too.
Gion insisted and he is
a very persistant child.
We can have a beer
if you want one.
No, please, I'm fine!
I should get outta here.
Thank you again.
For being so kind.
Wait! You can't
leave without eating!
I made you both plates!
Here! Eat up!
[YOSHIDA]
Thank you for the food.
So, at Sugadaira,
I suppose we'll play lots
of games there, right?
[KOMORI]
Mm.
Yeah. A lot, indeed.
Everyday, more than
once if it's possible.
Camp is gonna be a hell
of a lot of work,
that's for damn sure.
[RUGBY TEAM]
Huh?
Uh...
It's strange.
Took almost every dime
we had to pay for this house.
But with so many people inside,
it feels like it's small.
Ya know what I love
most about rugby?
It's a big group of people--
all with different thoughts
and unique perspectives--
who meet on the field of play
and charge into one another
in pursuit of a single ball.
But, men, if we wanna
be more than a group--
if we wanna come together
as a cohesive team--
then we can't half-ass it.
We have to work our butts off.
And I don't just mean
on our techniques.
I mean in our attempts
to understand one another.
In our attempts to bond.
You know what they say?
About rugby?
They say the outcome
of the match is decided
long before the
game ever begins.
It's true.
Upsets are very
rare in our sport.
They almost never happen.
The prepared team wins.
The underprepared
team always loses.
So lemme ask you, men.
Are you guys a
winning team? Or not?
'Cause you have to decide.
Do wanna you lose
or do you wanna win?
Win!
Have you worked
your butts off so far?
Have you gotten
yourselves ready?
[RUGBY TEAM]
Yes!
I have, Coach. I puked
during practice yesterday!
Hey! Some of us are eating here!
You have.
I've watched you put
in the necessary work.
You've laid the foundation.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll find out what
you're really made of.
Who you really are.
And, no matter what happens,
I know we're not gonna give up.
Right?
[RUGBY TEAM]
Right!
[RUGBY TEAM chattering]
Great speech, darling!
You're so cool!
[KOMORI]
Stop that!
[clears throat]
[YUMI] Hey, maybe I'll
go to Sugadaida, too!
[KOMORI]
Like hell you will!
[HACHIOJI]
Mrs. Yumi?
[YUMI]
Coming, dear!
There's a place I know of.
It's not fancy or anything.
But when I go to Sugadaira,
I like to go there for a drink.
We should go one night.
If you want to, that is.
Sounds good.
Eat up.
Yes! You're all
such wonderful boys!
Darling, I think I will go
to Sugadaira after all--
whaddaya say?
[KOMORI]
I said, "it's not gonna happen!"
[RUGBY TEAM]
Come on, Coach! Let her go!
But, dear!
I really would like
to go to training camp.
Why won't you let me come along?
I think you're bein'
a bit selfish.
Not to mention the fact
there'd be nothin'
for you to do there.
It'll also be really hot
outside and extremely crowded
and to be honest, I don't know
if there's a place for you
to stay, so let it go.
You are a typical man
if I've ever seen one!
Only concerned with
your own enjoyment!
Come on, Yumi, that's not fair!
What's not fair is you
leaving me behind
to fend for myself!
Fine, do whatever you want!
I don't really care
what you do anymore!
Hey!
[YUMI] You go ahead to Sugadaira
or Brazil or wherever!
I'll just stay here at home
for the rest of my life!
[TV GUY 16A] And now,
let's take a closer look
at this lovely creature.
The baby spotted seal
peaks its head
out of his den to survey
his surroundings.
--He smiles...
--[YUMI] Oh, my! Oh-my-oh-my!
Do you see that?
What is that thing, darling?
It's just so adorable!
Oh, my! So cute.
So cute! So cute!
It's so cute...
[KOMORI]
She's got a pretty easy life.
[groans]
Guys, pass me the
ball. No not that!
No... cabbage...
[GION] Next time:
"Summer Training Camp."