[MOM 19A] Oh, honey.
Don't you feel bad for Sunao?
[DAD 19A]
Feel bad about what?
[MOM 19A] I don't mind sending
him off to rugby school.
I really don't.
But perhaps it's
a little premature.
Maybe we should give him a few
more years in grade school.
He's so shy--I'd hate for
him to have to start over.
I know you're really
worried about him,
but ya have my word,
there's no reason to be.
He'll adjust to
the new environment
and before you know it,
the kid'll have more friends
than he'll know what to do with.
I promise.
[MOM 19A sighs]
[COACH 19A]
Hm.
I'm very glad to
meet you, Sunao.
So you're starting at Eno
Grade School next spring?
That's excellent.
That's the same school
Renpei goes to, I believe.
Let me grab him.
Renpei!
Renpei?
The kid's got a really
strong feel for the game.
He plays with the
grade school students
instead of the
other preschoolers.
Renpei!
[COACH 19A]
[SAKURA]
Hm?
[gasps]
What is it, Coach?
Well, this young
gentlemen will be in--
[OSAKA]
I'm Sunao!
[COACH 19A, SAKURA]
Huh?
[OSAKA]
Wow, Renpei!
You're totally the coolest
guy I've ever met!
Do you wanna be best friends?
Uh...
[OSAKA]
And that was that.
I've been following Renpei
ever since that moment.
I know how it goes.
Everyone makes a fuss over him
'cause he's such a good player.
But then...
[OLDER PLAYER 19A]
You're a mouthy little kid,
aren't you, Renpei?
Huh? If your passes
weren't terrible,
then I wouldn't criticize them.
Here's the deal, man.
This team'll never
get any better
with upperclassman like you.
You don't even show up
to practice on time!
Who do you think you are?
Renpei?
[OSAKA] And in middle school
and high school:
the same scenario.
Every single time,
like clockwork.
At first, everyone gets excited.
They listen to what
he has to say.
But after a couple of weeks,
they all turn on 'im
'cause he's never learned
how to keep his mouth shut.
[OSAKA] But Renpei is
still my best friend.
[HIROTA] Come on, Jinko--
let's kick some butt!
Come on!
We can still turn this
thing around, you guys!
Don't give up hope yet!
Sunao!
[OSAKA] Jinko's definitely
playing well today.
But we're beating
ourselves out here!
We gotta get our crap
together and fast!
And there he goes again.
Running his damn mouth,
and for what?
Why's he trying so hard?
It's only a practice match.
He's super annoying.
Look at that.
The defense is way
too far forward.
What are they doing?
Stupid idiots.
[SAKURA]
Weak tackles.
I swear, our forwards
really are useless out there.
Screw 'em. And screw
this team, too.
I hope they get
their asses kicked.
Look.
Tenjiku's fullback is
standing way down field.
What? Yeah, you're right.
He was in the thick of it
up until about a minute ago.
Well. How 'bout that?
Is Renpei giving up?
It sure looks like it.
Unless standing at
the back of the field
like a bump on a log is
a strategy I don't know of.
Then I'd say you're
100 percent right.
I guess he's phoning it in
'cause the game
doesn't mean anything.
Renpei!
[gasps]
Dude's done. That was
a half-assed kick.
I can't believe my eyes.
He's totally checked out.
[SAKURA]
I don't care!
[SAKURA] I play rugby
for a lot of reasons,
but making friends
isn't one of 'em, okay?
So don't worry about me!
[SAKURA]
Listen.
As long as we win,
that's all that matters.
[OSAKA]
That was his attitude.
And I thought it was cool.
Oh, man! This guy's a maniac!
[EBUMI growling]
[OSHIMA groans]
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Try!
[MIKI, UMENO cheer]
Good job, you guys!
Kifune! Time to make that kick!
[SAKURA]
Whaddaya want?
You gonna tell me you're upset?
[OSAKA] You coulda caught
him if you'd tried!
Why didn't you stop him?
I don't feel like
playing anymore.
You guys can do
whatever you want.
I'm over this pointless game
and you should be, too.
[OSAKA]
He isn't a bad guy, I swear.
[SAKURA] As long as we win,
that's all that matters.
[OSAKA]
Fine then.
Just stand there for
the rest of your life!
Actually, you'd just
be in our way like this.
Go back to the hotel, man!
You'd do as much good there
as you are here on the field!
So leave! Just leave!
I thought you were cool.
You're just pathetic
Sunao...
[SANO]
Sunao. Well said, man!
If Renpei'll listen to anyone
on this team, it's you.
You're no better than him!
None of you are!
Sunao--
[OSAKA]
You blame Renpei for everything
that goes wrong with this team!
There are 14 other players,
which means there's plenty
of blame to go around!
We only have a month before
the Hanazono preliminaries,
or did you forget?
[OSAKA]
Listen, guys.
I don't wanna be a losing team.
I wanna play to win. Do you?
You guys may not care,
but I do, so I'm gonna
do my best! To win!
No matter what happens!
--[whistle blows]
--We just made the kick!
It's 21 to ten now!
Here we go!
Come on!
[OSAKA]
I'll win it myself if I have to!
We're not a real team.
Everyone just does
whatever they want.
[OSAKA] We lack tradition.
We lack cohesion.
We have zero camaraderie.
Instead of coming
together to win,
all we ever do is
fight each other.
But after bein' on this
team for three years,
I can't just give up.
I can't turn my back
on them, not now.
We're teammates.
[OSAKA]
I wanna go to Hanazono so bad.
[OSAKA groans]
Hey, bro. Lemme help you up.
Uh. Thanks a lot.
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Knock-on by Jinko!
Scrum, Tenjiku.
Shake it off!
Stay cool! Get that ball back!
[SANO]
Set!
[OSAKA]
Come on. Just one.
One try!
[groans]
Sunao!
[OSAKA] I tried.
But I can't do it alone.
We can't win. It's hopeless.
You're not going anywhere!
Sunao! Get the ball out!
[OSAKA grunts]
[SEKI]
Let's go, guys!
[pants]
[SEKI]
Hey, Sunao.
Will you forgive me? Please?
I was wrong. I shouldn't
have given up on the team.
I'm sorry!
Seki.
[SEKI] I thought,
"there's always next year."
But I don't wanna wait!
[gasps]
[SEKI]
Let's go to Hanazono!
Tenjiku's team posture
has completely changed.
Their passes are starting
to connect, too.
I'm not sure what happened.
Maybe it has somethin' to do
with the argument they got into.
I wonder what that
was all about.
[HOSOTANI. GOSHOZOME]
Guys, look!
They're 22 meters inside
Jinko's territory!
Sunao. You're not
injured, are you?
Ya think you can
finish the game?
Oh, yeah. I'm good.
Their captain is a good guy.
Come on!
C'mon, defense. Let's not
give up any ground.
Wow, we're really on a roll now.
Come on! You got this!
Damn! Those passes are fast!
Sure are.
The reason Jinko's defense
is all clumped together
is because Tenjiko is
so close to the goal line.
[OSHIMA yells]
[HORIKAWA]
Oshima, their number 14,
is on the far edge of the field.
Ebucchi!
[OSHIMA]
Here comes the dynamite!
[yells]
[OSHIMA]
Boom!
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Try!
All right!
I totes did it, you guys!
My dynamite went boom!
Yeah, we know. We totally
heard you the first time.
Good job. Way to go.
We're still in this game!
Did ya hear the boom?
Doesn't he know
"boom goes the dynamite"
isn't really a thing anymore?
[MIZUNASE]
Yeah. I'd say no.
[OSHIMA]
You're the best captain ever!
It's 21 to 15 us.
If they make this kick,
they'll be one try away
from taking control
of the game again.
We've got over ten
minutes to play!
Yeah. A lot can
happen in that time.
[KOMORI]
Hey.
Oharano. You ready to play?
I guess.
My bad, guys.
Don't sweat it, okay?
I left you in a tough
spot for that kick.
[KOMORI]
Matsuo.
[KOMORI] We're switchin'
out our fly-halves.
Oharano's comin' in for ya.
[laughs] It's Oharano time!
Lucky you.
We gotta hang onto our lead.
Give 'em hell.
Yeah. Let's win this!
Hey! How do ya think I've
been doin' as a flanker?
Pretty good, right?
Yeah, if it's opposite day.
[GION]
Huh?
Ya need to run at least
100 times harder!
What? That's not
even possible, man.
But I could go... five,
maybe ten times faster.
[EBUMI]
Listen up, pretty boy!
If you think you can replace
Matsuo, you're wrong.
While you've been
sulking on the bench
like the turd you are,
he's been kicking some serious
butt on the rugby field!
I'm gonna help you out bud.
It's true you're
our fastest guy,
but I think I can make you
a whole lot better.
What?!
Matsuo, great job out there!
Thank you, Kibi.
Looks like they're
fighting already. Great.
What can you do?
You guys really
hate each other, huh?
It sure is entertaining.
Mind your own business,
ya frickin midget!
Yeah, get outta
here, tater tot.
Tater tot?
[TENJIKU NUMBER 4]
Let's score another try!
Come on, you guys!
Looks like Tenjiku's
on a roll out there.
Every single time
Jinko makes a good stop,
they come right back
on the attack.
No!
They're already 22 meters
into our half of the field!
Jinko! Hang in there!
[OSAKA]
We got this! We can do it!
Whoa, check it out!
[gasps]
[OHARANO] You can ignore
Tenjiku's forwards.
But if the ball gets
passed to the backs,
rush forward to meet them.
I don't need to defend
the forwards at all?
Nope.
Focus all your attention
on their backs instead.
Go get 'em.
[OSAKA] He's fast, but I just
have to pass it back inside!
[KIBI]
Ha-ho! An interception!
[EBUMI yells]
Makin' me work for it, huh?
See? I just made you better.
Who does that
freshman think he is?
I outta--
Oh...
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
High Tackle! Penalty on Tenjiku!
Owie!
Whoa. Sorry about that!
That was weak.
Can't believe you let him
catch you like that.
Jerk!
[GION]
Oharano!
Did you see that?
I rushed forward
just like you said.
Oh. Yeah, not bad.
Not bad?
I've got another job for you.
You really know how to
annoy me, you know that?
Iwashi, get over here!
Uh...
They're all getting along.
'Least, it looks that way.
[whistle blows]
A line-out?
Tenjiku's only ten meters
from the goal line, too.
Aw, man. Not good for Jinko.
Hey. We're counting on you.
[GION]
Hm.
[GION] Over here, Hachi!
Give me the rock! I swear,
I won't let you down!
What are you waiting for, Hachi?
--Gi... Gion.
--[GION] Come on, do it!
--What--
--Toss me the ball!
[ALL gasp]
[SANO] Damn! The little
guy was a decoy!
[HORIKAWA]
Check it out--it's a maul!
Push! Come on!
Let's go Jinko!
[JINKO TEAM,
TENJIKU TEAM grunting]
[KASHIMA]
Don't break! Whatever you do!
You can do this, Iwashi!
Keep fighting till the end!
Right.
Ise, get in the maul now!
What?
Screw your position,
just get in there and push!
Do it!
Push them back!
Go get the ball!
[OHARANO]
Now, Gion!
All right, buddy!
Let's have some fun!
[GION]
Yeah!
You guys, get in here
and push 'em back!
[TENJIKU PLAYER 19A]
Stay Strong! Don't give up!
All right!
Get 'em, you guys!
[ISE]
Only five meters left!
[ALL]
Come on!
[GION gasps]
Get the ball down
while you still can!
Score the try!
Do it now!
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Try!
[ALL cheer]
[JINKO TEAM cheers]
You scored!
Well done!
Nice try, man!
[HYOSU]
Way to go, Gion!
[BOTH gasping]
[UMENO]
It's 26 to 15 us!
OMG. I'll cry now!
No time for
celebrating, you guys.
Back to your positions--
we have a game to win!
Kifune, you're kicking, right?
[gasps]
Let's score one more
and put this to bed!
We can--
Uh...
Hey! There's no crying in rugby.
Besides, we haven't won yet!
Yeah, duh! And for the
record, I wasn't crying!
[OHARANO]
Hurry up, you jackass!
[GION]
You're the jackass! Jackass!
That's not an easy kick at all.
Let's see what he's got.
[whistle blows]
Nice kick!
Awesome!
Now it's 28 to 15 us!
It ain't over by a long shot!
Nice jump, Hoso!
Hurry up!
Two more Tries guys!
Two more Tries and
we'll retake the lead!
Huh?
[whistle blows]
[KOMORI]
Next time: "Aren't You Happy?"