[RUGBY TEAM grunting, yelling]
Hey, backs! I can't hear you!
[groans] I'm gonna die!
Me, too! The captain
means business today!
I wonder what's wrong with him?
[EBUMI]
Hey, Ise!
You need to get your
head outta your ass!
Yeah, my bad.
[sputters]
[GROUP]
Huh?
[ISE panting]
What was that?
[EBUMI]
Tch.
[NOKA pants]
Aren't you tired?
No. I'm... not... done... yet...
...must... go... on...
Gotta keep going--
Must get stronger!
You have way too
much energy, Gion.
[groans] If I wanna
make it as a flanker,
then I can't stop now!
A flanker! Flanker,
flanker, flanker!
Will you shut up?
Oharano, hold on.
Tell me what I need to do to
become a good flanker, please!
What? I don't know.
But you were the one who
told me to become one!
I didn't say that.
Ugh! Yes, you did! At the beach!
Own up to your words
and tell me what to do!
You suck.
Wow.
So you two had a bro-mantic
getaway together at the beach?
I had no idea you
were that close.
Do you seriously
think I would ever
go to the beach with
an idiot like Gion?
He's talking about the time
Coach made us go there
and dig holes all day.
Hey, Kitamachi.
What are you lookin' at, man?
[KITAMACHI]
Coach Komori's blog.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Wow, check it out!
The old man's been
eating some tasty stuff!
Speaking of, I'm starving!
[KITAMACHI]
"X Day?" What does that mean?
Could be a holiday
for good food?
Mikami, do you think the holiday
falls over the summer break?
[MIKAMI]
Maybe he'll take us to dinner!
[GION]
When is it?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Hopefully we'll get lucky
and it'll happen during
the week of training camp.
I have a question, Captain!
Is the food good
at Sugadaira?
Uh. Yeah.
There's an excellent
crepe shop there.
[MIKAMI]
Crepes...
[KITAMACHI]
The captain likes crepes?
[SEKIZAN] If I were you,
I'd go home and get some rest.
[RUGBY TEAM chatters]
Uh... Hey, Ise,
are you comin' or not?
Oh. No, you guys go on ahead.
[EBUMI]
Good work today, everyone!
Later, you guys!
Good work, Ise. See ya!
Natsuki.
Heh...
Ready to go?
[keys rattling]
[lock clicks]
[ISE]
Uh. Come on in.
[HACHIOJI]
Sorry for the intrusion.
[ISE]
I'm sorry. This place is a mess.
[HACHIOJI]
It's fine.
It could be a lot worse.
[HACHIOJI]
So... You talked to your brother
about training camp, right?
You said you were going to.
[door opens]
[door slams]
[HARUKI]
What the--?
Natsuki, is someone else here?
[HARUKI]
Huh?
I hope I'm not intruding.
Hi, I'm-- I'm on the
team with Natsuki--
Why haven't you
offered your guest
anything to drink? Idiot!
[HACHIOJI]
It's all rig--
No, no, I'm fine!
[HARUKI] Sorry about my
little brother. He's a moron.
Hey. Wait, you've
been here before.
You came last year, right?
But what's your name? I forgot.
Oh, well, who cares?
I gotta name for ya: piggy.
His name's Hachi.
Huh?
His name's Hachi!
--[HARUKI] What was that?
--[HACHIOJI] Natsuki, it's okay.
--Huh? Dumb-ass.
--[phone ringing]
[ISE]
Nothing at all!
Hello!
Oh! Yes, thank you for earlier!
No, no, it was
completely fine...
Sorry, man.
Don't worry about me.
Last night, Natsuki said
something interesting.
Something about a training camp?
[HARUKI]
I'm sorry, but the answer's no.
Yeah, but--
I let him attend
last year because
you were so persistent and
I wanted you out of my hair.
But this time,
I'm not giving in.
Thing is, our folks're dead.
There was an accident
six years ago.
I was 20 and Natsuki was ten.
I've worked my butt off
to put him through school.
I'm sorry. But it's
expensive and we're broke.
Plus, he promised me he'd
quit the club and get a job.
Right?
I think it's about time you
made good on that promise.
I'm the one who made
him join. Blame me.
[HARUKI sighs]
[HARUKI]
And why would you do that, huh?
[HACHIOJI] Well, I wanted
Natsuki on the team.
Because I thought it
would be lots of fun.
Ah...
And I was right, too.
He always works hard
and he always has
a good attitude.
[HACHIOJI]
His smile is infectious.
[HACHIOJI] I don't regret
recruiting him at all.
[ISE]
Please.
Huh?
[ISE]
Please, Haruki!
I'm sorry.
I-I know you do more
around here than I do.
I'm really grateful, brother.
For everything you've done.
[ISE]
But still.
This camp--it's everything!
I wanna play rugby!
Please let me go!
Natsuki...
Wait, are you two
a couple or something?
[gasps]
Uh...
Hey, it's cool. A lot of
fruitcakes play rugby!
[laughs]
Jeez, so dramatic.
All ya had to say is:
"I don't wanna be away
from my boyfrie--"
You're an asshole! Screw you!
You don't know anything
about me, you dick!
And now, it's my turn.
[ISE] Come on, Hachi!
You have to leave, now!
[HACHIOJI]
No!
[HARUKI]
Wait a second!
[HACHIOJI]
Natsuki! You don't have to...
I'm sorry, Hachi!
[HACHIOJI]
Y-You can stay at my house!
[ISE] I'm quitting the team.
Do you hear me?
So leave me alone!
[HACHIOJI]
This isn't right.
Don't do this!
Just tell Coach I can't
afford to play, okay?
[HACHIOJI]
Hold on!
[ISE] Tell the captain
I'm really sorry!
Hachi. Thanks for everything!
[HACHIOJI]
Natsuki! Just wait!
I'll be fine. Thank you so much.
[RUGBY TEAM panting]
[ISE] I'm quitting the
team. Do you hear me?
So leave me alone!
Hey. Ya seen Ise?
Huh? Now that you mention it,
I don't think he's here today!
Well, that's weird.
I guess he decided to
start skipping practice.
[EBUMI]
Like hell he has!
He's not a waste
of space like you!
[EBUMI]
You got a sec?
Ise. Have you heard
from him at all?
Not a peep. Sorry.
I wouldn't worry.
He's probably not feeling
well or something.
I'm sure he'll be back in
action in no time, I hope.
[EBUMI]
Hm.
[BOY 15A] Come on, man,
pass the ball over there!
No!
[BOYS chattering]
Later!
[BOY 15B]
Bye! See ya tomorrow!
[HACHIOJI]
Natsuki, just wait!
Uh...
When did you get home?
You're late!
Where in the hell have you been?
I thought you quit
the Rugby Team.
I'm sorry.
I stopped somewhere on
my way home from school.
Wait! You're not off
the hook, Natsuki!
Uh--
Go out and get us
something to eat!
[ISE]
I loved those guys so much.
Oh, drinks.
[machine beeping]
[EBUMI]
You're lame!
Uh?
Look at you!
Are you running errands
for your brother again?
So what if I am?
Why? Who cares?
Hey, not me. I just
came by to rent a DVD
and there's a store right
across from your place!
I wanted to watch
somethin' dirty!
[laughs] Yeah. You've
always been a big perv!
Yeah.
It's too bad the
jerks kicked me out!
You're lame. Not me.
Your pal, Hachi?
Well, he was being weird
at practice today.
[EBUMI] Did your brother
finally lose it on you?
[ISE]
Yeah.
Of course!
That d-bag's been terrible
to you since freshman year!
Man I bet he kicked your butt!
Look, here's the deal--
[ISE]
Just shut up, will ya? Listen.
I'm quitting the
freakin' team, okay?
[EBUMI] Your brother said you
had to get a job, didn't he?
[gasps]
I figure this is enough to cover
about one week of work.
Now you can go to
the training camp.
Uh...
Tell him to piss off.
Tell him to leave you alone!
[ISE]
Ebumi, come on.
Where did you get this?
Did you beat up a
bunch of freshman?
No!
Don't be stubborn
and take the money!
You know how it is, man.
[EBUMI] They've always given me
more money than I can use.
So I've saved it up.
Ah--
But, I can't--
Dude, please.
I'm not taking no for an answer,
so there's no sense
in arguing with me.
Let me go!
We're lucky to have
Hachi and Sekizan
and the other old
guys on our team.
They recruited us hard and now
they won't give up on us.
Even when we're idiots.
How did you find out?
Guessing Hachi told you?
No, he didn't tell me,
and to be honest,
he didn't have to.
He's a good guy, but he's
got a terrible poker face.
[ISE]
Oh.
The thing is...
[EBUMI]
Hm?
[ISE]
I don't blame my brother.
You see, after the accident,
I was supposed to go live
with my uncle in Kyushu.
But my brother, he...
I'm sorry.
I was ten years old
when Natsuki was born.
I couldn't have been
more excited to finally
have a little brother
to look after.
Words can't describe it.
He's the same age
I was back then.
And it's not right
to send him away
to live with someone
he barely knows.
I won't do it.
It isn't okay by me.
Let him stay. Please, I'll
take responsibility for him!
Haruki took care of me.
[EBUMI]
That was the past, man.
He may have been a good
brother way back then,
but what about now?
He treats you like crap!
You don't know what he
and I have been through!
Yeah, you know, you're
right, I really don't.
You sure about this?
[EBUMI]
Hm?
Are you really, really sure?
[EBUMI] We only have
a few years of rugby left.
A few years to do
what we love most.
It's not like we're
gonna go to college.
But--
[EBUMI]
So am I sure?
Totally, man. A hundred percent.
Some of the guys,
like Noka or Sumiyoshi,
will probably go to college.
Hell, they'll probably
play on the Rugby Team
and work out in a fancy ass gym!
[ISE laughs]
Yeah.
Those two wastes of space
don't even hustle
when we do drills in practice!
Come on.
They've been tryin'
a lot harder lately.
It's too little,
too late in my book!
Screw those guys!
You've got much bigger problems!
The little turd?
Oh, right!
I wanted to play flanker
long before he did!
[ISE] The truth is, I can't
stand being on the outside
of a scrum looking in.
It makes me feel useless
'cause I wanna help out
my team, but I can't.
It's a terrible feeling.
That's why I've been
working out everyday.
So I can switch to flanker!
Damn that turd!
Dude! Keep it down, will ya?
Little jerk has no respect for
the older guys on the team!
I totally agree, dude.
I mean, there's only one reason
Hyosu and Kasuga play flanker.
It's not cause they're the best,
it's cause everyone else
has a position already
or just isn't right.
You should work with
the little turd.
Send those two
back to the backs!
Huh?
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
I mean, we have to train
the freshman anyway.
Plus, if we don't
get more forwards,
then next year, we're screwed.
[EBUMI laughs]
Ya see, ya can't quit--
you love it too much!
[ISE]
All right, all right, you win!
[EBUMI laughs]
Buddy. That cash was
a loan, by the way.
So, ya better pay me back!
After you wad it up and throw it
in your brother's
face, of course!
If I didn't need it,
I'd throw it in your face!
[EBUMI]
Hm.
Uh--
You took your time.
[ISE]
I'm sorry.
Who is that thug
you were just with?
[ISE]
Oh.
[laughs] He's not a thug.
He's one of my best friends!
Maybe if I put on a disguise
I'll be able to rent a DVD.
A really, super dirty one.
Hm.
Ah, that'll never work.
[KOMORI]
Next time: "You've Prepared."