[OHARANO]
Dammit!
[OHARANO grunts]
Wow. So you're putting
Ebumi in the game?
If you want my opinion,
he's just gonna cause
more trouble for ya, Coach.
[EBUMI]
Hey, number 11.
I hope you realize
those digits you've got
on your back belong to me, kid!
What, you scared?
[MATSUO]
You guys!
[MATSUO] I'll play fly-half.
Maroudo, you're center.
Ebumi. You wanna be our wing?
Well, here's your chance.
Ha! I won't
let you down, Matsuo.
[UMENO]
You sad? Your other pea's gone.
You're all alone in the pod.
[GION]
No.
Next time I'll practice harder.
I'll get way better soon.
Just wait and see, Ume.
I'll be out there
where I belong.
[UMENO]
You're a good boy, Gion.
[GION]
Hey!
Don't pet me on the head!
I'm not a freakin' dog, okay?
[UMENO]
But you're such a good boy.
[GION]
Ugh. You're the worst, Ume!
[UMENO]
You don't mean that!
[GION]
Just leave me alone!
[HANADATE]
Well, look at what we have here.
Another dumbass.
[grunting]
[MAROUDO grunts]
I hope this works.
[SAGAMI PLAYERS gasp]
[YANE]
A high punt!
I've got it!
[HANADATE] These losers
keep kicking the ball around.
Do they even want
to go on the offensive?
[EBUMI chuckles]
[HANADATE groans]
[YANE]
Hana!
[HANADATE groans]
[whistle blows]
[REF 3A]
Try!
Wow!
I can't believe
that just happened!
He scored a try against Sagami!
[EBUMI] Hey, Matsuo!
You shoulda warned me
you were gonna boot the ball!
Nice kick!
[MATSUO laughs]
Well...
I knew you'd manage to
get it somehow, Ebumi.
Nice try!
Aw, man, he just
missed the conversion.
But it's seven to five now.
Who knows?
Maybe this will turn the tide.
[HANADATE] Why the hell
did no one tell me Jinko
had a ringer on the team?
That guy's good. Damn.
Hey, just shake it off, okay?
[HYOSU]
Dammit! They got the ball again!
Bastard!
Stay low!
[BOTH grunt]
--[whistle blows]
--[REF 3A] Knock-on by Sagami!
--All right! Yeah!
--Yeah!
Some of these guys
know how to tackle.
[ALL grunt]
[KAMO]
Ebumi!
Heads up!
[ISHIBASHI]
Him again!
This is not good.
He's got a one-on-one
against Hana!
[EBUMI yelling]
[WADA]
Hana! Stop him!
[HANADATE yells]
[whistle blows]
[REF 3A]
Try!
[HANADATE yelps]
[EBUMI]
Hey, freshman.
Piece of advice.
Make sure your
scrum cap's on tight.
Otherwise, I'll have
to be more careful
when I knock you
on your sorry ass.
[whistle blows]
We made the conversion,
It's seven to 12 now!
What an awesome comeback!
[clapping]
[YOSHIDA] Well! That was
certainly impressive!
Of course, it's not too
difficult to score a try or two
when you have a fast runner
on your team, is it, Coach?
I'm no sports expert,
but I always thought rugby
was about teamwork,
not the achievement
of one individual player.
[KOMORI] Talking to you about
rugby is like talking to a dog
about why it likes
to lick itself.
Listen up, you guys.
We won't stand a chance
of making it to Hanazono
if we can't beat one of
Kanagawa's worst teams.
[WADA]
Get your head in the game, Hana!
Uh, yes, sir!
[WADA]
Let's go!
Hey!
We're doing all right
against them.
Maybe our training camp
paid off after all!
[HYOSU grunts]
Gosh.
They're roughing
us up out there.
True, but that's
not why they're better.
They're better 'cause their
fundamentals are spot on.
They're showing us
their experience.
And their superior
work ethic, too.
[KAMO]
Ise!
Whoa!
[KOMORI] As a team,
their rugby acumen is very high.
An interception!
[NAGO]
Forwards, come on!
I'll stop him!
[KASUGA]
The first guy was a decoy!
The backs were behind him!
I can finally stretch
my legs, you guys!
Hey, Suwa!
You better not let him
get past you!
[SUWA panting]
--[SOGA] Ha!
--[SUWA grunting]
[SOGA yells]
[whistle blows]
[REF 3A]
Try!
Ya know,
I really shoulda scored
closer to the goalposts,
don't you think, Ishi?
Whatever.
Just be more careful next time.
--[whistle blows]
--Well, jeez.
That comeback you just launched
was rather short-lived,
wasn't it, Coach Komori?
[whistle blows]
[REF 3A] That's the end
of the first half!
Take 15!
[YOSHIDA]
Hello!
[laughs]
Well, boys...
You're putting up a fight.
[KOMORI]
Yeah.
It's not a bad showing.
You've started to make
a conscious effort to go low
when you make a tackle.
And you're moving the
ball around more, too.
Good work.
You've gotten better.
But you're still
not good enough.
They've got you licked.
The truth is you're just not
at their level yet, boys.
But now you have
a target to aim for.
[KITA] They scored on you twice
which can only mean one thing--
you're slacking off!
You had three missed tackles,
and you dropped two passes.
You're acting like you wanna get
second place again this year!
Fix it right now!
[SAGAMI TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[KOMORI] There's only one thing
to do in a game like this.
And that's steal
their techniques.
Learn everything
you can from them.
[KOMORI]
Watch how they pass and run.
How they get separation
from you on offense.
Try to figure out their goal
when they're moving the ball
all around the field.
If they try to provoke
you and get in your head,
then learn from that, too.
Everything we learn
gives us a competitive edge.
You won't face a
more informative team,
I promise you that, boys.
So get out there
and learn something!
That's all!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[EBUMI]
All right!
Now that's what
I'm talking about!
[JINKO TEAM chattering]
[HANADATE] You should've
hurt your buddy sooner,
then maybe my team
would've had a real shot.
If it wasn't for him,
we would've made it to
Nationals; there's no doubt!
[IWASHIMIZU growling]
[GION]
Hey, tree trunk.
What's up?
Why'd you get in
a fight out there?
Oh. Uh, well...
He sucks.
He's rude. And he was
really mean to me.
So I guess I lost control.
You know, I've been
thinkin' about ya.
[IWASHIMIZU gasps]
Do you realize the way
you stand is all wrong?
[IWASHIMIZU]
What?
[GION]
It's the truth.
You hunch over 'cause of your
height when you should be
standing up straight.
[GION]
Like this. See?
Yeah, man! That's the ticket!
Always stand up straight, okay?
Oh, wow! You look
so strong, man!
It'd be even better if you
tilted your head to the side.
[KAMO]
Yeah, like that!
[GION laughs] You sure know what
you're talking about, Kamo.
[KAMO]
O-Oh, Iwashi.
Look even meaner.
People pick on you out there
because the way you stand
makes you look like
a little weakling!
[IWASHIMIZU]
For real?
Hold your head
up high, tree trunk.
After all, you're
a badass, right?
[laughs]
[HYOSU laughing]
Iwashi, you look serious!
[HACHIOJI] What are you
guys doing over here?
They can joke
around all they like,
but at the end of the day,
it won't solve their
fundamental problem.
'Cause they're still
going to lose every game.
Every time.
And who are they going to point
the finger at then, Coach?
Tell me.
Did something happen
to you in the past?
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
that's none of your business.
[WADA] That winger, there--
He's the one we have to watch.
I can't believe Hana's been
so frickin' useless this match.
Maybe he oughta
go sit on the bench.
[whistle blows]
[REF 3A]
Second half starts now!
[IWASHIMIZU grunts]
Wasn't much of
a tackle, big boy.
[IWASHIMIZU yelling]
[ADACHIGAHARA grunts]
That bastard.
Who does that jerk think he is?
That's not the right time
to use your new look, pal.
[KAMO yells]
[ISE grunts]
[KURAYAMA, HIROTA grunt, growl]
They're puttin' up a good fight.
But there's no way they
can resist us to the end.
I can't catch up to 'em!
Hori!
What a takedown.
[HORIKAWA, SEKIZAN grunt]
[HORIKAWA]
You bastard. Damn you.
[whistle blows]
[SOGA]
Hey, check it out, Ishi,
I scored right between
the posts this time.
[ISHIBASHI]
Sweet.
[whistle blows]
Man, it still hurts. Dammit.
Why hit me that hard
when he knows
we're just gonna score anyway?
[WADA] One guy won't
win the game for them
unless we stop fighting.
So suck it up, Hori.
[HYOSU grunts]
[ISE gasps]
Dammit! The ball's
moving too fast!
Nice! Well, I guess
we've warmed up!
Too bad,
looks like this is turning
into a one-sided game.
You want some more? Chase this!
[WADA]
Whoa...
[WADA yells]
--[whistle blows]
--[HACHIOJI] Sekizan!
[REF 3A]
Stop! Stop!
[WADA]
Is he-- Is he okay?
[WADA gasps]
[SEKIZAN]
I'm all right.
Let's play ball.
[KOMORI]
Captain? Are you good?
Umeno. Come here.
Is it bad? I've never seen
so much blood before!
[KOMORI]
Relax.
[KOMORI] You bled a lot,
but the good news is
the cut's shallow.
[KOMORI]
What's this?
You seem happy
about it, Captain.
[SEKIZAN]
Yeah. I'm having fun.
Game's not over.
We've got Sagami
in our sights now.
Let's finish strong.
We still have time
to catch 'em, guys!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yeah!
[REF 3A] Sagami's ball.
We'll start with a scrum!
[REF 3A]
Crouch! Bind! Set!
[JINKO TEAM, SAGAMI TEAM grunt]
[ISE yelling]
[ISE grunting]
[HORIKAWA] Willpower alone
won't be enough to stop me!
[SEKIZAN, HORIKAWA grunt]
If a single player won't
get the job done...
[HORIKAWA groans]
...then we'll use two!
[WADA grunts]
And if two's not enough,
we'll bring three!
[WADA yells]
[YANE] Outside! Get the
ball to the outside!
Backs move up!
Keep the pressure on!
Don't let 'em think!
[SUWA, SOGA grunt]
[SEKIZAN]
Keep pushing them!
Don't ever give up!
Give 'em hell, guys!
Keep fighting till the end!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yeah!
[YOSHIDA]
No...
This isn't the Jinko Rugby Team.
Not the one I know.
Sir, you want me
to be the advisor
of the Rugby Team?
But I don't even know
how the game is played.
It's okay, no one does.
They're not a real club anyway.
Just as long as they don't get
hurt, then you're in the clear.
Trust me. It's an easy job.
[YOSHIDA] I have to at least
try to learn about the game--
it'd be rude not to.
[YOSHIDA] Hey, let's study
harder so we can win
next time, boys!
Oh, shut your face, will ya?
What do you know about
rugby anyway, ya big nerd?
Reading your stupid books
isn't gonna help us at all.
What?
If you think we're gonna
teach you the rules,
then you're outta
your freakin' mind!
Look, we'll handle
ourselves, okay?
Just go. Leave us be and
we'll do the same to you.
[HACHIOJI]
Hey! It's Mr. Yoshida! Hello!
[HACHIOJI] Man, that guy's
always so cold to us.
[HACHIOJI]
Score!
None of the
upperclassmen are here!
The only good thing
about our team is that
we have lots of books.
We suck, but at least
we're informed!
[JINKO TEAM, SAGAMI TEAM
yelling]
[UMENO] There are ten minutes
left in the second half!
[YOSHIDA]
What's going on?
Normally they'd be smiling.
[YOSHIDA]
Wait. When was that exactly?
[YOSHIDA] When was the
last time I actually
watched them play?
How long has it been?
How many years?
[YOSHIDA]
It was back when Sekizan
and the others were freshmen.
[EBUMI]
Don't write us off just yet!
[EBUMI yells]
[HORIKAWA]
Hey!
Come on, guys!
You can't just
throw it anywhere!
[UMENO] Let's go, Jinko.
Score another try!
Take 'em out, you guys!
[YOSHIDA]
Shinshi?
He wasn't that serious
about the team
when he was a freshman.
[ALL grunt]
It's not over! It's not over!
It's not over yet!
Keep fighting!
[SEKIZAN grunts]
Hey! That was clearly
a knock-on, ref!
[KOMORI]
I know how you feel.
There's nothing's
more frustrating
than when a ref misses
an easy call.
[MAROUDO, HORIKAWA grunt]
[WADA] I'm sorry.
I underestimated you at first.
[WADA]
What's this?
[SEKIZAN yells]
[KOMORI] Next time:
"I Ate Too Much Shaved Ice."