[PRINCIPAL 1A] And so,
to all students, new and old,
it is extremely vital that
you build the foundations
for living in a global society
by learning from one another,
studying together,
and supporting each other
in all your endeavors.
This is the core of our
institutional values
here at Kanagawa High.
So, ladies and gentlemen,
as you embark on
this new adventure...
[GIRL 1A whispering]
Hey, check it out.
[UMENO whispering]
What's up?
[GIRL 1A]
Look at that guy.
Right over there in
the new student section.
You see how big he is?
What is he?
Some kind of giant or something?
[school bell rings]
[THUG 1C] The nerd was diggin'
for change in the freakin'
vending machine, can you
believe that crap?
What a loser!
Hey, watch where
you're standin', jerk.
Uh...
Oh, crap! You're huge!
Are you... a freshman?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Yeah.
Then you need to watch out!
You're right! My bad!
There's no need to be afraid.
Look, this kid's a softy
[THUG 1A laughs]
What a freakin' joke!
Let's teach him a lesson!
[THUG 1C]
Yeah. Great idea!
[THUG 1C laughs]
[THUGS]
Huh?
Tch.
[GION sighs]
[THUGS laugh]
This year's freshman
sure are hilarious!
A massive freak who's too much
of a puss to fight back!
And a little wimp who's so short
he looks like a toddler!
So, what's your deal here, man?
What's a Giant like you doing
here in my hallway? Huh?
Well, guess what, freak show?
This is my turf
and I'm not gonna be--
[THUG 1B yelps]
Short? Short?!
Jerk! Don't call me short!
[BOTH]
Oh, crap, that kid's strong!
[THUG 1C]
Let him go!
[THUG 1A]
You little turd stain!
Wait. Wait, what'd you say?
You wanna see
a little turd stain?
I'll show you a turd stain!
[GION yelps]
[THUGS scream]
[BOTH]
Whoa. He's so huge.
[grunting]
Let's get outta here!
Uh... So that just happened.
[GION]
Enough, man! Put me down!
Hello? What's your
problem, are you deaf?
Put me down!
Hey!
Why'd you drag me
outta there like that?
Uh... 'Cause?
Those super-mean bullies
were about to gang up on you
and kick your face in on
your first day of school!
Oh. And, you saved my skin.
So thank you.
You're pathetic, dude.
Hey, that's not cool, man.
Why say something mean
when I was being so nice!
Listen. I wasn't
trying to save you.
I just hate jerks
who call me short!
And even more so!
Why would I even stick my neck
out for a giant I just met!
You're so cruel!
[whimpers]
Anyway.
I'm Iwashimizu Sumiaki.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yeah, whatever. I'm Gion.
[GION sighs]
[GION]
Why're you following me?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Sorry!
I just hate walking alone--
is that all right?
Oh, hey, volleyball!
[GIRL 1C]
Awesome!
[BOY 1A] How far do you
think we're gonna get
in this year's preliminaries?
--[IWASHIMIZU] Pardon--
--[GION] Listen--
[IWASHIMIZU]
My bad. Go ahead.
[GION] So. When you
picked me up earlier,
something occurred to me.
You're a really a big guy.
You can see more,
and you can do more, too.
And you wanna know something?
--[GION yells]
--[IWASHIMIZU yelps]
[GION]
That... pisses me off!
Dude, tell me your secret.
What kinda food
do I have to eat?
How many gallons of milk
do I have to drink
to get as big as you?
Um...
Well, at home, I normally
just drink hot barley tea!
[GION] So you're sayin'
I need to drink tea, too?
Well, no.
Actually, I think milk would
be better for growing.
[GION] Are you makin' fun
of me right now, tree trunk?
If there's one thing I hate,
it's people givin' me crap
'cause I'm short.
People think I wear
kids' clothes!
Girls don't wanna date me!
And grown men are the worst!
They treat me like a baby!
They all look down on me,
just 'cause I'm little.
And you?
I hate you most of all
'cause you're a big,
giant, clueless oaf!
[gasps]
--Uh--
--[footsteps]
[HACHIOJI]
Iwashimizu!
[yelps]
What's the problem, buddy?
How come you're runnin' away?
Huh?
Oh, Hachioji, it's you.
Dude. You're even
bigger than before!
I still can't believe
you're enrolled here.
It's awesome! And guess what?
Dude. We're besties now.
All year long.
Huh?
[GION]
Get the hell off me, you jerk!
Did you just give
birth? [laughs]
[HACHIOJI]
That wasn't a short joke, okay?
I legitimately thought you were
Iwashimizu's newborn child.
Shut up!
So, freshman, you got a name?
Tch.
I'm Gion Kenji.
Well, Gion.
Hope you're not busy.
Cause if you're free,
you should watch us practice.
We're about to start.
[GION]
Hm?
Practice?
Is this guy in a club
or somethin' like that?
Huh?
Oh, come on, you
haven't told him yet?
Uh... Well, it's...
...rugby.
[GION] So... What the
heck is "rugby" anyway?
Wait. Are you for real?
[HACHIOJI laughs] Wow, you don't
know much of anything, do ya?
If you're gonna play
with us, you'll hafta learn.
That's for sure.
[GION]
I'm not here to play with you.
For all I know, you guys're
a bunch of losers.
So don't get any ideas!
[laughs] Whatever you say, Gion.
Whatever you say.
But I think you might
change your mind.
Rugby's a fun sport. And once
you start, you can't stop.
And the best part is,
anyone can be the star.
Even me?
[HACHIOJI]
Even you, Gion. You'll see.
Hey, tree trunk.
The rules--what are they?
What? Uh...
[GION]
What's wrong with the ball?
It's not even round.
[gasps] You're joking, right?
Look. Something's
about to happen.
Oh. Yeah.
It looks like they're
about to play a mock game.
Just watch.
[GION]
So what's the deal?
Is it kinda like soccer?
[IWASHIMIZU]
No, not really.
You have to run the ball
past the goalposts
on either end of the field.
Whoa!
He just pummeled him--
that can't be legal!
Actually, no, it is.
You try to steal the ball,
violently if need be.
Big guys like me
have an advantage,
so they tried recruiting me
back in middle school.
Of course, a whole
lot has happened
in between then and now.
[MIYUKI laughs]
Oh, man, you're really huge!
Well, it looks like fun to me.
[gasps]
You don't understand,
it's not all about fun.
Rugby is one of the most
dangerous sports
out there, Gion!
[GION]
Who cares?
My dad and my brother
are both man-mountains.
Not me. I'm small.
When we fought, I got my
butt kicked every time.
Lookin' at all these
massive guys...
If I could steal
the ball from them...
...that would be awesome.
[GION]
But...
...they're so much bigger and
stronger than I'll ever be.
If I did try to join the team,
they'd squash me
like a freakin' bug.
That's not true at all.
[IWASHIMIZU] Sure, lots of
rugby players are really big.
But, trust me.
Size isn't everything.
[IWASHIMIZU]
Look closely.
Big guys, small guys, fat guys,
skinny guys, too--all
different types and shapes.
All with their own
unique skills.
[RUGBY PLAYERS grunting]
[IWASHIMIZU]
There are no star strikers.
No power hitters either.
[IWASHIMIZU]
If you're holding the ball,
then you're the star.
[whistle blows]
Well? What'd ya think?
Fun, right?
That's the coolest thing
I've seen in my whole life!
[HACHIOJI]
Sweet. Glad you liked it!
Hm... I think you'll work
best as a half-scrum.
Because you're small.
Then again,
I bet you're pretty quick
so you might do well as a wing.
Well, whaddaya say?
You wanna join the Rugby Team?
[GION] If you're that
desperate for me to join,
how can I say, "no"?
I'll knock the crap
outta everybody!
[laughs] That's the
kinda attitude we like!
I have a feeling you're gonna
fit in here just fine!
All right! Wait up.
Where are you off to, man?
I need you to teach me how to--
[IWASHIMIZU]
Listen. I'm sorry. I really am.
But I'm not interested.
What? Well, why not?
Because.
Bye.
[HACHIOJI]
There's no practice today.
[GION]
What?! Why?
[HACHIOJI]
'Cause we're recruiting.
Then what are you doing in here?
Guarding the base.
Who knows, a prospective
rugby player might
walk through that
door any minute.
But I wanna get started!
Right now!
That's not gonna happen, Gion.
I do appreciate your
eagerness though.
And I'd appreciate it even more
if you got offa my desk.
[GION growls]
[GION]
I'll teach myself!
[HACHIOJI]
Gion, hold on a sec! Come back!
Hey, Sekizan.
How did it go? Any bites?
Three guys. Only one
of 'em's played before.
[HACHIOJI]
Wow! Nice work!
I was hopin' to run
into that big freshman
you told me about,
but no such luck.
[GION]
Uh--
Who are you? Hachi,
you know this guy?
[gasps]
[HACHIOJI]
Gion. A freshman. He wants in.
[SEKIZAN]
Hm?
He's small. Too small, right?
[SEKIZAN] I have an idea
about practice tomorrow.
Once we're done introducing
the new players,
I think we should focus on--
[GION]
Small, eh?
Small?! I'll show
you small, jerk!
[GION yelps]
[GION grunts]
[SEKIZAN]
He's light, too.
Ow!
Gion, that was not a
smart move at all, bud.
This is Sekizan.
He's the strongest guy
on the Rugby Team.
Hey.
Big man, was that some kinda
rugby move you pulled on me?
A what?
Uh, he's new.
He doesn't know anything yet.
[SEKIZAN] Listen, bro,
I'm sorry I threw you.
That wasn't cool.
Could you maybe not
sit on the table?
[GION] I attacked you. So it's
like five percent my fault.
Just five percent?
[sighs] Listen, that "maneuver"
you were askin' us
about's called a tackle.
Awesome!
Please teach me your
genius ways, master!
You talk way too much, freshman.
[HACHIOJI chuckles]
Gion's havin' a rough first day.
[GION]
Oh, yeah. One thing.
Why won't that guy join?
The big guy. "Tree trunk."
Sorry! Please don't tackle me!
Oh. Iwashimizu.
Huh?
[HACHIOJI]
Hm...
Well, the truth is...
So, what kinda
books do you like?
Well, I like all kinds,
but lately I've been really
into romance novels.
Yeah! They're the best!
You know something?
At first, we were
pretty scared of you.
'Cause you're the biggest
person we've ever seen!
But not anymore--we think
you're awesome now!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Heh... Thank you?
Uh... Hi, Gion.
I need you to come with me, pal!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Wait. Do you mean right now?
Because I'd like to, but,
I can't. I have Book Club.
[GION]
Nerd Club's not goin' anywhere.
What was he talkin' about?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Uh... Gion?
So, are you gonna tell me
what we're doing out here?
[GION] Oh, is this it?
Dangit, no it's not.
This is it! No, false alarm.
Uh... Can I help out?
[GION]
It stinks in here!
Ah! Jackpot!
[yelps]
Why do we need a tackle bag?
[GION] Why do ya think,
tree trunk? For tacklin'.
Get ready, dude, cause I'm
about to bring the pain
like you've never seen!
[yelps]
[GION]
Just teach me how
to tackle, man! Now!
Uh, please?
[HACHIOJI] Hm. It's easy,
you just hurl your body
at your opponent.
I'd start off with the tackle
bag in the shed if I were you!
[laughs] You're goin' down, man!
[gasps] No.
Please don't do this,
I'm begging you, Gion!
Shut up!
[yells]
[IWASHIMIZU] Most people
are too afraid to charge
at someone when
they first start.
But not him--he's fearless.
Don't run.
[gasps]
[GION]
If you do, you'll get hurt.
Gimme that!
Tree trunk. Look.
You tackle me, okay?
Ah! I can't.
No! Don't make me
do this, please!
I'm twice your size!
I don't want you
to get hurt, Gion.
I won't run away.
I'm gonna hold my ground!
So you can't hurt me!
Come on.
What, are you scared?
Don't be. This isn't
middle school.
[IWASHIMIZU]
Back then, I had a classmate
who was a really
good rugby player.
[IWASHIMIZU] In fact, the only
reason I started playing
in the first place is because
he invited me to join the team.
All right, guys.
How 'bout we wrap up practice
with a team scrimmage?
[IWASHIMIZU] You're all
pumped up today, aren't ya?
I'm supposed to be!
I am the team captain, right?
Besides, man, if we
clean up at the next game,
we're going straight
to Nationals!
[RUGBY PLAYERS grunting]
[RUGBY GUY 1C]
Somebody tackle him already!
[MIYUKI grunts]
[IWASHIMIZU panting]
[MIYUKI screams]
[RUGBY GUY 1A]
What's wrong?
[RUGBY GUY 1B]
Miyuki?
[RUGBY GUY 1C]
Are you okay?
[screaming]
[RUGBY GUY 1A]
Oh, no!
[RUGBY GUY 1B]
Get a teacher!
Someone get a teacher now!
He's in a lot of pain!
[IWASHIMIZU whimpering]
[whistle blows]
[GREEN TEAM cheers]
[RED TEAM sniffling]
[IWASHIMIZU]
Poor Miyuki.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be so cocky.
You won't knock my
shoulder out of socket.
I can promise you that much!
It's not your fault, okay?
The guy you inured was
just weak, that's all.
[IWASHIMIZU] Don't insult
Miyuki, you understand me?
--[thud]
--[gasps]
No. Please.
[pants]
[laughing] Ow!
Huh?
Dude! Wow!
[gasps]
Nice hit! Rugby is amazing!
[laughs] Oh, man,
you're really huge!
Wanna join the Rugby Team?
You'll love it. Rugby's awesome!
Come on. What do
you have to lose?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Yeah.
[GION] Next time:
"I want to Tackle Someone!"