[thud]
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A]
Jinko did not release the ball.
[PLAYER 23A]
All right!
[PLAYER 23B]
Let's convert this one, guys!
This is not good.
We're making a lot of
mistakes out there today.
Sorry.
[GION]
Mm...
[NOKA]
Hm...
[ALL groaning]
[GION]
Which one is it?
Is it this one?
This is the worst!
I can't make up
my freakin' mind!
Dude. Can you give
me a hint please?
No! I'm not gonna
give you a hint--
I'm trying to win!
But maybe pick this one.
He's not some two-year-old
kid in diapers.
There's no way he's gonna fall
for a trick that obvious--
[GION]
All right!
[NOKA]
You sure?
[GION]
Yes, I am!
Aw, crap, I drew
the Old Maid again!
Did you really
just fall for that?
Don't get so worked up, Gion,
it's just a silly
little card game.
[GION]
Huh?
Well, guess I won, yup!
This sucks!
[NOKA]
Ugh. It's bedtime.
Not yet.
Don't be like that--at least
give me a shot at a rematch!
[NOKA]
Not a chance.
How do you have so much
energy left anyway?
Go run some laps or something.
Hey, Oharano.
I wanted to ask you
about this play.
Dude. I'm reading here.
[keyboard tapping]
[IWASHIMIZU sighs]
Maybe we should do some drills!
[screams]
Hey. Why'd you
sneak up on me, man?
'Cause there's something
extremely important
I need to ask you.
[IWASHIMIZU]
What's that?
[in a Romanian accent]
Vill you let me suck your blood?
[sighs] You almost made
me jump outta my skin.
Come on, dude,
take a chill pill.
I just wanted to hang
with you, that's all.
--[phone rings]
--Huh?
Yeah?
[TAIRA]
Miyuki!
What in the sam hill
you doin' right now?
Nothing.
Just chilling with the
Jinko guy's at their hotel.
[TAIRA]
Ooo de lolly?
You're seriously at
the Jinko Team's hotel?
Is Sekizan there?
No. He's not here. Sorry--
[TAIRA]
Where the hell is he then?
I've been blowin' him up!
But he won't return
any of my phone calls!
Sekizan!
Tell him to hit me up, bro!
[phone vibrates]
[KASHIMA]
Hey, Matsuo.
[MATSUO]
Hm?
Come with me.
[MIYUKI]
That guy's a few screws loose.
Don't you think it's weird how
obsessed he is with Sekizan?
Not really.
I think he just has
a bro-crush on him.
'Cause Seki's so awesome.
Maybe.
But that bro-crush is a one-way
street, that's for sure.
[laughs]
[IWASHIMIZU]
Come to think of it.
The older guys all disappeared.
I guess they went off
and had another meeting,
I wonder what about.
It's their last
year at Sugadaira.
I bet they're telling stories
and laughing about old times.
Wouldn't you do the same thing?
Yeah, I would.
[MIYUKI] You're cool
with barley tea, right?
[yelps]
Thanks, man.
[rattling]
[gasps]
[rattling continues]
[MIYUKI]
Huh?
[IWASHIMIZU screams]
There's somebody inside!
[GION]
I wish I could get in,
but this thing's
way too dangerous.
Wait!
What if I don't have to get
inside the washing machine?
What if I train by washing
the laundry by hand instead?
No. Because if I did that,
it wouldn't really
be training at all.
--It'd just be doing laundry.
--[IWASHIMIZU] Uh, Gion?
Huh?
Tree trunk? What's up?
What are you two doing?
You look like total weirdoes.
We were just about to ask
you the same thing, Gion.
Well. I'm secret training.
And I'm trying to incorporate
this washing machine.
Using a washing
machine to train?
Wow, I'm really
impressed. A novel idea!
"Novel"?
So. What kind of exercise
did ya have in mind?
I don't know. Just somethin'.
"Something"? What something?
That's exactly what I'm hopin'
to figure out here, okay?
See, I keep tryin'
to think of an angle
and I'm comin' up with a big
fat goose egg every time.
Hey! Wait a second!
Maybe you two can help me
come up with an idea!
[MIYUKI]
Hm...
How about this? We'll do
some scrum training!
[GION]
Okay!
Do it! Give it a go!
Am I doing it right, guys?
[MIYUKI]
Yeah that's pretty good,
but it won't feel real unless
we turn on the machine.
Oh, no, you don't!
What? Do you wanna put some
detergent in there first?
No, Miyuki, that's
a terrible idea.
Good call.
Maybe its better we don't
use the washer then.
What? We're not
gonna use it at all?
I've got an even better idea!
Ooh! Awesome! What is it?
You ready?
First extend both of
your arms out and up.
Right!
Next, let's get into
a deep back stretch!
Dude. Wait.
These are just radio exercises!
Well. Wanna play instead?
[GION]
This is lame.
Can we do something
more intense?
[MIYUKI] It's always good
to revisit the basics,
don't you think?
[IWASHIMIZU] Man, I really
hope we get to play
against Keijo again.
[MIYUKI]
If we're lucky we'll get to go
head to head in the prelims!
Whoa! Wait, the
prelims for what?
Huh? The National Tournament.
You know, at Hanazono.
Hanazono, huh? Count me in!
I hope we actually
make it that far.
It won't be easy.
No, it won't, man!
You'll have to beat us first.
You think you're
up for the task?
Duh.
Piece of cake!
How 'bout we play
a little game then?
Gion.
Let's see if you can
take the ball from me!
[GION] Hurry up, tree trunk,
let's get him!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Huh? What? Wait!
You're goin' down, string bean!
Ya gotta catch me
first, small fry!
[GION]
Gimme that ball!
Better luck next time!
Nice job, Gion.
Way to use your fist!
I know right?
Run, Iwashi, run!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Yeah, okay.
[MIYUKI] You've got
possession of the ball next!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Uh. All right.
[GION]
You're all mine!
Iwashi! Over here!
[GION]
Ah! Damnit!
Oops. Too slow!
[yells]
Catch!
[IWASHIMIZU]
I'm on it!
[GION yelling]
[laughs]
[laughs, yells]
[GION]
Got ya now!
[MIYUKI]
Pass it, Iwashi!
[GION yells]
[MIYUKI] What's wrong,
Gion? Can't catch me?
[GION]
I'm gonna get you, Iwashimizu!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Come on!
[IWASHIMIZU, GION,
MIYUKI shouting]
Weird. What the hell
are they doing?
[GION, IWASHIMIZU,
MIYUKI panting]
You guys, I'm not sure that
counts as real training.
But it sure was a
heck of a lot of fun.
[chuckles]
What are you
grinnin' about, dude?
Oh.
Just thinkin' about the
first time we talked.
You remember what
you said to me?
You talked me into
playing rugby.
[MIYUKI]
Hm...
[laughs] Oh, man,
you're really huge!
You wanna join the Rugby Team?
You'll love it. Rugby's awesome!
[BOTH]
Please, join. You'll be a star!
Hey, guys. What have
you been up to?
Super-secret training,
obviously, right?
Right!
[GION] I want my rematch
of Old Maid, Noka,
or I'm not letting
you go! Understood?
[NOKA]
No, please. Just let me sleep!
Hey, Matsuo. Where'd
you run off to?
Oh. Nowhere.
We just had a senior
meeting. It's no big deal.
[KIBI]
Well, that makes sense.
When all the older
guys went missing,
we figured something was up.
Guys. I'm really nervous.
What if I'm a starter
against Ryoin tomorrow?
I wouldn't worry about that.
Hey, dude. Not cool!
[MATSUO]
Ebumi!
Yeah? What's up?
Not much. Did ya go for a run?
Uh. Yeah.
Sweet. Nice job!
[EBUMI]
Stop rubbin' my head, bro!
[MATSUO]
Well, guys,
get some rest tonight!
We've got an important
game tomorrow morning!
[JINKO FRESHMAN]
Yes, sir.
Jeez. I feel so on edge.
[yawns] Hey. We
should go to bed.
Yeah. Right! G'night!
Oh, now you're tired?!
Hey! Gion!
Holy crap!
It's the greatest flanker
in the whole wide world!
No. It's just me.
Hey, dude? If it's all the same,
could you maybe
stop saying that?
I appreciate the compliment.
It's just embarrassing.
[GION]
Embarrassing?
If I was as good as you,
I'd tell everyone alive!
Hey there, Kamo. How goes it?
Hey. It goes well.
How you doin', bro? All good?
Uh. What's happening?
So... Your boys
like to be early.
That's refreshing.
The name's Minamoto--the head
coach of Ryoin Academy.
It's a pleasure to finally
meet you in person.
How you doin'?
I'm Komori, Jinko's coach.
Looking forward
to the match today.
I've heard a lot
about you from Kita,
Sagami's Coach. He has nothing
but great things to say.
Yeah, great.
Thanks for playing
us today, Coach.
I know it's short notice.
No please.
As a matter of fact,
the timing of this match
couldn't be better for us.
And I promise you this:
our second string
has come to play.
That's good. The same
is true for us, Coach.
What?! How come you're
not playing today?
'Cause our second
string is playing you.
I'll be watching though,
from the sidelines.
[MIKADO]
Hey, Sekito!
[SEKITO, GION]
Huh?
[SEKITO]
Mikado?
Gion. This's Mikado
Sho our Flanker.
He's starting.
This little shrimp?
I'm a shrimp?
Look at you, half-pint.
Hey! Who are you callin'
half-pint, jerk?
Listen, guys.
Not to split hairs, but if
we're being totally honest,
we're all pretty short.
After all, Mikado,
you told me the reason
you came to Ryoin in the
first place is 'cause
you looked up to me.
Yeah, that's true!
For small guys like me,
seein' you succeed here
was a game changer.
I admire you, man.
You're like a hero to me.
I love you, bro!
He's a nice guy. He just
watches way too much Yaoi.
[MIKADO] I have no idea
what you're talkin' about.
But I'll take it!
Well, I hope you two fellas
have a good game today.
And I'm sure you'll
be great friends.
[BOTH growl]
All right! Let's play! Game on!
We're all counting on you, Gion.
You watch. I'm gonna
bring the pain!
Get focused, guys.
But, Sekizan...
Don't worry about him--
worry about the game.
[SEKIZAN]
Let's make them remember us.
Come on. We got this!
Hey, Ryujin. It's starting.
[ZANBA]
Cool.
[REF 23A]
Ryoin will kick off first!
[whistle blows]
[MIKI panting]
Let's go! Come on, it's
gonna start any minute.
If we don't hurry, then we're
--gonna miss the kick off!
--[IKUTA] So?
What do I care
if we miss kick-off,
I don't wanna watch
this stupid game!
Yeah, well, I do!
[MARODO]
Captain!
[SUMIYOSHI]
Let's kick some ass!
[SEKIZAN]
He's small.
Does this twerp really
think he can take me?
What a hit.
[MIKADO, SEKIZAN grunt]
And that is the Sekito Special!
You're not my type, bro.
[REF 23A]
Knock-on by Jinko! Advantage!
[gasps]
Wait, what does that mean?
I don't know, but that
tackle was insane!
[UMENO]
Come on, Jinko, don't give up!
Fight back with
everything you've got!
Yeah! You can do it, Jinko!
[IKUTA] I didn't even
wanna watch this game.
Ah!
Stop tryin', losers.
Just give up.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[whistle blows]
[REF 23A]
Knock-on. Advantage!
Form a scrum, where
Jinko's penalty lies.
Copy Sekito's style of play
all you want, shrimp boat,
but in the end,
it's not gonna make a damn
bit of difference, guy.
I'm not copying anybody.
My friend taught me that move.
[IWASHIMIZU]
Hey, Gion. Over here.
[GION]
Hm?
[IWASHIMIZU]
Grab a hold of my back.
It might be a little difficult
at first, but it'll work.
If you say so.
[chuckles] This feels
a little weird.
[REF 23A]
Crouch. Bind. Set!
[JINKO TEAM,
RYOIN TEAM grunting]
[KASUGA]
Ball's out!
[OHARANO]
Since number 10 and number 12
have darted to the left,
they'll either pass the ball
to the outside or kick it.
Their number 13 came
around from the back!
Holy crap, man!
Well, this sucks.
[HYOSU]
He got through on the inside!
[RYOIN NUMBER 13 grunts]
Ah!
This is what it means to
protect your turf, kid!
Do you understand now?
That was so bad-ass!
Jeez, that guy's quick!
Come on, you guys! Run!
[pants, yells]
[GION]
He's goin' down!
[GION growls]
[MIKADO]
Adios, amigo!
[NOKA]
He leap-frogged him!
[SUMIYOSHI]
Wow! That was incredible!
Well, that's pretty good.
[SEKITO]
But will he score.
[NOKA] Crap! He's gonna
reach the 22-meter line!
[KIBI grunts]
[yelps]
[yelling]
All right!
Woo! Nice, Kibi!
See? Told you he's
nothing special.
Which side are you
cheering for anyway?
[KASHIMA] Keep pushing,
you guys. Get the ball back!
Hey. Where's the ball?
--I can't see it!
--[whistle blows]
Pile-up!
[REF 23A] Form another
scrum. Jinko's ball.
Nice job.
You saved our butts
big time, man!
[NISHI] What the hell was
that all about, Mikado?
[MIKADO]
Sorry about that, you guys.
I really thought I was
gonna score a try.
[MIKADO chuckles]
[IWASHIMIZU]
Hey, Gion. We got another scrum.
Their flanker's somethin' else.
For a backup, he's good.
[IWASHIMIZU]
But don't worry--you got this.
Ah--
Damnit.
Screw that bastard.
You okay?
[GION]
Ya know something?
I hate it that I
don't stand a chance
against big guys like you.
[GION] But it pisses
me off even more to be
completely underestimated
by a guy my size.
You're right though--
the kid is good.
Hell, he's on the Ryoin
Squad, so he must be.
But I don't care about that.
All I know is I'm not
gonna let him beat me.
In fact, I'm gonna destroy him.
[IWASHIMIZU]
I believe in you, Gion.
You can do it. I know you can.
[HACHIOJI]
Next time:
"The Opponent We Never
Could've Fought."