[snoring]
[IWASHIMIZU]
Hey, Gion.
Wake up. We're here.
Uh?
Yes! Sugadaira time!
[IWASHIMIZU] You realize you
slept the whole way, right?
That was a four-hour drive.
[GION]
Wow!
I've never seen this many
rugby players before!
[IWASHIMIZU] High school teams
from all over the country
come here for their
summer training camp.
Sometimes, even college
students turn up.
Oh, man! How cool!
There's even a rugby shop!
[IWASHIMIZU]
That's not the only one.
If you need some new equipment,
there are rugby shops
all over Sugadaira!
Sweet, dude! This rocks!
And guess what?
[GION]
What?
They even have a few
gift shops here!
[GION] This place has
everything, doesn't it?
[IWASHIMIZU]
See where we are?
This intersection is
the heart of Sugadaira.
[GION]
Nice!
[IWASHIMIZU] The scrimmage
match ups for each day
are written up here
on the big board.
[GION] Cool! Hey, check
it out. It's Sagami!
Yeah, look at that.
If we get lucky with our
schedule, we might even
get to see some
other teams play.
Come on, you two.
Let's get moving!
Umeno. How far is the
hotel from here?
About 15 minutes!
Keep walking, everyone!
[ALL]
Uh...
[UMENO]
We're pretty broke.
So I booked us the cheapest
motel I could find.
[YOSHIDA]
You don't say...
--Good.
--[YOSHIDA gasps]
[KOMORI]
Swanky hotels are for luxury,
not for extreme
mental preparation.
This place is perfect.
[IKUTA] You must be
the Jinko Rugby Team.
So, who're you, the coach?
Yeah, that's right, the coach.
We'll be here for five days.
Works for me.
If you have any problems with
anything, just let me know.
Uh. Okay.
What's wrong?
Uh. Well, you see,
the thing is...
Every year, our students
manage to get into trouble
while we're here.
Last go 'round,
if I remember right,
the seniors caused
quite an ordeal.
[KOMORI]
Hm...
Hah. It won't be a
problem this year.
Right.
Could you please show
these men to their rooms?
We have a scrimmage
at two o'clock today.
We won't be long.
After we drop off our things,
we'll head straight there.
[JINKO TEAM]
Huh?
Straight there?
You do know it's 11 am?
Sure do, Let's go.
[KOMORI] Put your things
inside and hurry up
and get changed, men.
We're jogging to the field.
What?
[JINKO TEAM]
Good work. That warmed
you all up a little bit.
[JINKO TEAM panting]
Uh. Hey, Coach?
Just so you're aware,
we normally give them lunch
at the Inn before we head out.
Wait. Lunch?
I thought we fed 'em lunch
on the bus ride here.
Oh. Well.
No, that was... Breakfast.
[SEKIZAN panting]
We're ready!
What drill do you
wanna do, Coach?
Run passes for an hour.
[JINKO TEAM]
Right!
[NOKA]
All right! Let's do this!
[HYOSU]
Hey, Ume! Balls!
[UMENO]
You got it!
Dude! The air here
is crazy fresh!
Yeah, but it's hot though!
It's not breezy, but it's
a nice change of pace!
I love it!
The weather could be
a whole lot worse,
that's for sure.
Guys! This is fun!
[EBUMI] It's a passing
drill, you little turd!
The grass out here's
really soft!
Oh, yeah!
Want sun screen?
You better put some on
or you'll get burned up.
Oh. No thanks.
[UMENO]
You sure about that?
You'll be red as a
lobster if you don't.
Put some on.
You're gonna watch the
team play, aren't you?
[YOSHIDA]
Uh, yeah.
Good to know! I could
definitely use some help!
[MIKI]
That's weird.
I haven't seen any
Jinko players, have you?
Yeah.
They headed straight to the
field right after checking in.
What?
Without having
their lunch first?
Yep.
If they come back
all covered in mud,
I swear I'll kick
'em to the curb!
But I brought the team dessert
as a way of saying
welcome. What to do?
[KOMORI]
Gentlemen, bring it in!
[JINKO TEAM moaning]
[SUMIYOSHI]
My legs are jello!
[ISE]
I'm dying!
All right, guys,
let's listen up.
Our opponent is the
Tenjiku Tech School of Osaka.
The team itself is pretty
new to competitive rugby.
But they produce results.
Just last year, they made it
to the Osaka quarters.
And that's no small feat.
If we're not on top
of our game today,
they could cause
us some problems.
It's ten till one right now.
They've probably finished eating
and are comin' to the field
to start their
warm up as we speak.
While they lounged around
in their hotel for an hour,
you were here bustin' your
humps on passing drills
and runnin' till you
were covered in sweat!
Their team is strong.
But, at the very least,
in the last hour,
the gap between us and them
has closed a little.
Trust yourselves out there.
And remember what I told you:
the outcome of a game...
[OSAKA]
We're playing Kanagawa?
What're they like?
[KOMORI] It's decided before
the whistle ever blows.
Huh.
There're people here.
That's weird.
Are they in the middle of a
practice session or something?
[OSAKA] Or maybe they
just finished playing?
We can win!
[JINKO TEAM gasps]
Ya think so?
[SEKIZAN] I do. We can win.
We can do this thing!
Hell yeah!
How 'bout we do some more
runnin' passes, you guys?
Come on! We'll be the
strongest team ever!
Hey, Gion? You can barely stand.
Maybe you need to relax a bit.
[MIKI] Uh, 'scuse me?
I'm from the Ikuta Inn.
Sorry to bother you,
but I heard you ran off
to practice without
eating lunch.
So I brought you some dessert.
Would you like some?
[JINKO TEAM moaning]
We sure would. Thanks a lot.
[JINKO TEAM]
All right!
Nice to meet you, Miki.
How old are you?
Oh, I'm 16.
I started working for my
uncle at the Inn this year.
Hey, guys!
Once we're done
eating our snacks,
let's get back to work!
What is up with these weirdoes?
[GOSHOZOME]
Dude!
Are we close? 'Cause
I'm tired of walking.
[KURAYAMA]
Relax, the field's right there.
[ADACHIHARA]
Who does Jinko play again?
I'm not sure.
Tenjiku Tech of Osaka.
They made it to the
quarters just last year.
Good. Our schedule's
been easy so far.
Plus, we get to see
Jinko's first match!
What's up, guys? Im Sano,
Tenjiku's captian.
And I'm Suna! The
team's vice captain.
What's up, dudes?
Oh, man. Look at their captain.
He's freakin' huge!
I'm so scared right now.
Take it down a notch!
I'm Sekizan, Jinko's captain.
And I'm Hachioji,
Jinko's vice captain.
You ready to play?
[gasps]
For sure.
We're all looking
forward to the match.
[giggles]
Uh?
You guys see his hair?
It's seriously whack.
And did you get a
look at their coach?
Somebody needs to get
Grandpa a wheel chair
and some depends!
[TENJIKU TEAM cackles]
[laughs] Those Tenjiku
dorks are super lame,
don't ya think?
Like you're one to talk.
Hori.
Yeah?
Does Tenjiku Tech have
any good players?
Don't know for sure.
Honestly, I'm only familiar
with the noteworthy
players in Kanagawa.
You're such a nerd.
I haven't done enough
research on Osaka
to know who's who yet.
But there's one guy
I have heard a bit about.
He's pretty well known.
And he's good, too.
He made All-Osaka.
And he did it when he
was in Middle School.
Ah.
You hair is totally bonkers
and I think it rocks!
Can I touch it, bro?
Pretty please?
I'm totally freaking
out right now.
I wanna touch your hair so bad!
[HOSOTANI] Hey, Suna.
You're being rude, buddy.
Stop it.
I'm not being rude,
I think it's really awesome!
Wow. It is kind of
awesome, isn't it?
Hey, Hoso!
Not to be a jerk,
but your buckteeth
are buckin' harder
than normal today!
[chuckles]
Ya see, man? Everyone
loves a good teeth joke!
Ignore him. He thinks
he's hilarious.
We're looking forward
to playing you today!
Suna. Stop joking around.
The backs need
to have a meeting.
So hurry it up.
And Hosotani, the forwards
are huddled up over there,
so get a move-on.
Sorry, Renpei. It won't
happen again, man.
Huh.
I wanted to play a real team,
not some squad full of losers.
Who the hell is Jinko?
Hey! Take it easy!
It was nice to meet you, fellas!
[HORIKAWA]
Sakura Renpei: Senior.
During his third year
of middle school,
he was the Osaka Team's
star fullback.
He's got all the
intangibles a player needs.
Well, I'll give you this much:
you've done your homework.
It sounds like
Jinko's gonna have
their work cut out
for 'em today.
Only one thing can
save them: luck.
The name's Futami.
I'm the head coach
of the Tenjiku Rugby Team.
Well, Coach, may
the best team win.
Thank you. On behalf
of the Jinko Rugby Team,
good luck.
[KOMORI] All right. Here's the
starting lineup for today.
Wait! He's really playing you?
Uh...
Well, that's new.
[HYOSU]
Kifune's starting?
[SHINSHI]
Well, that's different.
[KOMORI] Listen, you guys
know what to do.
Give it all you got.
One hundred percent!
You do that, you'll win. Now go!
[JINKO TEAM]
Yes, sir!
And away we go. Come on, sir.
Let me hear you make some noise!
Right.
Guys! Come on! Fight!
Go! Jinko!
[HIROTA yells]
Well, looks like these losers
have a little bit of
pep in their step.
Let's slow 'em down.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, wow!
Now that's a damn kick!
Yeah, you're tellin' me.
That's 40 meters at least.
Holy crap!
Get back, guys!
Kifune! Kick it as
hard as you can!
Yes, sir!
What? Lame.
I know girls who can kick a ball
farther than he just did!
That kid's not normally
one of their starters.
Get it together, Jinko.
Not another kick!
Backs! Move! Get that ball!
Aw, man, Looks like somebody
doesn't know how to
kick a ball properly!
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Tenjiku's ball. Line out!
[KIFUNE] Should I have kicked
that ball out of bounds?
Oh, man.
Huh.
Renpei, you're playin' so well--
the balls are soarin' off your
cleat today! Jinko doesn't...
Why don't ya stop
running your mouth,
and get your head
in the game, Suna?
Huh?
Tenjiku's forwards
are pretty big, huh?
Their number 4 is
189 centimeters tall.
[GOSHOZOME] How the heck
do you know that, man?
The official Tenjiku
Tech Rugby website.
Oshima, their number 14,
is just as big, even though
he plays out on the wing.
So they focus their
attack on aerial battles
because they're so good
at punting the ball.
That's one hell
of a kick, Toru!
Keep the pressure on, you guys!
Huh?
[whimpers]
Here!
Well.
At least their number 10
knows how to kick a ball.
[SANO]
Renpei!
Ha, ha. That guy's showboating.
He's got no respect for them!
Jinko's full back
is good. Real good.
Wha--?
[KOMORI]
Kibi.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Tell me this.
You've played full-back a lot.
How is Kifune's movement?
Oh. Well. Uh...
[KIBI] His positioning
isn't half bad.
He seems to know where
the ball's gonna drop.
He doesn't waste much
energy. He's calm.
But his kicks don't
have much distance.
Come on.
I can out kick that guy
with my eyes closed.
Distance isn't
everything, you know.
The idea is to get
a good bounce.
Take Sakura Renpei.
His kicks might be flashy,
but the kid's caught
every single one.
Renpei's not the best
full back on the field today,
not by a long shot.
The thing is,
everything about him
is so plain, Coach,
and I'm talkin' about
on and off the field.
You're right.
I'll admit, it took me
a long time to notice
Kifune's strengths as a player.
In rugby, the fullbacks
are the last line of defense
we have out there.
He may not be flashy,
he may be a little plain,
but as a defender,
Kifune is rock solid.
You could learn a thing or two
from the way the kid
plays the game.
[KIBI]
Damnit, you're right.
And I really hate
to admit that, Coach!
But after this game,
I'm gonna go pick his brain!
[OSHIMA yells]
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Knock-on by Tenjiku!
Yo! We're changin' up
the game plan.
Someone go tell Renpei.
[HIROTA grunting]
[KAMO grunts]
[gasps]
They got the ball back!
What? Damnit!
Tenjiku's hooker is pretty good.
Heads up!
Ha, ha! Jinko sure goes
for the low blows!
[OSAKA]
Although...
If they don't hit ya,
then who cares?
[SAKURA]
Suna!
Huh?
Gimme the ball!
Here ya go!
Renpei! You know
what to do, right?
Yeah. Don't worry,
I got it handled!
[KASUGA yells]
[KASUGA gasps]
He's good!
They changed their game-plan
'cause of Jinko's fullback.
They're giving up on
the long-range kicks.
Renpei! Pass me the ball, man!
Now!
[gasps]
Damn!
[KIFUNE grunts]
Whoa.
[whistle blows]
[KIFUNE whimpers]
[gasps]
[sighs]
Oh, man, dude.
Can't believe he made
the ball stop
right on the freakin' goalline
like that. He must be
some kinda rugby wizard!
Dude, you should have
listened to me.
I told you not to kick it, man.
Who cares? It worked, right?
[OSAKA]
Hey, Renpei! Awesome kick, bro!
[HORIKAWA]
A line-out five meters
from Jinko's own goal line.
[GOSHOZOME]
Damn, dude!
Those guys are in
some hot water now!
Hey. Can you explain
something to me?
Why did he kick the ball
out of bounds like that?
Why not move it up the field?
Trying to make an offensive
play with the ball
that close to the goal line
is basically suicide!
It's a heck of a lot safer
to hand them possession
and force a "line-out,"
that way, the entire team
can get back and defend.
Oh, all right.
Guys.
Ready?
I wont let you have the ball!
[SANO]
Here it comes!
[KURAYAMA]
A wild throw? What the hell?
[WADA] Did Iwashimizu's pressure
get to him or something?
No, look. It's a play.
It's a long throw-in!
That's not good!
[whistle blows]
[REF 17A]
Try!
Did you see that?
Normally, in that
kind of situation,
you'd go for a try with
a maul from the line-out.
But they went for a long throw.
And outsmarted Jinko's D.
A smart move.
Renpei! Nice run!
[SAKURA]
You know, you guys probably
wouldn't score at all
if it weren't for me.
[SANO]
What?
[SAKURA] You heard what I said.
Now get back in position.
I'm ready to kick off!
[OSAKA laughing]
Whatever you say, Renpei!
[whistle blows]
[
Don't give up, you guys!
Come on!
They may be down right now,
but Jinko's stayin' calm.
The game's not over yet.
[KOMORI]
Hm.
Ah!
[SHINSHI grunts]
[yells]
[HYOSU]
Shinshi!
Nice hit.
It was a great
tackle, but still--
They're gonna have to keep
the pressure on those guys.
Tenjiku's going for the ruck.
That's Oshima, their prop.
He's a sturdy player.
And strong, too.
[HIROTA yells]
[KAMO yelps]
[yells]
All right! We just
got the ball back!
[BOTH]
Nice job, you guys!
Ha!
[KOMORI]
All right, gentlemen, begin.
Do you see, gentlemen?
That's it. That's the
stance, my friends.
Huh?
[KOMORI]
It's called ruck posture.
Generally speaking, the
lower player wins in a ruck.
If you start from that
position, you'll prevail.
[KOMORI]
Push your opponent up diagonally
and when he gives,
flip him over.
[SHINSHI]
All right!
The sumo drill
is totally helping!
Good.
[KOMORI]
Next time: "Study."