[FIGHTER'S FATHER groans]
Well done. You've
become so strong.
[FIGHTER gasps]
Father! It's you?
--[PALADIN moaning]
--[FIGHTER giggling]
[DRAGON roars]
[PALADIN grunts]
There's no choice.
Go... Run away!
I will finish this!
No!
What the heck are you doing?
Are you betraying us?
[DARKELF]
Consider it fate.
Time for you to die!
[GOD] You've done well
to come this far.
I am God.
Come. Let us release
the seal upon this world.
[MAGE grunts]
[FIGHTER gasps]
[MAGE cries]
Sorry to say this, but
you're the one who's wrong!
[MONSTER A roars]
[PALADIN panting]
Everyone...
I will end this battle alone!
Please! Remember me!
[door opens]
[gasps, yelps]
[GOD]
This is the source of all chaos.
All forms of evil are
born in this chasm.
Whoa. You can't be serious.
That sounds intense!
[MONSTER B roars]
[FIGHTER]
Guys... Is this the end?
--[VALKYRIE] Not today.
--[FIGHTER gasps]
Brave heroes never quit!
[FIGHTER gasps]
[FIGHTER]
Whoa! Why are you two here?
Looks like we're
saving your hides!
Why don't you guys
take a little breather
and leave this one to
the higher levels like us!
[VALKYRIE, HUNTER scream]
[MAGE]
Valkyrie!
Hunter!
[DARKELF chuckles]
[FIGHTER gasps, sighs]
[FIGHTER]
This... This is...
The Legendary Holy Sword!
[MONSTER C growls]
[PALADIN yelps]
I'll finish this!
Go! Ahh!
[DARKELF chuckles]
[PALADIN gasps]
[DEMON KING]
I am the Demon King.
The entire world will
fall to its knees
and obey my every command!
Yeah, right!
No way we're letting you get
away with that, you Demon Jerk!
This world isn't a thing
for you to control.
It belongs to all the people!
And we'll do whatever
it takes to keep it safe!
Ready, Team?
Hell yeah!
We were born ready!
[ALL yell]
[VOICE A] This is only
the beginning for them.
[VOICE B]
Compared to us,
these silly girls are
nothing but weaklings.
[VOICE C] In the end, the
world will be ours forever.
[VOICES laugh]
[ALL panting, grunting]
Guys... Is this really the end?
--[gasps]
--[metal clink]
[ALL gasp]
[FIGHTER]
What? You're--!