[KING] We have long awaited
your arrival, Brave Warriors.
Raise your faces.
We have heard much
of your great feats.
Our lands would be ruined
if not for your heroism.
Valiant Fighter,
to have a warrior like you
in Our halls is a treasure.
Sire, you honor me.
[KING] Blessed are We to
have you with us, Paladin.
Verily, your feats
of strength in battle
are matched only by
your exquisite beauty.
You humble me with your kind and
generous praise, Your Majesty.
[KING] For one as young as you
to have such mastery over magic,
Mage, you truly are a prodigy.
Thank you, Sire.
Your words are far too kind.
[KING]
And you, Darkelf.
The tales of your intellect
and prowess in combat
reach far and wide.
[laughs]
Even to this decaying,
ramshackle little
town you call home?
[PALADIN]
You're so rude!
[KING] Your skill and courage
go unrivaled everywhere.
If only your aid
had arrived sooner,
we wouldn't find
ourselves plagued
by such a tragic situation.
[FIGHTER]
My Lord?
[KING]
Our very existence
now verges on the
brink of destruction.
No hope remains in this kingdom.
[FIGHTER]
Fear not, Sire, we're here now!
[PALADIN] We fight to restore
peace throughout the world,
no matter what the
personal cost may be!
[MAGE] Whatever ails
you and your people,
this party will not rest
until we see justice done!
[DARKELF] This darkness
will be no more, My Liege!
[KING] We were wise to
place such faith in you.
[KING]
Our fate is in your hands now!
Brave Ones! Defend us!
[ALL]
Right!
Uh, Sire?
Yes? What's the problem?
We assumed we were
done speaking.
[FIGHTER]
Sorry about that.
But see, the thing is,
we can't just go out and fight.
We need equipment and
supplies and stuff like that.
Oh! Yes. Our apologies.
In that case, take some gold
to aid you in your quest!
--[FIGHTER] Uhh...
--[MAGE] One, two, three,
--four... Uh... Yikes!
--[DARKELF] Do my eyes
deceive me or am I
looking at a measly stack
of ten gold coins on that plate?
Go! Fight hard, Brave Ones!
Highness? The thing is...
We can't.
We won't!
Apparently you think
saving your people
is worth the price of a potion.
So as far as we're concerned,
you can take your ten
gold coins and shove it!
Hey! Don't be rude.
I'm sure he means to give us
more gold than this paltry sum.
Unfortunately, this
is all I can give you.
Fight hard, Brave Ones!
[gasps]
My Lord!
Just to sleep at an
inn for one night
costs twenty pieces
of gold, per person!
With all due respect,
Your Majesty,
we'd be foolish to
put our lives at risk
for such a tiny amount of money!
Go fight hard, Brave Ones!
Wait! Just a second!
Couldn't you at least lend us
the legendary weapons that
you have in the castle?
Uh... Yes, those.
Um, well you see...
We have nothing
of the sort here!
Oh, come on!
What? Please.
You just said ya did!
Sorry, Brave Heroes,
but you are mistaken.
Now go and fight!
I've got an idea.
Why not sell the armor
off these guards?
Clearly they're not
getting the job done
on the whole defending
the kingdom front.
Then use that gold to
buy us some weapons.
[GUARD]
Hey! What did we ever do to you?
Your Majesty, you can't
possibly be saying that
our bodies are worth ten
meager pieces of gold, can you?
Uh, no... I don't
think anyone said that.
You guys, I know ten
pieces of gold isn't much,
but if we don't stand up
and fight for their kingdom,
then who will?
Give us your gold right now,
or your kingdom is doomed!
[DARKELF]
My Lord.
The decision is yours!
Why did it come to this?
[FIGHTER grunting]
Like you don't know!
[PALADIN]
Uh-oh!
This rope is in
an awkward place!
[MAGE]
Uh-huh! What were we thinking?
Please don't look at me!