[FIGHTER sighs]
We're totally broke!
[MAGE sighs]
So what now?
At this point, we can't even
afford to stay at the inn!
Then I have no other choice.
I must resort to
the only option.
You're not gonna start
selling your body
for money again, are you?
[gasps] Don't be absurd.
Just because I fantasize
about it every day,
doesn't mean I'm actually
going to go through with it.
I am a woman of
principle, after all.
Well, then what exactly
are you planning to do?
We're the heroes here, right?
So that means the
law is on our side!
Forgive our intrusion.
We are brave heroes in need!
As such, we invoke our right
to confiscate items
required to be successful
on our dangerous quest!
[PALADIN]
As you may know,
those ordered by the kingdom
to defend these lands
are known as heroes.
So, it is our privilege
to enter villager's
homes uninvited,
rummage through
their treasure chests
and take whatever we may
need to fulfill our mission.
[DARKELF]
Please continue eating your meal
as if nothing weird
is happening.
[MAGE]
So sorry to bother you.
Is this okay?
Antidotes. And herbs, too.
Plus, twenty gold coins.
Hm. I wonder if
we'll need these?
--[shatters]
--Hey!
Look at all this gold!
I'll use it wisely! I promise!
[MAGE]
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
[gasps, squeals]
Hey, you guys. Look!
I've always wanted
my own Mage's staff!
[DARKELF]
All right, let's move out!
[PALADIN giggles]
[FIGHTER groans]
[door creaks, slams]
Are you guys sure about this?
Is it really okay?
Of course! It's our right!
We're putting our
lives on the line
and embarking on an
extremely dangerous mission
to rid the world of evil!
Sorry if you feel guilty, but
small sacrifices must be made!
Right! We should go
pillage that house next!
[knocking]
We're heroes and
we're here to rob you!
[shattering]
Thanks for letting
me wield your steel!
[WOMAN screams]
[MAGE gasps]
Oh... I'm so sorry.
[rustling]
[PALADIN gasps]
You'll never guess
where I found the
Philosophers' stone!
Yeah! When I save
up enough money,
I'm gonna buy papa
the most amazing gift!
[FIGHTER gasps]
Sorry! But I need this gold
so I can protect the world!
[FIGHTER sighs]
You know, it's a good thing
heroes get special privileges.
Now we don't have to worry about
money to complete our quests!
I never imagined I'd get to
stay in a fancy hotel like this!
It's so awesome!
It looks like being a hero is
finally starting to pay off.
The law is on our side, ladies.
We fight for peace
and for justice.
Remember that all
of the common people
are counting on us
to save the world!
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[CHILD, FATHER growl]
[TOWNSPEOPLE grumbling]
[BOTH scream]
--[PALADIN screams]
--[DARKELF whimpers]
This is not good!
[FIGHTER cries]
I knew they were gonna be mad!
[MAGE, DARKELF sob]
I really am sorry!
[PALADIN grunts]
Those despicable ingrates!
We've done nothing wrong
but fulfill our sworn duty!
I will never forgive them!
Dumb jerks. They
stole our clothes.
Why would they do
that? I'm so cold.
[MAGE sobs]
I'm the worst.
Please forgive me!