[FIGHTER]
"World's greatest swordsman.
Inexperienced in battle,
but... kinda knows
the next-door neighbor of
the cousin of the friend
who defeated the Demon Lord
seventy years ago."
[DARKELF] So much for recruiting
another member of the party.
For someone who's all talk, this
guy sure is full of himself.
[FIGHTER]
Oh, and you're not?
[PALADIN] Have you forgotten
what you were like
when you first started with us?
[DARKELF]
So, you people have come here
because you want my help?
You've got a strong eye
for talent, that's for sure.
Whoa... I've never met
a Dark Elf before!
Wow! She looks really strong.
No offense, but what
can you actually do?
Not only can elves wield
swords and use magic,
but we live longer than any
human could ever dream of.
Not to mention, we're
very knowledgeable
in almost every aspect
of life as we know it.
Of course, I don't mean to brag.
Oh please, like hell you don't!
[chuckles] I know she's a bit
on the cocky side, but if we can
get her to join our party,
she'll be a powerful ally
to us on our dangerous quest!
Are you positive we're going
the right way this time?
Trust me, there's
no need to worry.
The great spirits of
the wind always guide me
and lead me towards the light.
That's what you keep
saying over and over again,
but we've been
lost for two days!
Ye of little faith.
Relax and leave
everything to me.
[MAGE cries]
Let me go!
[PALADIN yelps]
No! Don't touch me!
Please stop it!
[MAGE, PALADIN crying]
[FIGHTER] This one's
way too strong for us!
We'll see about that!
Allow me!
[gasps] What is that?
[gasps] I don't know,
but I'm sensing some powerful
magic emanating from her!
[DARKELF]
Ultimate... Thunderburst!
[sizzle]
[MAGE, PALADIN crying]
Seems he's much
tougher than I thought.
[FIGHTER]
Huh?
Oh, come on!
That's it?
Is this some kinda joke?!
Don't lose hope yet.
If we do that 100 more times,
I assure you, we'll defeat him.
I wonder what these
ruins are all about?
I'm sensing a strange
magical field in the area.
[FIGHTER]
Come on!
Let's hit it and
see what happens!
I wouldn't if I were you.
It's a magical gate
connecting to the demon world.
Are you sure about that?
Of course.
About thirty years ago,
there was this book or
scroll or something like that.
I vaguely remember it
talking about this gate.
[MAGE] Sorry, but that's
not very convincing.
Let's see.
If I recall, you just
push this stone...
[GROUP screams]
[PALADIN]
What have you done?!
Where are we? Tell me!
[BOSS] You've done
well to make it this far.
I am the Demon Lord
who dominates this world!
I am Deathgeld!
[GROUP]
Huh?!
[FIGHTER]
Wait a second!
Isn't this the final boss?!
[PALADIN]
This is ridiculous!
We're not prepared for
this sort of encounter!
[MAGE]
M-M-Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy!
Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy!
Relax, girls.
This was my plan all along!
[GROUP]
You're a liar!
[DARKELF] Now that my brave
companions and I have found you,
your terrible reign
of evil and horror
will come to a violent end.
We will stain our blades
with your sulfurous blood!
Please don't make
him mad, you psycho!
[BOSS]
Well, in that case, bring it on!
En guard!
[GROUP cries]