[WIZARD groans, grunts]
[FIGHTER]
Great.
All done over here.
Let's move!
[footsteps]
[WIZARD groaning]
[MAGE gasps]
[groans]
You all right?
[MAGE]
Die!
[FIGHTER yelps]
What was that for?
What in the world do
you think you're doing?
[MAGE]
Kill them all! Kill them all!
[DARKELF]
It's like she's turned into
a completely different person!
Yes! That's exactly
what's it's like.
I'm being controlled by magic,
can't you guys see that?
We're a team, do you really
think I'd ever try to hurt you?
Hey! What's the matter,
can't you hear me?
[growls]
You deserve to die!
All three of you!
You betrayed me!
Betrayed? What's
she talking about?
[ALL gasp]
Oh no!
[FIGHTER]
Is this because that one time
I gave you less food
than everyone else?
[DARKELF] Or is this about
the time I secretly tried on
your panties?
[gasps]
I didn't mean for them to rip!
[PALADIN]
Don't tell me it's because
I can't stop staring at
your adorable little body,
and wanting to lick
and rub you all over?
[panting]
You tried on her panties?!
What's wrong with you?
You're despicable!
Didn't you ever think it
might be wrong to do that?
What about you?!
It's true, you might
be terrible people.
But I swear, I'm not mad at you!
[MAGE]
Time to die!
[ALL gasp, yelp]
I mean, it's true that
we might have crossed the
line a couple of times...
...but still!
You were our friend once.
But anyone who stands in
our way must be defeated!
[DARKELF]
If this is how it has to end,
then so be it!
I'm sorry!
But we have a duty to
fulfill, no matter what!
It's sad, but true!
[whimpers]
Goodbye, Friend.
We'll never forget you!
[MAGE gasps]
Wait a second!
Guys, can't you see I'm
being controlled by magic?
Please! Don't
apologize like that!
Why aren't you listening to me?
[FIGHTER sniffles]
[yells]
No! Don't kill me.
--You can't. Please!
--[footsteps, slash]
We will continue our journey
in your tragic absence.
Watch over us.
[MAGE]
Uh, you guys?
I know I'm totally
dead and everything,
but if you just go and
pay the church some money,
they can bring me back to life!
Um...
I know you're already
aware of that,
but just in case you forgot.
Seriously though,
enough with the joke,
--it's not funny anymore!
--[CHERUBS laughing]
Hey! Please, guys!
You can't give up on me yet!
[cries]
[gasps, yelps]
Wait a minute!
Don't take me away!
I don't wanna die!