[NARRATOR] This is the
story of a group of young,
beautiful heroes who rise up and
fight to restore light and peace
to a broken world torn apart
by the forces of evil.
--[FIGHTER groans]
--Is it my turn already?
[roars]
[MAGE whimpers]
[screams]
So hot!
[DARKELF grunts, shudders]
S-S-So cold!
[PALADIN yelps]
Ah! It's melting right through!
[whimpers]
--[thud]
--[FIGHTER] Hey, guy!
This armor you sold
us is a piece of junk.
We're heroes, not a bunch
of bimbos on a beach!
I've got some of the
latest armor in stock
if you'd like to try it.
I think it'd be a perfect fit.
Yeah, it looks good on you.
Hey! These are the same
suits! You can't fool us!
--It's so cute!
--Huh?
This is, without a doubt,
the most beautiful
armor I've ever seen!
She's right.
It's fitting, but
not too revealing,
offering equal parts
comfort and protection.
It's the greatest!
When you're as good as I am,
you can tell the difference.
Our enemies will tremble in fear
when they see the four of
us approaching in these!
They're the same. Like, exactly.
[SMITH]
You gonna buy it or not?
[GROUP]
Yes!
I'm sorry, but I
think I'm gonna pass.
[FIGHTER]
Ah!
[groans]
[PALADIN gasps]
Hey, I'm not melting.
It looks like this new armor
was a good purchase after all!
No way!
--[DRAGON growls]
--[MAGE gasps]
[whimpers]
He's burning me up,
but I'm not even hot!
I'm sure glad I decided
to buy this new suit!
[DARKELF gasps]
I don't feel a thing!
This new armor is even
better than I thought!
Oh, c'mon! You're kiddin' me!
--[thud]
--[FIGHTER] Excuse me, sir?
Any chance I can purchase
some of that bikini armor?
Sure thing.
Would you like me to put
a set together for you?
[MAN A] Is that the party
everyone's been talking about?
[MAN B]
They are so awesome!
[WOMAN]
What armor class are they in?
[CHILD] Mama! Can I have
a suit like that, too?
[DARKELF chuckles]
Guess we have fans.
I could get used to this.
No one's ever paid
attention to us before.
This is so awesome!
Finally, an outfit
that's worthy of
our bravery, nobility, and
our truly selfless deeds!
This new bikini armor is
the best! Woo! [laughs]
I'm happy to see you're
finally admitting it.
It's good armor.
But I just finished a set
that's even better.
[FIGHTER moans]
[PALADIN gasps, moans]
[MAGE gasps]
[DARKELF moans]
Isn't this just
a bathing suit?
So filthy! So disgusting!
So obscene!
I... feel... cheap!
It's totally embarrassing.
How could I ever be seen
like this in public?
You, sir, are a disgrace!
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
How dare you ask us
to stoop so low!
But they look exactly like the
ones you were wearing earlier.
[ALL]
You're wrong!
These are completely different!