[ALL panting]
[FIGHTER]
Finally, another treasure chest!
It's been such a tough dungeon!
We're almost completely
out of health and mana!
We need a regen item.
If we don't find a way
to revive our strength,
then we're never gonna
make it to the boss!
I disagree.
The enemies down here
are too strong for us.
What we really need now
is a more powerful weapon!
Well... Let's open it!
No, wait. What if
it's another trap?
[GROUP gasps]
Yeah. Good point.
The treasure chests in this
place have been a handful.
[squeals]
A treasure chest already?
Heck yeah! We're on a roll!
[FIGHTER coughing]
Guys... It's a trap.
[ALL scream]
You guys! Help!
This chest is trapped, too!
--[PALADIN screams]
--[GROUP gasps]
[screaming continues]
Are you all right?
No! Please don't let go of me!
It's wedging in!
So deep!
[screams]
I'm gonna drop her.
[DARKELF]
With my magic,
I can see what's
behind any wall
or inside any treasure
chest, without opening it.
[FIGHTER] Then why didn't
you do that from the start?
[DARKELF]
I see it!
There's something inside!
[FIGHTER]
Okay! Here goes!
So gross! Why'd it
have to be eels?!
I told you there was something
inside of that chest.
Unless you can tell us what it
is, it doesn't really help much!
Oh my! Yes!
I'll admit, this feels
surprisingly delightful.
That's it, go faster.
Please don't stop!
[moans]
[squeals]
[FIGHTER]
It's true.
Most of the chests so
far have been traps.
But that doesn't
mean this one is too,
we have to take the risk!
I used my magic
to look inside it.
I'm absolutely certain.
There is something
in that chest.
We've already established
that doesn't help.
[MAGE] Yeah, but what if it's
a regen item that we need?
We have to open it.
Or we'll never
know what's inside.
She's right.
Let's decide who does the honor
with rock-paper-scissors.
[ALL]
First comes rock!
You cheated!
So did you!
Oh, please, like
you're one to talk!
[FIGHTER]
Whatever.
We're all in this
together, right?
Let's all open it!
[PALADIN]
Yeah, good call.
[MAGE gasps]
That's fine by me!
[DARKELF]
If it's a trap...
We're about to find out.
[FIGHTER]
All right.
Here we go.
One... Two... Three!
[ALL gasp]
[FAIRY chuckles]
Greetings, Warriors.
I'm the Great Fairy
of this realm.
What treasure do you seek here?
Perhaps you seek
the Token of Courage?
Or perhaps not?
Perhaps you want
the Crest of Justice?
We don't want either those.
What an honest person you are!
As a reward, I shall give you
both to aid you on your quest.
Look, I told you,
we don't want 'em!
Come on, don't you
have any weapons
or at least some healing potion?
Yeah, we're in a real
bad spot here, Lady!
You know, for a fairy,
you're pretty useless!
[ALL grumbling]
[ALL gasp]
[FIGHTER]
Wait! Don't run away!
[DARKELF] You're a fairy,
so give us something useful!
[PALADIN]
Please! We're begging you!
Help us out!