I'm sorry, Brave Warriors,
but you cannot pass through
the dungeon to Geldabar,
unless you possess the key.
So if you want it,
I'm afraid you'll have
to do exactly as I say.
This man's a vile sack of flesh.
Let's kill him.
We can't.
On a journey, a hero
will face many trials.
Tell me is this not one of them?
Vile or not,
we have a job to do.
[FIGHTER yelling]
[MAGE]
Guys, is this really okay?
We're just standing
here watching,
while the fighter
does all the work.
She's the one who agreed
to this in the first place.
It's her problem.
I didn't become a
hero just to move
other people's junk for
them, especially that creep!
[DOG barks]
[FIGHTER]
Here, doggy!
Chasing after a runaway dog?
I guess that's a job for a hero!
[DOG barks]
What the--?
Stop it. That tickles.
Come on now.
Seriously, I've had enough!
Whoa! All right,
that's too much!
No! Stop! Please!
You stop that!
No, really, you have to stop!
Right now!
The mayor invented a potion,
and he wants me to
find out what it does.
I guess this is a job
for a hero right?
So... Are you gonna drink it?
For real?
Something tells me
that's a bad idea.
Yeah, I'm with her,
a hero should never
have to stoop so low.
So what!
In the face of adversity,
a real hero doesn't quit.
A real hero fights
till the bitter end!
So!
[GROUP gasps]
[FIGHTER whimpers]
[moans]
My body...
It feels all hot and bothered!
It's like I'm burning
up on the inside!
[PALADIN]
What are you doing?
Let go of me right now!
Actually, that feels kinda nice!
On second thought,
don't let go of me right now!
Keep going!
Yes! That's so amazing!
People are starting to stare.
Why don't you two get a room?
Yeah...
Or maybe you'd just
not do it at all!
[FIGHTER screams]
[moans] This is an important
mission from the Mayor.
I have got to defeat
this monster!
If I do, the key will be mine.
Which means failure
is not an option!
I have to keep fighting!
[yelps]
[screams]
Stop! I can't take it anymore!
[yelps]
Whoa! That sure
was a close call!
Thanks. You saved me.
It's like you said,
if we don't find a
way to move forward,
then all could be lost...
You're unbelievable!
Leaving us out in
the cold like that,
while you get to have all
of the fun by yourself!
No! You're wrong.
This is bad.
It doesn't feel good
at all, I promise!
--[squelches]
--[moans]
Enough of that!
It's time to finish this!
[PALADIN, MAGE]
Alright!
Please! Don't! Stop!
Well done!
You did everything I asked
of you, Brave Warriors!
You truly are the most
valiant heroes of our time!
Great.
Now hold up your
end of the bargain.
Give our party the key
we need to gain passage
through the dungeons to
Geldabar, like you promised!
[MAYOR]
Yes. But don't you see?
The key you seek is
already inside your hearts.
[ALL]
Huh?
By fulfilling my
ridiculous requests,
you and your party
learned the importance
of putting the needs and desires
of other people above your own!
Because you've
unlocked this truth,
you now have everything you
need to become a real hero.
I believed in you from
the very beginning
and had all the faith in the
world you wouldn't let me down!
So...
I'm gonna hurt him now.
Yeah, sounds good.
Go on.
Yeah. Just try not to kill him.
[MAYOR screams]