[MAGE screams]
I got you!
[screams]
No, don't do it!
[DARKELF grunting]
[DARKELF gasps]
Now's your chance.
Run! Hurry!
[grunts]
[screams] Stay back, please!
Don't worry about me!
Just save yourselves!
Make a run for it now,
while you still have a chance!
[screams]
--[MONSTER growls]
--[FIGHTER panting]
[FIGHTER]
He's too powerful for us.
There's no way we'll be
able to defeat this monster!
[MAGE gasps] What in the
world are we gonna do now?
You guys stay back and
let me handle this one!
[FIGHTER]
What can you possibly do?
[DARKELF]
You can't mean!
[PALADIN chuckles]
It's been a true
honor everyone.
I'll see you in the next life.
[MAGE, DARKELF gasp]
You crazy fool.
I can't believe she did that.
[cries] No! Come back to us!
Seriously, what the
heck is up with you
and this whole
self-sacrifice thing?
[PALADIN]
Well, I am a Paladin.
We're sacred warriors
sent by the gods.
If it means protecting
innocents or saving the world,
then I'm happy to
lay down my life.
This is my sole
purpose on earth!
Yeah, well, one of these days,
you're gonna die for good.
[MAYOR chuckling]
I'm the Mayor around here.
But if it's all the same,
I'd prefer if you
just called me Lord.
If you want to
continue your journey,
then one of you has
to get married to me.
What?! No way!
[growls] Filthy perverted Mayor!
Can I kill him, please?
He's gross.
[PALADIN]
No, wait.
This is an opportunity for me
to make a sacrifice
for the greater good.
If it means helping the party,
then if I must,
I will marry you!
[GROUP gasps]
[PALADIN sighs]
Tonight I will boldly go
where no woman
will ever go again.
That vile, disgusting man
will have his way with me,
and my innocence
will be lost forever.
[pants]
But for the world
and all of its people,
and for the righteous cause
of peace and goodness,
I must deflower myself.
There is no other way.
This is the greatest
sacrifice I can make!
[MAYOR laughing]
Ah, yes...
Now, take off
your clothes, girl.
Show daddy what's
underneath that gown!
[gasps] Yes...
[MAYOR laughs] I'll take
really good care of you.
Now come here.
[PALADIN whimpers]
[whimpering]
[gasps]
--Stop right there, Freak!
--[MAYOR screams]
Hey! What's going on?
If you think you can just use
our friend as your plaything,
you've got another thing coming!
Yeah! What she said!
--[MAYOR screams]
--[WOLF howls]
It's a good thing
we made it in time.
We felt really bad about
letting you sacrifice
yourself for all of us.
Although... you don't
look very happy about it.
I'm not! That was my best chance
to have a meaningful sacrifice!
And you jerks blew it!
But... I guess it's possible I'm
a little grateful for it, too.