For today's lesson, we're going
to practice operating the basic
controls of the IS.
[Chifuyu] Orimura, Alcott,
you're up first.
Not a problem.
Okay!
What's the matter with
this darn thing?
Move it, Orimura.
Any experienced IS pilot...
should take less than a second
to deploy.
Just focus...
Engage, Byakushiki!
Hey, it worked!
Good, now fly.
Right!
Right. Up, up and‐ oh God!
[girls] Oooh...
[Chifuyu] You're too slow!
According to the output specs,
the Byakushiki is superior
to her IS!
That may technically be true,
but right now I'm focusing my
imagination on...
on deploying the pyramid part
forward, okay?
Aw man, I'm just not getting
this at all.
[Cecilia] An image is nothing
more than an image.
But it'll be far more productive
if you can figure out the method
that works easiest for you.
Yeah, well, in the first place,
I still haven't even gotten
use to flying the IS around
just yet.
Heck, I'm not even sure
what makes it fly.
Well, uh, if you're interested,
I'd be happy to give you lessons
everyday after school.
And when I do, it'll be
just the two of us...
[Chifuyu] Orimura, Alcott,
execute a power dive and then
come to a complete stop.
Right, roger that.
Well, ladies first.
Wow, she totally nailed it.
Now let's see how I do.
Oh crap, oh crap, oh crap!
[screaming]
[boom]
Ichika!
Orimura!
[Maya] Are you okay?
Oh man... I seriously thought
I was going to die.
You moron! Do you know how much
it costs to fill in a hole
this size?
I'm sorry about that...
That's pitiful, Ichika.
You still haven't mastered
a single that I've taught‐
[Houki] Hey!
Goodness! Are you all right,
Ichika dear?
Have you been injured?
Uh, no, I'm okay. Honestly.
Wait, "Ichika dear"?!
I'm so glad to hear you
say that.
Still, I do think you it would
be best for you...
to get checked out thoroughly
at the nurse's office.
In fact, I'll even go with you‐
[Houki] Not necessary.
It's impossible for anyone
to get injured...
while piloting an IS.
Oh, Miss Shinonono.
Please understand, it's
only natural for me to
care about others.
Oh yeah, because your bosom
overflows with human kindness.
Yes, it does, and it's so much
more pleasent than scowling
like a troll!
I don't get it. Exactly when
did those two start hating
each other so much?
[Rinin] So, this is the
IS Acaedmy.
[Tanimoto] Orimura,
congratulations on your
inauguration as class rep!
[girls] Congratulations!
Wait, how did I become the
class representative?
Oh, you were promoted because
I decided to step down!
Obviously, it's true that you
did lose the match,
but if you think about it,
that outcome was inevitable.
After all, what else could
possibly happen with me as
your opponent?
Well, I just felt awful for
behaving so childishly and
getting upset afterward,
so I decided to let you be
the class representative.
Wow! That's so considerate
of you, Cecilia!
I totally agree!
Since he's the only male
student at the academy,
we have to give him, like,
our full support!
Aren't you Mr. Popularity?
Huh? You really think so?
And exactly why are you in such
a bad mood anyway?
Hello there! I'm from
the newspaper club!
Oh, Cecilia, if you don't mind,
would you get into the
picture too?
What? You mean,
just the two of us?
Oh, you and your personal units
are the center of attention!
It'd look even better if
you guys shake hands
or something.
Oh, do you really think so?
You will make certain that
I receive copies of the
pictures as well, won't you?
Oh, sure! No problem!
Come on, stand up.
Alright, can I get you guys
to shake hands for me?
[Mayuzumi] Now, get a little
closer and just give me a
big smile!
Very good, just relax!
Say cheese!
Why are all of you
my picture?
Just calm down.
We can't let you get ahead of
us all by yourself!
[nervous laughing]
So, I guess that you had
a lot of fun today.
It just made me feel exhausted.
Do you honestly think you
would enjoy it if you were
in my shoes?
Well, if I had to hazard
a guess...
I think I actually would
enjoy it!
What was that for?
I'm going to change into
my pajamas now,
so I need you to look away.
I don't understand why you
didn't change earlier while
I was brushing my teeth.
Hmph.
[ziiip]
[Houki] Alright. I'm done.
[Ichika] Oh.
Hey, are you wearing a new
belt tonight?
Actually, yes. I can't
believe you noticed.
Well yeah, of course I noticed.
I mean I look at you all
the time, you know?
Well yeah, of course you do.
I mean I'm right here and
you're there.
Well that's perfectly normal.
Alright, it's time to
go to sleep!
Um, Ichika...
[Ichika] Uh huh?
I just, well I, I'm sorry.
I was frustrated.
That's all right.
Don't worry, okay?
Oh, good. That's nice to know.
Um, goodnight then.
You too. Sleep tight.
[students] Good morning!
[girl 1] The class league match
is coming up soon.
Oh that's right! Have you heard
that the representative for
Class 1‐2 has been changed?
Yeah, now it's that
new transfer student,
what's‐her‐face.
A transfer student?
At this time of the year?
Yeah, supposedly she's
from China.
I wonder if she transfered to
the IS Academy in order to
study my techniques?
Well I'm sure curious.
I bet she's good.
Well, the only classes with a
student with a personal IS
are Classes 1 and 4,
so we'll be fine.
[Rinin] That information
is outdated.
The class representative for
Class 2 now has a personal
IS as well.
So it's not going to be as
easy to win anymore.
No way! Is that really you,
Rinin?
That's right! I'm Rinin Fan,
China's representative
contender.
And I have come here today
to declare war!
[girl 2] So, that's the transfer
student from Class 2.
[girl 3] The representative
contender from China?
Exactly who is that new girl?
She seems much too friendly
with Ichika.
Good one. Coming in and acting
like a show‐off.
[Ichika] It's so unlike
you, Rinin!
What? Why would you say
something like that about
me, huh?
[Rinin] That hurt!
What did you do that for?!
Consider that your homeroom
bell being rung.
Ch‐Chifuyu?!
That's Ms. Orimura.
Now get back to your class.
You're in the way.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Okay, but I'll be back later,
so don't you run away, Ichika!
You mean she's a representative
contender too?
[Ichika] You could've knocked
me over.
I can't believe that you're
Class 2's new transfer.
You should have contacted me.
Don't be stupid.
If I had done that,
it would have totally ruined
our dramatic reunion.
Ah ha ha, and maybe because you
still have some issues with my
big sister, Chifuyu?
No, I don't have issues
with her.
It's just that I'm not good
at handling her.
Ramen. Same order as always.
It's been a whole year since
I last saw you.
So, how have things been?
Look, I've been doing
just great, really!
Maybe you're the one who ought
to get sick or injured for
a change!
And what in the heck is
that supposed to mean?
Man, I can't believe you become
a representative contender.
And what about you?
It knocked me over when
I saw you on the news.
You think you were surprised?
The last thing I'd have
thought...
is that I'd end up in a
place like this.
I heard that you operated an
IS at the entrance exam?
But how on earth could something
like that happen?
To be honest, I couldn't tell
you how...
[Ichika] You know that the high
school entrance exams...
are held in the city's big,
multi‐purpose facility, right?
Well, I got lost in it.
And even though I asked a lot
of people for help,
everything they told
me was useless.
That's an IS...
Wha‐? Guh, no way!
[Ichika] It just moved!
[door opening]
[woman] Hey there, you're not
allowed in here!
Look! I think that IS is
responding to him!
That's impossible!
[woman] There's no way a boy
can control an IS!
Well, a whole lot of crap
happened after that.
Next thing I knew, I was
enrolled in this school.
Huh. That is weird.
Ichika, I think it's about
time that you to gave me
an explanation!
That's right! You had better
explain this!
Don't tell me you're
actually dating this
transfer student now!
No, it's not like that at all,
I swear!
It's true!
We're just childhood friends.
[Ichika] What's wrong with you?
[Rinin] Nothing's wrong! I'm
fine!
Childhood friends?
Oh that's right.
I forgot Rinin transferred to
our school right after you
moved away.
That's Houki Shinonono...
I've told you about her.
Houki was my very first
childhood friend,
and later you became my second
childhood friend.
I'm first...?
Uh huh. Now I see...
It's nice to meet one of
Ichika's old friends.
Yes, nice to meet you.
Ahem. Since you seem to have
forgetten about me, allow me
to introduce myself!
I am Cecilia Alcott,
the United Kingdom's
representative contender.
As a matter of fact, Ichika and
I had a fierce battle over...
[Rinin] So I heart that you were
recently chosen to be Class 1's
representative.
[Ichika] Um, yeah. That's what
happened.
[Cecilia] [continues to talk]
You know, if you want, I could
help you with your IS
practice drills.
Wouldn't that be fun?!
Well, yeah,
that would help, sure.
Ah! Look here! Are you
listening to me?!
Sorry, I'm just not interested.
I can't believe you
said that.
And in any case, it's my job
to teach Ichika!
You're from Class 2,
aren't you?
I'm not looking for any
assistance from the enemy!
Look, I'm having a nice chat
with Ichika, right now.
We weren't talking to you,
so you need to back off.
Well, you certainly have a lot
of nerve! You're the one who
entered the picture after
we did!
Actually, it wasn't after you.
I mean, I've known him longer
than you have.
Don't go there, because I've
known him longer than you have!
In fact, we're so close,
Ichika's eaten at my
house several times!
Oh, mine too.
What a coincidence!
[Rinin] Ichika used to come to
my house and eat with us all
the time.
Ever since he was in
elementary school.
Ichika, just what is she
talking about...
and how come you've never
mentioned any of this before?!
You've never mentioned it
to me either!
I used to go eat at the Chinese
restaurant her family owned,
that's all.
Oh, a restaurant.
At least that makes sense.
Well, if her family owned
a restaurant,
I supposed it's only natural
that you would've eaten there.
So Rinin, how's your dad doing?
I think he's okay.
[school bell]
Alright, I'll see you
after school.
I'll come by around the time
you're finished practicing
with them,
so make sure you're
available, okay?
What the devil is going on
around here Miss Shinonono?
And how did you‐
[Houki] I've been given
clearance to utilize the
training IS.
And I'll be using it for
Ichika's intensive training.
Now hold on, that's the Japanese
production IS.
How on earth could she have
possibly obtained clearance
to use the Uchigane?
All right, Ichika, let's begin.
Oh, yeah, right!
You wait just one minute!
I'm the one who's supposed to
be conducting Ichika's training!
[Cecilia] Do you hear me?!
Concentrate, Ichika. We'll start
your lesson now.
No, let me start your
lesson, Ichika.
[Cecilia] Well, I suppose we can
call it a day now, can't we?
[Ichika] Uh huh...
[Houki] You feel that way
because you haven't kept
up your training.
Come on! That was two against
one out there!
Well then, Ichika,
I'll see you later then.
What are you still doing
down there?
We should head back to
our room now.
Yeah, you go on ahead.
I can't move my legs.
What am I going to do about you?
Alright, I'll go ahead
and use the shower first.
Yeah, fine.
I wonder if it's going to be as
bad as this all the way up to
the class league match?
[Rinin] Hey, good work out
there, Ichika!
You're okay with a sports
drink, aren't you? Here!
Ah, thanks Rinin. Have you
really been waiting for
me all this time?
You could say that.
[Rinin] So, we're finally
alone together.
Yeah, I guess so.
Ichika...
I was wondering if you
missed me after I moved?
Well, I suppose having one less
friend to hang out with...
did make me feel a little
bit lonelier.
That's not what I meant!
I'm a childhood friend you
haven't seen for a long time.
And I know you've got something
to say to me!
Oh yeah, I forgot something
very important!
Have you contacted any other
friends from school, yet?
I mean to tell them you were
back in Japan. I bet
they'd thrilled!
That's not it!
I was talking about‐
Hey, look, I need to get back
to my room, okay?
I'm freezing and hopefully
Houki's done with our shower
by now.
Shower?
And Houki's that girl
I met earlier?
What kind of relationship do
you two have?
Well we're just
childhood friends.
She was my first...
and of course you were
my second.
But what does being childhood
friends have to do with taking
a shower?!
Oh that! That's because Houki
and I are sharing a room
right now.
What?!
Well yeah, they couldn't get
me my own room,
so we're, you know...
So what you're telling me
is that you...
and this Houki person are
living together?!
Yeah, kind of. But thank
goodness it's with Houki.
If it were someone
I didn't know,
I'd be nervous and I'd never be
able to get any sleep.
Hey, what's wrong?
It's okay because she's
your childhood friend.
What I said was,
you don't mind...
because she's your
childhood friend!
And that is why we need
to switch rooms!
Is your brain malfunctioning?
Why switch with me?
Well, I figured it must be
horrible for you...
having to share a room
with a guy.
But I never said that sharing
with him was horrible.
Besides this issue is between
me and Ichika, got it?
[Rinin] Oh, don't worry!
After all, I'm his
childhood friend too!
[Rinin] Right?
[Ichika] I don't know why
you're looking at me!
In any case, I will not switch
rooms with you!
Now, go back to your own room!
Oh, by the way, Ichika,
do you still remember
our promise?
Promise?
[Rinin] Mmhmm. From school.
Stop ignoring me, you trollop!
Okay, it's come to this...
Not in the house!
A full partial deployment!
And fast!
You know, a normal person
would have been seriously
injured by that.
[Rinin] Well, nevermind.
Hey, I almost forgot!
You were just talking about
some kind of promise.
What was it about?
Right, well, you know...
It was just...
You do remember it, right?
Let's see...
Oh, was it that I'd eat your
sweet and sour pork every day...
if you become a better cook?
Yeah! Yeah, that's it!
[Ichika] And it'd be
you're treat, right?
[Rinin] What?
[Ichika] That's right.
You promised you would treat me
to a meal everyday, wasn't
that it?
That would be awesome since
I'm single and‐
What a jerk!
Uh, just hold on there Rinin...
How can you not remember a
sacred promise you made
to a girl?!
You're the most despicable
guy ever!
I hope a dog bites you to death!
I don't understand why
you're so mad!
I did remember the promise!
But you didn't get the meaning
of it! You didn't get
the meaning!
Well then maybe you need to
explain it to me!
[Ichika] What the hell's
the meaning?!
You want me to explain it?!
How could I do that with
someone who's so dense?
How about this, then?
In the next week's class
league match,
the winner will get to make the
loser do any one thing that he
or she wants!
[Rinin] What do you say?
[Ichika] Sure, why not?
And if I win, I'm going to make
you explain it to me!
And you had better be ready
for it, you understand?!
[door opening and closing]
[Houki] Ichika...
Yeah, what is it now?
I hope a horse kicks you
to death!
[students murmuring]
Man, Rinin's my opponent
in the first match?
[Maya] Her IS called Shenlong.
This model is a close‐combat
type just like your Byakushiki.
This match is not going to be
the same as the one between
you and me,
so please don't let your
guard down.
Don't get too stressed out.
You can win as long
as you fight...
like you would during practice.
Geez, I bet it would really hurt
to get hit by that thing.
[announcement] Will both
contestants...
move to your designated
positions at this time?
If you apologize now,
I'll lower the intensity of the
pain you're about to endure.
I don't need any favors
from you!
Hit me with your best shot!
Fine! But for your information,
the "absolute defense"
isn't so perfect.
If your attack is powerful
enough to rip through
the shield,
it's possible for you to damage
the opponent badly enough,
but not kill them.
[Ichika] I know that!
[announcement] Both contestants,
you may commence the match at
this time!
[girl 1] At last, the duel
between Ichika Orimura and
Rinin Fan has finally begun!
[girl 2] Orimura's got a plan!
[girl 3] But his opponent has a
third generation type weapon!
[girl 1] Is there even a chance
that Byakushiki can win?
[girl 2] Go Orimura!
[girl 1] Yeah! Show everyone
that you're a man!
[girl 3] The next episode:
"The Class League Match"
[girl 1] Don't you dare miss
the unexpected ending!
[girl 2] And remember! Being
"hot" is a very important
quality for girls!
[girl 3] But please keep in mind
that "hot" also refers to fire
and burning!