[Ichika] But even after six
years, I recognized you right
away, Houki!
[Houki] Don't look!
[Cecilia] This calls for a duel!
[school bell]
Orimura, I'm afraid that it
will be a while befor your
IS is ready for you.
What?
On the plus side,
due to certain issues,
the school will provide you with
a personal IS.
[Girl 1] What? A personal IS
when he's only a freshman?
[Girl 2] In other words,
that means the government
is supporting this?
[Girl 3] That's so awesome!
I want my own too!
Is having your own IS really
that major of a deal?
I'm actually rather relieved
to hear that!
[Cecilia] After all, in a class
representative selection match
between you and I,
the outcome is already obvious.
But it's simply not fair for you
to use a training model whilst
I pilot my own personal unit.
Hold on,
you have your own IS as well?
Oh, don't you know?
Very well then. As you are
a commoner, I shall have
to explain.
I, Cecilia Alcott, am the
glorious representative
contender for Great Britain.
In other words, I currently own
my own, personal IS.
There are only 467
IS units worldwide.
So, obviously those who have
their own personal units are
the elites of the elite...
amongst the planet's population
of seven billion!
Only 467? That's all?
That's because the
central component of
all IS technology, the core,
has never been released.
As a result, there are only 467
machines in the entire world.
And Dr. Tabane Shinonono has
personally produced every one
of those cores.
[Ichika] Wait, isn't that
Houki's sister?
[Girl 1] Supposedly, the IS core
is like a self contained
black box.
This is because no one other
than Dr. Shinonono can
create one.
[Girl 2] But the thing is,
so far she's refused to
manufacture more than a
certain number of cores.
Therefore, countries,
corporations and
organizations...
are forced to conduct their
research, development and
training using the limited
number of IS units.
[Chifuyu] To complete our little
history lesson,
personal IS units were
originally only intended
for those...
sponsored by governments
or corporations.
However, your case
is exceptional.
Therefore, they will provide
you with a personal IS for data
collection purposes.
[Chifuyu] Is that all clear?
Uh, I guess so...
Um, excuse me, ma'am...
Do you know if the Miss
Shinonono in our class...
is related to Dr. Shinonono
by any chance?
Actually, your classmate
is her younger sister.
[class] Huh?!
[Aikawa] Seriously?
She's her sister?!
[Girl 2] I heard that Dr.
Shinonono has gone missing,
and every country and
all corporations has been
desperately trying to find her.
[Tanimoto] Yeah, don't you know
where she is?
She has nothing to do with me!
I'm not my sister.
And there's nothing I can
tell you about her.
[bummed class]
Alright Miss Yamada,
shall we start?
Guh! Oh, right!
[Maya] Now then...
[Ichika] I don't remember there
being any bad blood...
[Ichika] between Houki and
Tabane.
[Maya] Everyone open your
textbooks.
[Maya] We'll continue from where
we left off yesterday.
The IS, or Infinite Stratos,
displays a special energy
barrier that operates as
protection for its pilot.
The unit's system has something
similar to a consciousness.
So, through shared dialog and
time spent together, the two of
you will actually get to know
each other.
Depending on how much time a
pilot spends controling an IS,
it begins to understand the
user's characteristics.
I just don't understand this.
So, your IS isn't just a tool,
instead, think of it as your
big, mechanical partner.
Are there any questions so far?
Yes, ma'am!
So, did you mean "partner" as in
boyfriend or girlfriend?
D'oh! I'm not sure! That is...
I'm not experienced that way
so I don't know.
[giggling]
But I wonder... oh...
[student] You're so cute!
Is this really a typical all
girls' school atmosphere?
[Ichika] Hey, Houki...
Miss Shinonono!
Let's go eat lunch!
[Ichika] Would anyone like
to join us?
Yes, me, me!
Oh! Me too!
I made my lunch,
but I'm coming too!
[Ichika] Sure, we should all try
to get along with our fellow
classmates, okay?
You agree with me, right?
I think I'll pass.
Daw, don't be such
a grumpy‐face. Come on!
I already said I'm not going!
Oh, you don't feel like
walking, eh?
I'll carry you piggyback!
[Houki] Let go!
[Ichika] Hey!
[Ichika] Ow, ow...
[class murmuring]
You're so strong...
Yeah well... maybe you're the
one who's gotten weak?
Hmph. That was a little trick
from my kendo training.
[Nohohon] Um, well...
[bold girl] We think that maybe
we should...
[Tanimoto] ...pass this time.
Yeah, what? You have something
else stupid to say to me?
Houki!
I told you not to call me that!
Come on, let's go eat.
Hey, give it a rest!
Shut up and let's go.
You didn't have to get so upset
like that.
I was just trying to
look after you, you know.
Yeah? Who asked you to do
that anyway?
Even if someone asked me,
I wouldn't normally do that.
I did it because
it's you, Houki.
What? What's that mean?
[Ichika] Look, I owe a lot to
your aunt too.
Besides, we're childhood
friends and roommates.
So, at least let me meddle
in your life a little.
Well I guess...
Thank you...
[cook] Here you go,
two daily specials.
Thank you.
Hey, Houki, did you see any
empty tables on the way in?
There's one right over there!
Great, what'd I do now?
[Ichika] Hey, Houki.
[Houki] Yeah? What now?
Would you be willing to teach
me more about the IS?
'Cause I think I'm going to
lose to Cecilia the way
things are going.
Yeah, because you let
her provoke you!
I know that, but please help me!
[senior] Hey, aren't you the one
that everyone's talking about?
You're going to be competing
against a representative
contender,
but you've never flown for
real, have you?
If you want, I could teach you
lots of things about the IS.
[Houki] No, thanks.
Actually, I'm the one who's
going to be teaching him.
But you're a freshman
too, right?
I'm a senior, after all.
I think I'd do a much better
job teaching him the ropes.
But I am Tabane
Shinonono's sister.
[Houki] But thanks for
the offer.
Fine! I guess some things
can't be helped.
So then, you will teach me?
[smack, smack, crack]
[Ichika] Ah! Ow!
[thud]
[Houki] Okay, what in the
hell is going on here?
I‐I don't know what you mean.
How did you allow yourself to
become so weak?!
What clubs were you in in
middle school?
[Ichika] The "go home" club!
Three years of
perfect attendance!
Then you'll retrain!
This problem comes
before the IS!
Effective immediately, you will
be in training with me...
for three hours everyday
after school!
[Ichika] Hang on, I wanted you
to teach me about the IS!
And I said, this problem
comes before the IS!
Man, Orimura is...
...kinda weak.
Do you think he can really
control an IS?
I wonder if I came down just a
little too hard on him?
No way, he had it coming!
It was obvious he hadn't
wielded a sword for at
least a year!
Otherwise, there's no way he
would've ever lost to me
so easily!
He's changed...
in the past six years when
I didn't see him.
Ichika's really changed so much.
So, this means his intensive
training will begin tomorrow!
That means I'll get to
be alone with Ichika
after school‐
No, I'm not thinking about
things like that at all!
It's just that I'm genuinely
upset over my childhood
friend's weakness, right!
That's why it's okay!
[Ichika] Uh, Houki...
[Houki] What now?
Well, the thing is, you promised
me that you were going to teach
me about the IS.
Hey, don't turn away from me!
Thanks to you, the only thing
I've done in this week is
practice kendo techniques!
Well, I can't do anything
about that!
And your IS hasn't been
delivered yet anyway.
Even without one, you could
still at least teach me stuff
about the basics!
And I said, don't turn away
from me!
[Ichika] So, that's her personal
IS? Woah...
Orimura! Orimura!
[Maya] Orimura!
It's here! Your personal IS has
just arrived!
Orimura, you need to get
ready at once.
[Chifuyu] The amount of time
we can use the arena is limited.
You'll have to learn how to
make it yours during the
match itself.
[Maya] This is Orimura's
personal IS,
the Byakushiki!
[Chifuyu] Hurry up and
get suited.
Since time's limited,
we'll do the formatting
and fitting...
while the match is in progress.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's not like the first time I
touched an IS. There's
something different.
[Maya] Orimura,
are you all right?
Uh huh...
[Ichika] I'm just fine.
There's something familiar
about it.
I understand it. I can
understand what it is
and its purpose.
Show you entrust your
life to it.
[Chifuyu] Let it take control.
The system will optimize
the rest.
[Byakushiki]
[Ichika] Byakushiki...
This is Byakushiki.
[Maya] Cecilia Allcot's machine
is called Blue Tears.
It's a long‐range model IS.
Blue Tears, got it.
[Maya] In every IS unit,
there's a feature refered to as
"absolute defense".
It's primary function is always
to protect the pilot's life
during any attack.
However, that deployment would
cause your shield energy to be
badly depleated.
Do you understand that?
[Chifuyu] So, Orimura,
are you feeling up to this?
Yeah, piece of cake.
We'll see.
[Ichika] Hey Houki...
[Houki] Hm? Uh, huh?
[Ichika] Here we go.
Oh, okay...
Win this!
I'm off!
[Cecilia] Just so you know,
this is your last chance!
[Ichika] To do what?
It's obvious to everyone
that I'm going to defeat
you overwhelmingly.
So why not simply apologize to
me right now and I just might
be able to forgive you.
[Ichika] You can't really call
that a chance!
Oh I can't?
Well, too bad for you.
Now then...
[alarm]
Time to say goodbye!
[Ichika] Damn it! I can't keep
up with Baykushiki's reactions!
Now you will dance for me!
That's right!
Dance to the waltz that
Cecilia Alcott and Blue
Tears are playing!
Aw crap! The shield is
getting weak!
Where are my weapons?
[Ichika] Is that's all?!
It's better than bare hands,
I guess!
So this is your brilliant
plan, is it?
Challenging my long‐range IS
in hand‐to‐hand combat?
Don't be ridiculous!
[cheering]
You're the first opponent to
last this long.
You've fought longer against
Blue Tears in an initial
match than anyone!
And I must applaud you for that.
[Ichika] Thanks a lot.
But now the time has come
for the finale!
I'll take your left leg!
[Ichika] It's all or nothing!
Orimura!
Ichika!
[Cecilia] You're reckless,
aren't you?
But it's a pointless struggle!
Well now I finally get it!
[Ichika] Your weapons won't move
without your commands. That's
the trick.
And there's more than that,
you can't make any other
attacks while you're in motion.
[Ichika] That's because you're
focused solely on defense.
Right?
That was reallyy impressive.
I can't believe this is his
second time in an IS.
Ugh, that idiot...
He's too worked up.
But why would you say that?
Haven't you noticed the way he
keeps opening and closing
his left hand?
Whenever the kid does that,
he starts makeing really
stupid mistakes.
[Maya] I get it. I guess it
helps to be his sister.
[Ichika] Two more left!
But I know she's going to
attack where my response
speed is the slowest.
That means...
It's to my advantage to
close the distance!
I see, he fell for it.
So sorry. There are more
than four!
Aw crap!
Ichika!
The IS saved him.
He's such a little twit...
Ichika...
What's happening?
The shape of Orimura's
personal IS has changed!
Huh? What's this?
That can't be!
That's your first shift?
How could anyone have fought
an entire battle like this with
their IS in a default setting?
[Ichika] I'm not sure what the
heck I've been doing,
but it looks like this IS has
finally become my own.
[Ichika] The Yukihira Nigata?
Isn't the Yukihira the same
weapon Chifuyu used?
Man, I really do have the best
big sister in the entire world!
[Ichika] But I think it's
about time to change the
relationship...
from where I'm the one who
always has to be protected.
From now on, I'm going to be
protecting as well.
Just what are you
talking about?
[Ichika] I'm saying I will
defend my sister's name.
It'll make her look lame if her
brother's a candy‐ass weakling.
Honestly! You're such a pain!
Too late! I've seen them now!
Yeah, I can do this!
[horn]
[announcement] The match
is concluded.
Winner, Cecilia Alcott.
[Ichika] What?
[Cecilia] What?
[students] What?!
Huh?
Wha‐?
Okay, so why'd I lose again?
You lost because you used the
barrier‐disabling attack.
Without taking into account how
using it would affect
everything else.
The barrier‐disabling attack?
Which punctures the opponent's
barrier and passes the impact
directly to its body.
That's something only
Yukihira can do.
[Chifuyu] However, that ability
has to cannibalize your own
shield energy...
in order to function.
Actually, I have to admit
that when I won the First
Mondo Grosso,
it was mostly as a result of
that one ability.
I see. So that's why
Byakushiki's remaining shield
energy suddenly dropped to zero.
[Maya] When a competitor's
shield energy becomes zero,
that player loses the IS battle.
The barrier‐disabling attack
does damage your opponent,
but in exchange it will cost you
your shield.
It's really a classic
double edge sword.
Right and it means your
IS is defective.
Defective, how?
[Chifuyu] Okay, maybe that
was a bad way to phrase it.
An IS isn't complete to begin
with, so it can't be defective
per se.
But since yours is so much more
offense‐oriented than others,
it can't be handled
the same way.
[Maya] At the moment, your IS is
in stand‐by mode,
but all you have to do it and
it'll deploy right away.
However, there are a lot of
regulations, so read this
thoroughly.
And now she'll be the class
representative, huh?
And what does that look mean?
Well, are you...
upset that you lost?
Well, yeah, sure.
Uh, so I guess
starting tomorrow,
maybe we ought to start some
intensive IS training?
I guess.
Umm... You still...
You do want me to continue
teaching you, right?
Of course I do.
I'd rather ask you than any
other girl.
I mean, you're Tabane's sister,
so who else would know as much?
O‐Okay...
All right, I understand.
I have to then.
Right, I here by agree to teach
you about the IS!
Starting tomorrow, I want you
to be waiting for me everday
after school!
[Houki] Okay?
[Ichika] Yes ma'am!
Hey, wait!
[water running]
[Cecilia] Why am I feeling
this way?
Even though I was the winner?
Ichika Orimura...
[Girl 1] Hey, who's that girl?
[Girl 2] And how come she seems
to be so close to Orimura?
[Girl 3] She's the one from
China, who has her own
personal IS!
Supposedly, she's Orimura's
friend from middle school.
[Girl 1] Not only that, she's
the class representative of
Class 1‐2! So, that means...
[Girl 2] She's going to fight
him at the class match!
[Girl 1] The next episode:
"The Transfer Student is the
Second Childhood Friend"
[Girl 3] Oh, I wonder if her IS
wears an outfit that's like a
Chinese dress?!
[Girls 1 and 2] No way, that
would be impossible!