[Rinin] Ichika, I was wondering
if you missed me after I moved?
[Ichika] You promised that
you would treat me to a meal
everyday, wasn't that it?
[Rinin] What a jerk!
[Ichika] Geez, I bet it would
really hurt to hit by that
thing.
Not bad.
You were actually able to stop
my first attack.
[Rinin] But that won't last.
[squealing, cheering]
Ichika!
Come on! What on earth
is he doing out there?!
You should be using the
cross‐grid turn I taught you!
Have you forgotten how
to do it?!
At this rate, the match is
going to be pretty grueling.
I need to create some distance.
So naive!
[Ichika] Guh!
[laughing]
And that was what you would
call a jab!
What the hell kind of
attack did she use?
What she used was
a shock cannon.
It's a weapon that manipulates
the barometric pressure...
of the surrounding atmosphere.
That's right. The Shenlong is a
third generation model IS,
just like my own Blue Tears.
[Rinin] You're dodging
pretty well.
I thought the invisible barrel
and ammunition were supposedly
this Ryuho's features,
however...
There's something else about
the shock cannon...
It fires at any angle unlimited
by its barrel's angle of skew.
So what you're saying is,
it doesn't have a blind spot.
Yes, I'm afraid that's
exactly right.
[Ichika] If I don't make some
kind of preemptive strike,
she's going to win!
I have to get it together!
I'm using the exact same
machine that Chifuyu uses.
So, is the Yukihira Nigata the
only weapon the Byakushiki has?
And I won the championship
using only that.
Just one swing is good enough
to win.
You know, I really wish you
wouldn't put me in the same
category as the world champion.
If you want to be realistic,
an amateur like you doesn't
have a chance of winning a
shooting battle.
[Chifuyu] Do you know anything
about recoil control, how to
distance youself from the
bullet line,
one‐zero stop, absolute turns...
What about ammo characteristics,
atmospheric conditions?
Or the intellectual aspects
of battle?
Such as the influence caused by
the opponent's equipment?
And that's only the beginning,
so can you handle all that?
Well can you?!
[Ichika] I'm sorry...
Look, I know you pretty well and
mastering one technique is
really more your style.
After all, you are my
brother, right?
The barrier‐disabling attack...
Can I use it?
[Ichika] Rinin...
[Rinin] Yeah, what is it?
[Ichika] Look, I'm warning you.
I'm not going to hold back.
What's that mean?
That's what you're supposed
to do!
Besides, I'll show you that we
are not in the same league!
It looks like Orimura's thinking
about trying something.
My guess is that he's using
the ignition boost.
Exactly like I taught him.
Hold on, what is this
ignition boost?
It's a form of surprise attack
in which you close in on your
opponent at a maximum rate
of speed.
As long as he can ignite at just
the right moment,
he even can go toe‐to‐to with
a representative contender.
Unfortunately...
This is his only chance because
it just works once.
[crack]
[boom]
What the‐?
[students] What happened?!
Did the attack miss?
Is it an Earthquake?
What? What in the devil
just happened out there?
Ichika?
The system's been damaged!
An unidentified object appears
to have penetrated the arena's
deflection shield!
Suspend the match!
Orimura, Fan, get out of
there immediately!
[siren]
[screaming]
Hey, what's happening?
What in the hell's going on?
Ichika, the match is canceled!
Get back to the pit now!
[Ichika] But wha‐ Huh?
Another IS?
And there's no indentification
on it?
Is it locking me out somehow?
How can it be locked?!
What are you doing?!
Get back to the pit!
Get back? And what are you
going to do?
[Rinin] I'm going to buy us some
time, but you need to get out of
here right now!
Now wait a second! There's no
way I'm going to leave a
girl behind!
You idiot! You're the weaker
fighter, so you don't get
any choice! Now move!
What?
It's not like I'm going to
handle this all the way to
the end okay?
I'm standing in...
until one of the teachers can
get out here and handle it.
Look out!
A beam weapon?
And it has a higher power output
than Cecilia's IS.
Hey, you idiot! You need to
let go of me right now!
Woah, stop moving around!
[Rinin] Shut up! Shut up!
[Ichika] Don't hit me!
Quit willing!
Here it comes!
Just what is that damn thing?
It not any IS I've ever
heard of.
Alright, you! Identify yourself!
[Ichika] Answer me! Who are you?
What are you doing here?
[Maya] Orimura, Fan!
You need to vacate the
arena at once!
The teachers will be there
soon with their IS units to
neutralize the situation.
No, we've got to keep it
occupied until everyone
evacuates!
I understand how you must feel
about this, but you just can't
do that!
Get out of there now!
[Cecilia] Ichika, run!
[Houki] Ichika!
Are you okay with this?
Are you talking to me, you jerk?
Can't you see that all I want is
for you to let me go?
[Rinin] I can't even move with
you holding me like this!
[Ichika] Oh, sorry.
[Rinin] It looks like she's
ready to do this.
[Ichika] Yeah, let's say
you're right.
Ichika...
How 'bout you charge at her
while I cover you?
That's your only weapon right?
More or less.
Right, let's do it.
[Ichika] Rinin! Wait!
[boom, boom, boom]
Orimura, please come in!
If you can hear me,
please respond!
Are either of you listening
to me? Fan, Orimura!
They said they could handle the
situation, didn't they?
So I say we let them go for it.
What? Please say that you're
not serious!
How can you say something like
that at a time like this?
Oh, calm down.
Just chill and have a cup of
coffee or something.
[Chifuyu] You're only
stressing because your
body's running low on sugar.
Um, before you drink that, what
you actually just added was
the salt.
Ichika...
Please, ma'am, give me
authorization to use my IS!
I can move out right away!
I wish I could do that, but...
Well...
The arena's deflection shield's
setting is currently at
Level 4.
And on top of that,
all the doors have been
automatically sealed.
Did that IS cause this?
It seems so.
As things stand,
we can't evacuate...
and we can't go in and stage
a rescue either.
[panic]
Very well, then! Deem this
an emergency and ask for
government support!
We've done that. The senior
elites are doing their best
to crack the system even as
we speak.
[Chifuyu] And just as soon as
they have the deflecting
shield under control,
we'll be sending in the troops.
So I guess that means that
for right now,
the only thing we can
do here is wait.
That's right. But you couldn't
help the shock troops in
any case,
so there's no reason for you
to worry about it.
Exactly what are you trying
to say?
I'm saying that Blue Tears is
designed to fight multiple
opponents by itself.
Which means that if you tried
to work with a group, you'd just
be getting in everyone's way.
No! That isn't true! I wouldn't!
How could you think I'd do
something like that?
So have you had group training?
What was your position
on the team?
[Chifuyu] What was your ally's
formation?
[Cecilia] But‐
[Chifuyu] How did your squad
assess the enemy?
And what was the duration
of the operation?
All right then, I give up!
You made your point already!
[Chifuyu] I hope so. You need
to understand why things are
as they are.
Ichika, do it now!
[screaming]
Oh you idiot!
Aim that thing like you're
supposed to!
That was your fourth
try already!
Hey, I am aiming it, damnit!
[Ichika] Aw crap...
I'll only be able to use the...
barrier‐disabling attack one
more time.
[Rinin] Ichika, break away!
[Ichika] R‐Right!
[Rinin] What are we going to do?
We'll never beat her without
some kind of strategy.
Hey, you can still run if
you want to.
Who said anything about
running, you jerk?
I'm still a representative
contender, you know!
All right! How's this sound?
You take the point and I'll
cover your rear end!
That's appreci‐
Stay focused!
Yeah, tell me something
I don't know!
You know what? Don't you think
that that thing's movements look
a little too mechanical?
Hmm? What do you mean?
It is a machine, you know.
No, that's not what I'm
talking about.
I'm wonder if there's really
anyone piloting it?
What? But an IS won't work
without a pilot...
[Rinin] Now that you
mention it,
I've noticed that it hasn't
attacked us much when we're
talking to each other.
It almost seems like she's
curious about our conversation.
[Ichika] Yeah, I know.
There's no way it can
be unmanned.
Someone has to be inside
an IS or it won't move.
That's just how it is.
[Ichika] But think about it...
What if... What if there really
is no one in there?
[Rinin] Wait...
Are you saying we could
beat it if it's unmanned?
Yeah...
If there's no one in there,
we can literally pound it with
everything we've got,
and it would be okay.
Pound it with everything
we've got, huh?
Reiraku Byakuya...
That's Yukihira Nigata's
all‐out attack.
[Ichika] The full force of
Yukihira Nigata is normaly
too powerful.
So, you can't go all out with
it during training or in a
class match for that matter.
However, you could if your
opponent was unmanned.
[Rinin] Look, I don't know
anything about your Reiraku
thing or whatever,
but you can't seem to hit
a darn thing right now!
Oh, I'll hit it!
[sigh]
Well, you sound
pretty determined.
So, even though I don't think
it's a possibility,
let's just say it's unmanned
and attack the thing anyway.
All right, so the plan is that
you shoot it with the cannon at
full blast,
but only when I give the signal.
Are we both agreed on that?
Sure, but it'll miss it.
It'll be fine even if
it does miss.
[Ichika] All right, let's do
this!
[Houki] Ichika!
If you're a man...
If you're a man, you'd better
defeat the enemy completely!
Aw crap!
Houki, run!
Rinin, do it now!
You've got it!
Hey, you stupid idiot!
What are you doing? Get out of
my line of fire!
Just shoot, damnit!
You crazy jerk! Whatever
happens is not my fault!
This is for Rinin, Houki,
Chifuyu, and everyone else
I care about!
I will protect all of you!
Ichika!
[Houki] Ichika!
[Rinin] Ichika, get out!
How's your aim?
[Cecilia] Perfect, of course!
[Houki] Cecilia!
[Rinin] But when did you...
Cecilia, take him out!
Roger that, I'm on it!
[Cecilia] It looks like we made
it with not a second to spare!
I knew you'd come through
in time, Cecilia.
O‐Oh? Do you really mean it?
Still, that's to be
expected, right?
Well, it's over now. In any ca‐
[alarm]
[Ichika] Oh, you're kidding me!
Ichika, it's still moving!
Rinin? What were you doing
just then?
U‐Uh, were you awake?
Why are you acting so nervous?
What makes you say that?
I'm not nervous!
That's a completely ridiculous
thing to say!
So, what happened to the IS?
It got shut down.
Don't worry though,
you were the only one who was
hurt in the attack.
Everyone else is fine.
I see.
[Ichika] You know...
Now that I think about back when
we were in elementary school,
wasn't it an evening just like
this when we had that talk about
eating sweet and sour pork?
[Rinin] So, if I become a
better cook,
will you eat my sweet and sour
pork everyday?
So, about that promise, was it
actually about something else,
Rinin?
Because I seriously thought you
mean you were going to treat me
to free meals everyday.
No, it's not about something
else! It's really not!
It's just that, when you
cook for someone else,
your cooking improves.
[nervous laughing]
You know, I'd love to try your
sweet and sour pork,
but to be honest, it'll be hard
to top your father's cooking.
Man I'd love to have that again.
Well, he uh, doesn't work
there anymore.
[Ichika] What? Why did he stop?
The thing is, my parents,
they got a divorce.
That's one of the reasons why I
decided to move back to China.
[Ichika] Hey, Rinin...
Would you want to go hang
out sometime?
You mean, like a date?
Surprise Ichika, dear!
I hope you're feeling much
better now.
But I've come to look after you‐
[Cecilia] Uh... What is this?
Just what are you doing here?
Remember, we decided no one
can make a move on Ichika
until he wakes up!
And what about you, then?
Because from my view
of your fat ass,
it sure looks like you were
trying to get ahead of me.
Oh, well, the thing is...
Get out of here, both of you!
Don't you understand that
Ichika's my childhood friend?
Well he's mine too!
You're from Class
2, Miss Take‐Away!
Hey...
Where's Chifuyu?
Now that you ask...
Yeah, where do you think
she went?
She was right there with us
until just a few minutes ago.
So, it really was unmanned.
And it seems the core
was unregistered.
I see.
[Maya] There are only 467 known
IS cores in the world.
And yet somehow, this IS was
equipped with a core we know
nothing about.
How can that be?
[girl 1] A new beautiful boy has
just appeared!
[girl 2] No way!
Where is he from?
[girl 3] He's from France
and his name is Charles Dunois!
[girl 1] He's not only good
looking, but he's nice, smart
and strong too!
[girl 2] Yeah, he seems to be
perfect in so many ways!
[girl 3] But it looks like he
might have some secrets.
[girl 1] The next episode:
"Boy Meets Boy"
[girl 2] Orimura and Dunois are
such dreamy boys!
And now they're both at the
IS Academy!
[in unison] And we're so glad!