[Laura] To think I am going
to face you in the very
first match.
How very convenient.
Now I don't even have to wait.
Yeah, that's how I feel.
Like Christmas with
more violence.
[beep, beep, beep]
[in unison] I will crush you!
[buzzer]
Just as I expected...
A.I.C...
And I thought he understood
it now.
A preemptive attack right after
the match begins?
You're so predictable.
Thanks so much.
I'm so glad to know that you're
able to read my mind.
[Charles] You won't get away!
Now, here comes the
rapid switch!
You'd better not forget
about me, gentlemen.
What are you doing?!
[screaming]
Poor Houki. Do you think Laura
thought that was helping her?
No, she was just in her way.
That stupid German cow.
I'm sorry that your
opponent's not Ichika.
What? Stop that!
[Maya] Hmm, so do you think
that their plan is to go after
Miss Shinonono first?
[Chifuyu] Smart strategy.
Bodewig doesn't understand
the advantage of...
having anyone else on her side
in a combat situation.
She's been unable to think of
her partner as an asset from
the start.
But in contrast to
Bodewig's approach,
the coordination that Orimura
and Dunois has been simply
brilliant so far.
Yes, but I would expect
nothing less from them.
[hiss]
[system shutting down]
[alarm]
[Houki] Is that it?
Thanks for waiting.
And thanks for the assist!
Merci, Charles!
So, where's Houki?
Oh, she's taking a break.
[Ichika] Now that
was impressive.
But I have a little something
else up my sleeve!
One more time.
Resistance is futile!
[Ichika] Sorry, Laura.
You're forgetting something.
There are two people
on our team, remember?
See that?
So predictable!
[Maya] Another combination?
[Chifuyu] He's finally realized
the fundamental weakness
of the A. I. C.
[Maya] Huh?
[Chifuyu] Its overall
effectiveness can only
be sustained...
while your focus remains
on your target.
[system shutting down]
[alarm]
Aw, you can't keep fighting...
now that your shield energy has
been exhausted, can you?
[Laura] Now you're just
in my way!
Charles, no!
Die!
[Charles] It's not over yet!
It has an ignition boost?!
[Laura] That wasn't in the data!
[Charles] That's right!
Because I've never used
it before.
You mean you just now learned
how to do that?!
But it's powerless against
my canceling barrier‐
[boom]
That's Charles' assault rifle!
Why won't you just die already?!
[Charles] You're aiming
the wrong way.
Or can't you hit me from here?
Nein! Not the shield pierce!
[screaming]
That's it!
[cheering]
No! I can't lose...
There's no way I can lose!
I can't!
[scientist] DNA reinforced
specimen C0037...
Your new code name will be...
Laura Bodewig.
[Laura] I was created, born,
raised and trained...
for one purpose only.
I was made to fight.
But not just a fighter,
I was an elite.
And I was always on top.
However, that all changed...
when the world's most powerful
weapon emerged.
The IS.
After that, in order to
enhance my compatibility,
a surgical procedure was
performed immediately...
and my eye was implanted
with a nanomachine.
I was willing to have
the modification.
However, my body was unable to
accommodate the augmentation,
and as a result,
I was labeled a failure.
Until one day, I met her.
And everything changed.
She was an extremely
skilled instructor.
And once again, in the IS
dedicated unit, I was to
become to best.
[Laura] I want to become as
strong as you are.
What is it that makes
you so strong?
I do it for my younger brother.
No...
But why is it you look so soft?
You have great strength,
dignity and confidence.
Those things are what
I admire in you.
That is why I cannot
forgive him.
That is why I cannot approve of
a male who can make my
instructor that way.
I want power.
[voice] Do you wish for it?
Do you want to obtain
greater power?
[Laura] Give me that power!
Give me unmatched power!
[screaming]
Mon dieu!
My god!
Security alert, level D.
Yes ma'am.
What is that thing?
[siren]
[announcement] This is a state
of emergency!
All tournament matches
are cancelled.
The situation has been
classified Level D,
and we are sending a team of
instructors to bring this
matter under control.
[announcement] All guests
and students must evacuate
immediately!
[Rinin] Poor Laura...
[Ichika] Yukihira...
Just like my sister,
Chifuyu's...
That thing out there seems to be
completely different...
from the one that attacked here
last month.
What do you think happened
to Miss Bodewig?
[Ichika] This one's mine.
[Ichika] Her sword technique...
I remember!
That was the first technique
I ever learned from Chifuyu.
Damn you...
You're copying my sister
to fight me?
How dare you?!
I'll make you pay!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Trying to get killed?
[Ichika] Let me go, damnit!
She's really pissing me off!
I'll destroy her!
[Maya] What's going on?
Why isn't she moving?
[Chifuyu] Perhaps it's some kind
of automatic program...
that only responds to
weapons and attacks?
[Maya] An automatic program?
But that would mean that Miss
Bodewig's will is...
[Ichika] Stay out of my way!
[Houki] Stop it!
What in the hell is
wrong with you?
[Ichika] What's wrong is that
she's using the same...
sword engaging technique
as Chifuyu!
That's my sister's!
That technique is
Chifuyu's alone!
[Chifuyu] Listen, Ichika.
You're supposed to swing
a sword.
As long as you let it swing you,
that's not swordsmanship.
It's heavy, right?
That's the weight of a weapon
that can end someone's life.
[Houki] But what can you even
do right now?
Can you even fight when
Byakushiki has no energy left?
No, you can't!
[Houki] Take a look, the
situation is being handled
without you doing anything.
[Ichika] You're wrong
about that.
You're dead wrong.
I don't want to fight
but I have to.
Because... because this
is about me too!
And just what is it you're
going to do?
[Charles] Actually, sometimes
the solution to no power,
is simply to borrow some.
[Charles] Now releasing Revive's
core bypass.
Energy transfer
process, authorized!
First, promise me that you
will not lose this fight!
You've got a deal!
I'm no man if I lose, right?
Sure!
However, if you lose...
you will have to come to school
wearing a girl's uniform.
Uh, sure thing.
[Maya] What are they doing?
They're not...
The instructors are ready.
They'll handle it.
The transfer is now complete.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Reactivating Byakushiki in
single‐pole mode.
Oh, I guess it was only
effective on the weapon
and the right arm.
Good enough.
[Houki] Ichika!
Don't die!
Don't you dare die!
Have some faith!
Don't stop believing, Houki.
[Ichika] Hold on to that
and have faith.
You do that and I'll win.
[Ichika] Reiraku Byakuya...
Activate!
Let's do this,
you cheap immitation!
[Laura] Why do you try to
stay strong?
Why are you strong?
[Ichika] But I'm not strong.
I'm really not strong at all!
The reason you think I
have strength,
is because my need to be
strong makes me strong.
That's what makes me that way.
The fact that there's something
I want, need to do.
[Laura] Something you want
to do?
[Ichika] Yes, I want to
protect someone.
And I need to use
everything I have...
to fight to protect that person.
[Laura] But that sounds exactly
like her.
[Ichika] You're right.
And I intend to protect
you in the same way,
Miss Laura Bodewig.
But I am not...
Mentor, what has happened to me?
This matter is of
utmost importance,
and also highly classified.
What do you know of the
VT System?
You're talking about the
Valkyrie Trace System?
[Chifuyu] Yes...
Its research,
development and usage...
have all been completely
prohibited by the
International IS Treaty.
However, it appears that your IS
was in fact equipped with it.
More over, it seems it was
set to activate only under
situations where there was
extensive damage,
and the pilot's mental condition
was completely and totally
focused on winning.
You willed it to happen.
[Laura] It happened because
I wished for it?
[Chifuyu] Laura Bodewig!
Yes, ma'am!
[Chifuyu] Who are you?
I am...
[Chifuyu] If you're no one,
then that's perfect.
From now on, you are just
Laura Bodewig.
But remember, you will never
be able to become me.
[giggling]
[Charles] Well, they ended up
canceling the tournament.
Never the less, they still want
to collect everyone's data,
so we will get to fight
one round each.
The chance to win it is
gone now...
To win a date...
Waaah!
[crying]
[Ichika] By the way, Houki,
about that promise from
last month...
I don't mind going out with you.
You what?
I said, I don't mind going‐
Really? Are you sure about that?
Do you really, really mean it?
Uh, well, yeah...
Why?!
I mean, please explain your
reasons to me.
Well, you're my good childhood
friend so why shouldn't
I go, right?
[Houki] Right!
It's just shopping‐
I knew you would say something
like that!
[Charles] Oh Ichika, sometimes
I really do wonder if you do
things like that on purpose.
[Maya] Orimura! Dunois!
I've got some wonderful news!
I know you went through
a lot earlier,
but I'd thought you'd like to
know that we've finally managed
to get both of you...
a wonderful place that
will reward you!
[Ichika] Huh?
[Charles] What place?
That's right! It's a new
men's bathhouse!
How refreshing.
[door opening]
[Charles] Um,
please excuse me...
What the‐?!
Don't stare at me you...
you pervert, Ichika.
Guh! Sorry!
What do you think you're doing?!
Does it bother you that
I'm in here?
No, it's not like that, but...
You know, I figured I should
check out the bath,
but if it bothers you that much,
I can go and leave now.
Uh, n‐no, please!
I'll leave instead!
I've enjoyed the bath already.
[Charles] No, wait!
I need to tell you something.
It's something important,
so I want you to hear
me out, okay?
All right.
[Charles] Well, it's about what
I told you before.
Uh, you mean about you staying
at the academy?
Yes, that's right.
I think I will stay here
after all.
[Charles] Because you're here,
Ichika, I think I want to be
here too.
Oh, I see.
[Charles] Besides that,
I've decided one more thing...
about the way I should be.
About the way you should be?
[Charles] From now on, would you
please call me Charlotte?
But only when we are
by ourselves.
Could you do that?
[Ichika] I‐Is that your real...
Oui, that is my real name.
The name my maman gave
me on the day that I was born.
As you wish...
Miss Charlotte.
Bon.
I'd like to introduce you to a
new transfer student today...
Hello, I am Charlotte Dunois.
And it is very nice to be
meeting all of you once again.
[class] Huh?!
[Maya] Uh, yes, it seems
Mr. Dunois turned out to
be a Miss...
[Maya] We were kind of
shocked too.
[girl 1] So you mean Dunois is
really a girl?!
[girl 2] I knew there was
something fishy about it!
[girl 3] He wasn't a beautiful
boy, but a beautiful girl!
[girl 1] Wait, Orimura's been
sharing the same room without
knowing anything about it!
[girl 2] Wait a second!
[girl 1] That means...
[girl 2] Didn't they open
the large bath to the boys
last night?!
[boom]
[screaming]
Ichika!
No, for the love of God,
don't shoot!
I'm really going to die!
Am I not dead yet?
Laura!
[Ichika] You saved me!
Thank you! I‐
Now, I have decided that I am
going to make you my bride!
That is final, and I will not
accept any objections from you!
[everyone] What?!
Huh?
Wha‐?!
[girl 1] At last, a hot steamy
summer has finally arrived!
[girl 2] And since it's summer,
we'll all be going to the beach
of course!
[girl 3] And tomorrow
happens to be Sunday!
[girl 1] We should all go
shopping together!
[girl 2] Shopping?
But what are we going to buy?
[girl 1] Swimsuits of course!
We're girls and we've got to
work it on the beach!
[girl 2] It's the next episode:
"Ocean's Eleven!"
[girl 3] Hey, it looks like we
weren't the only ones who came
here to buy swimsuits.
[girl 1] Yeah! I see her,
her and her too!