Fresh wasabi is great!
It's the real deal!
The "real deal?"
H‐Hey there, how're ya
doing, Charl?
I feel okay, thanks...
It was particularly flavorful
and delicious...
Oh man, I thought you knew
better than to do something
like that.
Are you feeling all right?
If you can't kneel for
a long time,
maybe you should move to
a table instead?
I'm quite all right!
And compared to the effort it
took to secure this place at
the table, this is nothing!
[Ichika] This place?
[Ceclia] Uh, it's nothing
at all! Honestly!
[nervous laughter]
[Charlotte] Ichika!
There are many different types
of girls, you know.
Oh, is that so?
[Charlotte] Yes, it is so.
[Ichika] Oh man, check
out the face on Houki...
I wonder what she could be
looking so upset about?
Hey, Cecilia, if it's really
that uncomfortable, do you
want me to feed you?
I've done it for Charl‐
[Charlotte] Ichika!
[Ichika] Sorry.
[Cecilia] Do you really mean it?
Do you really mean that you
would actually be willing
to feed me?
[Ichika] Honestly?
It would be an awful shame...
to let all this beauitful food
go to waste now wouldn't it?
[Ichika] Okay, sashimi first.
[Cecilia] Oh, right! But not too
much wasabi, if you please.
[Ichika] Right.
All righty!
[in unison] Aaah!
[girl] Aw! Cecilia's so mean!
She's having Orimura feed her!
[girls complaining]
Stupid Ichika! I'm sure he's
completely forgotten that
tomorrow is the 7th of July.
For the love of God, why can't
you all just eat your food
in silence?!
[girl] Um, yes Miss Orimura!
Orimura, stop causing such a
racket. Calm it down in
here pronto.
Uh, yes, ma'am. Calming it down.
Sorry about that, Cecilia,
I guess you'll have to do
it by yourself.
In exchange, why don't you
come by my room later tonight?
Okay?
Come to your room?
Oh Ichika, could you
possibly mean we...
Oh, after we got everything
ready, we really thought we'd
be able to play with Orimura.
[girl] What a disappointment.
Mmhmm. And he's been in Miss
Orimura's room forever.
[humming]
It's a good thing I was
prepared for this sort of
situation, just in case!
Oh wow! Ceci's wearing some
naughty underwear!
Is she, now?
Let's strip her and see it!
Yeah, peel it off!
Peel it all off!
[struggling]
[Cecilia] You get back! Stop it!
Don't touch that!
Oh! That's Freanch black lace
with no underwire!
[girl] Oh, so that's what
naughty underwear looks like?
[Tanimoto] Yeah and she pulls
it off well too.
[in unison] Oh la la!
Cecilia is so naughty!
I am not! It's not like that!
In fact, this is, uh,
merely a young lady's
personal preference.
That's right!
It's a personal preference!
Oh my, that ordeal
was simply beastly.
But I finally get to see Ichika
so it's all worth it!
What is going on here?
Ssh.
[Ichika] Are you nervous
Chifuyu? I know it's been
a long time.
[Chifuyu] Of course,
don't be ridiculous.
Hey, don't do it quite so hard.
[Ichika] Okay, fine.
What about here?
[Chifuyu] Oh, that is...
Oh no, not there!
[Ichika] It will feel good soon.
Looks like this has been
building up.
[Chifuyu] Uh...
[Cecilia] Oh! Oh my goodness!
[Cecilia] What in Heaven's name
is going on in there?!
[Ichika] What about here?
[Chifuyu] No, not there. Ow!
[Ichika] Sorry.
Okay, iditos. Just what was so
interesting about my getting
a massage?
Oh, you were giving your
sister a massage?
Ja, that's not what we
thought at all...
What did you think
we were doing?
Well naturally, we‐
Not a single thing!
Yes, we weren't thinking
at all.
[nervous laughter]
Uh huh...
He may not look like a massuer,
but he has amazing fingers.
Come to think of it,
maybe you should all
let him do you.
[in unison] Huh?!
[Ichika] Okay,
I'll do Cecilia first.
Oh! I'm going first?
Yes, that's why I asked you
here, so come lie down.
[squealing]
[Cecilia] O‐Ow! Ow!
Oh, sorry, I'll be gentle.
[Ichika] Let's see. It doesn't
hurt when I do this, does it?
No, not at all.
It feels quite wonderful.
I mean it feels so good that
I find myself becoming rather
sleepy in fact.
[Cecilia] I even...
Ah!
Oh my! How precocious!
[crying]
But these are really too
mature for you.
Nice shade of black though.
Please ma'am, I really do wish
you would put that down now!
[Chifuyu] What? Didn't expect
your lewd 15 year old desires
to be expressed to your teacher?
[whimpering]
Oh, I'm just joking, dear.
Hey, Ichika, why don't you
go and buy us some drinks?
Oh, okay.
Okay girls, what's with the
dead fish expressions?
Um, the thing is, we, uh...
You see, ma'am, this is the
first time we have ever spoken
to you in this way...
[Chifuyu] Okay.
We're finally getting down to
the nitty‐gritty, huh?
So, what do you girls
even see in him?
[in unison] Huh?!
I mean, my brother has his uses,
to be sure.
For example, he's good at
cooking, housekeeping, and
he gives fantastic massages.
So, any girl who gets him
would be lucky.
That said, he comes at a price.
[in unison] He's for sale?!
No, you fools.
[in unison] Oh...
Listen, if you're a real woman,
you've got to be willing
to do...
whatever it takes
to nuke your rivals.
Get with the program,
kiddos, okay?
[Ichika] Houki?
Okay, "Please pull", do you
think that this means...
Sometimes it's just better
not to know.
Hey wait, should we just leave
it lying there like that?
What are you doing over
here, Ichika?
Something I might regret...
Whoa!
[Ichika] Uh oh...
[Cecilia] Huh?
[Ichika] I knew it.
[screaming]
[laughing]
You fell for it, Ichikun!
Yay, yay!
It sure has been a long time,
hasn't it, Tabane?
[Tabane] Mmhmm!
Long time, no see.
A really long time!
So, Ichikun,
where'd little Houki go?
Uh, actually she's...
That's okay, I'll find her soon
enough just by using this Houki
tracking device I invented.
Okay, Ikkun, I'll see ya later!
Uh, Ichika, who was that strange
person just now?
That's Tabane Shinonono,
Houki's big sister.
[Chifuyu] As you can see,
everyone with a personal unit
has been assembled here.
Um, just a minute, ma'am. Houki
doesn't have her own unit,
does she?
Well uh...
[Chifuyu] It's all right,
Shinonono.
I'll explain everything...
The reason that she's here is‐
[Tabane] Cowabunga!
[Tabane] Chii‐chan!
Hello, hello, hello!
Oh, I missed you, Chii‐chan!
Let's hug and confirm our
love for each other!
Will you just shut up, Tabane?
[Tabane] Using the unforgiving
Iron Claw as always, aren't you?
Ta‐daa! Hi there!
Yes, hello.
[Tabane] It's been a while,
hasn't it? How many years
has it been?
I can't believe how much bigger
you've gotten, little sister.
Especially your boobies!
I will so hit you!
You say that afterwards?
That's so cruel!
She's a real dominatrix,
isn't she, Ikkun?
Uh, well...
You know, Tabane, you should
at least introduce yourself.
Ugh, that's such a pain!
Okay everybody, hi, I'm Tabane
the genius. Hello, that's all.
That's it!
You're Tabane?
As in Tabane, the brilliant
scientist who invented the
IS units?
The Tabane Shinonono?!
Now everyone!
Look, up to the heavens!
[Tabane] Ta‐daa!
This is Houki's own personal
unit, the Akatsubaki!
All of its specs are way above
the current models and it's
handmade by me, Tabane!
This little beauty is a
fourth‐generation type IS and
Tabane the Genius created it
especially for Houki!
[Charlotte] Fourth generation?
[Cecilia] Wait! other countries
have only just made...
the prototypes of the
third generation models!
[Charlotte] Yet she's already...
Don't worry, that's just
because I'm Tabane the Genius!
Okay Houki‐pokey, let's go ahead
and start with your fitting
and personalization.
Well mount up, Shinonono.
[typing]
Now, I already have some of your
personal data uploaded
and running.
[Tabane] So, I just have
to update it with your
latest information.
Unbelievable! Her speed is
simply amazing!
Okay, the fitting
is all done now!
That was super fast!
I did great, huh?
Well, take it out for a test
run; try flying it.
It should move exactly how
you imagine it will.
Okay, I'm ready to give
it a shot.
Okay, that's really fast!
So, that's the speed of a
fourth generation model?
Trés incroyable!
[Tabane] So, Houki,
what do you think?
It moves even better than you
thought it would, doesn't it?
[Houki] Yeah, I guess.
[Tabane] Try using its swords.
The Amazuki is the one
on the right...
and the Karaware on the left.
I'll go ahead and send you
some data on the weapons'
specifications.
All right, Amazuki, go!
Holy...
That was very nicely done!
And now you can try dealing
with these next.
Good luck, sis!
[collective awe]
[Tabane] Mmhmm! Super duper!
[laughing]
It's perfect.
This IS can do anything!
[Maya] Oh, no!
Miss Orimura!
[Maya] Look at this...
It's a Level A
priority mission...
and apparently it seems the
countermeasures have already
been activated.
This test is suspended for now!
[Chifuyu] I'm afraid there's
something I'll be needing all
of you for.
Hang on, who is that strangly
dressed woman?
That's Tabane Shinonono.
[Chifuyu] Two hours ago,
the Silvario Gospel,
a third generation IS
nicknamed "the Gospel",
jointly developed by America
and Israel, went rogue.
Reports indicate that the unit
began running wild during
test maneuvers...
that were being carried out
in the seas near Hawaii.
Word has now come that it's
disappeared from the area where
it was originally observed.
What's important, is that
according to our information,
it was an unmanned unit.
Again?
As you can see, satellite
tracking now indicates that
the Gospel...
will be passing through
our airspace two kilometers
from our present coordinates.
That will occur fifty
minutes from now.
The orders that we have just
received from the Academy's
board of directors...
have made us responsible for
handling this situation.
[Chifuyu] As we speak, our
instructors are taking the
training units...
and locking down all of the air
and sea perimeters.
The rest of the action will be
handled by the students who
have personal units.
Say what?!
In other words, we are the
ones who wills top that
out‐of‐control IS.
Wait, us?!
Must everything surprise you?
Before we begin the official
mission brief, this is the time
for any questions you may have.
[Cecilia] Ma'am. I would like to
have the full specs and data on
the target IS.
Yes, that's a
reasonable request.
[Chifuyu] However, if any of
this information is leaked,
you'll be tried in a court
of inquiry...
and placed under house arrest
for a minimum of two years.
[Chifuyu] Got it?
[Cecilia] Understood,
instructor.
[Cecilia] This is a special
artillery type designed for
widespread target
annihilation...
And like my own IS, it seems
that the Gospel is capable
of all ranges of attack.
All ranges of attack
plus maneuverability, too?
That'll be tricky.
This specialized weaponry looks
rather suspicious, n'est‐ce pas?
I think that continuous defense
will be quite difficult.
This data leaves
its hand‐to‐hand
capabilities unknown.
Can't we do so some
preliminary recon?
No, that won't be possible.
The problem is that the target
is currently moving across the
ocean at supersonic speeds.
So we'll only have one chance
to intercept it.
But if they're just going to
have one chance at it,
then that means...
only a unit that has single‐shot
kill capabilities...
will have any chance
of hitting it.
Hmm... Mmhmm...
Uh, what?!
We get this thing with your
Reiraku Byakuya.
It's the only thing that could
possibly do it.
But the problem will be...
The problem is how to get
Ichika to the cooridnates.
Success will be difficult unless
he conserves all his energy
to use in the attack,
so how will we get him there?
That's difficult. He doesn't
have an IS with enough speed
to catch up to the target.
And he will also need an
ultra‐sensitive Hyper Sensor.
[Ichika] H‐Hey! Now hold on just
a minute! So, I'm the one
who's going?
[in unison] Well of course!
[Ichika] Will you stop speaking
in unison like that?!
Look, Orimura, this isn't a
training exercise: this is
real combat.
If you don't think you're up to
it yet, no one here is going to
force you to go.
Oh, I'll go.
And I'll show you that
I can do it!
[Chifuyu] All right,
that's settled.
So, at the present time,
the personal IS unit...
that's able to go the
fastest is‐
[Tabane] Hold it, hold it!
Just put this operation on
hold for a minute, okay?
Hyaa!
Chii‐chan, Chii‐chan!
Guess what?
I have an even better plan
that's in my head and now
it's printing!
[Tabane] So where's your
printer?
[Chifuyu] Will you leave?
Just listen, 'kay?
First off, it's definitely the
Akatsubaki's turn to shine!
What?
All right, Akatsubaki,
let's go.
I'm just curious, but do the
top brass know that Professor
Shinonono is here right now?
I'll inform them later.
But stopping that runaway IS
is our top priority at the
moment.
All right now, Houki!
Unfolding Armor: activate!
[Tabane] Unfolding Armor is
now standard to all fourth
generation IS models.
To put it in simple terms:
The Akatsubaki is the next
evolutionary step of the
Yukihira Nigata.
The next step?
That's right! And I used
Unfolding Armor for the
unit's entire body! Yahoo!
Still, we do have
to deal with that.
Hey, I bet things running
amok by the ocean really
remind you of that Shirokishi
Incident, huh?
The Shirokishi Incident...
[Ichika] That was Ten years
ago, just one month after
Tabane unveiled the IS,
2,341 missiles around the
world were launched at once.
All of those missles' on‐board
guidance systems were hacked
simultaneously,
and they all headed
straight toward Japan.
And a single girl piloting
a silvery IS appeared out
of nowhere.
That IS, which would come to
be known as the Shirokishi,
single‐handedly shot down
all the missiles.
And as the sun set,
it simply disappeared.
As if it had only been
an illusion...
And who was inside that
Shirokishi, huh Chii‐chan?
[Chifuyu] I have no idea.
Well! I'll bet it was someone
who has a 35 inch bust line.
That's so cruel, Chii‐chan!
You've split poor Miss Tabane's
brain right in two!
Well isn't that nice?
Now your left half will be able
to take turns...
thinking with the right half.
Good one! Yay!
You're so smart, Chii‐chan!
Let's get back on topic...
Okay super genius, how long
until adjustments to the
Akatsubaki are finished?
[Cecilia] Miss Orimura!
[Chifuyu] Yeah, what?
[Cecilia] Ma'am, I'm sure that
I could achieve the objective
in my Blue Tears!
As you know, the Gunner
Strike, my high‐maneuverability
package, is on its way here now.
And does that package operate
on molecular exchange?
[Cecilia] Well, um, no,
not yet...
By the by, I could finish
adjusting the Akatsubaki in
seven minutes, no problem.
Fine, that's it. The mission
brief is Orimura and Shinonono
will engage the Gospel.
She drives, he shoots. Let's
blow that thing away, people.
We launch in thirty minutes,
ready or not.
So don't just stand there,
get your asses moving!
[Tabane] Well, this has a nice
feeling to it!
[Houki] No! You've got
it all wrong.
Aw, now don't make such
a frowny face, baby sister.
[Tabane] Your face'll freeze
like that! Ew!
This is the face I was
born with.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Anyway, let's hurry up and
finish adjustments to
the Akatsubaki!
I've got to make this work!
I'm the only one who can do it.
Who can execute a one‐shot
kill.
My own personal IS. At last,
you're finally mine.
[girl 1] Things have gotten
pretty intense, haven't they?
[girl 2] I never
would've believed that some
out‐of‐control IS might show up!
[girl 3] I wonder if Orimura
and the others are going to
be all right?
[girl 1] Ah, jeez! If only we
had our own personal units too!
[girl 2] Yeah, then we might be
able to go give them some
support right now!
[girl 3] Well, I guess there's
no other choice. All we can
do for now is pray.
[girl 2] The next episode:
"Get Ready"
[girl 1] Please, Orimura,
you and the others make
it back safely, okay?