[♪]
[Tabane] I know that ringtone...
Hi‐hi‐hidey‐ho!
This is Tabane Shinonono,
everyone's favorite superstar!
No, no! Hold on, please!
Don't hang up on me, Houki!
Hey Sis...
[Tabane] Hey to you too,
little sis!
Yeah, yeah, I already know what
you're calling about.
You want one don't you?
Your own personal unit!
Of course I have one ready.
It's over spec,
with high‐end capabilities!
It'll stand toe‐to‐toe
with the Byaku! Mmhmm!
This IS unit is known as...
Akatsubaki!
[screaming]
Hang on...
Is it morning?
When did you get in here?!
Ah! Not looking!
Cover up! Cover up!
But I have always heard that
there aren't supposed to be...
any secrets in a
healthy marriage.
You haven't forgotten I've made
you my bride...?
Bride?! What the hell are
you talking about?
Well, in Japan,
if there's someone you like,
you're supposed to call them
"my bride" or "one's bride,"
isn't that correct?
[Ichika] Wh‐Who...
What idiot told you tha‐?!
Ow, ow, ow!
You need to spend much
more time...
practicing your
hand‐to‐hand combat!
You're so strong!
If you would like to polish
your wrestling skills,
I offer myself to be your
training partner for this.
[Ichika] What are you blushing
about that for?!
[knocking]
[Houki] It's me, Ichika.
Time to start our
morning drills!
[Houki] It may be Sunday,
but that's no reason to
slack off, so‐
[struggling]
Such indecency! Barging into a
married couple's bedroom!
[Ichika] Wait, Houki!
[Houki] Married?!
You'll die!
[screaming]
What a terrible way to start
off my day!
U‐Uh, say, why did you invite
me to come along with you today?
Well the class beach
trip's coming up,
and I was thinking you said you
didn't have a swimsuit,
so I was going to come to town
and buy some new trunks
for myself,
and I thought,
while I was at it...
While you were...
Oh yes, I figured it must be
something like that.
Did you say something, Charles?
[Charlotte] Argh!
It's "Charlotte"!
I told you to call me that when
it's just the two of us!
[Ichika] Oh, you certainly did.
Sorry, Charlotte.
Men who carelessly toy with
young girls' affections ought
to be kicked by a horse and die!
Where'd that come from?
Still, I think any guy who's
like that probably does
deserve to die.
Hang on, why are you mad at me?
Here, I‐I will forgive you if
you would just hold my hand.
I see. So, that's it? Okay.
It would be bad if we got
separated in an unfamiliar
location.
So keep a tight grip!
Idiot.
Uh oh...
A‐Are they...?
They are...
They're holding...
[Cecilia] Holding hands...
I thought I was experiencing
a waking nightmare.
But if you see it...
Then it's time to kill him!
[Laura] Uh‐huh, you have
strange past‐times.
Laura!
[Laura] Oh, you do not need to
be so guarded.
Because it is no longer my
intent to harm any of you.
And you expect us to
believe you?!
Ah, I see.
[Rin] Hey, you wait just
a minute!
[Cecilia] Exactly what are
your intentions?
[Laura] It should be obvious.
I plan on joining them.
Nothing more.
Don't you know that you should
always spy...
on a new enemy before
confronting them openly?!
That's quite correct!
Surveillance is an art form!
First we must follow
them closely,
then we can determine the exact
nature of their relationship!
Mmhmm!
I see, you have a point.
[Ichika] Say, Charlotte...
Yes? What is it?
Everyone at the academy knows
that you're a girl now,
so it'd be normal for you to
go by "Charlotte."
Maybe I should think of
something else to call you, huh?
Something that's just
between you and me?
Huh? Really?
How about "Charl"?
That's easy to say,
and sounds friendly, right?
Charl!
Yeah, I think Charl
is wonderful!
Oh, okay then.
Wow, that kind of reaction must
mean that she really does
like it. All right.
Charl... Charl!
[Charlotte] That means I must
be special to him,
n'est‐ce pas?
[Charlotte] What is it, Ichika?
[Ichika] Sorry, would you mind
going on ahead for a
little while?
I just remembered there's
something else that I need
to buy.
[Charlotte] Something else
to buy?
Yeah, kind of.
[groaning]
[Ran] Hold on tight, bro.
If you drop any of those,
it's your head!
No matter what you're saying,
you're buyin' way too much.
The last summer of middle‐school
is special!
[Ran] Pool‐use swimsuit!
Beach‐use swimsuit!
"It's on!" swimsuit!
Ultra "It's on!" swimsuit!
Mega‐ultra "It's on!" swimsuit!
You need each kind to use as
the situation calls for!
Oh, what kind of
situations are those?
Huh?
Wah!
Hey buddy, doing some shopping?
Oh, yeah.
That's quite a load
you've got there.
Are all those bags
full of swimsuits?
[Dan] Yeah, the runt here said
that she was gonna show
them all off to ya‐
What was that?
What was that? Um...
So, did you come to buy a
swimsuit, too?
[Ichika] Yeah, our school's
class beach trip is coming
up soon.
If I'd known that before, you'd
have been able to help me
with shopping!
[Ichika] What?
[Ran] Nothing at all!
Oh, that's right,
I almost forgot!
Next year, you're going
to be my upperclassman!
[Ran] Isn't it great?!
You're applying to the
IS Academy?
Mmhmm! My first choice.
So, I'll see you there, right?
Yeah, I guess so! Study hard
for your entrance exam!
Okay, I will!
Thank you very much!
Um, let's see now, where did my
brother get to? Uh...
Ichika! Come with me!
Wow, he really is useless as
an older brother.
Where's Ichika?
Huh?
[Ichika] Wait! The sign says
"No shoes!"
Now why'd you drag me in here?
Because I want to know if the
swimsuit I chose looks good.
And for that I had to
come in here with you?!
Sssh!
Now, where could they have
disappeared to?
Surely they can't have noticed
us following them!
They can't!
[clerk] Oh, and here's this
year's featured suit!
[clerk] It's called the
"Ultimate Cleavage Model."
[Laura] These are all swimsuits?
I never had any idea so many
different types existed.
[girl 1] It's so hard to
choose, isn't it?
Yeah, if you wear one that
doesn't suit you exactly,
your man will turn on you
like that!
And even if everything else
is perfect,
if your swimsuit is bad,
then that's the kiss of
death for sure!
[bang]
[Charlotte] If anyone spots us,
they will get in the way!
[Ichika] Uh, are you looking
at someone out there?
No! No, no one is there!
But you just stay in here and
I will get changed quickly.
[Charlotte] I made all this
happen, but now what am I
supposed to do?
[Ichika] What's going on?
What does Charl want to do?
I don't get this!
I don't get this at all!
[Charlotte] Oh, enough!
I'm doing it!
She's really taking her
clothes off!
No! Bad Ichika! You must not
imagine it!
Think of something else!
Uh, I know! Pi!
Pi equals 3.141592...
653589793238462643‐
Okay, I'm done.
So... bad?
Oh no! Not at all!
I think it's really great!
And I mean that!
Okay, then I'll get this one.
[clerk] Uh, excuse me Miss?
Wait a second, was that...
Aah!
O‐O‐Orimura and Dunois
changing together?!
What are you two doing?
[Maya] Now listen up!
Even though the two of
you are classmates,
certain lines have to be drawn!
Boys and girls must not enter
changing rooms together!
[Cecilia] I never thought
that the teachers would
be here at the shop.
[Rinin] Yeah, it could get
really sticky if we rushed
things now.
[ringing]
Clarissa, I need your help.
We have an emergency situation!
[Clarissa] Captain
Laura Bodewig,
are you experiencing a problem?
[Laura] Ja, it's regarding that
Ichika Orimura I mentioned to
you before.
Ah, Instructor Orimura's
younger brother.
This is the boy for whom
you have affections?
[Laura] Jawohl. He is the same
one you kindly informed me I
should refer to as my bride!
It so happens that all students
from the IS Academy are about to
take a trip to the beach.
I am unclear as to what basis
for selection is when it comes
to the correct swim attire.
Therefore, I am requesting
proper instruction.
Ja, of course. The Black Hare
Corps is here to assist you
in this matter.
Incidentally, what are you
currently equipped with?
[Laura] I have a single,
school‐issue swimsuit.
[Clarissa] What foolishness
is that?!
The IS Academy uses old‐style
school swimsuits,
and while I normally approve of
tradition, in that suit...
In that suit...?
No naughty bits will show!
That's the XO of the
Black Hare Corps for you!
[girl] Her love of Japanese
manga and anime isn't just
for show!
[Laura] So, what do I do now?
I have a trick up my sleeve...
[Maya] It's 11:00 right
now, everyone!
You're free to do what you want
until sunset, okay?
Just make sure to get back
to the guest house in time
for dinner.
You got that?
Hey, Orimu, do you want to
play volleyball with us?
It'll be fun!
Volleyball's awesome.
Sure, sound's fun!
Wow, I'm up so high!
[Rinin] I can see really far!
[Ichika] What are you doing?
Do you think you're some kind
of cat?
Oh, that looks like fun!
When you're done with her,
I wanna ride you next, okay?
And it's my turn next!
[Ichika] I'm not an observation
deck! Get off me already!
Say, what the devil
is going on here?!
I think that it's obvious.
He's my lookout tower.
Oh, Ichika! Surely you can't
have already forgotten the
promise you made to me on
the bus?
All right then Ichika,
please get on with it.
And exactly what is he supposed
to be getting on?!
As you can see, he is to rub
suntan oil on my skin.
[Cecilia] It simply wouldn't do
for a gentleman to renege on a
promise he's made to a lady,
now would it?
All right then, if I must.
Yech...
Eep!
My goodness Ichika!
Warm your hands a bit before
applying the oil!
I'm sorry, but it's my first
time doing this, you know?
You mean that I'm going to be
your first time?
Well then, it's to be expected
I suppose.
Said the hungry spider
to the fly.
[Nohohon] That looks like it
feels so good.
[girl] E‐Even my heart is
starting to pound.
[Tanimoto] Cecilia, lend me that
suntan oil when you're done
using it, okay?
You just want me to do
your back, right?
No, there are many areas that
I can't reach.
So, while I have you here, I'd
like you to cover all of them.
All of them?!
Yes, please!
My legs,
my thighs,
and my buttocks.
Hey there, I'll do that for ya!
[Rinin] Here, here, here!
[giggling]
[Cecilia] Ah! That tickles!
[Rinin] Here! I've got
you covered!
[Rinin] And you wanted some
rubbed on here, too, didn't you?
Okie‐dokie! And we'll just
grease the rest of this down
while we're at it.
And "oops", missed a place,
right here!
Dammit Rin, that is
quite enough!
[screaming]
Dammit, I didn't do anything
wrong, so why did she have
to hit me?
Ichika, let's have a race
to that buoy over there!
If you lose, you have to buy me
some shaved ice!
What?! Where do you get off‐?
Hey, hang on! That's not fair!
Okay, that was a horrible thing
I did to Cecilia,
but I need her out of the way.
I couldn't stand the thought
of losing to her or Laura!
My leg!
My leg is‐!
Rin!
[Rinin] Ichika...
This is Ichika's arm.
Thank goodness.
[Ichika] Can you breathe?
Are you okay?!
[Rinin] Yeah, I'll be fine.
That was quite
catastrophic, Rin.
I should escort you back to the
guest house straight away.
Huh? No, wait,
maybe Ichika can‐
Excuse me, Takatsuki, would you
be willing to lend a hand here?
Sure, I'm happy to help.
[bickering]
[Rinin] Ichika!
Well, if she's that energetic,
she probably is all right.
[Charlotte] Ichika, so this is
where you've been!
So uh, what's the deal with that
beach mummy?
Come on now, you can let Ichika
see your suit.
It will be all right.
[Laura] Nein! I will decide
whether or not it is all right!
Wait a second!
Is that Laura's voice?
But Laura, you have
already changed,
so now you have to show him
your new bathing suit.
No, wait! I am still not ready.
First, I must prepare myself
for this.
[Charlotte] Oh? In that case,
Ichika and I will go out to
the shore alone.
Are you okay with that?
[Laura] No! That is forbidden!
I‐If you wish to laugh,
then go ahead!
It looks perfectly fine,
don't you think, Ichika?
Yeah, you look cute.
Oh! You think I am cute?
That is the first time I have
been called that.
I thank you very much for
your input and it is
greatly appreciated.
[girl] Orimura!
[Tanimoto] You promised.
[Tanimoto] Now let's play
some beach volleyball!
[Nohohon] Yeah! It's a battle
against Orimu! Zap, bang, pow!
[Tanimoto] Here! Catch!
An even three‐against‐three.
All right, let's do it!
[girls] Do your best, Orimura!
You too, Dunois!
They call me the Summer Devil
of July. Behold my power!
[♪]
I've got it!
Nice save, Charl!
Wow!
Hiii‐ya!
I'm cute...
I can't believe he called
me cute!
[Ichika] Laura!
[Ichika] Are you okay?
[Charlotte] Can you speak?
He... said... I'm cute...
That made me feel so...
[Charlotte] Are you still
embarrassed about that?
Laura?
[screaming]
What's up with her?
Should we go after her?
Oh, I think we should probably
leave her alone.
[Maya] Oh, who brought
the volleyballs?
That looks like fun.
Would you like to come play
with us, teacher?
[Maya] Sure!
You want to give the kids a
shot, Miss Orimura?
[girls in awe]
Miss Orimura looks like
a swimsuit model.
She's so awesome!
[Tanimoto] Please go ahead,
ma'am. I'll trade places
with you.
What the hell?
Okay! Let's do it!
[Charlotte] Uh, Ichika,
I was wondering...
Could it be that Miss Orimura
is your type?
What does that mean?!
Well, your reaction just now was
certainly a lot different...
than from when you
saw our swimsuits.
Nope, nope.
That's not it at all.
Sacre bleu! So many
rivals already.
Now I have to compete with Miss
Orimura on top of all that?
[Ichika] No kidding. Chifuyu's a
major badass volleyball player.
Ichika, you've probably got
the wrong idea.
Right! Serve's up!
[♪]
[Chifuyu] So, this is where
you've been hiding.
The ocean's not going anywhere
so, can you give me
your attention?
[Houki] Yes, Miss Orimura?
[Chifuyu] You've seemed
distracted for a while now.
Do you want to talk about it?
Well it's...
[Chifuyu] Is it about Tabane?
I contacted her the other day.
It seems that she had nothing
to do with what happened with
Laura's VT System.
I see.
Tomorrow is July 7.
You're expecting that something
might show up, aren't you?
[Tanabe] Of course I have
one ready.
It's over spec,
with high‐end capabilities.
It'll stand toe‐to‐toe with
the Byaku! Mmhmm!
This IS unit is known as...
Akatsubaki.
[girl 1] Hold on! Just wait a
minute! Who the heck is that?!
[girl 2] Wearing a frilly dress
and rabbit ears...?
That certainly makes one heck
of an impression!
[girl 3] So, her coming
here means an important IS
official's arrived, right?
[girl 1] Hey, it looks like she
brought some kind of present for
Miss Shinonono!
[girl 2] Whoa! But there's no
time to be surprised about that!
Because some other unexpected
news has just come in!
[girl 3] The next episode:
"Thin Red Line"
[girl 1] Our pleasant beach
excursion is about to...
[girl 2] suddenly become
completely crazy!