[Maya] I'm about to introduce
another new addition to our
expanding classroom.
[Charles] It's nice to
meet you, Ichika.
You can call me Charles
if you like.
[Houki] You have to date me!
[Laura] I do not approve.
In fact, I will never approve
that you're her brother!
[girls] 1, 2, 1, 2...
What I'm trying to say is you
have to do it like "whoosh",
and then "clang",
and then "bang", and then‐
You understand what she's
getting at, right?
It's all about your feelings.
Huh? Why don't you understand,
you moron?
For defense, tilt your
right side forward at
a five‐degree angle.
When you maneuver around,
tilt your body backward at
a twenty‐degree angle.
[girls talking over each other]
[Ichika] Let me be honest with
all of you...
[Ichika] I don't get this!
[Houki] Why don't you get it?
[Rinin] Yeah, just pay attention
like you're supposed to!
[Cecilia] I'll explain it to you
one more time!
You tilt your body forward
five‐degrees and‐
[Charles] All right, Ichika!
I'm here as promised.
I hope you're ready for a match.
Ready to compare your
IS with mine?
Hey, Charles! Sure!
So, I guess I'll see you
guys later, all right?
[girl 1] Check it out! It looks
like Orimura and Dunois are
going to fight.
[girl 2] Wow!
[girl 3] Dunois's personal
machine is called Rafale
Revive, right?
[girl 4] It's a
second‐generation
type IS from France.
Here we go, Ichika!
Yeah! Come on!
[girls in awe]
Ichika!
Bring it!
[Charles] Basically,
the reason you cannot win...
is becase you have very little
understanding of the shooting
weapons' characteristics.
[Ichika] And since all I have to
go on is theories,
I'm screwed.
That's right, the Byakushiki...
doesn't have an equalizer,
does it?
Ah, something about there not
being a vacant bus slot?
It's only speculation,
but I would think it's using the
space for its one‐off ability.
The one‐off what?
The ability that
naturally emerges...
when the IS and its pilot are
in their best condition
at the same time.
[Charles] For the Byakushiki,
your Reiraku Byakuya may be it.
Ah ha...
Wow, you explain everything
very simply, don't you?
[Houki] Hmph! And you don't even
listen to any of my advice!
[Rinin] And after I tried
to teach you so kindly too!
[Cecilia] And what was wrong
with my very articulate
explanations?
[Ichika] The thing is,
the Reiraku Byakuya is
an insane attack...
that even consumes
the unit's shield energy.
It's the same ability that Miss
Orimura's IS was using,
n'est‐ce pas?
You are not supposed to be able
to employ the same technique...
merely because the two of you
are siblings...
[Charles] D'accord,
let's try it again, shall we?
[Ichika] Hold on, I thought
I couldn't use someone
else's equipment.
[Charles] Normally, no.
However, if the user unlocks it,
anyone can use it as long
as that person is a
registered user.
Oh.
[Ichika] Am I using the
right stance?
[Charles] Let's see...
Keep your arms close
to your side,
and your left arm goes here.
Easy, no?
Yeah...
[Rinin] Hey,
doesn't it seem like...
those two are getting along just
a little too well?
[crash]
[crash, crash, crash]
Woah...
Well?
Yeah! That was so cool!
And this! This gun of yours
is super fast!
[girl 1] Woah, check it out!
[girl 2] Hey, isn't that the
German's third‐generation?
[girl 3] I heard that it's
still in its trial period
here in this country.
Laura Bodewig!
What? Bodewig?
That representative
contender from Germany
who slapped Ichika?!
Ichika Orimura...
That's right.
[Laura] So, you also have
a personal machine.
That will make it much easier.
Now fight me!
No way.
There's no reason.
[Laura] You might not have one,
but I do.
[Ichika] It doesn't have to
be right now, does it?
The class league match
is coming up soon,
maybe then, all right?
Or not...
[Ichika] Charles!
[Charles] I can't believe she
just challenged you like that!
Of course Germans do get
hot‐and‐bothered easily!
How dare you block my way with
some pathetic second‐generation
French machine?
A machine that works much
better than your German
third‐generation type,
which currently has no prospect
for mass‐production!
[instructor] Attention:
Students on the field!
What are you doing down there?
I will allow you to escape
for the day.
Okay, what was that all about,
Ichika? Spill it!
Yes, did something happen
between you and Laura
sometime in the past?
[Charles] Um, Ichika,
are you okay?
Yeah and thanks for saving me
earlier, by the way.
I really owe you one for that.
[Charles] Well, I'm heading back
to the room now.
What? Aren't you going to take
a shower here?
[Ichika] Hey, how come you
never do that?
[Charles] Uh...
Does my being naked around
you bother you that much?
Uh, no! You being naked doesn't
bother me at all!
Oh come on, I know that it does!
Why don't we get dressed
together for a change?
No thanks, I'm fine...
We're roommates!
Don't be like that!
[screaming]
[Charles] I have to go!
[Ichika] Charles?
Huh...?
[Laura] I do not approve.
In fact, I will never approve
that you're her brother!
Please answer me, mentor!
Why are you at a place
like this?!
[Chifuyu] Don't make me say the
same thing over and over again.
I have my own role to play.
That's all you need to know.
[Laura] What kind of role could
you possibly have to play...
here in the Far East?
I'm begging you, mentor!
Please come back and teach us
in Germany once again!
You can't even exert half
of your ability at this
wretched place!
[Chifuyu] Uh huh.
[Laura] The students at this
academy do not deserve...
[Laura] to be taught by someone
of your stature!
They lack a sense of danger and
they mistaken the IS for
some kind of extravagent
fashion accessory!
I find it unbelievable that you
could even give the time of day
to these people!
I think I've heard more than
enough, little girl.
You've grown up quite a bit
since I last saw you.
But not enough to assume you're
the chosen one when you're
only fifteen.
[Laura] I was just...
[Chifuyu] I'm a busy woman and
you need to get back to your
dorm, girl.
[Chifuyu] Male student over
there, were you eavesdropping?
Or indulging in some aberrant
sexual behavior?
How can you say that, Chifuyu?
You're my sister for
cripes sake!
At school, you will call
me Miss Orimura.
Yes ma'am.
You don't have time to waste
lurking in the bushes,
you should be out
there training.
At the rate you're going, you're
going to be defeated...
in the first round of the next
month's tournament.
[Ichika] I know that.
In that case, fine.
Hey, wait a second!
I wanted to ask you something
about what Laura said to me
in class earlier...
[Ichika] She said she doesn't
approve of me being
your brother.
Was she talking about...
the way you missed out
on the chance...
to win the second championship
because of me‐
[Chifuyu] That's all in
the past, kid.
There's no need for you to
worry about it now.
Later, 'kay?
[Ichika] It was the
2nd Mondo Grosso,
the second IS world
championship...
And on the day the final
match was supposed to
take place,
someone kidnapped me.
To this day, I still have
no idea why they did it.
But I was detained
and imprisoned.
And my big sister Chifuyu
abandoned the final match in
order to come and rescue me.
So, my sister lost the
final match by default.
No one had any doubt
that she was about to
win back‐to‐back victories,
so it caused a controversy when
she pulled out of the match.
And to top it off, in order to
repay the German Army...
for helping find information
about the location where I
was being held,
Chifuyu agreed to stay there
and serve as an instructor
for the German IS unit for
over a year.
I felt as though it
was all my fault,
like I was good‐for‐nothing...
A totally pathetic excuse
for a brother.
Which is why I can't let
my big sister watch over
me anymore.
I'm back!
Are you here, Charles?
[running water]
[Ichika] Oh, that's right.
Hey, Charles, I think we're out
of body soap in there, right?
I brought you a new‐
Well uh...
I brought you the soap.
Oh yes, thank you.
[Ichika] Well, see you later.
[Charles] Uh...
[Ichika] Umm... So...
Do you want some tea?
Uh, sure, why not?
Here.
Oh, thank you.
[Charles] Ah!
[Ichika] Hey!
Oh God! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Sorry!
Ichika! Are you all right?
Let me see it.
[Charles] Oh! It turned red.
I'm so sorry!
It's okay, I'll be fine...
But the thing is...
those... they're... touching me.
You're a pervert!
[Ichika] Me? How in the hell do
you figure that?!
So, why did you pretend
to be a guy?
My family wanted me to do it.
[Ichika] Your family?
Oh, you mean your
family's corporation...
Oui, my papa is the
company's CEO.
And this whole plan was
his direct order.
[Ichika] What?
To be perfectly honest...
I am not the child of his wife.
[Charles] I was separated from
him for a very long time,
but two years ago,
he took me in.
That was right after
my mama died.
The people from the Dunois
family came to pick me up.
After various tests,
they found out that I was
exceptionally compatible
with the IS.
And though it was unofficial,
they secretly made me a test
pilot for the IS.
But I have only seen my father
twice before,
and we have only spoke
for no more than an hour.
And then Dunois
Corporation encountered
some financial difficulties.
[Ichika] Difficulties?
But I thought that they
ranked third in the world...
when it comes to
manufactuing IS units.
That is correct, but the Revive
is a second‐generation type.
[Charles] Currently, IS research
is focusing on development of
the third‐generation type.
I think the reason Miss Cecilia
and Miss Laura transferred to
this school...
was because they needed
to collect data for
that development.
The Dunois Corporation has
already begun developing
third‐generation models,
but progress has been slow.
And at this rate, their
development permit is in
danger of being withdrawn.
But what does any of that have
to do with you coming here and
pretending to be a boy?
[Charles] It's simple.
I'm merely the
advertising platform
for attracting attention.
As for this charade, it was felt
I had a better chance...
of meeting you if I pretended
to be a boy.
The hope was that I
could collect data on
your machine as well as you.
[Charles] Basically, what they
asked me to do...
was to come here and
steal your data...
by pretending that I was a boy
named Charles.
Now I feel a huge burden
has been lifted.
Thank you for listening to me.
And I am so very sorry about
lying to you all this time.
[Ichika] But you never
wanted this, right?
I mean, this entire plot.
There's no way that you did!
Uh, Ichika?
Our parents are important or we
wouldn't be here without them,
but even so...
A parent can't just use a kid
as a tool like that!
That's wrong in so many ways!
[Charles] Ichika...
[Ichika] My sister and I were
both abandoned as kids...
so I know how you feel.
The difference is that I have
no interest in ever seeing
them again.
But you do.
So, what are you going
to do now?
What am I...?
Now that you found out
I am a girl,
I am sure I will be called
back to my home country.
I don't really know
about the rest.
Sent to jail, if I'm lucky.
[Ichika] What if you just
stay here?
[Charles] What?
You'll be fine as long as
I don't say anything right?
And even if they do find out,
I'm sure your father...
or his company can't do
anything about it at this point.
It's right here in the IS
Academy Special manual...
All students of IS Academy are
under its exclusive control,
and no nation, organization or
other group can interfere with
their attendance here.
In other words, you'll be
safe for at least the
next three years...
as long as you keep
attending this school.
[Ichika] And with that
protection, you'll have
time to engineer a more
permanent solution.
I can't believe you knew that.
I mean there are fifty‐five
of those to remember.
Well, it might not seem like it,
but I do study hard!
[laughing]
[Charles] Ichika...
Thank you for covering for me.
Well, no problem.
[Ichika] Uh, your breast!
I can almost see your breast!
Oh! Uh... does it
really bother you?
Well of course they do!
Would you like to see them?
[Ichika] Say what?!
You are a pervert.
[Ichika] Me?! Who's a‐ what?!
Where the hell did that
come from?!
[Cecilia] Ichika,
are you in there?
I noticed that you haven't
had dinner yet.
Are you feeling ill?
Ichika, I'm coming in.
Oh, what are you doing
over there?
N‐Nothing, it's just
that Charles...
told me that he might be coming
down with a cold,
so I put a blanket on him.
[Cecilia] Oh really?
[fake coughing]
Dear, I'm sorry to hear that.
Would it be all right with you
if I borrowed Ichika for a bit?
[fake coughing]
[Charles] Go ahead.
Well it just so happens that I
haven't had my dinner either.
Would you care to dine with me?
Uh, sure?
[fake coughing]
[Charles] Enjoy yourselves.
[giggling]
[Cecilia] Let's be off then!
[Ichika] Hey...
What are you doing?!
We're on our way to dinner.
Just the two of us together.
[Houki] But why do you have to
have your arm through his arm...
and get so close to him
to do that?
Oh, don't you know
that a gentleman is always
expected to escort a lady?
Actually it feels more like
I'm being escorted...
Then, I'm coming along
with you two!
I didn't have enough at dinner
earlier, so I'm still hungry.
Very well, but eating like that
is sure to put even more weight
on that boyish figure of yours.
Hmph. Well that's none
of your business, is it?
[Houki] We'll have some
sword practice later.
That's a good way to burn
off calories!
[Ichika] Ugh,
more with the hitting!
Then it's settled.
Let's be off, shall we?
Miss Houki, what do you think
you're playing at here?
[Houki] You said a gentleman
is expected to escort a
lady, didn't you?
[Ichika] Hold on, you two!
It's really hard to
walk like this‐
Owww!
[Cecilia] Do you mean you don't
have anything else...
to say about this situation?
[Houki] Yes, such as how
deliriously happy you are,
you lucky dog.
[door opening and closing]
[Ichika] Hey, it's me.
I think...
Uh, welcome back.
Is there something wrong?
Don't you worry about it.
[Ichika] I brought some food
for you.
Thank you, I am hungry.
What's wrong?
[Charles] Uh well...
Oh, you can't use chopsticks?
I have been practicing,
but still...
No problem, I'll just run back
and get you a fork, okay?
Huh? No, that's okay.
You know, you're going to have
to learn how to take advantage
of your roommate's kindness a
little better.
[Ichika] What is it they say
about he who hesitates is lost?
So, you take advantage of
me this time...
And I'll take advantage of
you some other time, okay?
[Charles] Well,
all right... I...
[Ichika] Hm?
Couldn't you just feed me?
You said I could take advantage
of your kindness...
[Charles] No?
Okay! My word is my bond!
Here comes the IS...
Now say "ah"!
Aah...
[Ichika] So, do you like it?
Oh, very!
That's good to hear!
More fish coming up!
[Charles] Well, I think I want
to have some rice next.
You want rice now?
[Ichika] Here it comes!
Get ready!
Hangar open! Say "ah"!
[Charles] Aah!
[Ichika] Oh, you got some
rice on your...
[Charles] Oh! Better get it.
[Ichika] Okay, I guess I have
no choice...
[Laura] Mentor...
Your absolute and
incomparable strength...
is a goal I seek. The very
reason for my continued
existence.
And Ichika Orimura...
The person who cast a stain upon
my mentor's name...
I swear that...
I will get rid of you by any
means necessary!
[girl 1] Oh, my goodness, it
looks like there's a fight
in the arena!
[girl 2] No way!
Who's fighting?
[girl 3] It looks like one side
is the powerful duo...
of Cecilia Alcott and Rinin Fan!
[girl 1] And their opponent
is Laura Bodewig!
[girl 2] Two against one?
That sounds like too much
of a handicap!
[girl 3] Hang on, something
seems to be wrong!
[girl 1] What?!
[girl 3] The next episode,
"Blue Days ‐ Red Switch"
You don't want to miss
the true power of the
third‐generation type IS!