[Houki] But don't worry, okay?
You can always trust me to get
you where you're going.
[Ichika] I have to try!
[Houki] I'm finished as a pilot.
I quit.
[Rinen] So are you going to get
up or are you just a pathetic
coward, who can't fight when it
really counts for something?
[Houki] Because I'm not
going to lose this time!
Don't hold back! Keep firing!
[Laura] It's faster than
I expected.
I've got him!
At this rate, we'll never shoot
him down!
[Ichika] Why does this...
remind me of something I've
seen before?
They're calling.
You have to go now.
Did you get it?
No! Not yet!
[Armored Girl] Ichika, do you
desire power?
[Laura] Houki, release your
weapons and run!
Houki!
Are you all right?
Yes I am. I'm just fine.
Ichika, do you desire power?
Mien Got! It's shifted
into Secondary form!
Ichika, do you desire power?
Why do you desire power?
Uh...
I want to... protect
my friends...
I mean, my comrades, that's
what I want.
For your comrades?
[Ichika] Yes, it's like,
there's so much in this world
that you have to fight against.
Do you understand what
I'm saying?
This world is consumed with
irrational violence.
I want to fight it and to aid my
comrades in that battle as
much as I can...
That's what I need the power
for, to help them.
Yes, I see.
It's your fate, you have to go.
[Girl] Do you understand?
[Ichika] Uh‐huh.
Houki! No!
[Houki] I miss you...
I miss you, Ichika.
I miss you.
Ichika...
[Ichika] Houki...
Ichika?
Yeah, I'm sorry about the wait.
Ichika!
But your wounds!
Are you?
Oh I'm okay.
I can fight too.
Everyone tried to stop
me though.
I'm...
I'm so glad...that
you're alright.
[Ichika] Hang on, are
you crying?
No, of course I'm not crying!
Well just in case, here.
To be honest I like your normal
hairdo better than this.
[Ichika] But um, Happy birthday.
By the way.
Today is July 7th, isn't it?
I'll be back, just have faith.
Oh Ichika...
Why haven't are transmissions
gone back to normal yet?!
Because, the kids probably shut
it off themselves.
[Tanimoto] Ms. Orimura!
[Nohohon and Kanarin] Ma'am!
Just stay out!
We're busy in here!
We understand that, ma'am...
But Orimura is...
[Nohohon starts crying]
[Chifuyu] What?
That's the Byakushiki's second
form: Setsura!
Setsura, change to Shield Mode!
That's the Reiraku
Byakuya shield?
Houki!
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me!
I'm sorry.
It took some time to recover.
Right, then it's time to stage
our counterattack!
Laura! Cecilia!
Alright Ichika, let's finish
this up in short order.
We have enough energy for this.
[Charolette] So you don't worry
about us.
[Ichika] Rin! Charl!
Come on! Let's do it!
Ichika...
I want to fight along side you.
I want to have your back.
What's going on?
My energy's recharging!
This is the Kenran Buto...
So this has to be the
Akatsubaki's fourth gen's
special ability.
Right...
Let's do this, Akatsubaki!
The Byakushiki has fallen to
just ten percent.
Oh, no! My energy level!
Ichika, here take this!
[Ichika] What the hell? My
energy's been recharged!
That's right! Now go and finish
it off!
[Ichika] Right!
[Ichika] Let's go!
[Houki] Right!
[Laura] Yeah!
[Rinen] Let's do it!
[Cecilia] Roger!
Ichika, now!
Laura, now!
Jawohl!
I'm right over here you monster!
Ichika, hit it one more time!
Rin!
Please hurry Ichika!
We can't hold on!
You won't get away this time!
Is it over?
Yeah, it finally is.
[Chifuyu] Mission accomplished!
Well that's what I'd like
to say.
But the fact is you've committed
a grave offense here.
[Everyone] Yes, ma'am!
When you get home, I want you to
all write an essay on what you
did wrong.
And in the mean time I'll be
preparing some especialy
grueling training for you
as punishment.
Uh excuse me, Miss Orimura?
But shouldn't we call it a
day now?
[Yamada] I'm sure everyone is
very tired.
[Chifuyu] But inspite of
all the screw ups, you did a
good job.
And...I'm glad you all made it
back alright.
[Chifuyu] So um, take the rest
of the day off.
So um, like hey...
And just what happened
out there?
What really made the Gospel
run wild?
Is it true there was no one
inside it?
Weren't you afraid when you
were fighting? Wasn't it scary?
Come on you guys, tell us.
The teachers aren't saying
anything to anybody.
So sorry.
The officals labeled the whole
thing top secret.
No kidding, even we haven't been
told all the particulars yet.
I understand you're curious
about the situation,
but if you knew more they would
place restrictions on you
as well. Okay?
Uh, no, I don't think I'd
like that.
I wouldn't wanna be spied on
or anything.
Hold on, just where have Ichika
and Houki wandered off to?
[Tabane] The Byakushiki sure is
surprising. Isn't it?
It even has the capability
of being able to revive
its pilot.
Just like...
[Chifuyu] Just like
the Shirokishi?
Core number 001, which you
poured your blood, sweat and
tears into,
the orginal I. S. Unit.
What's up, Chii‐chan?
[Chifuyu] I'd like to speak
hypothetically.
Let's say that a certain genius
could have an I. S. planted at a
certain location on the day of a
certain boy's high‐school
entrance exam.
The genius makes sure that's
the only time this I.S.
ever moves.
That way, it would look like a
boy, who can't operater an I. S.,
actually made it move.
Then, that would have been
the only time it moved,
wouldn't it?
[Tabane] But to be honest with
you, even I don't know exactly
why the Byakushiki moves.
It's really a mystery.
[Chifuyu] Alright then.
Let's talk about
something different.
A certain genius decides she
wants to debut her precious
younger sister with a big bang.
So for her sister, she prepares
her own personal unit,
and another I. S. that may just
run amuck.
And then when an
incident occurs,
she drops her sister's new
state of the art unit into
the mix.
Quite a debut for little sis,
don't you think?
[Tabane] That really would be a
super genius, huh?
Mhm, a true super genius,
a super genius who's already
managed to hack into the
military computers of at
least twenty countries.
[Tabane] Say, Chii‐chan...
I wonder, does the world seem
like a fun place to you?
[Chifuyu] Fun? More or less
I suppose.
[Tabane] I agree.
I finally did it, I protected
my comrades.
[Houki] Ichika?
Hey Houki.
So you came down here to
swim too?
Uh‐huh, that and I wanted to
clear my head a bit.
So, um, I guess you had the
same idea.
Uh...I really wish you
wouldn't stare.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Ichika] So um...I
was wondering.
[Houki] Uh, yeah?
[Ichika] Is your hair okay?
It got kinda burned back
there, right?
[Houki] Yeah, oh it's no
big deal.
It'll grow back and as for
the ribbon...
Well, I got a new one.
I'm really glad it'll be
fine then.
And that everyone got back okay.
Even my injuries were nothing
major in the end.
But are you really okay?
I mean, I didn't think you'd be
able to recover from something
like that so easily.
Well it wasn't nearly as bad as
it looked.
So there's no need for you
to worry about it anymore, okay?
But, I do!
I do! It's my fault that you
were injured in the first place!
If you has made just one wrong
move, you might have
been killed!
So you're wrong...
don't forgive me like it's not a
big deal.
[Ichika] Okay if you feel like
that, how about some punishment?
[Houki] Punishment?
[Ichika] Yes, punishment.
Now close your eyes.
[Houki] That's fine, I
deserve it.
[Ichika] Okay, all done.
[Houki] Are you making fun
of me?
[Ichika] Hey calm down, don't
get so excited.
Don't get excited?!
How can a warrior be calm
when her pride has
just been sullied?!
[Ichika] Houki, THEY'RE
touching me!
Okay, now they're not.
But um, can I ask you how
they compair?
What?
[Houki] Look! This is what I'm
talking about.
I'm asking if you've noticed me
as someone of the opposite sex.
Uh, I suppose.
Is that so?
We noticed that the two of you
had disappeared.
That's right! What were you
doing here on the beach?
Yeah, let's kill him.
Well maybe a flesh wound!
Houki, time to leave!
[Charolette] Zut alors!
Stop dodging!
[Laura] You can't escape!
[Rinen] You're dead!
Stop running, Ichika!
[Charolette] We were worried
something had happened to you!
[Ichika] Please! Forgive me!
[Cecilia] You'll be sorry you
were transfered to this
school at all!
[Laura] You are ill‐prepared to
be my bride!
[Ichika screams]