[Chifuyu] What? Didn't expect
your lewd fifteen‐year‐old
desires to be expressed to
your teacher?
[Tabane] I have an even better
plan that's in my head, and now
it's printing!
[Chifuyu] I'm afraid there's
something I'll be needing all
of you for.
[Houki] My own personal I. S. At
last, you're finally mine.
Now, Byakushiki!
Here we go, Akatsubaki!
Okay, Houki, It's on.
You know I'd have never let a
man go before me, before this.
But I think I can make a special
excemption this time.
Especialy since we're
alone together.
[Ichika] Listen, Houki...
This isn't a practice match.
So we need to be really
extra careful about how...
You're not telling me anything I
don't know.
But don't worry, okay?
You can always trust me to get
you where you're going.
So just rest easy and let me do
the driving.
You seem to be really getting
into this.
Did a new attitude come
with the personal unit?
Oh I'm just the same as always.
But you know, you need to
remember to stay calm out there.
I know that.
[Chifuyu] Orimura, Shinonono,
do you read me?
Yes ma'am.
We read you loud and clear.
The success of this whole
mission is dependent on a
one‐shot kill.
So get in there and finish it
off as quickly as you can.
Your target the rouge
I. S. unit:
will be referred to simply as
the Gospel. Is that clear?
[Ichika] Yes ma'am!
[Houki] Understood!
Um, Miss Orimura, should I
continue to provide Ichika
with tactical support as
the situation calls for it?
If it calls for it, yes. But
don't push yourself too hard.
Remember, you have no battle
experience in the Akatsubaki.
[Chifuyu] It's a prototype
unit and an unforeseen problem
could suddenly arise.
Understood, ma'am. But I'll do
what I can, to the best of
my ability.
Does Houki sound a
little strange?
Yes, she sounded that way to
me too.
I can understand, but...
Open a private channel
to Orimura.
Right.
Ichika.
Y..Yes!
[Chifuyu] The reason I'm using
a private channel is so that,
Shinonono can't overhear our
conversation, so play dumb.
I think she's getting a little
carried away.
She's overly excited, and in
that fram of mind she could
make a fatal mistake.
Should anything happen,
lend her your support.
[Ichika] I'll keep that in mind.
You can count on me ma'am
Very well.
Switching to an
open channel.
Standing by.
Commence the operation.
Ready?
Always!
Where is all this speed
coming from?!
The Akatsubaki is amazing!
The Ignition Boost cannot
even compair to this!
Such astonishing speed...
[Houki] Establishing temporary
satellite link.
Information collation complete.
The target's current location
has been confirmed.
Ichika, are you ready to go in?
Yeah! Ready.
Ichika, I see it!
Yeah, that's the Silvario
Gospel alright.
I'm increasing speed.
Just ten seconds till we make
contact with the target.
Keep going! Don't slow
down, Houki!
It dodged it?!
Houki listen, let's try hitting
it from the left and right
at once.
I'll take right, you take left.
Understood!
Ichika, I'm going to try and cut
off its movements!
Got it!
Ichika, engage now!
Roger!
Ichika!
[Houki] What the hell are
you doing?!
You just blew our chance!
Our intelegence
was wrong,
the teachers didn't scan
the water,
there's a ship down there!
A ship?!
[Ichika] It looks like a
poaching vessel.
Are you nuts?
There's no time for that now!
They're just criminals.
Forget about them!
No I can't turn my back on them!
Idiot! You'd put protecting them
ahead of this?!
You need to get out of here!
Houki!
[Ichika] Please Houki, don't
talk like that...
That's not the Houki I know.
Don't you remember?
With great power comes
great responcibility.
That makes protecting people
like them our job.
You can' turn a blind eye
towards them.
That's really not like you
at all.
But I was just...
I...I was...
So is it out of energy as well?
I have to try!
Ichika!
NO!
[Yamada] It looks like it
stopped now.
Do you suppose weadquarters
will still want us to continue
with the operation, ma'am?
Until we receieve the order to
stand down, we have no choice.
But how?
And with what means ma'am?
[Charl] Excuse me.
Who is it?
[Charl] It's Dunois.
You're on standby!
You're not allowed to enter!
We have to obey the order of
our superior.
But...I am certain that she is
as worried about Ichika as
we are.
She's his sister!
And he still hasn't regained
conciousness yet.
She did order Ichika's treatment
but she still hasn't gone over
to check up on him...
Alright, what should we do?
Well Ms. Orimora hasn't gone to
speak Houki yet either.
I understand that the mission
was a failure, but isn't that
being rather insensitive
towards her?
Right now, she is concentrating
on tracking the Gospel.
The instucter is simply doing
what she knows must be done.
However it must be difficult for
her too.
That's the reason she has
locked herself into the
operation center.
She is worried about him,
but would visiting Ichika do
anything to help destroy
the Gospel?
A much more pressing
problem is...
[Chifuyu] This mission was a
complete failure!
If there are any changes to the
situation, I will convene
a meeting.
And until I do, consider
yourselves all on standby!
I...
[Ichika] No! I can't turn my
back on them!
Idiot! You'd put protecting them
ahead of this?
Don't talk like that. That's not
the Houki I know.
You can't turn a blind eye
towards them.
Remember with great power comes
great responcibility.
No! That's not it!
I haven't become blind.
You say that those guys
are simply "weak"?
And that they need to
be protected?
They break the law and
hurt others.
How is it you're able to
forgive them?
Is that your strength?
It is isn't it?
That's what makes you
so different.
And compared to you, I'm...
All this time I've
talked of strength,
but have I just been using that
to vent my inner rage?
In your eyes, that poaching
vessel and I deserved to be
protected equally.
But I...
[knock on the door]
[Yamada] Shinonono...
You really ought to get some
rest as well, you know.
It wont help anything if you
push yourself too hard and get
sick because,
everyone will worry about you.
[Houki] But I want to be here.
[Yamada] That won't do.
Please go get some rest now.
That was a direct order from
Miss Orimura.
Understood?
Miss Shinonono...
[Houki] Understood.
[Bully 1] Hey, tomboy, how come
you don't have your wooden sword
with you today, huh?
[Young Ichika] Shut up you guys!
You loud mouths need to quit
goofing off!
Help out or go home! Okay?
What's the deal, Orimura?
[Bully 2] You mean you like
this tomboy?
[Bully 3] Yeah! Don't you know?
They're, like, married.
[Bully 1] I know!
Hey I'll bet you guys have been
all lovey‐dovey with eachother
since this morning.
Haven't you Orimura? OoooOou.
That's right!
The other day, she had a
friggin' ribbon on,
how dumb a tomboy
wearing a ribbon.
What a laugh. Ha!
[Young Houki] You're an idiot,
aren't you?
[Young Ichika] Huh? Why would
you say that?
[Young Houki] Don't you under‐
stand that doing something like
that will cause you problems
later on?
[Young Ichika] I don't think
about it.
I just smack down bad guys.
Look, don't worry about
those losers.
That ribbon you were wearing
looked good on you.
I think you should wear
it again.
Well forget it! I'm not ever
taking any orders from anyone!
[Young Ichika] Well, I
better be going.
See you, Shinonono.
[Young Houki] Hey Wait!
Just so you know,
my name is Houki.
Remember that!.
Because here at this dojo, my
mom, dad and my sister,
are all Shinonono,
and it's confusing.
So just call be by my
first name.
If you wanna.
[Young Ichika] Well okay:
Ichika.
[Young Houkia] Uh what?
Oh, that's my name.
There's another Orimura too,
so you just call me
Ichika. Alright?
[Rinen] There you are!
Pathetic. You're so predictable.
Running off, assuming what
happend was your fault.
That's what you've been thinking
isn't it?
So, enjoying your little self
pity party for one?
Well too bad! Cause it's over!
[Rinen] Now listen here! You've
got a job to do and we need you!
So stop sulking and get back
to work!
I'm finished as a pilot...
I quite.
Stop being such a spoiled brat!
We don't have time for you to
play these games!
Not when you just got your own
custom made personal I. S.
So are you going to get up or
are you just a pathetic coward,
who can't fight when it really
counts for something?
[Houki] What else should I do?
It's not like we know where the
enemy is!
But when the time comes I swear
that I will fight!
Okay she's got her fire
back now.
[Rinen] Told ya! It takes a pain
in the ass to handle one.
What's going on?
All of us feel the same way
about this.
We can't let this end with us
losing, can we?
[Rinen] Laura, have your friends
found the Gospel?
[Laura] I have the confirmation.
The target has been confirmed
30 kilometers from here, in the
air and also offshore.
The unit is currently in
stealth mode, but it does
not seem to have any kind
of optical camouflage.
We were able to locate its
position via satellite.
That's the German Army's
Special Forces for you!
Those girls kick ass.
And what is everyone
else's status?
Are the rest you ready to
do this?
Of course. The Shenlong's
offensive specialization
package has been installed.
And I'm ready to keep the
British end up.
Preparations are complete on
my end.
I can go anytime.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean by "Go"?
Isn't that against
direct orders?
So what?
You just said you'd fight when
the time came, right?
Yeah, what will you do?
I...
I will...
fight.
I'll fight and win!
Because I'm not going to lose
this time!
That's right, and this time,
we're going to nail that thing
for sure!
First shot is a hit!
Ma'am, that was...
I saw...
But that's against orders!
We have to call them back!
[Chifuyu] I always suspected I
it would come to this in
the end.
[Cecilia] At last the final
battle is now at hand.
And I can hardly wait!
[Rinen] It got us good last
time, but the counterattack
has begun!
This time we'll avenge Ichika!
[Charl] And we cannot drop our
guard for a moment.
We still do not know the full
extent of the enemy's power.
[Laura] But we must put a stop
to this, no matter what takes.
Let us show it how strong
we are!
The next episode, "Your Name Is"
Ichika, please allow me to
protect you this time.