This just keeps getting worse!
[NARRATOR]
The year is 2016.
The world faces its end
and the only person who seems
to notice is homely high
school klutz, Minoa Asagaya,
seen here being
slapped in the face.
Her friends are the
rich otaku, Alice Kamiigusa.
The glasses girl character,
Miko Koenji.
Club president and
cosplayer, Erica Aoyama.
And the guy who thinks
he has evil eye powers,
Kai Musashisakai.
Unfortunately, they've all
been swallowed up by anime.
Minoa's friendship with Aurora
Nakano also came crashing down
when she discovered that
he was a cowardly traitor.
Aurora revealed one
shocking truth after another,
making the show very meta.
For starters, reality and the
Anime World exist in parallel.
Also, apparently
the anime club room
was the site of
the first anime studio
and that's why it has
a magic door in it.
Aurora himself is from the Anime
World and is also super evil.
Minoa had to scream about it.
"You suck, Aurora"!
Is that what's happening?
Well, thanks a bunch.
What about me?
I'm a part of this
story, too, y'know!
Hey, don't call me Aurora,
whoever you are!
And c'mon!
Did you have to diss me
so hard in my character intro?
[NARRATOR]
Minoa complained pointlessly
about my highly
accurate assessment,
but her words fell on deaf ears.
Ah?!
Okay, you jerk.
[NARRATOR] The mysterious
man with the magic beret
sought to rewrite reality
during his dramatic
appearance last episode.
Unfortunately, it turns out
that he was a talentless hack,
unfit to wield such
mighty hat power.
Rejected by both
anime and reality,
he was killed
unceremoniously offscreen.
[MISTER KITTY]
Death by narrator!
[AURORA]
No!
But, you promised me,
you bastard!
Did you make some
kind of deal with that guy?
Once he was the director, he
said he would change my name.
Maybe he did!
Before the universe
erased him from existence!
Yeah!
I bet it's just fine!
Tell me my name!
Aurora.
It's not fair!
Where's the beret?
I'll fix this!
[MINOA] I still don't
understand, Mister Kitty.
Anime's something
that people create, isn't it?
[AURORA] Oh, you'd like to
believe that, wouldn't you?
But the truth is,
we've always existed!
The anime you make
merely depicts us.
An ignorant portrayal of
a world beyond your grasp!
As anime has slowly
spread into this world,
I've seen it happen with myself.
I'm always the same character,
but the depiction of me
changes to match the times.
[AURORA]
Soon, you'll become anime, too.
But none of that matters to me,
I just want someone
to change my name!
[KAI, MIKO]
Aurora.
[AURORA]
Stop! Stop harmonizing it!
You can't even sing!
I hate you!
[MINOA shrieks]
Huh?
[ALICE]
Minoa.
Is something wrong?
You're spacing out.
I, uh...
[ALICE]
Did You watch Ancient Bride ?
Last night's episode
was simply lovely!
I was stunned!
The art is beautiful!
[ALICE] I love how the
eyes shimmer on closeups!
I wish mine did that!
[MIKO]
Those are nice,
but I'd rather have
their hair gradients!
I'm so jealous!
[YUI]
No kidding, right?
That studio is great!
They really know
how to bring out
the best in characters,
don't they?
Seems normal enough!
I guess it was just a bad dream!
[YUI]
Totally.
[MIKO] I have some
new script ideas, too.
I can't wait!
Taking charge again, I see.
Don't worry,
you're going to love it.
Aw, yeah!
[MINOA screams]
[coughs]
[MINOA]
What the heck was that?
An explosion?
[TORU] Oh, you have
got to be kidding me.
[ALICE]
Looks like the Robotics Club
botched their weapon test again.
That's the second
time this week.
The second time?
It's nothing to worry about.
[ERICA]
Minoacchi.
That's some face!
What are you staring at?
Perhaps the land of phantoms
is reaching out to her.
Hey, Alice.
Call Sebasu for me.
Call Sebasu?
What for?
Just do it!
Take that mask off!
[MIKO sighs]
Sloppy.
Mon peti coeur.
So that means
I wasn't dreaming after all.
I was sure we had you
for a second there.
Oh well.
Minoa, why are you running away?
We just want to be
friends again, I promise!
Don't forget!
Club meeting at lunch!
[MINOA pants]
[MAYA] So, Dad,
your pick for this season
is the new YoYoYo series?
[MINOA]
Why are they home?
[SHUGO]
Absolutely.
If you count
returning series, too,
then my favorite is August
Comes in Like a Reindeer .
[SHUGO]
Uh, I'm looking for something
a little less depressing.
Papipupepopip seems promising.
[MAYA]
It got delayed.
[SHUGO]
No way!
[AI]
Well, hi!
Welcome home!
Hey, Mom.
Does Dad have the day off?
He's back early.
[AI] I keep forgetting
you don't have club practice.
There were no afternoon
classes today, either.
I walked straight out
of the office!
What's your favorite show
this season, Mom?
[AI] Oh, probably A Little
Sister's the Last Thing I Need .
Miyako's so adorable!
I love her!
Excellent taste
as always, my love!
[AI]
Oh, you!
I'm here.
Can you not see me?
[MAYA] Mom, I'm having
some friends over.
Can they sleep in
the empty room upstairs?
[AI] They can't just
stay in your room?
[MAYA]
Well, it's three people.
[SHUGO] Just don't
touch my figures, okay?
[MUSHROOM]
Submit to anime.
Give it up!
[gsaps]
Let anime consume you.
It'll be fun!
Your friends are doing it!
[MINOA]
Am I really the last one?
What's the point
in fighting anymore?
The world has already
been swallowed up.
It's not like I'll become some
kind of zombie or anything.
You won't be lonely anymore.
[MINOA]
You think it's better that way?
Then why do you look so sad?
[ALICE]
Hurry up, will you?
[ERICA]
Become one with her.
Open the door to our world
and leave it all behind.
[MIKO] Your friends know
what's best for you, Minoa.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Huh?
I thought Alice and Miko
would be hard to talk to,
but once we bonded over anime,
we were friends in no time.
We made even more friends
after we started the anime club.
Erica, Musashisakai,
even Aurora, and Mister Kitty.
Sharing anime with
them made me so happy.
I know.
I don't want to lose them.
Then we should
become anime, too.
It's not right.
That hurt!
[SHUGO laughs]
Now you're getting it, Maya!
Ha! Told ya!
[SHUGO] Want to go to
the next event as a family?
[MAYA]
Ew, gross.
[SHUGO]
Is your dad not cool enough?
[MAYA]
Nope.
[SHUGO]
Awww...
[MINOA gasps]
Huh?! What the heck?
Oh, hey.
Got time for a little cat chat?
You bet I do!
Meow-meow-meow.
Meow.
[MISTER KITTY] All right, if
you're ready, then let's run!
Meow-kay!
[MISTER KITTY]
You've rejected anime,
so anime is rejecting you.
So, what does that mean?
It means you're going to
be wiped out of existence.
Surely there's some way
to get things back to normal!
[MISTER KITTY] If we get
that beret, we're good.
And don't call me Shirley
What's the deal
with that anyway?
You never told me.
It links your world here
to the Anime World.
And right now, it can
reshape the both of 'em.
[AURORA]
I found it!
Finally!
Yes.
Ha! I can change my name!
We'll take the hat to
the border between worlds.
Then we'll toss it back to
the Anime World and we're done!
Or that's my guess at least.
So where is the border?
Are you dense or what?
The door in the club room!
I think I follow,
but how did all of this
happen in the first place?
[MISTER KITTY]
Pretty simple, really.
Like so.
Then all of this's
your fault, you big dummy!
Heh heh heh!
I can't believe you!
But it's your fault too.
I mean, even if I don't
technically belong
in the real world,
things were just dandy
until Aurora tricked
you into opening that door.
Oh my gosh, you are not going
to pin this whole thing on me!
[AURORA]
Hmph!
What the?
What's that ahead?
[MISTER KITTY]
The mid-episode eyecatch.
Oh no!
We survived it somehow.
Sorry.
Forgot those were a thing.
Is that snow?
It's pieces of reality
the beret's throwing away.
It's making the world
a blank slate.
[MINOA]
What does that mean?
[MISTER KITTY]
It's erasing your world.
You didn't tell me
the world was gonna die!
[MINOA]
Welp, that's it.
I'm finished.
It was such a short life.
What a pity.
Whoa. Whoa. Wait!
What is this, a recap ep?
C'mon, this is
the dramatic finale,
there's no time
for that nonsense!
You're the only person
that can protect this world
and its memories!
What d'you mean memories?
[MISTER KITTY]
If this world disappears,
then your friends and all
their memories will be caput!
Capicè?
I'll protect them!
Whatever it takes!
That's the spirit, kid!
[MINOA]
Nice paw pads.
Ha! You don't
gotta tell me, babe.
Chicks always dig 'em.
Better hurry!
It's catching up quick!
[MINOA]
It's all going white!
I said it's erasing
the world, didn't I?
And there's no one out
there who can help us?
Sure there is.
[GIRL laughs]
Hi Minoa.
You're from
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi !
But how do you know my name?
The robot, too?
Wicked!
You cherished their show.
Anime never forgets that.
You have a bond of love
that will persevere
till the end of time!
Come on!
You gotta work!
Please!
The world needs me!
I didn't notice you there!
I'm getting kinda nervous.
It's like we were holding hands.
This isn't a romance.
Just pull the throttle, kid.
Yeah, okay!
I got it!
Now let's go!
Listen to my song!
Knock 'em dead!
This is my Eternal Symphony!
Well, crap, we're stuck.
Not a chance!
'Cause my drill
will pierce the heavens!
Outta my way!
Meow!
[MINOA]
Katharsis!
We did it!
Huh?
Where did the school go?
Why'd everything get so quiet?
Wasn't this supposed
to be the climax?
This is what happens
when you go against the world.
You get erased.
No way.
[AURORA]
Mikene!
[MINOA]
Aurora?
Mikene!
Hey, Mikene!
Mikene, Aurora's
calling for you!
You're Mikene, you idiot!
Have you lost your mind?
I'm Minoa!
[MISTER KITTY]
Oh, this is bad.
We're back to
the planning stage.
[MINOA] Why does everyone
have such stupid names?
I got the beret, but I still
can't change the world.
The hat doesn't work if
an anime character wears it.
[AURORA] Then you
put it on Mikene, please!
It's Minoa.
[AURORA] This hat can
rewrite the universe!
It's a symbol of absolute power!
Absolute authority!
[MINOA]
You're wrong.
The man who wore this beret
never wanted anything like that.
This is a symbol of dreams,
inspiration, and passion!
It's the bridge between
the Anime World and reality!
Okay, fine!
So use it to fix my name, okay?
Ugh... Has he got
tunnel vision or what?
I need to get to the door.
Open the way.
Huh?
[gasps]
Don't do this.
You're making a big mistake.
[MINOA] If I don't do something,
we're all gonna disappear!
You're just being
stubborn, Minoa.
[ERICA]
We don't need reality.
We have anime.
[KAI] Leave your flesh behind
and join us in glorious 2D.
Your war on anime is over.
I'm sorry, you've got it wrong.
I love anime!
I learned so much and had
so much fun talking to you guys
in the clubroom.
Anime made us all friends!
Alice, even though we
hardly knew each other,
you opened your heart to me.
You were so kind
and enthusiastic,
I never would've gotten
into anime without you.
Miko, you never gave up,
no matter how many times
we asked you to
rewrite your script.
I learned how much passion
it takes to make anime.
Erica, you showed me how
anime brings people together.
How to enjoy it as a community
full of wonderful people.
And the club would've died
for sure without Kaikai.
I'll never forget the
speech you made.
It touched my heart.
[KAI]
It's Kai.
Y'get it?
I love you guys!
And I love anime, because
it brought us all together!
It's wonderful!
But not this.
Our world, and everything
in it is fading away.
This anime is garbage!
I hate it!
Minoa.
Huh? Hold on!
Alice, no!
[AURORA]
Oh!
The world is dead.
My name will disappear!
It's not over, Aurora.
Don't call me that, okay?
No matter what.
I'll always think of you
as one of my friends.
Even if you do bad things,
you're still the one who
taught me to keep fighting.
So, thank you for that.
I admired you.
And you were right.
I should never give up!
It's gone.
I'm too late.
[gasps]
Alice!
Just get up here!
[MINOA]
You came back for me?
Of course.
There's still anime we need to
watch and talk about together.
Oh, Alice.
[ALICE]
Nice speech, by the way.
I'm flattered you
think so highly of me.
For a mere mortal, you're
quite impressive, yourself.
We're all lucky to have you.
We're here.
We have our club.
The world ending isn't that bad.
Maybe!
But if I can get this
beret through that door,
I might be able to save it.
The question is "how"?
Oh, no way!
[ALL]
Robo Alice?
Haha! It sensed your distress
and came from a distant
dimension to aid us!
[MIKO] The artwork still
looks pretty shoddy, though.
[ERICA] Maybe, but I wouldn't
have it any other way!
Are you ready?
Let's go!
[ROBO ALICE]
Alpha!
Alpha! Alpha! Alpha! Alpha!
[ROBO ALICE]
I require more money.
Should've expected that.
Alice, stop!
You can't solve every little
problem with your checkbook!
We're sort of trapped in a void.
What else do we have?
Our burning hearts!
Let's set them free!
Every good robot
has a rocket punch!
Now it's time to let it, fly!
Let's get to that door
while it's still unlocked!
[MINOA]
Huh?
Mister Kitty.
[MISTER KITTY] You're goin'
back where you belong,
you hat bastard!
[MINOA]
You're leaving, Aurora?
I hate that name,
but I'm stuck with it.
Even though I became a villain,
you still said
I was your friend.
Maybe next time, my character
will turn out nicer.
We'll keep this naughty beret
where it belongs from now on.
See you in the funny papers!
Hold on!
You can't go!
Not like this!
Don't worry.
You'll do great, kid.
Who knows.
Maybe I'll pop in again someday.
Aurora, wait!
Auroracchi!
Aurora, no!
[AURORA sighs]
I told you not to
call me that, didn't I?
I almost forgot, Minoa!
Change my name, hurry!
Huh?! Oh, I dunno.
Uhh...
Uh, Grovelboy!
What the hell?
Kitty!
So have you picked out
a club this year, or what?
Uh... Not yet.
This season.
I'm totally into
Hero School and Ru: Zero .
Oh, and the protagonist
in Shikabari is a real dear!
Oh, and the Time Travel
Shounen OP is so cool!
Like when Jun does
that stylish fence jump!
I don't get any of that,
but I'm glad you're happy!
[MINOA] This season is nothing
but shounen fight stuff, though.
Do you like anime?
Yeah!
Like, crazy about it!
Oh my gosh, me too!
That's so cool!
Any show by Ogikubo is
my absolute favorite!
You've got good taste.
I approve.
[TSUBAKI]
What's all this squealing about?
[MINOA] Sorry, I got
a little carried away.
[TSUBAKI]
If you like anime so much,
why don't you join
the anime club?
Huh?
We have one?
Tell the president
that Tsubaki sent you.
They're a little odd, but I
think you'll get along fine.
Why do you always
walk off without me?
Best of luck.
[ALICE]
This is it.
Uhm.
Hello?
[MINOA]
Uh. I can't see.
Miko?
We've been waiting for you.
Why didn't you say something
to me, you big dork?
Ah-ha!
Some fresh blood!
Welcome to our
humble anime club!
Mikocchi, can you do this
part of the script over again?
But I've already re-written it!
You're gonna slay this,
Miko Baby!
Oh.
Is that a character
for the short?
Maybe.
He's a stylish,
dancing, idol otaku!
And he's from another world.
[MINOA]
Huh?
What's in there?
Well, see for yourself!
Awesome!
It's a mountain of treasure!
What?
We're seriously doing this?
We have a heartwarming
finale and instead of
ending on that note,
we're doing sexy Santa now?
Well, whatever.
So long and merry Christmas!
Also, have a happy new year
and whatever the hell
comes after that!
[ALL]
Meow.