The characters
in Dub Tone are so cute!
Oh, I can't even
pick a favorite!
Erica told me to check out
Sweetness and Champion ,
which was also like
super adorable!
Then Miko had
me watch Ange Visual ,
which had cute girls
and a cool story!
You're all about anime
these days, aren't you?
You gonna be marathoning these
shows over the break, too?
You better believe I am!
Not so fast.
We've got a big event coming
right around the corner.
Huh?
[MIKO] Not "a" big event.
The big event.
Yes, it won't be long.
You're scaring me, guys.
Huh?
[YUI groans]
Dang it.
Now, let's talk summer plans.
And by that, I mean our
pilgrimage to "you know where."
To attend "you know what."
The big "you know what"
by the sea.
The dark ritual.
The festival of desire
where greed runs wild!
Sorry.
I'm lost here.
Can someone explain this
to-- Whoa, what is this?
[MIKO]
A catalogue for the event.
All of your answers are here.
I'm not supposed to read this
whole ginormous thing, am I?
Examining it from cover-to-cover
is a rite of passage
for all anime fans.
Uh, that's not
even remotely true.
Just reading the bookmarked
sections should be adequate.
If you have any questions,
feel free to give me a call.
I'm an expert on the subject.
"Notes on entering the event.
Wait in the entry line
until the venue is open.
It is recommended that you take
the earliest train available,
as lines will form
in the morning."
[knock, knock]
Yeah?
Hey, Mii.
Thought you might be hungry.
Wait, you're not
studying, are you?
Uh... Kind of?
It's complicated.
Oh, while you're here,
do you know if we
have any folding chairs?
Like, you would use
at a picnic or something?
[MINOA]
Yeah.
Our club needs them.
Are you guys going
on a camping trip?
Uh.
The big "you know what"
by the sea.
[MINOA]
It's a seaside event.
Ah-ha!
So, like a fair on the beach?
Must be in Odaiba, then.
[MINOA]
Uh, something like that.
Anyway, there's gonna
be a ton of people there.
Huh!
I didn't think the anime club
would be into stuff like that!
[MINOA]
It's a pretty big event.
The lines are long,
so we might want to sit down.
Sounds like a good call.
I think we've got one chair
downstairs, let me go grab it.
That sounds great!
Thank you!
What's that?
Going camping?
Actually,
Mii's going to some
festival thing in Odaiba
with her new anime buddies.
I see!
She's having so much fun
with her new friends!
Isn't that nice?
[yawns]
You're up awfully early.
I have to take the first train,
or I won't make it on time.
Oh, hey.
Did Dad go somewhere?
Yeah.
He's got some seaside party
going on today too.
Huh... Well, whatever.
See ya!
You have a safe trip!
Nobody is awake yet.
It's weirding me out.
Wassup?
[MINOA]
Mister Kitty!
Don't freak me out like that!
Weirdo!
[MISTER KITTY]
You headed to the big event?
Yep!
Then lemme give
you one piece of advice.
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention:
Train arriving for
Ikebukuro on track one.
When you're at war, if you let
your guard down, you're dead.
Remember that.
It's an anime con,
not a war, Mister Kitty.
I surrender!
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Uhm.
Coming through.
Sorry, 'scuse me.
Sorry.
Right here, Minoa!
I thought I was gonna die!
I forgot to tell you
the train is a war zone!
Congratulations on
making it out here alive!
Don't let your guard down.
That was only the first round!
It's calling me!
The sweet siren song of
anime merch beckons me
to its inner lair!
Can you take it down
a notch or maybe ten?
We'd better get in line.
Did you bring a sports
drink like I told you to, Minoa?
Yeah.
No heatstroke for me.
It's right here.
I don't think that's
going to cut it.
[MINOA]
Huh?
The sun is a deadly adversary,
I hope you know!
[MINOA]
Huh?!
Maybe grab another drink
before we get stuck in line.
[MINOA] Lemme run to
the convenience store!
I'll hurry!
I'm worried about her.
I should probably go.
I can't even reach the shelves.
What am I gonna do?
Just follow the line,
it'll work out.
Miko.
[ALICE] Prepare yourself,
convention center,
for I have arrived!
Really fired up, huh?
I can't blame you,
but don't wear yourself
out before it starts.
Of course not!
I'm just trying to get
everyone else excited!
Is it working?
[MINOA]
Mm-hmm.
[ERICA chuckles]
Okay, let's move.
[MINOA]
Huh?
But isn't the building that way?
[ERICA]
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We have to make it
through the line first.
[MINOA]
Huh?!
Minoa.
[MINOA]
Huh?
Did I doze off?
Didn't get much
sleep last night?
Usually, the only reason
to get up this early during
summer break is to watch
Sunday morning shows.
Like which ones?
He means the kid's anime
and tokusatsu block
that airs on Sunday.
Oh! That's when PreFae comes on!
Unlike late night anime,
the Sunday morning shows
have wide audience appeal.
They're for children,
families, and fans of all ages.
Speaking of appeal, the rider
and ranger tokusatsu shows
may be live action,
but they set my heart on fire!
Those shows were
created by a manga artist,
but they're still not anime.
You shouldn't expect
anything too mature.
But even if the shows
are mostly aimed at kids,
there's plenty of things anime
fans can enjoy about them!
Even if it's just a
story about friendship,
once you get
into the characters,
it can move you to tears!
Ooh, and I love when
they have handsome villains
you can feel sorry
for in the end!
I always tune in to
watch the dance sequences
they have during
the PreFae credits.
They use choreographers
from real idol groups for those!
Ahh, I knew PreFae was cool,
but maybe I should
get into it more!
It has great fight
scenes sometimes too.
[KAI]
Indeed! You know,
some famous animators got their
start working on that series.
You like anything with good
fight scenes, huh, Kaikai?
It's Kai!
[MALE STAFF]
Thank you all for coming today.
We'll start moving
the line soon.
Does anyone need
to go to the bathroom?
Not really. I'm fine for now.
You should go before
you really have to.
[ERICA] That's a rookie
mistake, Alicecchi.
I should try to set
a better example.
You're right.
Well, guess
I'd better go for safety.
I didn't notice the
bathrooms; where are they?
Over there.
And that is the line.
Huh?! There's even a
line for the bathrooms?!
It's big business here.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, that's obvious, right?
[chuckles]
Okay, it's potty time, Minoa!
Did I miss something?
Hey, I'm back!
Hope we didn't take too long.
We're lost, aren't we?
This is bad.
No, nothing to worry about.
Sebasu!
[MALE STAFF]
Hey buddy, no sliding!
Not happening.
Well, Alice, got a Plan B?
Nan dao nimi lule ma?
Huh?
[MINOA]
Who the heck is that?
You know her, Minoa?
Uh-uh.
[MINOA]
She sure is pretty, though.
Cute dress.
[MINOA]
Nevermind!
I need to say something!
But what language was that?
Not English or French,
I don't think.
Help!
Uhm, German? Guten Strudel!
You want strudel?
Sorry, I don't have any.
Oh, you can speak our language?
What a relief!
Yes! Let's go!
Huh? Wait a second!
What is happening?
Where are you taking me?
I need to find my friends!
Hey! Am I being abducted?
[ERICA]
Minoacchi! Alicecchi!
Over here!
Huh?
Hey!
Hold me!
Is there some joke
that I'm missing here?
These two were very
sad looking for you guys.
[ERICA]
I see. They got lost.
Thanks for bringing back
our missing children.
[ALICE]
Sorry, but who are you?
[MIKO] She was waiting
in line behind us.
I need to go to the bathroom,
could you please hold my spot?
[ERICA]
Mm-hmm. Of course.
[BABY] When I was coming back,
I ran into you,
and I think that's
the whole story.
It all makes sense.
I'm sorry if I was rude.
Not rude at all!
I just wanted to help,
but maybe I acted weird.
I don't get it.
Alicecchi,
you've been here before.
How did you get lost?
It's all my fault!
I lied.
I've actually never been
to the convention before.
I guess I just wanted
to look smart or something.
I'm a phony.
It's not that big
of a deal, really!
I agree.
In fact, I think you two would
have gotten lost either way.
That's just uncalled for.
[MIKO]
But it's my fault, too.
I should've gone with you.
Miko.
[BABY]
Hey.
First timers!
It's my first time, too!
Wow, really?
It's true!
We had some trouble,
but we all overcame it together!
We should not let our first time
here be spoiled by a bad memory!
Don't you think?
Yeah, you're right.
It's an anime festival!
We should have fun
together, shouldn't we?
You said it.
Thanks for that.
Oh, it's my pleasure!
I'm surprised you
remembered Minoa's face,
since we didn't
even talk to you.
Not so much face, more
the button she has on her shirt.
Oh, this?
I love Ru: Zero . It's popular
in Beijing like Japan!
People in Beijing watch it, too?
[MINOA, ALICE]
Beijing?
That's right! She came
here all the way from China!
My name is Baby Yang.
And I'm Minoa Asagaya.
Nihao!
Alice Kamiigusa.
Would you believe she's in
Japan, just for the convention?
[MINOA]
That's amazing.
I didn't know people
came from overseas, too!
It's the biggest otaku event
in the world, after all!
I just had to come!
I couldn't resist!
Whoa, hold up, Ru: Zero was
just on TV over here, though.
How did you get it
in Beijing so quickly?
There's no delay now!
[ALL]
Ohhh...
Wow, that's really handy.
It used to be 6 months after the
DVD release for foreign markets.
Now it's at the same time.
It's funny.
People get confused.
[ERICA]
Confused?
[BABY]
When I say I like anime,
Japanese fans always
ask me about old shows.
Those are okay, I guess, but I
want to talk about the new ones!
They're trying to be nice,
but it's backfiring.
Where do you get news
about new anime?
Online, usually.
I guess that's how everyone
does it these days!
I always read what
Japanese fans say.
It turns out you like the
exact same shows as I do!
How can you read what they post?
Wait, you're talking
to us like normal.
That's a dumb question.
It's fine.
I know it seems strange.
Learning a language
just because of anime.
In America, I met fans
who did the same thing.
Just not as well.
Awesome, it's like
the power of anime
can bring everyone
in the world together!
Yep.
It may sound cheesy,
but the proof is right here.
Hey, Baby.
If you'd like, we could
check out the con together.
Yes, of course!
Thanks!
I'm so happy!
Now we just have to
wait for the thing to start!
It's getting so hot.
We were spared
the sun's wrath before,
since we got here so early.
The humidity is awful too.
Baby, are you
hanging in there or--
[gasps]
Ooh, this is cold!
We don't have cooling pads
like this in Beijing,
so I had to try one!
[ALICE] It's funny that you're
more prepared than us.
Well, at least we don't have
to stand right in the sun.
Like him.
[MINOA]
Kaikai! Oh no!
We're just fine,
but he's cooking alive?
I refuse to submit!
Helios, I shall defy thee!
A line logistics issue.
[aaplause]
Okay.
Now we're getting
things started!
We did all that clapping,
but we've still been
waiting half an hour.
We've probably got
another hour to go.
[MINOA, ALICE]
Another hour?
I'm sick of the outdoors!
No offense,
but your body heat is not
what I need right now.
Just try to be patient, okay?
Nope.
Too late, I'm dead.
[MALE STAFF]
All right, people.
The light at the end
of the tunnel is near,
so don't you go
and die now,
or else you might
restart back at home!
What's up?
Is he a comedian or something?
Well, they do this every time.
Fans seem to love it.
[MALE STAFF] Be sure to stay
hydrated so you don't collapse!
Aquina isn't here to save
you with her water magic!
That goes for all you
Aquina cosplayers as well!
The staff are all
anime fans too.
The jokes are bad,
but I'm not hot anymore!
[chuckles]
[ALICE]
The time has come, Minoa.
[MINOA] Mm-hmm.
It was a long journey.
[ALICE] But at the end
of our harrowing ordeal,
we have arrived at the
gates of paradise itself.
It's a whole
new world before us.
[MINOA]
Alice, what is this feeling?
My heart's pounding so fast!
[ALICE] Mine is too,
but don't be afraid.
We'll take the
first steps together!
Are you ready?
[MINOA]
Yes. Take my hand!
[FEMALE STAFF A]
I know you're having
a special moment right now,
but please enter single file.
We finally made it in!
Exhausting, huh?
If it's cool with you guys,
let's split up for now.
Now to release the
chains of frugality
that bind my
immortal golden wallet!
With this legendary relic.
I shall hunt down all the
Shikabari merchandise
in these halls!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Hmm.
[MINOA]
Look at all the people!
Have you seen any
Ru: Zero stuff anywhere?
[FEMALE STAFF B]
Fliers.
Huh?
Check out our booth, you guys!
Oh! Thank you!
I got bags. Here.
Oh, that's so cute!
I didn't know they
would give us free stuff!
Neither did I, but this
is the best thing ever!
It's a new show
starting this fall!
Some paper fans?
Take one, they're free!
Would anyone like a bag?
So, heavy!
I know!
My poor shoulders!
Everyone hands out stuff.
You can't possibly take it all.
A little late to say that now!
I got one!
I'm so glad they
didn't sell out of these!
It's just a keychain,
you shouldn't stress out.
Oh yeah?
Then why did you
dive across the table,
shoving money in their face
like your life depended on it?
I'm glad we all
got what we wanted!
I know!
We should all take
a photo together!
Oh! Good idea!
You ready?
Come closer!
Here!
Miko, you too!
I'm taking it now!
Say cheese!
[ERICA]
Hey, Saori.
What's up?
Wow, looking good!
I don't think I've met her.
Is she a friend
from college, or what?
Oh, no, not that.
She's one of my
old cosplay buddies.
A fresh, young high school girl!
Don't be gross.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mutsuki.
Like the shirt says,
I'm from the Jouhoku
High School Anime Club.
I'm Erica.
I guess I'm the president of the
anime club at Sakaneko High.
Sakaneko High School?
Oh, I've heard of your club!
You guys are a big deal, huh?
Uh, sorry, is that wrong?
A graduate from Sakaneko
told me your club was amazing,
but maybe he was
playing a joke on me.
I dunno.
Uh-huh...
[MINOA] I need a break
from all those people!
Jeez!
[MIKO]
That's no surprise.
There's almost
200 thousand after all.
[ALICE]
It keeps getting bigger!
[MINOA]
That's crazy!
[BABY] Last time, it was 600
thousand over three days.
[MIKO]
See? Baby read the catalogue.
When you look at it that way,
we're lucky the lines
aren't even worse!
You line up to come inside,
only to wait in more lines.
You get up early just
to suffer all day long.
But it makes me happy!
The suffering?
It's not suffering if
you share it with friends!
I'm here with my
new friends in anime.
I'll wait in any line for that!
The hot sun and the long waiting
will become good memories!
Even your getting lost
helped you find a new
friendship, right?
I guess you're right.
I'm glad we got lost
and ran into you!
I'm glad too!
Good!
[ERICA] Sweet. Looks
like everybody's arrived.
You ready to take off?
What about the guys?
Don't tell me they left already?
Oh, I'll send a message on
Line and tell them we're going.
Baby, are you staying
or leaving?
I'll stay.
I enjoy watching
all the other fans.
It feels nice just to be here.
That's cool.
Bye Minoa, Alice, Miko, Erica.
Thank you for today!
No need to thank us,
I'm glad we met!
Bye, Baby!
Good day to you!
Ah! Should've gotten
her contact info!
I didn't think of that!
We really messed up.
I was so excited
to make a new friend.
It's not fair.
Anime brought you together.
And if it can do it once,
I'm sure it can do it again.
You're right.
[ERICA] We've got one
more important thing to do
on the way back.
[MIKO]
Oh yeah. That.
[ALICE, MINOA]
Wait, what?
This is cool!
[MINOA]
Baby was right.
Even the lines and the sun
feel like good memories now.
We oughta come back every
year now, don't'cha think?
Yeah! 'Course we do!
I didn't see
Musashisakai all day.
Do you know what he's doing?
Huh? Sorry Miko,
I can't hear you!
Meeting once on
the battlefield is chance.
Twice is destiny.
Next episode,
someone is shrouded in light.
If you wanna know who,
then watch the damn show,
why don't ya?