Rise, robot!
Huh?
This is the part
where you stand up!
You're a rather
stubborn one, aren't you?
Sebasu!
Better!
Much better!
[ALICE laughs]
Uh, uh?!
Now, up!
[MINOA]
Huh?!
[ALICE]
Well? Which anime is it?
Do you remember now?
Come on!
Pull it together, already!
[MINOA shrieks]
[tumbling sound]
[MINOA groans]
These anime dreams
are getting kinda weird.
[MAYA]
Mii, is everything okay?
[MINOA]
Huh?
What on earth was with
all the screaming in here?
Did you fall out
of bed or something?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Just a bad dream.
Did you sleep?
You look so tired
Where'd you get all
those DVDs? School?
Yeah, I brought
them from school.
You could say they're
part of my homework.
[ALICE]
Never fear.
I shall lend you a small
selection of beginners titles
from my humble library.
[sighs]
Mii, you're up awfully
early for a change!
[MINOA]
Yeah, I have club work.
Really?
You joined a club
without even telling me?
That's awesome!
What's the club?
It's the anime club.
[AI]
That's unexpected.
[MINOA]
Yeah.
But, wait.
You don't even
watch anime, do you?
Well, not much.
[YUI]
Minoa!
I called yesterday,
but you didn't answer.
You did? Ah!
This what you're
lookin' for kiddo?
Sorry, some crazy stuff was
going down and things got messy.
Long as you're okay!
No big deal!
Uh, lovely morning,
huh, Kamiigusa?
[ALICE]
That it is.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Uh, hi!
[ALICE]
Good day to you.
Uh, morning, Kamiigusa.
Good morning.
[MALE STUDENT B]
She said, "Good morning"!
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Like a poor person!
[MINOA]
You made these?
[ALICE] How else are we
supposed to find new recruits?
Right, new recruits.
One sec I'll--
Sebasu!
[MINOA]
Huh?
Ah?! What? What? What?
[ALICE] Come on, chop, chop!
Get those clothes off!
[MINOA]
What're you doing?
[ALICE]
Now, don't be shy!
I can assure you it's all in
the name of productivity!
[YUI]
What?!
[MINOA]
What is this for, exactly?
I did research on
recruitment strategies.
It turns out that bunny girls
are the way to go!
You could ask first!
[ALICE]
Less crying, more recruiting!
The school anime club
is back in action
and looking for new members!
C'mon.
You too!
Uh, the anime club...
[ALICE]
You'll have to be louder.
But, my clothes.
Minoa, are you okay?
Pardon me, but don't you have
track practice to attend to?
Uh! Yeah. I do.
Yui!
Good luck, pal.
[MINOA]
Don't leave me!
Now, shall we try again?
You like anime?
Come join our club!
[MINOA]
Well, I'm already here, I guess.
Hey! Anyone like anime?
[ALICE]
Come join our club!
[MINOA]
Here! Please! Take a flier!
You know any anime fans?
[MINOA]
Uh, join the anime club!
Pretty please?
[ALICE]
Like anime?
[MINOA]
Here, take a flier.
[MALE STUDENT C]
Weirdoes.
[ALICE]
Sign-ups start at lunch break.
Please stop by!
[MINOA] Anime club,
looking for recruits!
[ALICE]
Please take a flier!
[MINOA] Sign up today
at lunch or after school!
Do you like anime?
H-Hi, you like anime?
[ALICE]
Come check out our club!
Sign-ups start
today during lunch!
We'll need someone on
staff to supervise the club.
You mean like a teacher
who's really into anime?
No way.
I'd much rather have
someone who doesn't care,
so they'll stay out
of our business.
It's kind of late
in the semester.
I imagine everyone
is too busy by now.
I suppose they would
have to be terribly bored.
[MASATO]
Man, I am bored.
Just crackin my arm.
Crackin my arm.
Cracky crack crack.
An anime club, huh?
You're our only hope.
You got a room?
[MINOA] Yes, at the
far end of the third floor.
[MASATO]
The far end, you say?
Okay.
You can go ahead and
put my name down then.
[MINOA, ALICE]
Thank you, sir.
I'm not gonna, like,
do anything, though.
I'm a very busy man, you see.
Uh-huh.
I hope lots of people come!
I'd love to find more people
as passionate as
you are about anime
Hey, did you watch
Thousand last night?
Huh? It comes
on at like, midnight.
I'll catch it on stream later.
Unacceptable! No matter how
you may "tire, face" anime
in real time or not at all!
Huh? Tire face?
[ALICE]
Are you even listening to me?
Uhm, can you explain, please?
What if you ran into
spoilers on the internet
before you could
watch the episode?
Everything would be ruined!
For an anime club member,
that would be a shame
that could never be erased!
I... I didn't know!
Don't you dare miss
Gaka Stray Dogs tomorrow.
Is there something wrong?
Koenji?
Wait, what?
You're joining the club?
Cool!
Indeed.
But... I-I thought you
were more into literature,
since you're always
reading those books
with the long titles.
Sure you're not
too fancy for this?
These days,
light novels are infamous
for having excessively long,
complicated titles.
Light what?
They're short novels.
Often fantasies
or school dramas.
They're usually
targeted at teenagers,
but they have a broad audience.
They tend to have
cute artwork, as well
Sold Out Online was a big one.
The Melancholy
of Happy Vuvuzela .
They often become anime
and make a stir every season.
A stir, huh?
[ALICE] Is that
what you're into, Koenji?
[MIKO] Indeed, I try to
watch all the adaptations.
[ALICE] That includes
Ru: Zero , I presume?
Yes. It's quite good.
[MINOA]
Um...
Team Am? Or Emily?
I don't have a team.
I think they're all adorable.
Except "Peekle Juice," but of
course, he's still my favorite.
You have sophisticated tastes!
My brain is trembling!
It's nice. Am's voice
actress really fit my image.
All of this stuff
makes sense to them!
I always saw you
reading light novels,
but I never said anything.
I should've talked to
you about anime sooner.
[MINOA] You read those
complicated-title books, too?
If the anime is good enough,
I might be inspired
to take a look at the
original afterwards.
[MINOA] You don't ever
read the novels first?
[ALICE]
No, why?
Whenever a light novel I really
like gets an adaptation,
seeing all my favorite scenes
animated is the best part.
Seems like that would make
the anime boring, though.
The story would
already be spoiled.
If that's how you feel,
then does that mean
you never watch your favorite
shows a second time?
Of course, not.
I watch them plenty of times.
You notice little plot
details you missed,
or you can focus on
the animation and music
and things like that.
You watch the same
show more than once?
And you don't?
I don't know. Okay. So, uh...
I should definitely try reading
the light novels first then?
Well, if there's an
anime adaptation,
you might as well
start out with that.
You don't understand at all.
[gasps]
[MINOA]
Whoa!
Let's calm down!
[ERICA]
'Sup guys.
I'm Erica Aoyama,
Class 3-B, here to join.
[MINOA]
A senior?
Nice!
We're all freshmen.
So, I was worried we wouldn't
have any upperclassmen join.
Let me just say,
your bunny girl outfits
this morning were on point.
That's very kind of you.
On the upside, I'm glad all
that embarrassment paid off!
I'm sorry I ever doubted you!
It's fine.
I'm so glad you
showed up too, Koenji!
Sure.
[MINOA] So why don't we have
Aoyama be the club president,
since she's the oldest?
[ALICE]
Is that fine with you, Aoyama?
Call me Erica.
Erica it is then.
You wanna be our club president?
No problem.
I can totally do "president."
"Fall before my
beautiful technique!"
Stuff like that?
"Don't let your guard down,
or I'll steal your heart."
Now, that's what
I'm talking about!
Yeah? That was really good?
I, uh...
Gonna pawn off all the hard work
on your upperclassmen, huh?
"I see right through you."
[ALICE laughs]
I love it!
Okay?
Whatever. Works for me.
Oh my gosh, thanks!
That's four.
Just two more.
I have someone in mind already.
You'll get it as soon
as you meet him.
Danger approaches.
Danger approaches. Hyah!
[ERICA]
Kaikai.
[KAI]
Hmm?
Huh? It's the weird book guy!
You got a sec to talk?
Certainly not!
Can you not sense the
arcane energy accosting us?
He's putting up a barrier.
For real?
That's Kaikai from Class 2-B.
[KAI]
My true name is...
...Musashisakai kai!
So, you done with the barrier?
You're gonna join
the anime club, right?
Anime club?
It takes tremendous power
to penetrate my barrier.
[chuckles]
A mighty wind is beckoning
me to be by your side!
So, on Old Game your
favorite character is Run?
And on Gaka Stray Dogs ,
you like Picasso and Dali?
[ALICE]
They're moe.
I see. You watch
for the characters.
Kaikai here's into
mech battle anime.
[ERICA]
Mikocchi's into light novels.
[MIKO] Gekisen Garumu was
a particular favorite of mine.
[ERICA]
Minoacchi.
Uh-huh?
Are you okay?
You keeping up with us?
Heh heh... Actually,
I hardly understand anything.
You guys are awesome, though!
Why did you enter our domain?
Just a burning curiosity?
I'm having a great time!
I mean, I'm confused,
but it feels like I'm stepping
into this amazing new world!
[KAI] The gate you've opened
does not easily close.
So, hey, what's with the cat?
[MINOA]
Good question.
I found him in the closet
and he keeps hanging around.
[KAI] Rather ugly
for a mascot character.
Well... Lunch is ending.
Let's meet again
after school, team.
[ALICE]
Very well then.
[MISTER KITTY]
Yo.
Hey, something up?
[MISTER KITTY]
You're a real fish out of water.
Am I?
You don't know jack
about anime, do you, kid?
Nuh-uh. Sorry.
[MISTER KITTY] Hmm...
I think we can work it out.
Huh?
Sit back and learn.
If they're talking about anime,
don't change the subject.
Just listen and
pick up what you can.
Okay! That sounds
like solid advice to me!
So, do you have
a name, little kitty?
That's a tough question.
I've gone by many.
In that case,
can I just call you Whiskers?
That's a little on the nose.
Well, how about Michael, then?
Cheese? Or Baron? Or Tom, maybe?
Oh, Dorae--
[MISTER KITTY]
Don't say it!
Fine. How 'bout Mister Kitty?
Works for me.
A little basic, but good!
Oh, by the way,
did you take something
out of that room?
The storage closet, I mean.
Huh?
Don't think so.
Not that I remember.
[MISTER KITTY]
I see.
Then close the door!
If you're staying here, you
need to make me two promises.
First don't tell your little
friends that I can talk.
Second, keep the door closed!
'Kay.
[ANNOUNCER] The choir
will be meeting at 4:00 today
to discuss the
upcoming competition.
So, Koenji,
have you always been
into light novels, or what?
I've liked reading
since I was little.
And anime?
[MIKO] I got hooked
on adaptations
of my favorite books.
Oh, I get it now!
That's so cool!
It's cool?
[MINOA]
Yeah! You have this, like,
love and devotion to something!
[MIKO] I like books because
I can enjoy them on my own.
Huh?
I don't do well in
most social situations.
Like you saw, when it
comes to something I love,
I tend to be a bit sensitive.
I can be a real pain.
I'm sorry.
No way!
You're just enthusiastic!
We'll have to take a club trip
and check out
the anime hot spots.
Our holy grounds?
Tama, Tachikawa,
and Hachioji for sure.
Kawagoe and
Kawasaki will be mandatory.
I insist on Oarai.
All of those are close.
Why don't we all go to Nagano
for a ski trip or something?
Never mind.
We'll have to go to all
of the big events together!
Next year's Anime Jipang is one!
Anihaku and Anisute for sure.
And Comiboot, please.
What if we did a tour
of local school festivals?
I guess not.
[MINOA]
Wow, I really don't fit in.
It's fine, Asagaya.
Just keep watching anime
and you'll catch up
to us soon enough!
There's kind of a lot to cover.
I can give it my best, though.
[chuckles]
What makes a "classic" anime?
Huh?
What defines a classic?
It has to be fun, right?
Good answer!
Yet "fun" is a nebulous concept.
It differs from viewer
to viewer and era to era.
Do you follow?
That makes sense.
But... there are
certain features
that automatically make
an anime a classic.
Like what?
[ALICE] An anime with running
during the end credits
is a classic.
Wait, it has to be
the ending, though?
If there's a badass older dude,
then it's a classic.
For real?
[KAI] If the supposed main
character dies in episode three,
it's a classic.
That's awfully
early in the series!
[ERICA] An anime with "God"
in the title is a classic.
[MINOA] Does it receive
some kind of blessing, then?
An anime with a
baseball game is a classic!
But other sports are no good?
An anime where the hero's mech
is mass-produced is a classic.
Now I just feel like
you're talking to me in code.
If anybody pukes,
then it's a classic.
Puke?
--[ERICA] Good one!
--[ALICE] Perfect!
This season's puke anime
is Ru: Zero . Classic.
Is that deep or just gross?
I'm frustrated, though.
This week's episode didn't
make a whole lot of sense to me.
[MINOA] Anime confuses
you sometimes too?
[MIKO] It's because you
haven't read the original.
That episode skipped over a
key scene from the light novel
and just moved on.
It would have taken
too long to depict
and it's not directly related
to the rest of the episode,
so maybe that's why it got cut?
It's a shame, though.
The audience is missing out
on the true meaning
of that plotline.
That's why it's always
better to read the novel.
The anime should
stand on its own merits.
[MIKO]
It's not even their story.
That is just rude.
What's wrong with
praising the original
when the anime is flawed?
Guys, don't get angry!
[ALICE] People who haven't
read the books are fans, too
Don't act like
you're better than us.
[MIKO]
I never implied that!
I'm not judging you for
how you enjoy the series,
but the anime still
made a mistake.
If they mismanaged
the source material,
that's worth
complaining about.
It's not fair to
the original creator.
As a fan, you should care.
"As a fan"?
It's okay! Stop fighting!
This is good!
You have people
to talk to about anime!
Have fun!
Ugh! How am
I supposed to have fun
if the only thing she wants
to talk about is the book?
Buzz off and read on your own!
Don't scare her away when we're
one member short of a club.
Better to have no club at all
than one that
can't even get along.
[MIKO]
I agree.
Koenji, no!
As you said, maybe
I should read on my own.
We won't even make
it to an episode three.
Why can't this work?
Good day to you.
[MINOA]
I hate this.
I'm sorry.
I think you're making a mistake.
I don't make mistakes.
And you, too.
You're both in the wrong.
I don't know much about anime
or light novels or whatever.
But still...
I can tell how important
your hobby is to you.
When I saw your eyes light up,
talking about anime,
I wanted to help
you find friends
you could share that with!
I know you're only mad 'cause
anime means so much to you,
and that's great.
Koenji's the same way.
You just like different stuff!
Or the same stuff actually,
just in different ways.
But the point is
you're both really passionate
about something
and that's wonderful!
I have an older sister I end up
fighting with all the time.
We're nothing like one another.
Sometimes I even wonder
if one of us was adopted.
Anyway, she's into lacrosse
like you guys are into anime,
and when she's playing,
I think she's super cool.
And ever since I was little,
whenever I found something
I was into, she'd cheer me on.
So, I think whatever it is,
it's really special to find
something you love!
And it's even more special to
find people to share it with!
If you love anime that much,
don't fight over it!
You'll make anime cry!
I'm sorry.
I don't even know
what I'm saying.
[AURORA]
I like your song.
It set my heart aflutter.
You certainly have passion.
I'm sure you can apply
it to anime someday.
What the heck?
You think I have passion?
I'm embarrassed,
but that's quite flattering.
So how many
members have you got?
[ERICA]
Five.
Just one more.
Well, you're looking
at number six right now!
Is that weird?
You mean you
don't know who he is?
Nakano's practically
a celebrity!
Even the senior girls
are totally into him.
He is hot.
I still don't remember
him at all, though.
You're so rude!
A handsome prince saves the day
and you can't even be impressed!
[laughs]
[KAI snickers]
She's never even heard of you.
Why that must be quite
the blow to your ego, Aurora.
Hey, Kaikai.
Musashisakai.
Kai!
[MINOA]
So, you like anime, Nakano?
Heh!
Is that a Dub Tone T-shirt?
This guy is hard core.
Trust me.
That's it.
We have enough members now.
That is, assuming
that you still want to stay.
[MIKO]
I'll stick around,
but only because Nakano
made the club official.
So sassy!
You sure showed me!
Kamiigusa, just shut up.
Nope. Now, just Alice.
Oh, Miko and Alice!
[ALICE, MIKO] That doesn't
mean you can say it.
Huh? I'm sorry!
[laughs]
You're such cute little kittens.
Kittens?
[AURORA]
Yep.
Sweet little kittens.
But why kittens?
Is this an anime thing?
You're just kittens.
Does it have to make sense?
Well, that nonsense aside...
The anime club
is prepared for action.
All right!
Hello.
New recruits?
[AYAME]
Effective immediately.
Your little anime club
is henceforth prohibited
from using this room.
How'd you know?
We haven't even
registered the club yet,
have we?
[MISTER KITTY] Any anime
with a cat is a classic, too.
Don't forget it.
Next time, the anime
club has just started,
but they've already hit a twist,
that is to say a snag,
that is to say a sort
of "hitch in the get up,"
that is to sa--