[MINOA]
Morning.
[yawns]
You're up awfully early today.
I dunno why,
but I couldn't sleep.
[SHUGO]
Sweetie, look!
You're not gonna believe this.
[AI] That's right
after we got married!
I found it when I was cleaning
out the downstairs office.
[AI]
I look so young!
Wow, I was pretty cute, huh?
And, you've gotten
cuter every single day.
Huh? Would you stop it?
[SHUGO laughs]
Every moment we spend together
is like a dream come true!
[AI]
Aww, Shugo.
[SHUGO]
Ai.
[AI]
Shugo.
[SHUGO]
Ai!
[AI]
Shugo!
[SHUGO]
Ai!
[AI]
Okay, stop.
Ahhh! I slept in late!
Hey, wait a second.
Do you--?
Sorry, no time, Mii.
[MINOA]
Uh! Huh?
You're late?
But I thought you quit
the lacrosse club.
Yeah, I did, but I've got
a yearbook committee meeting.
[MAYA]
Catch you later!
Huh?!
You quit your club?
[MAYA]
Hmm?
[gasps]
[SHUGO]
Minoa? Is there something wrong?
[MINOA]
Did you see her face?
It was weird!
You... Huh? Huh?!
[BOY C]
Hey, toots!
Stop it!
Jeez!
Yui-miliating!
[ALICE]
Their faces changed?
Yeah, but it lasted
only a few seconds.
Can you elaborate?
They changed in what way?
It was like...
Like, anime in the 90s
with these weird flat faces.
You might be getting too
stressed out for your own good.
[MINOA]
Huh?
I can hardly blame you,
we've been through a lot lately.
You guys gotta believe me!
I'm sure I--
[MINOA]
Huh?!
[YUI]
Morning!
[MINOA]
Yui!
Good!
Look at their faces!
What's wrong?
They're all so weird!
[MIKO, ALICE]
Wow. Rude.
What d'you mean?
[MINOA]
Their cheeks!
And their weird pointy chins!
Uhm...
[MIKO] First period
is art class, remember?
Let's go.
[YUI]
C'mon, cheer up!
Huh?! Whoa, whoa,
what the heck is going on?
Huh?!
Eh?!
What now?
You okay?
[YUI]
Minoa?
It's the void!
It was right here!
Some big, empty, black hole!
An endless darkness!
An all-consuming void,
like a portal to hell,
ready to swallow me up!
You've got to pull
yourself together!
I'm afraid I don't
see any dark void.
[MINOA]
It was real!
You walk over here and then.
Huh?
Hold on.
Uhm.
That's weird!
Did you eat something strange?
If you're on drugs, Minoa,
I think you should tell us.
Maybe you should
go to the nurse.
[MINOA]
Huh!? No, it's real!
I nearly fell right in!
Hey! Ahh...!
[yawns]
[YUI]
I'm so hungry!
So, Minoa.
What's your plan?
Boxed lunch?
Or school food?
The cafeteria is
serving chicken katsu.
Oooh, then I might
have to go for that!
We're having a club meeting
during lunch, okay?
[MINOA]
Nothing's okay!
Huh?
We just got here
a second ago, right?
No way, nuh-huh!
That is not how time works.
You can't just skip around to
get through the boring parts!
You should calm your
nerves with some tea.
One moment. Sebasu!
Now that's not right.
The usual.
As you command.
I live to serve you.
[MINOA]
And she talks!
S'il vous plaît.
Splendid. You may
excuse yourself.
With moves like that, you'd
be perfect on the track team.
Come see me after school.
[ALICE]
Here you go.
[YUI]
Those are so cute!
Do you mind if I borrow one?
Please, help yourself.
Sparklies, yay!
Me too! They're
lovely, aren't they?
[TORU]
Am I irresistible or what?
How did you--?
This is wrong.
[ALICE]
Indeed.
Upon closer inspection,
you're right.
I see now.
Then you believe me?
It's plain as day.
This was clearly
supposed to be Earl Grey tea,
but it's hojicha.
[MINOA] That's what
you have a problem with?
[ERICA] We still need to choose
a president for next year.
[MINOA] We've got bigger
problems right now!
[ERICA]
Seriously?
Don't tell me the school
has another issue with us.
That's not what
I'm talking about!
Never mind our club,
the whole world's upside down!
What do you mean?
She's been like this all day,
talking about crazy stuff.
Crazy?
Everything's perfectly normal.
[MINOA]
That's not normal!
You mean you're seeing things
that other people can't see?
Acquired the power of
my Evil Eye, have you?
[MINOA]
I'm serious!
Everything's changed!
You haven't noticed?
It's news to me.
Huh, maybe so.
[MIKO]
Now that you mention it,
things do feel
a bit "different."
It could be a new
production team, right?
Wait, what're you talking about?
Can't be.
It's way too late for that.
Did Tahiro run away?
He's just doing
series composition.
It's not like
anyone would miss him.
"Tahiro"?
Who the heck is that?
We can't be certain
until we confirm it.
[ERICA] Want to watch
the opening again, then?
Yeah, ok.
We are not on the same page.
I'm gonna rewind.
[MINOA]
Huh?
What the heck is going--
Jeez!
Yui-miliating!
[ERICA]
It's still him!
[MINOA]
Huh?
Why is everyone okay with this?
All of you are acting
like it's normal!
You shouldn't
derail the narrative.
If we betray the audience's
expectations too much,
we might get canceled.
[ALICE]
But it's too late in the season!
You think this is too different
from what we've been doing?
What's our genre?
It's not slice of life.
It was slice of life, but it's
turning into something else now.
Should we try to increase our
appeal to moe or otome fans?
It's hard to tell what's genre
and what's subversion
of genre these days.
At the very least,
let's decide if this is a gag
show or a realistic one.
[MISTER KITTY]
Mm-hmm!
Let's explode.
Do what?
Get your safety
goggles on, everyone.
Okay.
Now it's a gag show.
I'm blind!
My eyes!
And now this show's realistic.
Huh, but we're still alive?
So it's not that realistic.
Shall we make
it extra real, then?
Let's try.
After this, I get sushi.
[MINOA]
Mister Kitty!
That's real.
Super real.
Intense, huh?
Hardcore.
Mister Kitty, no!
What have you done?
That was a cat-tastrophe
Are you gonna be okay?
[MISTER KITTY]
Yesh, I ain't dead, am I?
Hey, Minoa.
You're not going home yet?
I wanted to talk to Mister Kitty
some more, that's all.
I see.
I was worried since you were
having such a tough time today.
I hope you feel better.
Uh... Yeah, thanks.
[MINOA] The whole world
is completely bonkers,
and they think
I'm the weird one.
Sure.
Catch you later.
[MINOA]
Hey, Aurora?
Aurora?
Nakano?
That's me.
Uh, well, I, uh...
You said you had
five siblings, right?
I was just wondering.
Do you have a brother that's
a whole bunch older than you?
Like maybe.
Twenty years or so?
Not that I know of!
Why d'you ask?
[MINOA]
Nuh-uh.
Forget I said anything.
Sorry.
See ya!
[MISTER KITTY] What's this
brother stuff all about?
It's nothing.
[exhales]
Hey, I'm back!
[FAMILY]
Welcome home.
[MAYA] It was raining
out there, wasn't it?
Are you okay?
[AI]
You're home awfully late.
[SHUGO]
Sorry, we already watched
today's episode
of Tennen Maid .
[MAYA]
Earth to Mii.
Uh, yeah, I hear you.
Okay, nothing creepy.
You're acting weird.
Maybe you just need to eat.
Oh yeah.
We watched
Molly the Witch , too.
Hope you're not mad.
Oh, please, no!
I'll get started cooking dinner.
I can lend a hand.
Let me help, too.
Aw, thanks!
Let's have a
race to the kitchen!
[MAYA, SHUGO]
Ha HA!
[SHUGO]
Looks good.
Take this.
[AI]
Of course!
[voices murmuring]
[ERICA]
This is bad!
What's happening?
[MIKO] A Gigamanchinju
showed up nearby.
Gigamanchinju?
It's headed for
the school as we speak.
[KAI]
Worry not!
I've got you covered.
My barrier's impenetrable.
[MINOA] I guess Kaikai hasn't
changed much, has he?
That's strangely reassuring.
Musashisakai.
Kai, okay?
C'mon!
Guren Shoot!
That's the fifth goal
he's burned down.
It's wrong.
Why don't any of you have
a problem with this?
The world's messed up!
This isn't an anime!
"This isn't an anime," she says.
What's there to complain about?
You've been acting
strange lately.
Anime is life and life is anime,
exactly how it should be.
If you've been possessed by
evil, then I will purify you!
You guys have got to wake up!
Anime's anime, it's not reality!
Don't act like I'm crazy!
Are you rejecting anime?
Huh?
[ALICE]
What a terrifying child!
I thought you
loved the anime club
more than anyone, but now this?
You traitor!
You're missing the point!
[ALICE]
What a terrifying child!
[MINOA]
Alice!
If you can't embrace the world
of anime in its every form,
then you're not
a true fan at all.
You've disappointed
me greatly, Minoa.
We're done with you.
Aren't we friends?
[MINOA] Why is it
sunset all of a sudden?!
This is stupid!
You've disappointed
me greatly, Minoa.
We're done with you.
[voices crying for help]
[MINOA]
Huh? Oh no.
The voices. They're back.
Go away!
What's with the screaming?
Hey, I'm here.
[MINOA] Is there
something wrong with me?
I don't know
what's real anymore!
Please!
Tell me I'm okay!
Just tell me I'm not crazy!
[MAYA]
It's okay.
Of course you're not crazy.
[MAYA] Hang on just
a little bit longer.
There's only one
episode left, after all.
[MINOA]
Stupid freakin' thing.
Huh?
[MINOA]
Morning.
[MIKO]
Good morning.
[MINOA]
Morning, Yui.
[YUI]
Hey.
It's crazy,
but ever since I got here,
I feel like the whole
school's been staring at me.
What do you expect?
Huh?
After all, you said
you hated anime, didn't you?
I did not!
That's ridiculous!
Good day to you.
Let's talk.
Aurora.
[AURORA] Could you, uh,
not call me that, please?
You're right.
Our world has
definitely changed.
[MINOA]
You believe me?
[AURORA]
I do.
Though I wonder if
I would have noticed
if you hadn't mentioned it.
I'm so glad.
No one else cared,
so I started to think that
I was the crazy one.
There must be
a cause for all of this.
Like what?
Like some sort of catalyst
that could make
the impossible, possible.
You know of anything
that sticks out?
Before the world changed, right?
This is all your fault!
'Scuse me?
[MINOA] I should have known
a talking cat wasn't normal!
And it took you this long
to come to that conclusion?
You showed up the second
I opened that weird door.
I remember.
That is correct, yes.
I never thought to question
why that room was off-limits.
And now, everyone else is
talking to you like it's normal
and reality is falling
apart more every day.
You're behind
all of this, admit it!
Right?
I mean he's gotta be.
It's time. We're going to
get to the bottom of this.
Uh... Uh, no! No, wait!
[AURORA laughs]
Huh?
It's gone.
[GUY] I summon the Black Eyes
Red Blue Yellow Golden Dragon!
Attack!
[GIRL]
Kick it into turbo!
[ALICE, MIKO] Essa essa, hoisa
hoisa, essa essa, hoisa hoisa.
[MINOA]
Alice!
Miko!
What is it?
[MINOA gasps]
[shrieks]
It's all anime now.
Even me.
The shackles have been broken.
What d'you mean?
With the Observer absent,
chaos will reign.
Order will be destroyed.
Oh no.
Did you betray us again?
Who are ya?
Huh, punk?
You from the other side?
[AURORA laughs]
That's right.
I'm from the anime side.
Same side as you, kitty.
You're from the anime side, too?
[MISTER KITTY]
You're asking a talking cat?
Soon, this world won't exist.
It will be engulfed in anime!
What does that mean?
So who do you work for?
[AURORA]
See for yourself.
It's a new world.
A big bang!
[shrieks]
[laughter]
Everyone.
Huh?
Take a peek at the truth.
I was thinking, this episode?
No anime talk.
Which is funny, 'cause Anime-
Gataris means "anime talks."
Y'know, let's check
the opening to be sure.
[YUI]
Jeez!
Yui-miliating!
[MISTER KITTY]
Yui-miliating.
Man, that's a good one.
[laughs] They should give
that girl her own show.
Retro remakes are
in these days, right?
Okay, here we go, the title.
Anime-Gataris.
Anime talks.
Anime non-talks? What the?