[pants]
Morning, everybody!
Hello?
Oh.
Guess nobody's here.
Hey, you mind
keepin' it down a bit?
Some of us're tryin' to sleep!
Sorry, Mister Kitty.
I was excited and woke up early.
I should've known everyone
else would be busy.
[DELIVERY GUY]
'Scuse me.
Uh, yes?
Delivery here.
[MINOA]
Huh?
Uhm, okay.
What's this?
[DELIVERY GUY]
Have a nice day.
[MINOA]
Avalanche!
[YUI]
Ready.
[TSUBAKI]
Curse you, anime club.
I'll shut you down yet.
This battle is just
getting started.
Someday.
We've returned.
[AYAME]
As instructed, we researched
the club's expenditures
and dug up any information
we could find on the members,
including their
favorite anime titles.
I think you'll find
that our investigation
was quite thorough!
I see.
Search for any infraction
that you can find,
however small it may be.
[MATSURI AYAME]
Yes, ma'am!
Hot damn.
That was a close one, wasn't it?
You coulda helped me
instead of just jumping away.
[AURORA]
Are you all right?
[MINOA]
Nakano!
Thank goodness!
I was buried alive!
You're safe now, little kitten.
Ohhh... Meow!
You know what
these boxes are about?
Ah-ha!
[AURORA]
Hmm?
You can't beat
overnight shipping!
This stuff is all anime?
[ALICE laughs]
We can't very well
have an anime club
without a proper
library of titles.
I made sure to
rectify that myself.
Oh! Hello there,
you expensive limited edition
of the Dub Tone movie.
I haven't watched
the extended version
of the big concert
scene in this yet.
[KAI]
I see you acquired
the Chaos Mad Nova
boxed set as well!
That includes the little sister
scenes too gory for TV!
This is the latest
volume of Anosuba !
Now I can make everyone watch
that useless goddess
Aquina barf over and over!
[ALICE chcukles]
You're about to get
hit by some flying discs.
[MINOA]
UFOs?
No, you goofball!
DVDs, BDs, LEs,
physical media anime!
I see!
Late night anime,
like most of these here,
don't make money
from sponsors
like a regular
prime-time show would.
So disc sales
are very important.
They may seem
expensive at first glance,
but they often come
with tons of bonuses,
like concert raffle tickets
and event invitations
in addition to all the usual
interviews and artbooks.
Then you get soundtracks,
drama CDs or even figures.
Sometimes it's like the extras
are the most important part.
When shots from the
broadcast version look sloppy,
they'll often redraw them.
While the internet makes
fun of the off-model designs,
the animators work
tirelessly to fix them.
Thus, transforming them
into something beautiful
for the disc release.
Once you're a
true master like I am,
you'll have one copy for
storage, one for display,
one for watching, one for
backup, one for evangelism,
and however many more you need
to get all the preorder bonuses.
A true fan will purchase as many
copies as they deem necessary!
We get it.
[KAI] These discs are like
irresistible tiny black holes
sucking away all my money.
I'll tap into my
Swiss bank account.
There's no other choice.
So, the money anime makes,
only comes from the
sales of discs like these.
It's more complicated than that.
But like I was saying before,
the actual TV broadcast
doesn't earn them any profit.
You know, anime can be
pretty expensive to make.
Usually, a bunch
of different companies
will all invest
in a single title.
When they come together,
they form what's a called
a "production committee."
And then what?
[ALICE] Then they
come up with the budget
for the anime
and distribute revenue
from discs and merchandise
after it airs on television.
They also sell licenses
for online streaming
and overseas markets.
If the sales figures are good,
maybe they'll make
a second season!
Sometimes they'll follow
the manga or light novel.
And other times, for
whatever business reason,
they'll change the content.
If the anime is a giant robot
and the studio is its pilot,
then the production committee
is the secret organization,
pulling strings
from the shadows.
Oh, wow.
That's a big deal!
That may be why secret
committees are in so many anime.
Sakaneko Private
School Student Council's
one that comes to mind.
You think our student council
is a secret organization
controlling us from the shadows?
Minoa, sounds like you've been
watching too much anime.
Although, it's still not wise to
mess with the student council.
So wait, did you buy
all these for the club
with your own money?
Well, what belongs to
the club belongs to me,
and if it belongs to me,
it belongs to me.
[ERICA]
Uh?!
[MINOA]
Uhh...
That didn't really
clear anything up.
We've got you now, anime club!
Your days are numbered!
Huh?
It's them!
They're out of the shadows!
What now?
[ERICA]
Nothing.
Ignore her.
What's up?
Those are some serious faces.
Look at this.
The receipt for club spending.
What are "anime media costs"?
Is it this garbage?
Personal indulgences purchased
with official club funding?
The jig is up, you miscreants!
The criminal is among you!
That's me, over here.
[gasps]
No fair!
You're not supposed
to admit it yourself!
This was my chance
to shine as the VP!
Sorry, but this is a
job for the treasurer.
A total cost of
over 340 thousand.
This is clearly meant
as personal property.
But the club's property
is my personal property.
My money, and my club.
Do I need permission
from the student council
to buy something for myself?
Yeah, okay,
we get it; you're rich!
Specifics aside.
A newly formed
club is not allowed
to spend so much money
with official funding,
regardless of
where it came from.
Then I'll return these
and have the orders
shipped to my estate.
Now, Sebasu.
Hey, hold on.
Let me talk.
As the club's president,
it's my fault for not
checking into this,
but it won't happen again.
Like you said, we're a new
club, so we're still trying
to work out our place
at the school and all that.
"Your place at the school"?
In that case,
why don't we have you
assist the other clubs
for the rest of this week?
When you're done,
I will evaluate your work
and decide if your
club deserves to stay.
[ERICA]
Oh, come on!
Why is that a problem?
Is it because you know that the
anime club isn't worth anything?
You have nothing to contribute.
Not to the other clubs
and not to this school.
You're just dead weight,
wasting our time.
If you don't appreciate
what I'm saying,
then feel free to
prove me wrong.
If you can.
[MATSURI]
Have fun.
[AYAME laughs]
[MINOA sighs]
Just let us have our club room.
Why do you hate us so much?
[AURORA]
Thirsty?
[gasps]
[MINOA]
Oh, uh, thanks.
I guess I was lost in thought.
Funny.
Never knew we took the same bus.
The student council threatening
to shut down a school club.
I thought that stuff
only happened on TV.
Yeah, I saw a drama about
that just a few months ago!
Well, I was thinking anime.
Right! 'Course you were.
So I know you like Dub Tone ,
is that the only reason
you joined the club?
Not really.
It's not about anime as much
as it's about finding a place
with like-minded people.
That moment where
everyone comes together
and shines like
the stars they are.
That can be a really beautiful
thing, don't you think?
'Cause then,
we're almost like the
Onotokisaka Academy Idol Club.
I don't know that school.
If it wasn't for the Idol Club,
the whole place
would've been shut down.
You see in order for
them to form their club,
they also had to fight
against the student council
And they started from
nothing, just like us?
That's awesome!
Let's do it!
Just like Ono-whosie whatsit!
[AURORA]
Should I tell her it's an anime?
[ERICA]
Anime club, here!
Ready to help you out,
free of charge!
Does your club need anything?
Just ask and we'll deliver!
[MINOA]
Huh?!
Is that Erica?
[ERICA]
Morning, Minoacchi.
Neat costume,
but what's going on?
[ERICA] It's my way of saying
the anime club means business.
I need to resize this, though.
[MINOA] Here, give me
some of those fliers!
Anime club!
Me too.
Let me help!
[ERICA]
Aw, thanks you guys.
It appears that I must unleash
my dark powers once again.
Well, we can't really
give up now, can we?
Whatever it takes,
I'm on board, cosplay kitten.
I will neither hide nor
run away, hear me?
All my pitches are
straight down the middle!
[REF]
And that's a game!
Uh, uh... Hello, everybody--
Were you bowing?
[KAI]
Behold!
The dough is transforming
inside its electron purgatory!
At my command,
this time-altering gadget
makes quick work
of any confectionary!
Miko, if you're still here,
then please,
show me your Hand of God!
[MINOA]
We suck!
I had no idea that we were
so terrible at everything.
Where is Mister Gomon
when we need him most?
On a foreign business trip,
evidently. In China, I think?
[ALICE] It's almost
like he's mocking us.
We only have two days
left to be useful.
Frankly, I fear that
our demise is inevitable.
I can't help
but blame you, Alice.
In that case, I'll simply
acquire this academy,
oust the student council
and institute new--
You're the devil.
Just with a checkbook
instead of a pitchfork.
I second that.
Hey. I'm trying to help!
[MINOA]
Guys, come on.
[ERICA]
Cut it out.
Instead of pointing fingers,
let's try searching
for a solution, 'kay?
Good news, kittens.
It's a request
from the drama club.
They're performing a big musical
the day after tomorrow
to welcome our new students.
The costumes they ordered
won't come in on time,
so they're in serious trouble.
[MIKO]
Costumes?
[MINOA]
Huh?
You could totally
help them with that!
[ERICA]
Huh?
Well, I don't know.
I could try.
Possibly.
[AYAME]
That's all I have to report.
The anime club is making
costumes for a musical?
Ha! What a waste of time.
Hate it.
This isn't going to work.
[MINOA]
What should we do?
Is it because you know that the
anime club isn't worth anything?
You have nothing to contribute.
My name's Erica.
I moved here from Japan.
And I guess, that's it?
[FEMALE STUDENT D] We're
ordering pizza tonight. You in?
Uh. Hello.
[FEMALE STUDENT D]
Yep!
They've got PreFae ?
I didn't know they
showed this over here!
[FEMALE STUDENT E]
Hey, Erica!
Whoa, cool PreFae buttons!
You watch it?
Yeah, 'course I do!
We're cosplaying the characters,
but we don't know
the transformation
lines in Japanese.
Can you help us?
Sure!
It's real easy!
Enemies of Mother Earth,
your time has run out!
Cease your wickedness.
Or face punishment!
Huh? Uh?
You came back!
Listen, I have a suggestion.
There's an idol anime I love
that has some costumes
you could use for inspiration.
[ERICA]
I guess that could work.
[AURORA] It was in
the pile that Alice bought.
She might've saved us.
Huh?
I wanna make the best
costume in the whole world!
We'll need to raise
some silkworms!
And plant mulberries for dye!
[GIRL A]
Ono toki!
[GIRL C]
[GIRLS] Ono toki! Ono toki!
Ono toki! Ono toki! Ono toki!
We did it!
[AURORA]
See?
As the sparklies indicate,
these costumes are dazzling.
Idol anime isn't always
about a school club.
Sometimes it's about the
talent agency, or small town,
local idols,
the possibilities are limitless.
They might even break into
motion-captured CG animation
with realistic choreography!
But they're always cute!
Dancing on the stage of your TV.
You can almost smell the
sweat glistening on their brow,
or feel their hot breath.
And yet they're
too beautiful to be real!
And the costumes!
Of course, the costumes are
elegant, fabulous, excellent!
They're icing on the cake,
the jewel in the crown,
the piece de la resistance!
I'm going to explode.
But more than cute,
the costumes are inspirational.
Carried on wings of hope!
The point here, is that all idol
anime have one thing in common.
They're about coming together.
Being yourself and
conquering adversity as a team!
[FEMALE IDOL GROUP]
For beauty!
[ERICA]
You mean.
[AURORA]
Just like us.
And this is it.
Our inspirational moment
to come together and succeed!
I'm inspired!
How 'bout you?
I know we can be a pain,
but you're the only
one who can save us!
We're lucky to have
a president like you,
so I hope you'll stick
around a long time!
Really think so?
We feel the same way.
All right then.
We don't have much time!
Nakanocchi,
make the designs with me.
[AURORA]
Right.
Okay, Kaikai and Mikocchi.
You go buy the fabric.
As for Alicecchi and Minoacchi.
You can do the tacking.
[ALL]
Got it!
Huh?
It's fine.
After all, there's no point if
I can't accomplish this myself.
Wow, Mii.
Really up late tonight.
Uh. Yeah, I'm almost done.
Just a little more and
then it's sleepy time.
Anime or whatever it is,
I'm glad you found something.
Pick it up team!
We don't have
much time to finish.
[ALICE, MINOA]
Yes, ma'am!
They're useless!
They couldn't even
finish the costumes!
You think the drama club
will hold off the play
till they're done?
They can't.
I told them that
they weren't allowed
to go over their allotted
time in the gym.
This is gonna be
a massive trainwreck!
It's showtime!
Ladies, let's get
that sparkle on!
[KAI]
Three, two, one.
[gasps]
No way.
That was close,
but who's counting?
We did it!
Shut us down now!
[TSUBAKI]
I intend to do exactly that.
You're sorely mistaken
if you think one little stunt
earns you a happy ending.
Your club is still a
meaningless waste of time.
[ERICA]
It's not meaningless at all!
When I was stuck in a foreign
country with no friends,
anime saved me!
So now.
I'm not giving up
on the anime club,
because it's a place for people,
for my friends, to belong!
And you're wrong about anime
not contributing anything.
You've seen for yourself
the good it can do.
And I don't just mean cosplay.
I mean a bond
between two people.
Why are you so eager to
throw all that away, Tsubaki?
It's not right.
[ERICA]
Tsubaki, let's transform!
'Cause PreFae is a team,
and you're my partner!
Erica.
[ERICA] Enemies of Mother Earth,
your time has run out!
[TSUBAKI] Cease your wickedness
or face punishment!
We aren't the same anymore.
I'm the student
council president.
I can't let you do
whatever you want.
Let's raise the curtain!
[FEMALE STUDENT F] Our
costumes today are all thanks
to the anime club's hard work.
We were in a tight spot,
and they really came through.
We couldn't have put the
show on without their help.
Everyone, give them
a big round of applause!
Thanks for pitching for us!
And thanks for
recording with us, too!
They bought us a brand new
microwave thanks to you!
This is ridiculous,
but I do know when I'm beat.
I can't very well shut
down your club yet, can I?
[ERICA]
Tsubaki!
Don't get sentimental.
And don't think you're going to
change my mind on anime, either.
Huh?
Wait a sec!
That's it?
[AYAME]
You're too merciful!
Where's the wrath?
Okay, now, I think we're safe.
I'll be more careful
with my ludicrous
expenditures next time.
I'm just glad I have you guys!
[MINOA]
Erica!
[AURORA] They're truly shining,
like stars in the sky.
You can almost see
the sparklies on them.
[TSUBAKI]
That's correct.
My attempt to shut down
the anime club failed.
Despite my best efforts,
I fear the situation
is beyond my control.
Of course.
It's settled then.
[MATSURI]
President.
You won't believe
what they just bought!
[AYAME] Three hundred thousand
yen worth of cosplay
I don't need any
more reports on them.
[TSUBAKI] Your fight
isn't over yet, Erica.
In fact, I'm afraid
it's only just begun.
Back in the day,
anime girls could become idols
with just a few magic words and
a flashy transformation scene.
These days, the poor girls
gotta train and audition
and all that crap, 'cause
I guess a little optimism
would kill these
stinkin' script writers!
So anyway, next episode
the anime club
gets a spot along the wall.
Now don't stay up all night!