I'm looking at the
anime club's plans
for the school festival,
and this is a load of crap.
An anime screening
is pretty weak.
After what
happened last time,
I don't know if the
president cares or not,
but they are really
getting on my nerves.
Anyway, this had been
bugging me forever.
Uh-huh?
[YUI]
So I finally asked,
and it turns out it's the word
for the back of your knee!
[MINOA]
What? Crazy!
Hello, everybody!
Uh-oh, it's the
production committee!
Try "student council."
Nobody laughed.
This must be serious.
Huh?
Alice spent way too much
money again, didn't she?
'Kay, that "again"
was not necessary.
Surprisingly, no!
"Surprisingly"?
We submitted our proposal for
the school festival, but...
Well, you explain.
"An anime screening?
Come on, guys.
I refuse to accept that,"
says the council president.
That's not her voice.
Arts clubs are required to show
projects at the school festival
to demonstrate that
they've actually been
working on something.
So, unless you
can show something
you've actually created, I'm
afraid your proposal's rejected!
The whole purpose
of our club
is to watch and discuss anime.
Screening an anime is the
only thing that makes sense
for our club to do.
I'll talk to Tsubaki about this.
She's too busy to see you.
Either make something
awesome or pack your bags.
Huh?! I thought we were
done with this nightmare!
So we're dead, right?
We'll do something.
We've handled everything
else they threw at us.
There's no reason
for us to give up now.
[sighs]
We could make
a doujinshi , maybe.
We can do a concert
with cute costumes, of course.
I've got a whole notebook
full of battle anime ideas
that I can talk about
for hours and hours.
How about we invite
some voice actors
and hold a public recording?
Money, again?
I know!
Instead of talking about
anime, let's make one!
Uh...
Minoacchi, do have
any idea how much work
goes into anime?
Uh... Is it a whole bunch?
The writing, storyboards,
artwork, recording.
It takes a tremendous
number of people.
To be quite frank,
not even my Swiss bank account
could finance such a production.
Well, that's
because it's not real.
[MINOA]
Don't give up yet.
[gasps]
I want everyone to know how
much anime means to our club!
I want to make something
amazing with my friends!
And show the world!
In the face of
such enthusiasm,
how could I ever say no?
I see.
This is real money.
I knew you were rich,
but this is just sick.
I can't say no to that.
With this budget,
we can make an anime
that will bring the
world to its knees!
Well, Miss President?
Yes, to the anime, but sorry,
I'm saying no to the money.
How can you do anything
without a budget, though?
Let's start by doing
some brainstorming,
then we'll see if the
other clubs can help.
We have three months
until the school festival.
Let's make an anime with
everything that we've got!
Okay.
Ah!
First, we need a good concept.
Anyone cooked up an idea yet?
I know what
you're all thinking,
but an idol anime
is the way to go.
It'll take place right here.
They can have
the final dance-off
at our school festival!
A swirling cyclone of music
and passion and love!
If you want real passion,
then you'll find it in the
heat of battle, not in dance!
The protagonist in my tale
is the Mad King Kai!
I... I mean he,
commands the most
powerful magic in existence.
Its name?
Amethyst Extra Circulation!
If we're talking magic,
then how 'bout this?
These aren't just magical girls;
they're magic magical girls!
The new season of
PreFae is doing this,
so you know it's gold.
I came with one too!
It's based on that
anime I saw as a kid.
The main character's
separated from their family.
They use magic, they transform,
they pilot robots,
and at long last, they're
reunited with their mother.
Then, in the last episode,
they're welcomed into heaven.
There won't be a single dry eye
in the audience, I know it!
How many episodes
are you thinking here?
Oh, like two seasons, I guess?
[KAI]
Keep dreaming.
[ALICE] None of these
are the least bit practical,
especially after you
so callously refused
to accept my funding.
Sebasu!
This is brought to you by the
Supreme Production Commander:
Me.
[ALICE]
It is the galactic era.
A super robot saves the world
with love, passion and money.
[ALICE]
Super Warrior: Alice-borg!
Alpha!
[ALICE]
You will see the tears of money.
[ERICA] And you say
our ideas are impractical.
Right.
[MINOA]
That was so cool, though!
How did you make it?
[ALICE] Sebasu did
the script, storyboards,
key art, backgrounds,
photography,
and editing all by
himself just last night!
[KAI]
Who needs an anime club?
We'll just have
Sebasu do everything!
[sighs]
Now, I'm worried.
We got all pumped up,
but I wonder if we took on
a bit more than we can handle.
[MIKO] Then perhaps
I should remind you,
that you have a well-read
intellectual on your team,
who just so happens to have put
together the perfect pitch!
I propose an
alternate world story,
as they're the current trend.
Wait is it a whole season?
We can't do all that.
No.
It's three minutes long.
An anime short.
That makes sense!
Okay, that I think we can do!
It's just three minutes?
Since production schedules and
budgets are tight these days.
Every season, they make
a couple three minute
and five minute anime shows.
That's perfect for us!
The scriptwriter for
Yasuda and Iwakura had
to get really creative,
because the episodes
were only a minute and a
half long, but they used the
same thirty second shot
in the opening every time.
Some shorts, like Immun-kun ,
are based off of comic strips
and appeal to a wider audience
than most other anime.
In Malcom Academy
they brought together
a bunch of characters
from different RPGs
and kept all of their original
voice actors, making the
frankly insipid production
seem like a waste of talent.
What's Up Girl Zoo
or Whagzoo ,
was based off of an idol anime,
but for whatever reason,
they had a character die
in each episode of the shorts.
It's almost like a
race against time.
Stuffing as much
material as they can
into a little-bitty timeslot,
so the audience stays happy.
Also, they're really nice
to watch on your phone
when you have
five minutes to kill.
They're short enough
to marathon, too.
[KAI]
Mm. Mm.
That settles it.
Time to get rolling on
that screenplay, Mikocchi!
I've already worked
out the scenario,
so this should be
a piece of cake.
[ERICA]
Okay, script meeting number one!
Hope you enjoy my work.
The main character walks
through a shopping center door,
then he's in another world?
That's kind of mundane.
It sets up their need for
food in the alternate world.
We've got three minutes,
forget the food!
We've gotta end it
on a big tear-jerker.
After this, she'll transform!
My blood was
not boiling at all
when I read about these benign
special powers of theirs.
So I took the liberty
of rewriting the script.
There's no mid-story
climax to speak of.
We should add a concert.
[MINOA]
Where do the commercials go?
It's only three minutes long.
But wouldn't it be funny
if we added one?
Just bam!
Right in the
middle of the story!
Another lunchbreak
with no progress.
Feels like we're hitting a wall.
Turns out anime shorts
are quite formidable.
Trying to do a standalone story
with so little
time is difficult.
Hey, Mikocchi.
We still haven't
come up with anything,
even after all
these discussions,
so I really don't think
just tweaking the dialogue
or whatever is gonna cut it.
Let's scrap it.
Back to the
drawing board, I mean.
[MIKO]
All that was for nothing?
You can whip something
new up no prob, right?
Actually, I think you had
the right idea the first time.
Just rework it a bit.
Get it done
before school's over.
[MIKO] I'm sick of you
ordering me around!
And if my work was
good in the first place,
then why did you put me through
this, you bunch of jerks?
I'm through with this!
Do it your damn self!
We kind of need her.
Production issues already.
[MIKO growls]
Don't stop me!
I'm going to sleep!
Right here and right now!
Ow!
Huh?
[ALICE] Those look like image
boards from some anime.
Huh?
Don't open that door?
I'm sorry!
I guess the old club
was making a short, too.
Wonder if they had any luck.
The concept looks like
a mess, so not likely.
You say that, but it has
everything we like in it.
No way!
It's like that anime
from my dream!
Okay, I know it looks
like a mess on paper
and maybe it was
a mess in motion too,
but it was also awesome!
It is like that one you
were talking about!
I think it'll be more fun
if we all make our own
characters and in our own style!
Let's try it!
That just might work!
Whatd'you say,
Mikocchi, you got this?
[MIKO]
Mmm... Nuh-uh.
Miko, baby, we need you!
You're a superstar, sweetheart.
You're the team MVP!
You're the only one here who can
bring this crazy thing together!
You're the one that polishes
that diamond and makes it shine!
[KAI]
We found our producer.
[ALICE]
She's perfect for it
I'll accept that
compliment and the job, too.
Now, let's figure out
everyone else's jobs.
I'll be the character
designer, naturally!
I'm good with computers,
so I'll do digital production!
You can leave
the audio work to me!
I guess Mr. Gomon will be
our production assistant then.
So, uh, what about me, then?
[ERICA] There's something
only you can do, Minoacchi.
Right.
Like taking out
the trash, you mean?
You're the director!
Wait, are you sure about this?
You're the one who
came up with the idea!
Work out the
details with Mikocchi
and once you have a script,
draw the storyboards.
Huuuh? Wait!
Help!
What's a storyboard?
[MIKO]
I leave my legacy to you.
[ERICA]
Nice work.
So now what am I supposed to do?
A storyboard?
Think of it as sort of
an "anime" blueprint.
You take the script and
then make rough sketches
that lay out the
action and direction
and alla that sorta stuff
Look at the scene composition
in other anime, first.
I'll try my best.
Maybe it'll make sense later.
[MAYA]
Mii, the bath is ready!
[MINOA] Uhh...
I think I'll take one in a bit.
Something going on?
[MINOA]
My club's making an anime.
So I'm trying to figure out
how storyboards work.
Oh yeah?
Let me know if I can help, 'kay?
[MINOA] Actually,
we don't have a voice actress
for "Cute Girl A" yet!
You could do that, right?
Sure, I'm cute!
No problem!
[MINOA]
Now, I just need "Man A."
[coughs]
Are you sick or something?
Uh, no.
It's nothing.
[MIKO]
You took out the dialogue there.
Huh? Sorry!
It was kind of dragging on,
so I wanted to get
to the action sooner.
So as long as its flashy,
you can throw the
script writer to the dogs?
[MINOA] I'll see if
I can fit it back in later!
I promise! I promise!
The character designs
are coming along fine.
My character is super glamorous!
I can't wait to show you!
[laughs]
It's got too many details.
There's no way
we can animate that.
Try again.
[MINOA]
I leave my legacy to you.
[ERICA]
Nice work.
I'm not so sure.
You've changed so
many things from my draft.
Can we go over this again?
Everything's perfect, Miko Baby.
Minoacchi's just taking your
masterpiece and spicing it up.
Trust me, this'll look stellar
on your resume.
I guess that's true.
Are we cool?
Okay, now it's time to
kick this into high gear!
[MATSURI]
Miss President.
It seems that the
anime club's project
is progressing rather well.
[AYAME] It's gonna be
garbage, don't worry!
Is everybody ready in there?
Uh-huh!
[AURORA]
This is the moment
when the characters
really come to life.
So pour your hearts
into this, okay?
I'm some kinda magician?
Mm-hmm. Be yourself
and you'll do awesome!
Mister Kitty,
we just need you to meow!
I forgot to tell you, Nakano.
My sister has club practice,
so she couldn't make it today.
We can record
her separately later.
No big deal.
Okay, let's preview the video
so you get a sense
of how the timing will work.
Cool.
[YUI]
Black and white?
[AURORA]
Uh-huh.
The visuals aren't always done
by the time recording starts,
so we'll have to make do.
Actually, we're lucky to
have rough art to work with.
Sometimes, the actors don't
have anything but storyboards
or stand-in art to play off
of during dubbing.
Of course, you'd never guess
that just by watching the show,
because the voice actors give
it their all no matter what.
Summoning the character
forth, just like magic!
So yeah, that's what
you guys need to do.
Ready?! Okay, then!
Let's go!
Scha-winga!
[AURORA]
Stop, stop.
Alice, that's way
too much emotion.
Try to be more mech-like.
[ALICE] With all due respect,
I'm the main character.
I have to make an impression.
The robot's just the robot.
One more.
Are you sure?
Scha... Scha-wing.
Let's split the difference.
Come on.
I require more money.
Give me some more money.
Ha, ha, ha.
It's morphin' time!
[AURORA]
Stop, stop.
Erica, you're
breathing into the mic.
Watch those "H" sounds.
Also, Alice.
What this time?
Can you speak
the G-syllables
more through your nose, please?
A velar nasal.
Nasal what now?
It's something that
makes G-consonants sound
more pleasant to the ear.
[ALICE]
Sorry, I don't get it at all.
Your "g" there was too harsh.
Come forth!
Mighty Kaikai Blade!
I mean, Musashisakai--
[AURORA] Stop. We need
you to stick to the script.
[KAI]
The humiliation!
You may call me Yuirin!
And explosion magic
is the only magic for me!
You got it?
[AURORA]
Oh wow, you're good at this.
You really think so?
No, but I'll keep
that one to myself.
Meow.
[AURORA] Stop. More like
a cat and less like a man?
You're telling me to fly?
But that's impossible.
Together, anything
is possible for us.
Ohhh! Yes!
But you can do it
one more time if you like
or just do it all day
long while I watch!
After a valiant fight,
the Earth is safe once more.
[AURORA]
Okay, Minoa.
That's a wrap!
We did it!
What's this?
[AURORA]
For the wrap party, of course.
All of you did
a great job in there.
Now we need to match
the art to the dialogue
and add sound effects.
I can practically
see the finish line.
You think so?
We're that close, huh?
I mean, there's still
plenty of work left to do.
But thanks to everyone help,
we might actually pull this
off in time for the deadline!
Uh-huh!
Having the recordings
should speed things up!
You can't stop us!
[laughs]
Anime club, let's go!
[MASATO]
One more scene.
One more scene to go.
[ERICA] What do you mean the
ending theme isn't done yet?
We won't have it in time
for editing at this rate!
You're a failure as an artist
if you can't meet deadlines.
This is way off model,
it's nothing like
the design I drew.
You're saying you have
a problem with my art?
[ALICE]
Frankly, yes!
You want me to redraw all these?
If you could,
that'd be real nice!
[sighs]
So close.
[AYAME]
Miss President, I have bad news!
[MATSURI] The anime club's
project is actually shaping up,
I'm afraid.
I see.
Demand that all other clubs
cease their
cooperation with them.
Should they resist, their club
will be shut down immediately.
Uh...
That's a bit much.
[TSUBAKI]
Oh?
You're not questioning
my authority, are you?
Inform the clubs
before it's too late.
[AYAME, MATSURI]
Y-Yes, ma'am!
[TSUBAKI] Uhh...
One more thing you should know.
[chuckles]
[MINOA]
Ahh! It's perfect!
[KAI] Three more days
until the school festival!
I think we've got this!
[ALICE]
This is bad, you guys!
It's Mr. Gomon.
[MINOA]
What about him?
The production assistant
ran off alone?
I guess the pressure
was too much.
The concert band
says they aren't
doing the ending theme
for us anymore.
The broadcasting club
won't lend us the studio
to record the rest.
This is so sudden.
What happened?
[TSUBAKI] I have good news
for you, anime club.
We've prepared a special
venue for your big premier.
[TSUBAKI] The audience will
watch from the track field.
If you can't fill the seats,
your project will be
considered a failure.
Tsubaki, what is this?
[TSUBAKI]
Hmph!
Don't worry, I'm
sure your presentation
will be thoroughly entertaining.
[laughs]
There's no way.
We can't fill the whole track
with just one anime short.
I think we're dead this time.
For real.
I can do more than
meow this cat's got range.
What? You don't think
I was phoning it in, do ya?
How dare you!
I'm a professional!
Next time,
is the anime club
finally done for?
They better not be I still
need hear to my voice on TV!
And you'd better
watch it, too buddy!