At any rate,
the club is now defunct.
[MINOA]
Nakano, why?
What is this?
What the hell, Aurora?
You're our friend!
Do me a favor.
Don't call me
that name ever again.
I gave the club room keys
back to the student council.
Then it's over.
Sorry.
This mess is my fault.
After all, I was the president,
I should've stopped him.
No way.
We couldn't have
anticipated this.
Damn it!
Aurora!
I should have seen
the wickedness hidden
behind your handsome face!
I failed!
And it's all gone,
just like that.
Everything was going so well
after the school festival, too.
You know, even if we lost this
house, we'd still be a family.
Wait, are we losing the house?
[gasps]
Don't tell me.
You lost your job again?
Huh? Again?
[SHUGO]
It's an analogy!
[sighs]
Okay, so what's your point?
It isn't our home
that makes us a family,
but the bonds that we share.
The same with my friends, right?
[SHUGO]
Mm-hmm.
[STUDENT A]
Hurry!
[STUDENT B]
Yeah!
Huh? What's wrong?
Get out here and face us!
The anime club has got to stay!
Huh? Well, this is crazy!
[ALICE]
Minoa!
Huh?
Over here!
Please tell me you guys
know what's going on.
It was like this
when I showed up.
This school can't live
without the anime club!
I'm pleased that they finally
recognize our greatness.
[ALICE] I'd be flattered,
but I'm mostly concerned.
[OGIKUBO] I have an
announcement, students.
It's the principal!
[OGIKUBO] I would sooner
shut the entire school down
than reinstate the anime club.
And if you don't behave
yourselves out there,
I will do just that.
[CROWD]
Huh?!
Is that good enough for you?
Of course.
No matter how big a fish gets,
it's harmless once you
take it out of the water
[STUDENT C]
Get out here, Ogikubo!
Explain yourself!
I'm sorry!
We've been ordered
not to let anyone through!
[moans] Don't touch me,
you naughty children!
I'll defend this door,
no matter the cost!
If you want to pass.
Well, I'm afraid you'll
have to get rough with me!
They're really angry,
aren't they?
How did it come to this?
Make way!
Gah! That's a bit
too much for me!
Aw, crap!
[beeping]
What the?
You dope!
Now the office is on lockdown!
You're all coming with me!
To the staff room, right now!
[MISTER KITTY]
This is my secret feeding spot.
Uh, hey.
Are you gonna be all right?
Stop gawkin'
and help me already!
[MINOA]
Ahh!
Huh?
Whoa, the office!
Ahh! Uhm, excuse me, sir.
My name's Minoa.
I'm a member of the anime club.
Listen, it's Minoa's voice!
It's me! Open up!
I don't know if they can
hear us in there.
Why do you hate the
anime club so much, sir?
What in the hell was that?
[MINOA]
Huh?
The short you made
for the festival.
The art was a mess, and
you broke the 180 degree rule.
It was a barrage of poor jokes,
read by talentless voice actors.
And the writing was amateur!
You wanna go little man?
I poured my heart and soul into
that mess, I'll have you know!
Hate to admit it, but all
those criticisms are spot-on.
I pretty much agree with
him on all those things.
[laughs]
What's more, you didn't
even finish the end credits!
And that title sucks!
[MINOA]
I, uh...
Don't even try to deny it!
You paid such close
attention to our anime!
Oh, thank you so much!
[ALICE]
That was some killer trash talk.
The title stinks, does it?
Well, what do you know?
Does this mean the
principal's a fan of anime?
If that's the case,
then why has he unleashed
his wrath so thoroughly on us?
Okay, I agree.
Some parts were a little iffy.
But still...
It has everything I love,
all in one place!
It's a tribute to
my favorite show!
And what show is that?
Some anime I saw
when I was a kid
that stuck with
me all these years!
Robots, bam!
Some old guy, pchoo!
A magical girl defeating
bad guys with a song!
Fishies go flop flop!
And then the angels come!
I still dream
about it to this day!
Sounds like Burn Down ,
and Stretch Dawn Mermaid
Melody Pichi Pichi Pacchi ,
and Andromeda Angel .
All masterpieces, but
scarcely reflected in your work.
Oh, wow!
You're like an anime expert!
But none of those you mentioned
are the anime I'm talking about.
[OGIKUBO]
Then what is?
I don't remember!
[OGIKUBO]
You're in the anime club!
How can you not remember the
title of your favorite program?
Is the girl from
Secretive Blue Midia ?
Is the giant mech GahXephon ?
The singing part sounds like
Super Dimension Bonsai Micross ?
Are the angels from
A Dog of Decadence ?
[MINOA]
Hmmm...
Don't think so.
If he's going to be so bossy, he
should run his own anime club.
Maybe he's just jealous.
[ALICE] Come to think of it,
those sketches we found
in the club room were a lot
like Midia and GahXephon .
[gasps]
You think he ran the club
before he became the principal?
Let's find out.
Have you seen Micross ?
There's a famous scene,
with a girl named May Minling.
She's riding with the
protagonist in a mech.
He asks if her life or
her hair is more important
and she says, "hair."
And Pretty
Fighter Sailor Bunny !
That was the big thing for young
girls before PreFae came out,
but I remember how men
and women of all ages
were moved by
the phenomenal finale!
And do you know,
Hum from Nurusei Yakara ,
who always zapped
her cheating hubby?
She could zap me any time,
I'll tell you that!
Hiatari Sokosoko and Kimamani
Orange Road had cute girls, too.
You should see
them if you haven't.
They're pioneers in
the slice of life genre.
[ALICE, MIKO]
Holy crap, it's him!
What did anime do to hurt him?
I wonder why he changed?
Maybe he was an aspiring
writer who came to hate anime
after he was forced
to rewrite the school festival
script over and over.
[STUDENT C]
Don't give up on the anime club!
Don't give up on the school!
Little pests.
We didn't have the internet,
so we got all our news
from Animeta magazine.
Ooh! I'll study that!
[OGIKUBO]
It's too late now.
That school festival
garbage you made
will haunt you for
the rest of your life.
Don't be rude!
Anime's hard to make and
we gave it our best, you know!
It's a battle of
passion and personality,
with looming deadlines
and dwindling stamina!
But with the magic
of a good director,
everyone can come
together as one!
In this case, that's me!
You don't understand
directing at all!
A director is a
high-minded figure,
with wisdom far exceeding
anyone else on the staff!
He suffers in solitude
and bears the burden
of the entire production
on his back!
He deserves admiration!
Loyalty! Worship!
Oh, yeah, absolutely,
I totally get it.
She totally doesn't get it.
But jeez, is the principal
stuck up, or what?
[gasps]
With the way
he's talking, though,
it seems like he used
to be an anime director!
[AURORA]
It's possible.
[KAI]
Aurora!
You've got some nerve!
Forgive me!
Huh?
[AURORA] There's a reason
why I betrayed you.
Get out of here I don't
wanna see your face!
It's too late to
apologize; we're done!
I have five siblings,
so life is tough at home.
Six Auroras?
Oh my gosh!
[AURORA] My older brothers
are all good for nothing, so...
Wait, never mind that.
The point is, I had
to work long hours
at a coffee shop
just to stay alive.
It turns out the principal
was a regular there.
Taking pity on me
for my poverty,
he offered to let me attend
this school free of charge.
So even if it makes me sick,
I have to do what the
principal says, or I'm ruined.
I had no clue.
I'm so sorry you
went through that!
You always kept
a smile on your face.
Oh, Aurora, I never
should've doubted you!
We forgive you, Auroracchi.
Right then.
Welcome back.
[AURORA]
Uhh...
Everyone, thank you.
But uh, please stop
calling me Aurora.
Seriously.
The director's the
heart of the entire show!
Yeah, you're right! Uh-huh!
After talking to you, I can't
wait to work on my next project!
[OGIKUBO]
Wait, what?
I'll do much better this time!
[OGIKUBO]
You're not quitting?
I love anime!
Why would I ever give up?
Even without the anime club,
we're all still friends.
And as long as we're together,
we can make another one!
[OGIKUBO]
There are no second chances.
Huh?
[OGIKUBO] Once you screw up
the first episode,
then your dream is dead.
You can pour your heart and soul
into two seasons
of material, to no avail.
If your show gets canceled,
there's nothing you can do!
[gasps]
Whoa. This is crazy!
It's not my fault,
not my fault, it isn't!
Those stupid fans were wrong!
Every stinking night,
they crawl out of their holes.
Posting garbage on the internet,
picking apart every
frame of every show.
Who the hell is "anon" anyway?
Screw you!
[gasps]
Wait a sec, are you saying
you directed an anime before,
just like me?
So he was a director, then!
But his show got
canned right away.
He got dissed on the
internet and couldn't take it.
As a fellow creator,
I have nothing but sympathy.
[OGIKUBO]
What does it matter?
My work was banished
into oblivion!
Jeez. Whatta pain.
[MIKO]
It's the little kitty.
[MISTER KITTY]
That's Mister Kitty to you!
Gross!
Why is there a
cat door down here?
Even a hardass like him
can't resist the fluff.
Minoa.
Are you okay?
[shrieks]
What's that door?
Open up, quick!
[MINOA]
Uh.
There's an awful lot of buttons.
I don't know where to start.
Ogikubo!
What's the password?
The guys in his own world,
he can't hear a stinkin' word.
The lock to that door
is the lock to his heart,
you might say.
That's so poetic.
So he's trapped in
a cage of his own torment.
Unless we can reach out
to his stone-cold heart.
That's fantasy!
You're one to talk.
A password to open his heart.
I see.
If the principal broke down
because of anime,
then I say anime's the only
thing that can save him!
Indeed!
A ray of light at the
end of the tunnel!
And we'll find it, for sure!
Begin Project M!
Let's be ambitious, team!
Hey, we'll get you outta there,
Minoa, just hold on!
We'll find the
principal's anime!
[MINOA] The sooner the
better, if you don't mind!
[ERICA] First let's try to
gather some information.
I'll see if any of
the store clerks know!
Good luck!
Search engine's showing nothing.
Guess we'll just have
to crowdsource it, then.
Uh, hey, Saori.
There's something
I need to ask you about.
A live stream might be
a good option, too!
Good day to all
anime fans out there.
My name's Alice Kamiigusa.
I'm looking for the
name of an anime.
I call upon your endless
wealth of knowledge
to aid me in this
important mission.
It features an homage to
Midia and Dog of Decadence .
It uses imagery from
shows like GahXephon
and Super Dimension
Bonsai Micross.
It was canceled in one episode.
[ALICE]
We need all the help we can get.
Send us anything,
no matter how small.
She's a cutey!
What's up?
[ERICA]
No clue, huh?
Oh well.
Sorry to bother you!
Well, any luck?
They're just talking
about how cute Alice is.
For real?
Well, if it goes viral, we're
sure to get some new leads.
[OGIKUBO moans]
Anime took everything
away from me!
But it has the power to
bring people together, too!
Anime gave me a dream to follow!
[OGIKUBO]
A dream?
It is a nightmare!
No, it's a treasure!
Huh? A treasure?
Bam!
Pchoo! La-la-la!
Oh, look at me, I'm flying
That show you like so much?
Yeah.
I know it's weird since
I can't even remember
the name of the anime,
but I swear it was really great!
If you could watch it,
you'd agree!
[CASHIER]
Canceled after a single episode?
Yeah.
Does that ring
any bells for you?
Nuh-uh.
[MIKO sighs]
Thanks anyway.
Canceled after one ep.
What was its name, Etashin ?
It's something like that.
[CASHIER]
Nishiazabu, get back to work!
Coming!
[ALICE gasps]
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi:
Eternal Symphony !
We got it!
All right, let's do this!
C'mon!
Huh? That's not it?
Alice, notice me.
Oh, notice me, please!
C'mon, Alice. Notice me!
Eternal Symphony
has a nice ring to it!
Seems our principal's taste
is as exquisite as my own!
I don't know if I like the
thought of you two getting cozy.
We're getting a ton of replies!
We're trending!
It's got a giant robot
with an awesome design!
And its control lever
has piano keys on it!
All of a sudden, this old dude
goes flying into the sky!
Then this girl's
pendant starts to glow,
and she has a magical
transformation scene.
But they both die,
and they're surrounded
by a bunch of flopping fish.
Then angels come for them.
That's the end of
the first episode.
I was so excited
waiting for the next one.
What could possibly happen?
I waited week after week,
but it never came back.
I never learned
how the story ends.
[OGIKUBO sighs]
That's because the director kept
all those secrets to himself.
[MINOA]
Huh?
Whoa!
We're going viral now!
Got it!
A fan sent me a link!
That's the show!
[MIKO]
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi .
Why are they showing
it on the screen?
It's called Ultra Katharsis
Koritsi: Eternal Symphony ,
and you know the
director of the show?
In a sense.
He is right in front of you.
Ah!
Awesome!
I'm a fan!
A big fan of your show!
I gathered.
[MINOA]
It's a treasure.
I love it.
Okay, okay.
After all this time,
I suppose I should be happy
my work touched
someone's heart.
Bam!
Pchoo! La-la-la!
Thanks to me, you made that
abomination of an anime!
Everything's falling into place.
Sorry to make you wait!
You're back!
You got some news?
The password isn't "catharsis."
We tried.
[laughs]
"Katharsis" with a "K" is
a Greek word, you know.
The philosopher
Aristotle described it
as the purification of the mind.
You're here!
[ALICE]
We were so worried about you!
I was fine.
What happened?
You're drenched!
Did the sprinklers go off?
Yeah, the floor's soaked, too.
Well, it, uh...
Here, let me dry you off.
[OGIKUBO sighs]
Huh? What is that?
Just look.
Open the window.
They are here
for you, after all.
[voices]
[gasps]
[OGIKUBO]
What's happening?
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi !
We got it on VHS video!
Oh, Alice!
Yes.
I'm just like you.
I love anime with all my heart.
Even now.
A tragedy's effectiveness is
dependent on its ability
to invoke both fear and
sympathy in its audience,
thus purging them
of those emotions.
The moment their souls are
freed, is known as "catharsis."
[OGIKUBO]
Toodles otakus!
[ERICA exhales]
Guess it's nice having
a club room after all!
It is pretty chill in here,
I gotta say.
[MIKO] Just how I like it,
Mister Kitty.
Now gimme a hug.
[MISTER KITTY]
Don't mind if I do!
Miko, wait.
I didn't know you could
understand Mister Kitty!
Of course, she can.
Wait, are you kidding me?
Huh?
[MINOA]
Did something weird happen
while I was in the office?
[AURORA]
Hmph!
[gasps]
He really did summon
that rain, didn't he?
What is that? A yearbook?
It's the principal!
Huh?! No!
That can't be right!
[MINOA]
Is that Aurora?
Next time, we finally
reach the climax.
Don't believe anything!
And don't take
the bait out there!
'Cause if you do... Ahhhh!
You'll end up like this.