[MINOA]
Why?
And we were so close, too!
What are you trying to pull?
You haven't even officially
registered your club with us.
If you want to hang out,
you can do it somewhere else.
[ERICA]
We have the members.
Make it official.
We have received
your application
and are evaluating its merits.
If we decide that the anime
club is a worthwhile addition
to our school, then you will
be informed accordingly.
You're a grownup, Mister Gomon,
what do you mean
you can't fix this?
Well, sorry!
The principal already okayed it,
and they're a more
important adult than me.
I should have known.
We can't count on you at all.
I told you I wasn't
gonna do anything.
[AURORA]
Doesn't sound good.
I think we're done for.
Although technically,
we never even got started.
I guess it's back to watching
anime at home alone again.
Hey. You're leaving?
Why don't we all go to Akiba?
Akiba?
Whoa! This is cool!
Hey! It's that movie
Alice lent me!
Oh, and look!
It's Miko's book
with a weird name!
Light novels!
Try to save some
excitement for the actual store.
I know it's your first time
here, but let's pace ourselves.
[ERICA]
Here's an idea.
We'll come back to
the big book store later.
You need a real lesson first!
[MINOA]
Ohh...! Ah...!
Cool.
I take it you've never
seen one of these before.
This is a cosplay shop
if you couldn't guess.
Wow.
It's like anime is real!
Or like, in 3D, I mean.
Although I would agree that you
can't find a store like this
anywhere but Akiba,
I'm still not sure
it's the first place
I would take someone.
Wait, where's Erica?
Oh, cute, I've seen
that outfit before!
But from where?
[ALICE]
Oh my gosh!
Nacchan from Dub Tone !
You're like an
angel in the flesh!
Sorry I kept you
waiting so long,
but I just had to
try this one out.
Wait, that's Erica?
Is it, really?
Uh-huh!
It was like you
completely transformed.
[MINOA]
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
I have the opposite issue.
I don't recognize cosplayers
when I see them out of costume.
[KAI]
Cosplay problems, huh?
That part comes
with the territory.
The real cosplay problem is
when you want to coordinate
with your friends but
you're all into different series
or you all like
the same characters.
That's a pain.
Coordinate?
Doing a group of characters
from a particular show.
I've tried on so many
costumes, working that out.
Yeah. Like which ones?
It's more like which
one's didn't I try on?
We went through
that whole wall there.
That sounds fun!
[ERICA]
We practice poses, too.
That's as important
as the costume.
But watch the anime first,
so you're not a poser.
I wonder if I could
pull off cosplay too.
I got a big kick out of
your bunny girl cosplay,
so that's a good start at least.
[MINOA groans]
You know, we almost have enough
people for a Toumabu group.
You wanna try it?
Minocchi?
I don't think I--
Maybe Nakimushi Saddle
would be better.
I have a riding jersey
you could wear.
I'm not sure.
It's fine!
You just need to look cute.
I'll handle the wigs, poses,
makeup, and accessories.
As long as you don't expect
too much, I could try it.
[KAI] She's been sucked into
the swirling vortex known as:
Aoyama's Cosplay Universe.
Now you just need
to watch Saddle !
It's good!
[KAI] And now,
our next stop, Anime Soul!
This place truly is
a tower of dreams.
I prefer to think of it
as a Tower of Babel
where lust and vices flourish.
[chuckles]
Asagaya, are you prepared
to set foot into a new--
Anime magazines.
A whole gigantic pile of them!
Why are you guys
just standing out there?
[ALICE]
As you can see,
the first floor is magazines
and the second is new books.
The third floor
is for older titles.
Most light novels
are there, too.
[MINOA]
Doesn't sound too different
from a normal bookstore so far.
[ERICA]
Right. "So far."
But starting
at the fourth floor.
This place is anime merch only!
Oh, wow!
There's so much stuff!
Where do you even start?
These Odopuri badges
are simply to die for!
What's a "badge?"
These little buddies.
[MINOA]
Oh, like buttons.
Minocchi!
These Micross Gamma
keychains are cute!
Ahhh!
So you can put your favorite
character on your school bag?
[ERICA]
They call that a chibi.
It means they're small and cute.
And that you have
to buy them all.
[ERICA]
Well, of course!
How can you say no to
those poochy little cheeks?
[AURORA]
Cuteness... is justice!
[ALICE]
Agreed!
Oh, hey.
Where did Miko run off to?
[AURORA]
No Kaikai, either.
Guess they went up.
[MINOA] I'm headed up
anyway, I'll go see.
[MINOA]
Hey there, Kaikai?
So... having fun?
[shrieks]
[KAI] Wh-Wha-What
sorcery has allowed you
to approach me undetected?
You must be one of "them"!
Sorry.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
What are you up to Kaikai?
Musashisakai Kai! Got it?
What are these dealies
you're looking at here?
She's cute.
It's Margedo Lee from
Arina, the Scarlet Eye !
Wielder of the infamous
book of evil, Grimoire!
Huh?
Oh neat. So that's
the book you had, right?
Ahh...
[sighs]
Ah!
But if she's just got a book
how's she s'posed to fight?
An excellent question
coming from a rookie!
This is one of the finest
features of battle anime!
[MINOA]
I'm listening.
Objects that aren't
normally weapons
and skills that aren't
normally meant for combat
are utilized in creative
and destructive ways
in battle anime!
[MINOA]
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Other than books,
you might see...
Paper!
A coin.
Electricity.
Or cards!
Some characters even fight with
abstract concepts like words!
That doesn't make a lot of
sense, but it sure is unique.
You lack imagination,
filthy rookie!
Very well...
I shall enlighten you
on the virtues of
battle anime and, uh...
You're smiling at me.
You're not bored?
Huh?
I keep talking.
I feel like I'm
forcing this on you.
No, I love learning about it.
It's great!
You're a real
weirdo, aren't you?
[MIKO]
If I may...
[shrieks]
Where'd you come from?
Are you aware that Margedo Lee
has an extensive backstory
in the light novels that was
excluded from the anime?
She does?
It was so good, I nearly
stained my book with tears.
You have gazed upon secrets
that I've only dreamed of.
You have truly taken
a step into the other side.
Of course,
I'm a huge fan of Arina
the Scarlet Eye , after all.
The light novel at least.
[KAI]
Hmph. I must say,
you freshmen certainly
are fascinating creatures.
[chuckles]
[ERICA]
What did I miss?
I'm so happy those
two are hitting it off!
That's the magic
of Akiba, I guess!
[ERICA] Yeah, let's
just leave it at that.
[MINOA] Thanks for the tour,
that was really fun!
I know, right?
Whenever I'm bummed out,
this place cheers me right up.
Uh-huh.
Hey. We don't
need to get approval
from the school
to have an anime club.
That's a waste of time.
We'll hang out on our own.
[MINOA]
Uh, yeah, but...
Objection!
[gasps]
That's a double
dose of discontent!
Whoa, did I hit a nerve somehow?
Of course!
Have you forgotten Elegant
Fish Cat's Club Room Life ?
Well, they had a
club room, didn't they?
I'm still trying to
figure out that title.
It's a slice-of-life
show that focuses
on conversations in a club room.
I saw people online
cutting it after ep. three,
saying it put them to sleep.
A three ep. cut is too cruel!
What's wrong with having a chill
show every once in a while?
[KAI] Fine! Don't tell me,
tell the internet!
Three-cut-what?
They're talking about
dropping an anime
after the third episode.
A lot of people do that when
they're bored with a show.
Is there something
special about ep. three?
Sometimes the
budget drops a bit,
but a lot of anime
feature a twist
or a turning point
in the third ep.
You start off thinking it's
just a normal magical girl show,
and then suddenly,
a head gets torn off.
They practice their songs,
work on their costumes and
make their big idol debut.
Only no one bothers
to come see the show.
Huh?!
It's a technique
to shock the audience
and keep them watching
until the end of the series.
Wondering what crazy nonsense
might sneak up on them next!
[ERICA]
Anyway,
if the audience can make it
over the three episode hurdle,
there's a good chance they'll
stick with the entire series.
But unfortunately,
a lot of viewers will say,
"it's not my thing," and
give up early in the season.
But that's not fair!
Episode three is when
the cast and the backstory
have all been introduced,
so the series can really
start to move forward!
The characters build more
interesting relationships
and the dialogue between
them plays out in fun ways!
It's foolish to give up
and put three episodes
of setup to waste!
Right?
You're quite the pair.
Huh?
At this rate, our club is
going to get the three ep. cut
from the student council.
With the state we're in, it's
a zero ep. cut. Technically.
Back to what
I was saying earlier,
one of the best parts of battle
anime is when the characters
unleash their hidden powers.
[MINOA]
Uh-huh?
For example, removing
a bracelet from their wrist,
taking off an eyepatch--
unsealing the
forbidden magic within.
The catharsis is
pure bliss, indeed!
Ohh...!
As for my own hidden power.
You have hidden
powers too, Kaikai?
Call me Kai!
When I remove
this Witlim Opticum,
handed down to me from
sages of generations past,
the power of my evil eye will
be released and the flames
of retribution shall
rain down from the sky!
[laughs]
[sighs]
Hey, we're here!
Tell me more about
anime stuff sometime, okay?
Bye!
[MINOA]
I hate to split up like this.
If we had a club room, we could
sit around and talk for hours.
[ALICE] Now the student council
is pushing to abolish the club!
What is their deal?
Can't you tell them anime
isn't hurting anybody, please?
Actually, I'm the one who
suggested this whole meeting.
This forces the
student body to vote on
if the club is
worth anything or not.
If you win, then the council has
no choice but to back off.
Of course, you'll get
your club room back, too.
And if we don't win the vote?
Shut it down!
[moans]
That's all the student council
was willing to agree to,
so take it or leave it.
You asked me to do something,
and this was the best
I could come up with.
[MINOA]
This sucks!
[sighs]
At this rate, we won't get our
anime club this year either.
[KAI] And what do you
plan to do about it?
Nothing. But if the freshman
still want to keep at it,
I'll have their backs.
[KAI] Don't have
any fight in you, huh?
Come on.
What's wrong with doing
the club outside of school?
You didn't say it,
but I bet you were thinking
the exact same thing.
[ALICE] Erica already said
she's not making the speech.
[MIKO sighs]
No surprise,
since she's content with getting
together outside of school.
I know.
But I don't want to give up.
We should have a club room where
we can talk forever and ever.
I know we can live without it,
but I still want a place we
can call our own, you know?
Minoa.
[MINOA] You'll fight with me to
get our club room back, right?
We can do this! No problem!
Yes. I'll write you
the perfect speech.
I'm certain you
can handle the rest.
[MINOA]
Mm-hmm.
Huh?
We're here for you.
There's no need to be nervous.
The future of
our club is shaky,
but I'm confident leaving
it in your capable hands.
Oh. Uh.
We'll be here cheering
for you every inch of the way!
Watch this anime tonight.
It has my favorite speech in it.
You'll be inspired, I'm sure.
'Kay.
Huh?! Don't leave me!
[ALICE]
I'll write the best speech
the world has ever witnessed!
[MIKO]
We will surely be victorious.
Why are you so confident?
[MISTER KITTY]
You look rough.
Huh?
Mister Kitty, help!
Everyone has too
much faith in me!
[MISTER KITTY]
Here.
Huh?
[MISTER KITTY]
A good luck charm.
Take it.
A sardine?
Good luck, samurai girl.
[MISTER KITTY]
I always wanted to say that.
[TSUBAKI] The purpose
of any extracurricular activity
at this academy is
to enrich school life,
to improve relationships
between students,
and ultimately to create
something meaningful
to the world.
But the anime club?
They only want
to watch cartoons!
Was she just looking for
an excuse to trash-talk anime?
[ERICA] It's not like
she's wrong, exactly.
From the school's perspective,
an anime club wouldn't
contribute that much.
You agree with her?
Not quite. I can't say
what anime is really worth,
but that chick has
no right to, either.
[TSUBAKI]
...no place here.
It becomes a hindrance
to our education.
Abolishment of the anime club
is the obvious course of action.
[ANNOUNCER] Now, Minoa
Asagaya from the anime club
will make her speech.
Uh, right!
Are you guys sure
she'll be okay up there?
The speech is perfect.
There is no way
this could go wrong.
We've lost a club room
to our noble glorious cause,
but does this
foreshadow our defeat?
No, it is but a new beginning!
Huh?
Alice said this would
get big cheers!
Did I mess it up?
You really thought
this would work?
There's something
wrong with our generation
if they don't respond
to this work of genius!
It is a classic!
You're a lost cause.
Uh... Moving on.
We of the anime club
seek to research anime
from an enlightened perspective.
Well not so much
researching as just watching.
And then we like,
talk about it...
[MALE STUDENT]
Huh? This is a joke, right?
[FEMALE STUDENT]
They just want to hang out.
[MALE STUDENT]
They don't need a club.
[MINOA] I, um, I actually
don't know anything about anime.
So for me, the club is a
way to, uh, no, never mind.
I mean, anime is,
um... It's a...
[gasps]
[KAI] When I remove this Witlim
Opticum, handed down to me
from sages of generations past,
the power of my evil eye will
be released and the flames
of retribution shall
rain down from the sky!
I love when an anime
has crazy fight scenes!
It's the best!
Why, you ask?
I could give you many answers.
In battle anime, even
characters who seem weak,
with abilities
ill-suited for combat,
turn their talents
into deadly weapons!
Engaging in struggles
impossible in reality,
they raze entire
buildings in their wake!
It is magnificent!
We're done!
He's wasting our time.
Let's vote.
No, let's abolish the anime
club without a vote...
You will let me
finish my speech!
But the real best part
of any battle anime.
Well...
[MINOA]
That's what he said before.
He never finished!
The heroes, always side
with the weakest of us,
and overturn the tyranny
of the strong and wicked.
They hear the
voices of the voiceless.
They become power
for the powerless.
And that is the true
essence of battle anime!
It's all make-believe?
It's childish?
Laugh if you must but
anime has meaning to me.
It has taught me
the value of justice,
of perseverance and friendship!
What gives the
student council the right
to declare something
like that "worthless"?
They have no psychic powers.
They can't command magic.
They're just bullies.
Just, episode villains!
So, you can side
with them if you want to
and end the anime club
out of ignorance
or whatever excuse you make.
But those are the actions of
a bit character, not a hero!
You should strive to make
decisions for yourself,
so you can at least be the
main character in your own life!
That's what I do!
Because it's right and because
that's what anime taught me.
Now, I'm done!
[applause]
Huh?
You really can't see a thing
without your glasses on,
can you, Kaikai?
It's Kai.
And that's good, since
I couldn't see the crowd.
[MINOA] We won about
half of the male vote
but the female
vote really seemed
to swing things in our favor.
So now we have a club
and a club room.
[ERICA]
All right.
That's that.
It's happening. Again.
[ALICE]
It was hard fought,
but it really is nice to
have a place of our own!
[MIKO]
So relaxing.
[KAI] All opposition falters
before my god-like skills
when my power is unleashed!
Feel free to
worship me if you like!
[laughs]
[ERICA]
Hey, Mister Gomon.
Did you know things
would turn out this way?
[MASATO] It's more like,
the student council
would've shut you down sooner
or later if you
couldn't pull this off.
Apparently, there's a long
line of kids who have tried
to set up anime clubs
and the student council tears
them to pieces every time.
What does it matter to them?
Just a rumor. I don't know.
You like that one, too?
[MINOA]
Finally.
We're like a real club.
Your lecture on the
virtues of battle anime
has only just begun.
And you can dig even deeper
with the light novels.
Uh.
This is the beginning
of a long training arc!
Uh-oh.
In that case, I know
exactly what you need!
I can't watch all of these!
I don't have the time!
That's not true at all, Minoa!
We have a room, right?
We can watch all these together,
then quiz you on them
when we're done!
[shrieks]
[ERICA] We're still
doing cosplay, right?
[MINOA]
Not you too!
Some folks drop a show
at the first happy ending
and miss out on
a crazy plot twist!
Our next episode is
club room explosion.
That sound foreboding
enough for you?