[ERICA] And now, a toast,
to our smash hit anime premiere!
Cheers!
[ALL]
[MINOA]
Great job, you guys!
Studios have one
afterparty for the recording
and another for the show?
[KAI] Yes, and they
can get quite lavish!
At least that's what I heard.
Can't really blame them, though.
You gotta feel like all
that pain was worth it.
Supposedly, they hold
bingo competitions
and give out huge prizes.
I haven't heard
anything about bingo,
but I have seen pictures
on social media of cakes
with the characters
printed on them.
I imagine it's a good time to
make connections as well,
since the staff has
a rare opportunity
to leave their desks.
Ahhh. Hope I can go someday!
Since animators don't
go to fancy parties much,
I hear it's tough for them
to find something to wear.
And it can be a
challenge working
around everyone's schedules.
The actors and staff might
have already started working
on new shows, after all.
[MASATO] It must be tough
being so popular, huh?
I bet the writers
feel out of place.
It's so awkward.
Why? I don't get it.
[MIKO]
A lot of time passes between
when the script is written and
when they hold the after-party.
Oh, I get it.
The rest of the staff
just finished the show,
so they're in a completely
different mood than the writers.
They'd be happier without us.
No one wants writers anymore.
Come on, that's not true at all!
Pro'bly.
So, you hear anything from
the student council president?
Apparently, she came
down with something.
I haven't even seen her
at school since the festival.
[MASATO] Well, that makes
it easier for us at least.
Maybe I got my hopes
up a bit too much.
I got so wrapped up
in our happy ending,
I thought we could
be friends again.
I didn't know what to expect,
but that anime of yours
sure got me fired up!
I'm glad you enjoyed it,
but I'd be a lot happier
if we'd actually finished.
The audience
didn't seem to mind,
so I'd still call it a win.
It seems like all of
our hard work paid off!
Sure wish it would work
out that way for me.
What d'you mean?
I gave it my best shot,
but it's never quite
good enough for the win.
[MIKO] Did something
happen at track practice?
[YUI]
No.
I just can't jump
like I want to.
[MINOA]
Like, the high jump?
I can't seem to break my record.
Even though I practice
so hard every day.
That's a shame.
At times like these,
Musashisakai would say,
"Look to the saddle"!
Seems like sound advice.
Ah! Yeah!
Nakimushi Saddle
sure gets you pumped!
An anime?
It's a show about bike racing.
The characters are cute,
but it gets way intense!
Before you know it,
your heart starts racing
and you're cheering
at the TV like crazy!
It's not about track,
but I think you might find
it inspirational all the same.
[YUI]
Huh.
Sounds like it might be fun.
If you're interested...
...I can lend you my blu-rays.
You sure?
That would be awesome!
Didn't know you
watched anime, Yui.
[YUI]
Mm-hmm. I do these days.
I'm taking after you.
Once you get into it,
it's really fun.
Yeah, I know!
[ALICE]
I'll lend you more!
Just ask, any time!
[YUI]
♪ Hina... ♪
Morning, Yui!
[YUI]
♪ Hina, Hina. ♪
Oh!
Hey, how's it going?
Just fine I guess.
But what's that song?
You don't know the
Hina song from Saddle ?
Y'know, it's the one
that Azemichi sang!
[TORU] Everyone's running
and singing in perfect harmony!
Really does the trick!
Thanks to your song,
we might "hina" our way
straight to nationals!
Well, it's all thanks
to the anime club.
[RUNNERS]
Hina! Hina! Hina! Hina!
Great suggestion!
Yeah?
Glad you think so.
I'll see you in class, okay?
Bye!
Well, if it works for them,
I guess that's good.
A baseball anime?
The track club's kicking ass.
Our team needs to
step it up like them.
[PLAYERS]
We need anime!
I don't know.
You boys came
to the right club room.
Burning hearts!
Tough battles!
Victory!
Sports anime does it all,
with a heaping helping of drama!
So, take your pick!
Indeed!
There are a
bevy of sports titles
that're considered
anime classics!
For baseball, there's
Miracle Titans Mudou-kun ,
or if you want something
more recent: Ace of the Bench !
Sports shows have
tons of characters,
so there's always
someone you can relate to!
Even the adversaries on rival
teams become fan favorites!
The uniforms are great,
and they're perfect
for cosplay, too!
It's even more fun
if you've got a whole team
of friends to do it with you!
Which, of course, you do.
The often-mocked
hyperbolic training scenes
and wildly impractical
techniques seem silly
from an outsider point of
view, but once you watch,
you'll want to try them too!
[PLAYER A]
Take this! Lightning...!
[gasps]
[PLAYER A]
Mach Ball--
[ERICA]
Hey, Minoacchi!
How's it goin'?
I'm fine, but one question.
What's that?
[ERICA]
His pitch?
Mudou's Lightning
Mach Ball, of course.
If he gets hurt,
I feel like it's our fault.
Maybe we should stop him.
Hey, you see my moves?
It's still a work in progress,
but I'll get it soon enough!
Looking good!
A little training
and I'm sure you'll nail it!
Next group in line
can enter the club room!
Alice, what is going on?
Awesome is going on.
We're consulting
all the other clubs!
Said you've got a
grudge match coming up?
In that case, you need to watch
the Fresh Prince of Tennis:
Kanto Regionals !
And remember, "Build your empire
with a cool, collected mind."
Makes sense to me.
Thanks!
A robot competition, huh?
Then you need
Tengen Bakuha Guden Daran !
You'll be smashing through
both karma and fate!
Get ready to pierce the
heavens with your drill!
Yeah, big bro!
Your team doesn't
have a single win yet?
Simple enough!
Then Slash Dunk and Tarako's
Basketball are all you need!
If you give up,
the game's already over.
Anime club, I want
to play basketball!
Well, well, look at you, the
fancy-pants popular kids club!
I don't get it, either.
Hi-ya!
Prepare yourself!
It's time to unleash
the Frozen World!
I'll annihilate the
opposition basket and all!
Cower before my
Hammer of Destruction!
[ALICE] You want to
get better at mahjong?
Then just watch Shake !
Wow, mahjong sure
is fun, isn't it?
A band competition coming up?
Then Timbre! French Horn
is the anime for you!
Be sure to stand on a bridge and
yell, "I want to get better!"
I liked it better
when it was quiet in here.
[STUDENT A]
Hey, it's a kitty!
Are you part of the club, too?
He's just like Yabanyan, huh?
[STUDENT A]
So cute!
[MISTER KITTY]
Aw, cut it out.
Ok. See you later!
[MISTER KITTY]
Meow meow, ladies!
On second thought,
no harm in helping out
some cuties from time to time!
[AURORA]
I agree.
As long as
everyone's having fun,
why shouldn't we
share the joy of anime
with all the other clubs?
[MISTER KITTY]
Fair enough.
[MINOA]
Well, I guess so, but...
Wait! You were just chatting
with Mister Kitty
like it was normal!
You know he can talk?
[AURORA]
Mm-hmm.
By the way, do you know
what's my favorite part
of sports anime is?
Panning shots,
repeated in turbo!
Three in a row,
with big sound effects!
And old school
sketch filters, too.
[MISTER KITTY] Complete
with lights that go "shing!"
Not only are they friends,
they're in their own
little world without me.
[YUI]
Minoa!
Hey, what's up?
You tell me!
Sounds like the
anime club's hot stuff now!
You must be happy, huh?
Oh, these?
The robotics club
whipped them up for me.
Sweet, huh?
My speed is gonna
go through the roof!
[MINOA]
Huh?
[YUI] They said they got
the idea from some anime.
I mean, they look neat,
but isn't that cheating?
All I needed to break my record
was some robo foot wear!
'Kay, I'm heading
back to practice.
[MINOA]
Uhm...
Engage Dash Mode.
Yui, no!
Yikes! Are you okay?
You kidding?
That was awesome!
So cool.
[TORU] Obata, what have
I told you about Dash Mode?
Are you pumped for this
week's Show Up Rockin' ?
We could watch
it together, Minoa!
Dad is a fragile person,
you shouldn't break
his heart like that.
Hey, you're in the school
lacrosse club, right?
What do you guys do
at your practices?
Just the usual.
About what you'd expect.
There's a lot of
sprinting, I guess.
We practice our swinging.
That sorta thing.
Hypothetically, if you
could make a robo stick
that let you shoot super far,
then would you?
I don't need robo parts.
That'd be cheating.
That would only happen
in anime, obviously.
No kidding, huh?
[KAI] Ah, the martial arts club
is really working hard!
Their new training grounds
are coming along nicely!
Is all of that really necessary?
[ALICE] I heard they're going to
duel at the top of that pyramid.
[MINOA] Huh?!
That sounds super dangerous!
[ALICE]
Look, Minoa.
The volleyball go club!
[MINOA]
How does that work?
It's time.
Now, face your destiny!
This is the Hand of God!
Behold!
Our expert advice has
transformed their boring clubs
into something magnificent!
You're right!
It's like the whole school
is brimming with life!
Oh good, we found
you guys just in time.
The robotics club is
testing its prototype,
and you don't wanna miss it!
The fateful test launch begins!
[ALICE]
Let's go watch, Minoa!
Hold on.
A prototype of what now?
[SCIENCE BOY A]
King Sakaneko, test version one!
Legs-only prototype!
Activate!
[SCIENCE BOY A] Our scientific
prowess is unrivaled!
Bow before me!
Oh, that looks bad.
Real bad.
Well, hey, look at that.
You came prepared!
[KAI]
How strange.
It's usually the
mass-productions models
that are evil and go
roaring out of control.
Maybe they haven't
found the right pilot yet.
[ALICE]
Taking bets.
When do you think they'll get
that robot running properly?
Big news you guys!
Jeez, you're excited!
What's up?
[MASATO] A TV station
wants to interview us!
About what?
I'm clueless about TV.
It's just the
magic anime box to me!
[MASATO]
Well, that's fine,
'cause it turns out that this
has everything to do with anime!
They said they're doing
a special on our club,
'cause we revolutionized
the whole school
with the power of anime!
[MEMBERS gasp]
And we have you to thank!
Splendid work!
We'll be famous!
Amazing!
Uh-huh.
Look out, world!
Our era has arrived at last!
We're coming for you!
It's my big TV debut,
I can't believe it!
Why, yes, this beautiful,
young light novel author
would like a book deal.
I wonder what I should wear?
You think I should cosplay?
Oh! A shave!
I need a decent shave!
I can't let them know my secret.
I shall conceal the power of my
evil eye in front of the camera!
Ah...
Autographs!
I need to make a signature!
[MINOA]
Uh, see you guys tomorrow.
Everyone seems so happy.
I don't want to rain
on their parade.
The people in the other
clubs are having fun too.
But I dunno.
You feel like the
whole world's gone crazy,
and you're the
only one out there
who's got her head screwed
on straight anymore?
[MINOA]
Mm-hmm.
Well, don't worry,
you're not alone, kid.
You've always had someone
at your side you can count on.
[MINOA]
Huh?
Like Alice?
[MISTER KITTY]
Oh, come on!
Ugh. I'm done here!
You need support,
get it from him.
[MINOA]
Wait, who?
You left by yourself all of a
sudden, so I was a bit worried.
There's something worthwhile
you got out of the
anime club, isn't there?
Something irreplaceable?
I guess there's a whole
bunch of things I got, really.
Alice and Miko.
You and Kaikai and Erica.
Something to love and
people to talk to about it.
And happy memories, too.
More than I can count!
That's right.
Because anime has the power
to bring people together
and to bring them happiness too.
That's exactly what's
happening at our school.
[MINOA]
Huh?
[AURORA] Just like anime
brought us together, it gave us
a connection to all
the other students.
It would be wrong of us not to
share our happiness with them.
It works out best
for everyone this way!
You haven't done anything wrong
and neither has anyone
else in the anime club.
Otherwise, they wouldn't
be putting us on TV.
[MINOA]
You're right.
I didn't think of it that way.
[MASATO]
The Sakaneko Anime Club.
Believes that all
activities can benefit
from anime-style training.
And we're seeing
the results already!
My idea, by the way.
I admit, it seems
a bit absurd at first,
but if you want to break
through your shell and exceed
your limits, a certain degree
of daring is necessary.
In other words,
to achieve the impossible,
you can't be held
back by reality!
That's my philosophy!
That's my passion!
Free ideas, unrestrained
by common sense.
I think that unique approach
is what draws people to anime.
In our imagination,
humanity knows no limits.
Creativity gives us the strength
to believe we can go anywhere.
And that's the power of anime.
She's right!
Of course!
'Cause that's what I taught her!
This guy!
Anime Master, right here!
[TORU]
It's a new record!
[MINOA] Oh my gosh,
Yui, that was so cool!
That was crazy!
Congratulations!
I have you to thank!
I never even dreamed I could
accomplish something like this,
till you got me into anime!
[AURORA]
You haven't done anything wrong
and neither has anyone
else in the anime club.
[MINOA]
I was wrong.
This is wonderful!
I know it isn't much,
but here's a little "thank you."
Here take it. It's money.
[MASATO]
Oh, no, I can't.
It's no big deal,
Mr. Gomon, just take it.
We'll add it to our club budget.
[MASATO]
Uh, I dunno.
[AURORA] Just imagine,
you could buy another VHD deck.
[MASATO]
Very kind of you.
Great work you guys.
Think it's 'bout time
to call it a day.
[STUDENTS]
Okay.
[ALICE] What shall I
watch when I get home?
[MINOA]
How 'bout Dirlish Bumper ?
[MIKO] I like the
lead girl in that one.
She's really silly.
What was her catchphrase again?
With the laugh?
[ALICE]
It's in the bag! Gahaha!
Tsubaki is texting me?
[ERICA]
"Be careful"?
What the heck?
[MATSURI]
We have an announcement to make!
[AYAME] By order of the school,
the anime club...
...is hereby shut down!
[MATSURI]
They ignored us!
[ERICA] Yeah yeah,
heard that one before.
You two are becoming
comedic relief villains.
Not a good look.
[AYAME growls]
Sorry, but your mockery
comes to an end now.
Why, you ask?
Because the person
shutting you down...
...is none other
than this man here!
[MASATO]
The principal!
Is that who it is?
Never seen him before.
Yeah, not ringing
any bells here.
Are you kidding me?
You see him at the
front gate every morning,
you absolute imbeciles!
I'm still not piecing
this together.
[ALICE, MINOA]
His artwork's off model!
[MASATO]
Girls, stop.
[OGIKUBO] I never
thought I would step foot
in this room again.
Let alone under
circumstances like these.
"A-Again"?
[AYAME] Anyway, it's an order
from the principal this time,
so you don't get
to save your club
with some absurd challenge.
Yeah! But this is tyranny!
Do you even have a
reason to shut us down?
Sakaneko Academy Codebook.
Article 13 Section 2:
A club shall not receive money
for its activities
outside of allocations
approved by the academy itself.
[MASATO]
Receiving money?
Who's receiving money?
What did you do?
Not a darn thing!
[AURORA]
Come on, Mister Gomon.
I saw you take the money myself,
you might as well come clean.
I'm being honest.
The TV crew wrote a check.
And before you ask,
there was no mistaking it.
They were perfectly clear.
Wha...? But why?
Hah. You already bought
a new deck, didn't you?
[ALICE]
Mr. Gomon!
Don't spend club funding
without asking us first!
[MIKO]
You are so out of touch here.
Ahem! At any rate, the club is
now defunct, and Mister Gomon,
you're suspended from your job.
No way!
You've done well.
Much appreciated.
Nakano, why?
What is this?
Aurora!
What the hell, Aurora?
You're our friend!
Do me a favor.
Don't call me that
name ever again.
[AURORA laughs]
A traitor must
never be forgiven.
This is the code that the
Cat Knighthood must live by!
Someone, will change their ways.
Next time, betrayal.
I know your name well!