[NAOFUMI]
All right, the lighthouse
and its barrier should be
under our control now.
And the embers of rebellion
have been fanned into a flame.
Now, before we try tackling
any other problems
I want to go
over some things.
First of all... hold up.
What's with
the pitiful expressions?
I thought you'd be more excited
about all of this happening.
I'm so sorry.
It's just that...
[AIDE] W... water!
Was it really necessary
to challenge all of them
to a drinking
competition?
I did?
Goodness grief.
At this rate
[scoffs]
Well, start shaking off
those hangovers
'cause we don't have time
to waste here.
[FILO groans]
If you can
exactly where
the emperor should be.
We can negotiate
or kill them
[RALUVA]
I'd be happy to.
The current emperor of Q'ten Lo
resides here, in the capital.
Really?
That's not where they lived
back when I was living here.
Well, you see
took over the throne
So that's how it is.
But the home of the old
emperor still exists.
It's just called
the "old capital" now.
Our best bet would be
to start our conquest there.
Oh, wow.
You've thought
about this.
What do you mean?
You see
is where the previous emperors
would take the royal throne.
So if Raphtalia were
to do the ritual there
she'd be able to use
the blessings
like any other emperor.
- Oh.
- Pretty smart.
Having an advantage like
that is bound to help us
in any of our
future battles.
It's strange though.
Why would they go
and abandon the old capital?
It's so risky.
Yes, it is, but the emperor's
puppet master of an advisor
Makina
Makina?
Does that mean
she's still around?
Unfortunately, yes.
- And she's evil.
- Evil, huh?
Great.
In that case
a pretty good chance
she comes after us
now that we've taken
her lighthouse.
Meaning we need to be
prepared to deal with her.
[RALUVA] Yes, sir!
Now then
we should have Raphtalia
wear her miko outfit
and have a parade
to raise the people's spirits.
I understand
your thinking behind that
but why would me wearing my
miko outfit help boost morale?
It looks good!
Raph!
Uh. [Laughs awkwardly]
[distant boom]
Now what?
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
EPISODE 8: OROCHI
[stirring music]
They're attacking
us already?
That or the big party
that was going on in town
just got way
out of hand.
But it didn't sound
like either of those.
I can feel a strange flow
of energy now.
What was that?
Did anyone else
hear that sound?
I don't see how
they couldn't.
[chirping]
Huh?
Look, over there!
[eerie music]
That's where
the old burial mound is.
What's going on?
[SOLDIER] M... monsters!
I can't see
everything clearly
it looks like multiple
snake monsters.
Snake monsters?
What?
[MURAMASA]
Hey, kid.
I guess I shouldn't be too
surprised that the government
isn't holding back
against us
but freeing a monster
from its seal?
That seems a little
overboard, even for them.
Its seal?
Do you know anything
about this?
I don't answer questions
from other men!
And why would I tell someone
who's too dumb to make a harem
when he obviously could?
This idiot!
[grumbles]
Raphy.
All right then.
How's about telling
little ol' me about it?
Anything for you, dear!
Well, I'll tell you
whatever you want.
There's an old ruin
in the mountains over there.
Within those same ruins
a monster that once brought
disastrous harm
to this country
is sealed away.
However, the legend
the government's peddled
is that the emperor
defeated it.
But in reality
Up till now, I had only
ever heard it was defeated.
Well, considering
the location of the ruins
it makes sense only
a few know the truth
about the
monster's fate.
But I am the government's
favorite blacksmith
so of course I know.
[NAOFUMI] Why lie
and say it was defeated?
Hmm.
They said that the reason they
sealed it here was in order
to help strengthen the barrier
that separates Q'ten Lo
from the rest
of the world.
It acts as a
protective god.
There are ruins
just like the one
I mentioned scattered
across the country.
[NAOFUMI] So you're saying
the government
has multiple monsters sealed
away and revived one of them?
[MURAMASA]
Yes, exactly.
And there's
another problem.
Well, this did happen a little
while ago, but listen to this.
The current emperor
decided they really liked
all the monsters
and wanted to reduce the strain
on our protector gods.
The best idea that
they could come up with
in order to do that was
granting them the blessings and
the Sakura
Emperor's stones.
Are they idiots?
They went and strengthened
a giant monster
that brought disaster
to their country
then chose to revive it?
We could barely beat that
bear creature from yesterday!
Master Naofumi
[NAOFUMI] It's a pain
Huh?
What if the first
thing you do
as emperor is defeating
a giant monster
like that, one that
the government intentionally
freed to hurt
its citizens
the entire country
knows about it?
Oh, if that happens...
Mhm.
It will show the people
their government hates them
and that a revolutionary
army is here now
to fight on
their behalf.
[SOLDIER 1]
Revolutionaries?
[SOLDIER 2] Now, that's
something I can get behind.
But for this to work
before it reaches town!
Gaelion!
[squawking]
Speed's our priority.
We'll split up and have Gaelion
and Filo bring us there.
Sounds good to me.
I don't know if brother
will help much
but we're coming
along to fight it.
Yeah.
Wait, Atla!
[wings flapping]
[stirring music]
Go on.
We'll follow your lead.
Show us the way.
♪♪
No way is Gaelion
beating me there!
Ah!
[MURAMASA] Hey, ladies
just remember, you can feed
that loser to the monsters
and run away!
Come on, master
[chuckles]
[thrilling music]
I have a feeling
a hydra will be
rather difficult
to deal with.
[NAOFUMI]
Seven and eight.
It's not multiple
monsters.
You're right, Gaelion.
It's an eight-headed
hydra we're fighting.
[SADEENA] Holy ropes
and the Sakura Emperor's Stone.
We can assume
it's been blessed.
[NAOFUMI] So they did go out
of their way to power it up.
[whoosh]
With the Sakura Emperor's
Stone barrier and the blessing
that hydra is going to weaken
the hero's protection
if we end up
getting too close to it.
We have to destroy it
before it reaches the town.
[humming]
[GAELION] I'm beginning
to sense draconic power.
The water dragon may
be trying to help us.
Well, that's awfully nice
of him, but...
It's not going
to last forever.
Which means
we have to finish it.
Right.
I'll make use of the Sakura
Sphere of Influence.
[whoosh]
[boom]
Itsuki, where's your Sakura
Emperor's Stone weapon?
[ITSUKI] Here!
[RISHIA]
It's ready to go!
Hey, I can help
too, you know.
The blacksmiths gave me
this earlier!
[NAOFUMI] I see.
So this is making up
for the hero
stat buffs that
were nullified.
You did a
fine job, Elhart.
[ATLA] Quit squirming.
Just give me
one of the stones
But didn't he
give you one, too?
Yes, but I didn't like
the way
that creep was
touching my hands
so I went and threw
it away right after.
That's enough.
Atla, you're to stay back and
help Itsuki, S'yne, and Rishia.
Got it?
Huh?
Oh, I understand.
All right.
Sakura Sphere
of Influence
[magical beams]
[roars]
Ready or not,
here I come!
[boom]
[NAOFUMI]
It doesn't have much defense
but Gaelion
called it a hydra
[squelching]
I knew it.
I'm not done yet!
Huh?
[FOHL] Hope you don't
mind me taking a lift!
Ah!
[boom]
Raphy.
[NAOFUMI]
Aim for the torso!
I think it's weak there!
OK!
Ah!
[clank]
It's strong!
Huh?
[whimpering]
[flames blaze]
[GAELION] It's absorbing
part of the Dragon Vein.
We can't dispel it
unless we cut off
all eight heads that are
generating the barrier at once.
What's the plan?
We don't have time
to wait around.
I know!
Everyone, listen!
Raphtalia will be the first
to attack the hydra.
After she destroys
its magical protection
we'll chop off all its heads
at once and finish it off!
Got it?
Understood.
Sadeena, do a choral
magic spell with me!
Ready when you are!
Go!
[whoosh]
[roars]
[boom]
Supreme Ultimate
Slash of Destiny!
[squelch]
[chittering]
[flames blaze]
Filo, trigger
the hydra's barrier!
[FILO] On it!
Ah!
[boom]
[chittering]
The Sakura Emperor's Stone
should now be nullified.
Good.
Now it's our turn!
Summon Thunder God!
[electric crackle]
I'm not letting you guys
have all the fun!
[boom]
Ah!
Eagle piercing shot!
Hengen Muso Secret
Technique, Rolling Spin!
[boom]
[wires squeaking]
Critical wire!
[squelch]
Drifa.
Chain Lightning!
[electric crackle]
Hurry, Raphtalia!
Stardust Blade!
[Shing]
[squelch,
resounding thud]
That was a whole lot easier
than I thought it'd be.
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, no kidding.
[RALUVA] Raphtalia!
[NAOFUMI] Well, look
who decided to show up.
Hmm?
[rumbling]
[NAOFUMI] What the?
This is certainly
strange.
It's like...
[squelching]
It isn't finished
with us.
Run away!
[panicked screams]
[ominous music]
[boom]
Meteor Shield!
[crackling]
♪♪
The barrier!
[NAOFUMI]
This is bad.
[GAELION] It would appear
our enemy
is more formidable
than we thought.
[chittering]
[NAOFUMI] What?
♪♪
It's back, but it
looks purple now!
[NAOFUMI] Is this one different
from the one we fought before?
[GAELION] Both it and the one
before aren't the real body.
Destroying the real one
won't be so easy.
I'll stop it from
advancing!
Me too!
[hissing]
Whatever happened, it
seems stronger than before.
[whimpering]
[NAOFUMI] Is there some
way to deal with this?
[GAELION]
It's a type of dragon.
I'm sure of that.
And you know a little
about dragons, right?
Then there's a core.
So that's why the last
one didn't have one.
Which means the real core
is inside of there.
Meaning our best bet is
to keep those monsters
from exploding while we
steal the core back, right?
[GAELION] Yes.
Only the empty shells
will remain.
[NAOFUMI] What do we do with
the core after we get it?
[GAELION] I, the weakest
Dragon Emperor
will have
to restrain it.
[NAOFUMI] Can you?
[GAELION]
If it's just the core
even the weakest of us
should be able to do it.
Ah!
[slice, squelch]
[lightning crashes]
[tense music]
♪♪
The hydra seems to only
be targeting Raphtalia.
My best guess
is that she probably
reminds the hydra of the
emperor that sealed it away.
I'm not sure
I like that.
We could use the fact that
it's targeting her to lure
it away from
here, but...
[NAOFUMI] Yeah, but there's
no way to nullify the hydra's
protection
without Raphtalia.
There's enough of us
here to handle it.
And we have a strong army
here to help us, too.
Oh, right.
Fine, then.
Raphtalia, Sadeena
you're coming with me.
The rest of you
We need you
to buy us time, not kill it!
Understood.
Yeah, 'cause I definitely
planned on killing it.
Oh, why did I have to throw
away my weapon earlier?
I'll be right here
to provide you backup, Atla.
We're here to help you
however we can.
Quick, one of you go
and evacuate the town.
Yes, sir!
[growls]
[NAOFUMI] Let's go!
Zweit Thunder Burst!
Meteor Shot!
[lightning crackles]
[coughs]
Are you OK, Raphtalia?
Yes, barely.
[NAOFUMI] It's not magic
terrible in
the air here.
We can't stay too long.
Whatever it is, it's taking
over this protective barrier.
We have to hurry before
they end up freeing any
of the other
sealed beasts.
[NAOFUMI] Damn it.
The government here
really is run by idiots.
Hmm.
[mysterious music]
I can read this.
Is this the hero
language, then?
"How to strengthen
the cardinal shield weapon."
[humming]
[shimmering]
I'm sensing magic.
I'll read the
rest out loud.
"How to strengthen the cardinal
shield weapon, method one.
Share the methods
of getting stronger
with the other cardinal
weapons or vassal weapons."
I already knew that.
This is worthless.
But is that
everything it says?
Maybe if Ren
or Itsuki reads it
it'll say something
different.
I'll have to bring
them here later.
[humming]
Is it below?
No, it's not!
Everyone stand back!
[rumbling]
Ah!
[splash]
That was awfully close.
What a waste of time
that was.
[GAELION] Not quite.
After all, the real one
is coming out now.
[rumbling]
[thrilling music]
The purple light glowing from
its body must be the core.
So we have to repeat
what we did before?
[GAELION]
This one is stronger.
It appears to be
gradually absorbing
the power that dispersed
into the Dragon Veins.
[RISHIA] Sorry, but I don't
know how much longer we
can hold this one back.
You heard the girl.
Let's hurry it up.
After all, you like
things done fast
and without
causing a fuss
What's got you
so cooperative?
I always am
to rule this
country, Naofumi.
I don't want it
getting ruined.
Well, I don't know if I'll
be the one who's ruling it.
[SADEENA] Either way, I just
want to help however I can.
[NAOFUMI] Good, 'cause
I need your help right now.
Sadeena.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI] You can do
a beast transformation too.
- Oh, my.
- [NAOFUMI] Want to try?
[SADEENA] Of course.
Is there any
other choice?
OK, let's do this.
Sakura Sphere
of Influence!
[laughs]
[mystical music]
♪♪
Amazing!
I can feel power
flowing through my body!
It must be
Naofumi's love!
Is that really what she
looks like when transformed?
I can sense her power
from here.
[SADEENA] I think I can hear
the Water Dragon's voice.
I feel unstoppable!
[NAOFUMI] Then quit
yapping and do something!
[SADEENA] I'm on it.
Oh, is this
how I say it?
Thunder God!
[thunder cracking]
And now Sea God!
[chittering]
Is this the true form
of the Water Dragon's miko?
It's like a battle
of the gods.
[SADEENA]
Let's finish this, Raphtalia!
Right!
[electric crackle]
♪♪
Supreme Ultimate
Slash of Destiny!
Nice!
Its protection's gone.
Finish it!
[epic music]
♪♪
Kagura Dance of Sakura
Ah.
I... incredible.
With these
folks leading us
and their evil advisor
Makina won't stand a chance!
Stand proud and let
loose the victory cry!
[soldiers chant
and laugh]
I have no doubt in my mind
that this is supposed
to be the hydra's core.
[RAPHTALIA]
But it's a sword.
The cursed blade
of Ama-no-Murakumo.
Just touching it would
be enough to curse you.
Well, if that's the case
So what do we do?
[MURAMASA]
Oh, looks like you got it!
[ELHART]
That was amazing.
Look, I had heard rumors that
your fights can get pretty
intense, but
that was insane!
No kidding.
[MURAMASA] Wow, that blade
sure looks mighty sharp.
This must be
the hydra's real body.
Wait!
[mystical music]
Oh, shut up.
Calm yourself.
[sighs] This thing's
packing a serious curse
so we can't
use it for a while.
How are you just holding it
without getting cursed?
I am a blacksmith,
aren't I?
And blacksmiths don't allow
weapons to curse them.
That's my master for ya!
OK, can you make sure it
doesn't go out of control then?
[scoffs]
That's not my problem!
It may not affect you
then people will suffer.
I just wish you
had asked me earlier.
I'd be honored to be
of service, young lady.
What an idiot.
Anyway, now that
the hydra's taken care of
we have to make sure the whole
country knows about it
that they hear all about how
the revolutionary army and
their new emperor destroyed the
government's monster before it
was able to hurt anyone.
[chuckles] So we're the good
guys who saved the day, huh?
It's just a performance.
No one's actually making
you become emperor.
Yeah, I guess not.
[RALUVA]
Is this... sorry, I've been
wondering since before
the battle started.
[NAOFUMI] Yes, she is
Sure am!
My name is Filo.
Nice to meet you.
[NAOFUMI] She gets special
powers if a hero raises her.
Incredible.
That white form.
A Filolial with
a sakura-colored pattern!
It's so perfect and will only
help serve to our advantage
even more.
[soft flute music]
Hmm?
[theme music
and Japanese singing]
♪♪
EPISODE 9: ZODIA