[stirring music]
[GAELION] According
to the Water Dragon
the barrier is controlled
from that lighthouse.
If we're going to regroup
with those on the ship
we'll have to disable
the barrier.
I'd like to get them
in port as fast as we can.
[sighs] Well, for the time
being, their stats seem OK.
♪♪
[ELHART] Feels like
no matter what we do
we can't get any
closer to land.
No kidding.
I hope that the others
are OK out there.
Master Naofumi.
Raphy says they're fine
Ugh! I don't have to worry
about Master Naofumi
but that doesn't mean that
I still can't miss him!
Huh?
[shimmering]
(distorted) Where
did Naofumi go?
[grunts]
[SADEENA]
Here we are!
I don't know about this.
[NAOFUMI]
I think it looks great.
[gasps]
Not to mention
it hides your face.
- [chuckles awkwardly]
- Oh, and Raphtalia
make sure that you don't
let your tail and ears show.
Right. Oh.
What is this?
It's proof that
the Water Dragon
has vowed to protect us.
It's actually an object
of worship in this country.
So it's something holy?
Well, if we're all
done changing, let's go.
[ALL] Mm.
[NAOFUMI] Our top
priority right
now is to break
that barrier.
[theme music]
♪♪
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
♪ Hey, no need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Nothing standing
in our way ♪
♪ Fight it right now ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
♪ Don't let it go ♪
♪ Don't tell me
nor anyone else ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I will protect
your resolution ♪
♪ No matter
what comes next ♪
♪ 'Cause every time
again I stand my ground ♪
♪ We'll never
lose and cry ♪
♪ Now nobody can
stop us, no way ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
♪ We protect
our resolution, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, no need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Nothing standing
in our way ♪
♪ Fight it right now ♪
♪ Hey, no need
for hesitation ♪
[singing in Japanese]
EPISODE 7:
"ARRIVING IN Q'TEN LO"
[RAPHTALIA]
It really is beautiful here.
[SADEENA] Come nightfall, the
Sakura Lumina begin to shine.
They're also used as an energy
source for a lot of tools.
[NAOFUMI] Why don't
we take some home
and grow them
in our village?
[SADEENA] The thing is
properly in
this country.
[NAOFUMI]
I see.
Are they fishing out there?
[SADEENA] Looks like
they're gathering seaweed.
[GAELION]
It would be a lot easier
if we could
just fly there.
Until we get ourselves
shot out of the sky
it's better to play it
safe and travel by land.
♪♪
[waves lapping gently]
This place is bizarre.
It's like Japanese
Raphtalia land.
[RAPHTALIA]
Why all the decorations?
[SADEENA] They're put there
in honor of the emperor's clan.
[NAOFUMI] So the emperor's
clan is loved by the people?
I don't understand.
If the emperor is adored
then why did
my mom and dad
have to leave Q'ten Lo?
[sighs]
[boy screaming]
What's going on?
[grunts]
[whimpers]
- Master Naofumi.
- On it.
Hold on.
Huh?
Do your thing, Gaelion.
[chirrups]
It's best you two
stay out of this.
[yelling]
[whimpers]
[NAOFUMI]
Can you stand?
[screams]
Hey, wait!
What was that about?
How could you?
Why do such a thing?
Aren't you scared what
the magistrates will do?
[footsteps approaching]
[staffs clanging]
[tense music]
Am I correct to assume
that you killed that monster?
Is it really so wrong
to save a helpless kid?
I'm afraid you're mistaken
because all that happened here
was one monster
devouring another one.
[crowd gasping]
Enough of the lies.
Would you disobey
the emperor?
Of course not.
You seem like a smart
enough fellow
which means you know what this
monster here is, don't you?
A servant
of the Water Dragon?
[gasping]
Please forgive us!
[PEASANT 1] Are they
messengers of the Water Dragon?
[PEASANT 2] They must be
if they have that orb.
I can't believe
it's gotten this bad.
Huh?
[MURAMASA] Splendidly
done, young lady.
Huh?
[crowd murmuring]
[MURAMASA] While everyone else
was too scared to speak up
you went and took action
to save that child's life.
I think anyone
with a conscience
would have done
the same thing.
Your actions have
moved me, young lady.
You've won my heart.
Huh?
My name's Muramasa.
It'd be my pleasure
to buy you a cup of tea.
Sorry, but what is
it you think I did?
That's very kind of you
Oh, you're unbelievably
beautiful, too!
Please, I beg of you
[NAOFUMI] He's going
after every girl he sees
like Motoyasu.
How very kind.
But I am taken.
And like I said before, we
are in a bit of a hurry here.
Oh, come on.
Don't say that to me.
[SADEENA]
Zweit Thunderbolt!
[screaming]
You've got some
kick to you, huh?
[gasps]
Looks like we've
attracted a crowd.
We should get a move on.
Yeah, no kidding.
Let's hurry
up and leave.
[SADEENA] Agreed.
[RAPHTALIA]
What a strange old man.
[crowd murmuring]
[sighs] What the hell
was all that about?
The magistrates were
upset because the emperor
forbids killing all living
things, even big monsters.
[gasps]
Sounds like the beliefs
of one of the old shoguns.
Do you mind explaining
what a shogun is?
In any case, I'm
glad Gaelion was here.
[chirrups]
So what you're
saying is they can't
punish a monster for the
killing of another
monster, huh?
Well, if the monster's
owner made them do it
I'm sure the owner
would be punished.
But they can't do
anything if it's
a servant of the
Water Dragon.
It sounds like we made
the best use of what
the Water
Dragon gave us.
Hmm.
Which means it's illegal
to even fish in this country.
That is exactly correct.
That's why those fishermen
were gathering seaweed.
[FISHERMAN]
Please don't!
If you take that
Those who don't
pay their taxes
are no different
than mere traitors!
[grunts] But, sir
Do you mean to say that you
would disobey the emperor?
[sighs]
[somber music]
Raphtalia.
We might just be able
to use this to our advantage.
Huh?
I can't imagine that
too many of the citizens
are very happy
about this law.
Hmm.
Hmm, what's wrong?
We're not alone.
♪♪
A magistrate?
I couldn't say.
[NAOFUMI]
We'll use invisibility magic.
[SADEENA] Right.
[gasps]
[mysterious music]
Forgive me!
Wherever you are, please
know I am not your enemy.
The sea people
have shared with me
the words of the
Water Dragon.
I've sought you out to welcome
you here with open arms.
If you are still here
- [NAOFUMI] Raphtalia.
- Huh?
[SADEENA] He must
be telling the truth.
The timing would be
far too convenient.
[NAOFUMI] Hey.
[grunts]
Get off your knees
and face us.
Mm.
So, um...
You have our attention.
So let's hear who you
are and what you want.
My name is Luminus.
My father is Raluva
[NAOFUMI]
Just get to the point!
But, sir...
You can relax.
There's no need for all
the formalities.
Then so be it.
In that case, the people
here in this city
are in desperate
need of your help.
But why seek
us for help?
Take a look around.
It doesn't take
much to see
what's been
happening here.
You mean the "no killing
living things" law?
And the taxes
are horrible.
Some of the people
are even starving.
This can't continue.
This tyranny must
come to an end!
So the people aren't
happy with the emperor.
Is that it?
And there's more.
Allow me to explain
back at the mansion.
Would you be willing
to come with us right now?
I suppose it couldn't
hurt to hear him out.
I don't see why not.
Don't get any ideas about
setting us up for a trap.
Look, I would
never do that!
If I somehow
offended you
I'll happily strike
myself down.
My name is Raluva.
I'm the city mayor.
If it's not too
much trouble
of looking
upon your face?
[men gasp]
Ah. I see now you resemble
that of your father.
So wait. Then does that
mean you knew him?
Your father was
very kind to me.
I'm starting
to remember things now.
You were close with
him, weren't you?
You're the former miko
of the Water Dragon.
It's been a while.
My name is
Naofumi Iwatani
I'm familiar with you.
Though we haven't met
You have my eternal thanks
for keeping Raphtalia safe.
I thought this
place was cut off
but you know about
the outside world.
Why, yes. After all
That makes sense.
Well, let's cut
the chit-chat.
What exactly do you
mean you want our help?
Mm.
What we want
for Raphtalia
to take the throne
and put an end
to this government.
Take the throne?
Do... do you
really mean...
We came to this country
to work things out
with whoever it
was that's sending
assassins
after Raphtalia.
Once things have been
settled, we'll be leaving.
I am aware
of your intentions.
And you're not
opposed to that?
If she would become
a puppet emperor
she would be no different
than the current one
and all the people would
still be suffering.
For the sake
of the world
They should be
a driving force of good.
Even Raphtalia's father
felt the same way.
[gasps] Is that
the reason he left?
I had no idea it had
to do with all of this.
That isn't the
only reason.
In that time, there was an ugly
fight over who was to be
crowned the
next emperor.
[clattering,
woman screaming]
[woman sobbing]
If he stayed
in this country, it
would have meant accepting
a most horrible death.
So that's it.
We've waited up until
this very moment, the moment
the true emperor finally
returned and put an end, once
and for all, to the tyranny
we've been facing.
So what is your plan
going forward?
First, eliminate
the magistrates
guarding the lighthouse.
That will likely
start a revolution.
If I'm not mistaken
Do you have all
your troops ready?
I have my clan, also
the people of the town
all of which are
ready to rise up.
Good.
Master Naofumi.
Raphtalia, get
the miko outfit.
[men gasping]
Are you positive?
If I wear it, then
that means...
[RALUVA] Here.
The second I wear
this, we'll be attacked.
Well, they're going to be
coming after us anyway.
And it's always better
to have more allies.
I understand, but...
I want to get
that barrier down
fast so we can finally regroup
with those on the ship.
And besides, just look.
Judging from their eyes
a long time
for a sign of hope to appear.
I'll help you put it on.
[men gasping]
[men grunting in unison]
Oh, don't do that.
WATER DRAGON'S
MIKO DRESS - CRUDE
Please, Emperor, we ask
that you guide us to victory.
Just say the word.
We're ready to follow
your every command.
Proud citizens
of Q'ten Lo, hear me now!
[MEN] Huh?
The true emperor
has returned to you!
Now is your chance to finally
put an end to this government.
Offer up your hearts, and the
true emperor will lead you.
For Q'ten Lo!
For the people!
Come with us if you
want to fight back!
[men yelling in unison]
[soft music]
♪♪
Master Naofumi, you imitated
Atla to get them fired up.
And it worked
brilliantly.
I'm getting excited
just thinking about it!
It's better if we
take the lead.
I don't want any
unnecessary casualties.
[sighs] I understand.
We can't avoid this
[tense music]
[footsteps marching]
Halt right there!
You approach holy
ground belonging
to the emperor himself.
Go and tell your leader
that the true emperor requests
an audience with them.
You must be the false
emperor and the holders
of the evil spirit
implements!
We don't negotiate
with traitors!
Eliminate them!
[dramatic music]
[NAOFUMI]
Can't say I didn't expect this.
Attack!
[yelling]
[yells]
Meteor shield!
If you think
that'll work
[sword clanging
Gah! Damn it!
The bastard blinded me!
You weren't the only ones
getting ready for this!
All Zweit Aura!
Raphtalia.
Right!
[blasting]
[grunts]
Follow the true
emperor into battle!
Yes, Father!
[men yelling]
[chirrups]
Now's our chance!
Let's go!
Right!
♪♪
This is the lighthouse.
[RAPHTALIA]
If we can put out that fire...
[staff clanging]
What are you lot doing?
Stop dawdling
around like fools
and strike down
the false emperor!
This guy must
be the boss.
It would seem so.
[BEARGA] Coward who
claims to be the emperor
you shall soon feel
the mighty wrath of I
Bearga, he who has been blessed
by the one true emperor!
[staff clanging]
- What the hell?
- What happened?
The protection Naofumi gave
us, he somehow disabled it.
That stone!
A Sakura emperor stone!
That weapon weakens
the power of spirit
implements and increases
the power of anyone
blessed by the emperor.
Sounds like
the perfect weapon
for stopping
cardinal heroes.
Here I come!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Zweit aura!
It's able to block
hero magic, too?
Kill the traitors
at all costs!
[men yelling]
A source of thy
power, I order thee
decipher the
laws of nature
and strike down my foes
where they stand.
All Drifa Chain
Lightning!
[lightning crackling
Whatever happens, I won't
let any harm come your way
so rest easy
knowing that!
She's not the only one
who can lend a hand here!
[roars]
[grunts]
[groans] I know you.
You're the miko
of slaughter.
And yet, you would oppose
us, despite your wickedness?
Why, yes. Now, let's get this
slaughter started, shall we?
[NAOFUMI]
What do we do?
- [MAN] Get them!
- [gasps]
Kill the false emperor
and holder of the evil
spirit implements!
Drifa aqua slash!
Drifa rock blast!
- [groans] Sadeena!
- [MEN] Ah!
[laughs] That was pretty
clever, even for you, Naofumi!
[grumbles]
[laughs] You're
actually not half bad
but this fight
ends here!
[MEN] (chanting) We carry
out this secret act on behalf
of the emperor,
the Pacifier.
We turn our whole
selves into blades
combining power of thine
eye and bringing a destiny
of destruction
to these fools.
Don't tell me...
Astral Enchant
What is this?
Now, then, it's
time to end this!
[growls] Is that
all you've got?
[grunts] The hell
kind of power is that?
The power of Astral
Enchant, an enchantment
that allows those
blessed by the emperor
to gather the powers
of others who've been blessed.
And as you can see
Ha!
[coughs]
They're sharing
life energy, too?
- [laughs sinisterly, yells]
- Ah!
[grunts]
[RAPHTALIA]
Sadeena!
Gaelion!
[roars]
[gasps]
[laughs] Is this
pathetic display all
the false emperor
can manage?
Say what you will
Let's see you win
when you're dead!
[MURAMASA]
Try using this!
[grunts] Huh?
What the?
SAKURA EMPEROR'S
STONE SHIELD
Sakura Emperor
Stone Shield?
[MURAMASA] That should
help boost your abilities
a little more, even
when inside the Sakura
Emperor's Stone barrier.
It's you again!
Traitor! How dare you?
Why would you help
the false emperor like this?
I'm no traitor!
In case you forgot
lies with the side who
has the hot chicks!
Oh, oh!
I have no idea
what's happening
but I'm gonna use this!
APPLY SKILL POINTS?
I feel my power
coming back.
Hmm.
Now we can fight back.
You got that right!
Give 'em hell, girls!
I'm gonna tear you
all limb from limb!
Sakura Sphere
of Influence, Attack Support!
[groans]
- Raphtalia!
- Right!
Kagura Dance
of Sakura, Blossom!
You ready, Gaelion?
Touch the Sakura Lumina!
Hey!
Be gentle!
[groans] Crap!
This is really bad!
The barrier is
under my control!
OK. Sadeena!
In the sealed land
of the heavenly emperor
the feelings of its people
washes away the tyranny of old.
Once stagnant water
becomes a stream.
Dragon vein
I, Gaelion, give my orders
to the heavens and the Earth.
Sever the laws of reality
and bind them together.
Lend me your strength
the power to destroy
the foolish disciple
standing before me!
[GAELION, SADEENA]
Water Dragon, Sakura Lumina
Destroying Wave!
[screams]
Supreme Ultimate
Ah!
I'm not done!
No.
It's over.
[screams]
[men cheering]
[MURAMASA]
We did it!
[chuckles softly]
[waves lapping gently]
[serene music]
♪♪
Master, I always
knew you were safe!
Raphy!
Master Naofumi!
Looks like
everyone is OK.
It feels like
it's been forever.
It does.
[grunts] Master
Sorry for getting here
late, Master Naofumi!
Oh! [Grunting]
Oh.
[grunts]
S'yne's here?
She must
have teleported.
She says she couldn't bear
to wait for you to get back.
(distorted) I'm
glad you're OK.
Who said you could
hug him before me?
Get off! It's my turn!
Would it kill you
to behave for once?
What is all this?
Some kind of harem?
No way.
I'm glad to see
that you're safe.
Wait.
Master?
Huh?
Hmm?
Is that you, Elhart?
How have you been?
Seriously?
This guy is your...
Yeah.
You must be tired from
being stuck on that ship.
How's about we have
us a little tea?
- I respectfully decline!
- Oof!
[RAPHTALIA] I guess he's
even more of a ladies' man
than we were told.
[NAOFUMI]
Now it makes sense why
he agreed to
help us earlier.
Well, now that
everyone's here
we should have
a victory party!
[yells]
- [excited chatter]
- Huh? Wait.
Don't just
leave me here.
Hey, wait for me!
[theme music]
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
EPISODE 8: "OROCHI"