[NAOFUMI] Raluva told us there
was once a Filolial Queen
one that
looked like Filo
that was worshipped
throughout Q'ten Lo.
Because of that
as we began our march
to the old capital.
The effect
was incredible.
We were welcomed
in every town we passed.
Not to mention we were able
to garner their support
without having to
raise a sword.
I can't believe she's having
such an incredible effect
- on people.
- [laughter]
Funny you say that, 'cause
the same could be said
for you, Raphtalia.
Huh?
He's correct.
Seeing you
in their clothes
will cause any
who are unsatisfied
with the current emperor
to join our cause.
It will help us expand
our forces even more.
Right.
Thanks to you and that
big divine bird of yours
the old capital
is growing near.
For the next few days
as we have to wait for the rear
units to catch up to us.
I don't love the idea
of stopping our march
but I understand.
Once the old capital
is in our control
the imperial
succession ceremony
will be at the
Holy Grounds.
Ah.
It'll give you
the emperor's powers.
But in no way does it mean you
have to become the emperor.
So try not to let it
worry you too much.
I'll try my best.
[rustling]
Hmm.
Oh, dear.
This way?
That way?
Where are they?
I heard they were
somewhere around here.
But where?
Huh?
Is that them?
All right.
That way!
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
[theme music]
♪♪
♪ No need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Nothing standing
in our way ♪
♪ Fight right now ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
♪ The reason that I choose
to fly when I travel ♪
♪ Prove that I exhale ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Leaving no regrets ♪
♪ It seems like
a never-ending genocide ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
♪ Let the pieces
of your story grow ♪
♪ Don't let it go ♪
♪ Cause you don't want
me nor anyone else ♪
♪ No limit to
where we go ♪
♪ I will rock the show ♪
♪ No matter
what comes next ♪
♪ 'Cause every time again
I stand my ground ♪
♪ We never losing prey ♪
♪ Now nobody can
stop us no way ♪
♪ We break
through every time ♪
♪ It was just pushing
through the frame ♪
♪ To something that
we can stake out ♪
♪ Even if there's no end
to this road ♪
♪ We protect
our resolution ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Hey, no need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Nothing standing
in our way ♪
♪ Fight right now ♪
♪ Hey, no need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ No space for it ♪
♪ Go now ♪
EPISODE 9: ZODIA
So I take it our enemies
still don't want
a ceasefire with us?
The imperial advisor
would never allow that.
I've been hearing reports
that the government's army
is gathering
at the old capital.
Sounds like they're ready
to go to war against us.
The emperor's
personal troops are led
by the Water Dragon Miko
who has already entered
the capital.
What information
do we have on them?
Unfortunately, we've sent
many spies to find out.
But not a single one
has returned.
Hmm.
I really wish
I could help
has happened
here since I left.
I'm sure it's someone
from my clan, but...
So even if we get
to the old capital
we'll still end up having
to fight, won't we?
Stay sharp out
there, everyone.
[ALL] Right.
[suspenseful music]
♪♪
Oh!
I hope you're hungry
food's ready, Master.
Sorry.
I'm actually going out
to check the forge.
You guys go ahead
and eat without me.
Raphtalia and Filo, there's
another parade tomorrow.
Try and get some rest.
Atla and Fohl, I want you
training after dinner.
Please be careful
You really ought
to just let me accompany you
as your bodyguard.
It's too dangerous
to go alone.
I'm fine. Thanks.
Just to be safe
let us protect you while
you're on your way there.
After that, I promise
we'll do whatever you want.
That's kind of you
I told you two
to train together.
Stop spoiling Atla
and do what's best for her.
I will be the protection
you require.
She says nobody
gave her orders.
So she's protecting you
of her own free will.
Oh.
I'm leaving
you in charge.
OK.
Good luck.
And take good care
of him, Sane.
Well, I hope
you're happy.
I lost my job
because of you, brother.
Atla!
I was doing it for you.
I didn't ask you to.
You should have
stayed out of it.
[FOHL] Stayed out?
[crickets chirping]
[footsteps, clash]
[NAOFUMI] Whoa!
Ah!
I'm so sorry about that.
No, it was my bad.
Is there
something wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you OK?
Yes.
But maybe you
can help me.
Do you know where I can
find the main street?
The main street, huh?
I know.
It's right down
that road over there.
Whoa!
A talking
stuffed animal.
How cute.
Oh, you're
flattering me.
Well, don't let us keep you
from your destination.
Oh, that's what
I was doing.
It's just over this way
[NAOFUMI] No!
Huh?
It's that way.
[laughs] I remember now.
Thank you so very much.
What was her problem?
- [NAOFUMI] How's it going?
- [ERHARD] Ah. Hey, kid.
You came at
the perfect time.
Now tell him to take these
damn ropes off of me.
The hell did I just
walk in on?
Earlier, he said he
was going to ditch work
and go out drinking.
- Hmm?
[struggles]
It's nice to
see you again
You're looking
gorgeous as ever.
In fact, your beauty
is so dazzling
I can hardly
see right now.
- How about that new sword?
- Yeah.
What ended up happening
to that cursed sword
we gave you
the other day?
Have you fixed it?
Oh, that sword?
For a master blacksmith like
me, that curse isn't nothing.
That said
can only be found at my forge
in the old capital.
I know, young lady.
How about you and I go
looking for them together?
With you by my side
and be back in here
in no time at all.
There's something
wrong with you.
Sadly, he's not lying
about his forge
being in the
old capital.
Oh, great.
So we have to retake
the old capital to reforge it?
[GIRL] Umm...
Oh!
Excuse me.
What the...
it's you again.
I'm always getting
lost here. [Laughs]
Young lady!
Who might you be?
Oh, um
you can call me Zodia.
Zodia?
You have a truly
spectacular name.
And as for me
the best one there is.
The name's Muramasa.
[quirky music]
- Oh.
- Huh.
I know a place that serves
the most wonderful saké.
Why don't you
come try it with me?
Hey, get these
ropes off me!
[ZODIA] That's very kind
I have to decline as I'm seeing
the parade for the person
who will be the
new emperor.
You're seeing
the parade?
That isn't
until tomorrow.
Oh, dear.
Hey, I'll show you
the way tomorrow.
So tonight, how about
the two of us have some saké
and get to know each other
a little better, huh?
Huh?
I wouldn't mind going
if you're tagging along.
Sorry, but
I'd rather die.
Let's go, Sane.
Come on.
There's no need to be
such a party pooper.
Ah!
Please, I'll fix that
cursed sword for you
and do whatever you want
for the rest of my life.
I'm begging you.
Look, he's strange
[sighs]
All right. Fine.
I'll go.
Hooray, saké!
[MURAMASA] Hooray!
[MURAMASA]
Well, folks, here we are.
[NAOFUMI]
It looks like it's closed.
If I'm not mistaken, this
is actually where I'm staying.
The second floor
of this building is an inn.
Seriously?
Then it must have been fate
we came here.
Stop causing
a ruckus out there.
The world's too messy
for me to be serving drinks.
Go try somewhere else.
Come on, have a heart.
We won't be long.
Oh!
[laughs]
Welcome back, Miss.
Come in.
Make yourself at home.
It's good to be back.
I'm coming in
right behind you.
Hurry up
before he changes his mind.
[gentle music]
[ZODIA] Wow!
This meal's amazing.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
For you.
Oh, thanks.
A toast to our meeting.
Bottoms up.
Who made you the leader
of this dinner?
Mm.
My gosh.
What are you, crazy?
Huh?
[ZODIA] You sure can
hold your liquor.
Incredible.
Oh, if it's not too
much trouble, I just...
[NAOFUMI]
Don't even try.
Oh.
[ZODIA] By the way, you
never told me your name.
So what is it?
It's Naofumi Iwatani.
Great.
I'll call you Naofumi then.
Huh?
So, hey, if you don't mind
me asking, what race are you?
I'm a human.
Oh, I'm actually
a Komai.
I didn't know that humans
could drink this much.
How cool.
Well, in that case.
Oh, I think it's time
we get a game started.
A game, huh?
Hmm!
This one should make
for a memorable night.
This is the
emperor's game.
Masuzu cards!
Uh...
[MURAMASA]
Masuzu cards?
Sure. Sounds fun.
Hang on.
I never said that
I would be playing.
My master says
she can't wait to play.
There. Now let us begin.
♪♪
I guess I win.
You're kidding.
But I thought this was your
first time playing this game.
I've played something
similar before.
Wow, wow.
You're amazing.
Another drink, please.
[MURAMASA]
Damn it, I lost again.
[ZODIA] No fair.
You're too good
at this, Naofumi.
Oh! That's OK.
I'll win the next one.
Ah!
He's out at last.
Huh?
My master says
she's tired too.
We have
an early day tomorrow.
Let's start
heading back.
[ZODIA] Oh!
One more game.
Come on.
Let's just play
one more game.
You're going to see
the parade, aren't you?
If so, you should
get to bed too.
Next time we meet, we're
gonna play Masuzu cards again.
You promise me!
[NAOFUMI]
OK, I promise.
Guess we have to drink
to our promise then.
You're still drinking?
[laughs]
Oh!
[NAOFUMI] Don't worry.
I'll get him home.
Get home safe.
I wish you
didn't have to go
have just the best time
playing games with you.
Probably
because you're drunk.
Oh, that's right.
[laughs]
Here, for you.
What is this thing?
A card with my autograph
to celebrate our meeting.
Oh, no.
I'm so embarrassed.
Hey, I know it's fast
Huh?
[laughs] Only joking.
Gotcha, huh?
I'm not wasting
any more time with this.
[laughs] I hope I see
you again soon, Naofumi.
I'll miss you, OK?
All right. Whatever.
Just go to bed.
♪♪
How funny.
I really meant
what I said.
[cheerful music]
[RAPHTALIA] I'm amazed you
were able to find so much food.
Yeah, well, I only got all
of this thanks to the emperor.
What exactly
did you do for it?
Here, eat up.
Oh, thank you so much.
Anything I can help with
I think we've got
everything under control.
But can you stop
calling me big sis?
Oh!
Line up over here.
Hey, no
cutting, big guy.
Well, I did try.
Big sis, huh?
You see
What did you talk about?
[FOHL] Hey,
wait a second!
Not much.
We just chatted about Atla
for a while, that's all.
[blows landing]
Good grief.
You never stop
Don't you understand
I'm doing it for you, Atla?
Yeah, well
I'd be with
Master Naofumi.
All right. Fine.
I'll go see if
we can slip out.
Perfect.
Fohl!
Ah!
We can go, right?
I'll only be
gone for a bit.
I completed all
of my training.
And Atla says
she wants to go...
You don't always have
to give in to what she wants.
If you're doing
what's best for her
then I won't say a word
and I'll let you sneak out.
However, from where
I'm standing
it seems like you're only
doing this to spoil her.
No, I just...
But seriously
something terrible
could end up happening.
If you really want
what's best for her
sometimes you have to
put your foot down
even if it ends up
hurting her feelings.
You want to protect her
the same way
any good older brother would.
Oh.
You're completely
right, big sis.
Huh? Big sis?
I'll stand up for myself
and be the big brother
that she deserves.
[laughs] I'll be a great
big brother, the way
you're a great
big sister.
[laughs]
So that's how it is.
[crowd chatter]
But why though?
[ominous stings]
[MAN] Hey, look, look!
[cheering]
[clattering]
[NAOFUMI] Ah.
Tomorrow we finally enter
the old capital.
What?
Hmm?
I knew I'd
see you again.
What the?
I hope there's room
for one more.
Wait, stop!
What are you doing?
[splash]
Unreal.
Let me guess.
You got lost again, huh?
Well, did you
see the parade?
I did, and I got
to see the new emperor.
Did you get
to see her too?
Yeah, I guess
I kind of did.
OK, and
based off of that
What's the new
emperor like?
Why do you care so much
about the new emperor anyway?
Well, I think the current
emperor is doing their best.
I know Q'ten Lo is in bad shape
and everyone is suffering.
Yeah, well, it's hard
not to blame the emperor.
It feels like my job's been
getting harder and harder
and now I have
to do dirty work.
That's not what
I ever wanted.
Then again, is anybody
excited about dirty work?
Sounds like
interesting work.
Oh, it certainly is.
But it's very difficult
right now.
I want everybody
to be satisfied
but it just doesn't
work like that.
I can relate.
But at the parade today
for the first
time in forever.
And the new emperor was at
the center of their happiness.
When I saw
that, I thought
some kind of way
to make the whole country
smile that way again.
So I decided
I'm going to find her
and talk to her
to see for myself.
Sorry for rambling
about all of this.
It's fine.
Hey, we still have to play
Masuzu cards again, right?
You promised we would
next time we met, didn't you?
I guess I did, didn't I?
Let's head back to my inn
and play it there.
It'll be more fun
with more people.
Excellent.
We should warm ourselves up
with a drink before we go.
Huh?
Oh!
I think I accidentally
left something in the bath.
I'll go ahead and check
the men's section.
Just wait here.
OK!
I'll be waiting.
I've come to fetch you.
Oh, dear.
Here you go.
Is this it?
Hmm.
I guess being
the Water Dragon Miko
must be a hard job
for one person.
It certainly is.
Everything you do
is to serve the emperor.
Water Dragon Miko is
a fancy name to have.
But what I would do was
hardly fitting of that title.
I was leading armies
or carrying out
death sentences
on criminals.
I can't imagine
that's easy.
They were not
all bad either.
Being a criminal
merely meant you caused
a problem for
the emperor.
It's sad really.
Sounds like you were
doing his dirty work.
Even now, I'm sure another
member of my clan is doing it.
It's sobering
to think about it all.
You mentioned
your clan before.
But what do you
mean by that?
You see, because of
our fighting prowess
our race always
gets chosen.
It's gotten to the point we're
called the slaughter Miko.
What a terrible
nickname.
[SADEENA]
Scary, isn't it?
I'm actually
pretty spooky.
Boy, do I know it.
Oh?
You were only following
orders back then.
And given your position
it's not like you had
much of a choice.
It's rare to see the two
of you together like this.
Naofumi was being sweet
You were being nice?
Yeah, maybe I was.
We've got a busy
day tomorrow.
Let's head to bed early.
[BOTH WOMEN] OK.
[suspenseful music]
♪♪
Message!
Last night, a town to our rear
suffered a surprise attack
by the government army.
[gasps]
This is bad.
We left Itsuki and Rishia
in the town behind us.
Atla, Sane, and Fohl, can
you take Gaelion and go help?
- We're on it!
- Leave it to us.
♪♪
[panting]
What's wrong?
Look at this!
What is going on?
Reporting!
We have a message
from someone claiming
to be an enemy
messenger.
From the enemy?
To the commanding
rebel leader from the...
Water Dragon Miko.
The Water Dragon Miko?
[MAN] What's it say?
Read it aloud, please.
[MAN] Yes, ma'am.
Last night, one of my units
took rash action.
This was not my wish
as commander
of the government army.
I have regained
control of them.
For this war
representatives
of both sides meet
and try to
talk things out.
I will represent
our army.
And I would have
your commander
or someone
of equivalent standing
represent your side.
That's a rather
one-sided ask.
Well, for my family
shockingly considerate.
Let me see that letter
for myself.
Yes, sir.
♪♪
[theme music]
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
PRAYER