[wind sound]
[♪ Melancholic music]
Jaralis.
Our supply lines
have been cut off
[SOLDIER] with no chance
of reinforcements.
[SOLDIER]  I'm afraid
there's no hope.
So this is it.
[♪ Dramatic music]
[gasps]
[panting]
[SOLDIER] Jaralis, give us
the order to retreat!
[SOLDIER] Jaralis, sir!
All right, my
fellow warriors.
Time to show them
what you're made of.
If we fail to defeat the rebels
here on this battlefield
they will not stop
until they reach the castle.
[JARALIS] For the unification
of our homeland.
And our comrades!
You, brave soldier
to prevent the advance
of the enemy.
All rise!
[hesitation]
Ready?
And now, charge!
[soldiers roaring]
Well, at the very least
As for me, I must stay alive
to see this through.
[SOLDIER] It's Tiran!
His reinforcements have arrived.
[grunts]
[soldiers roaring]
Take courage!
And we'll show them
we're the pride of Siltvelt.
[SOLDIERS] Yes, sir!
Tiran.
[grunts]
[gong]
[panting]
Those accursed eyes
are so familiar.
[♪ Opening music begins]
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
[♪ opening music ends]
EPISODE 4:
ENTRUSTED POWER
[♪ dramatic music]
[scream]
The Minotaur with the axe
has quite a shine for Atla.
It's just so
frustrating.
All we can do now
is watch what happens.
For now, we'll just have
to place our faith in them.
[grunts]
[panting]
[scream]
Nothing but a brat.
[exhalation]
[scream]
You never leave
an opening during a duel.
Oh, that wasn't
an opening.
[battle scream]
He has speed
Maybe…
[JARALIS] You really thought
you could defeat me?
Child!
[gasping]
[panting]
Hm.
Is that all you've got?
In the end
[grunt]
[scream]
[groan]
How's it going?
You all right, brother?
Oh, yeah.
Compared to our training back
in the village, this is nothing.
[grunt]
[deep exhalation]
[combat sounds]
[panting]
Interesting.
You're much sturdier
than I tthought.
I figured you would have
gone down by now.
[sigh]
It's been a long time
since any warrior has made
my blood run so hot.
This will be fun.
Come on.
Entertain me some more!
Show them, Lyceras
Go, Jarlis! Bring judgment
on those tainted tigers!
Hey Filo, we must cheer
for them really loud right now!
Yep.
Raphy!
Go, Atla! You
can do it! Woo!
Yeah!
Oh, Fohl. If you win
I'll make sure to thank you
for being such a good boy.
[stammer]
[cough]
[screams]
Oh no.
[ATLA] Brother! As soon as
I'm done with this guy
I'd be happy
to take your place.
[FOHL] I'll finish this
before you do!
Takes me back watching
those youngsters fight.
What is it?
Ah yes, like when I used
to watch Tiran fight.
[gasp]
Yes, I can see it too.
And he has
the same spirit in him.
Who's this Tiran guy
you're talking about?
He's the father
of Atla and Fohl.
[ETHAN] Well he was.
[♪ Music with flute]
Their father?
[ELDER] Yes.
Tiran, son of
King Tyran.
The powerful king of the race
of the white tiger Demi-humans
here in Siltvelt
[ELDER] His talents succeeded
even those of the former king.
[ELDER] Yet he tried to avoid
combat at all costs.
[ELDER] Thus, he and
the last king did not get along.
[ELDER] And he was expelled
from the family.
[old door closing]
[ELDER] After
Tyran's death
rebellion broke out
all over the nation.
[ELDER] I'm told
that Tyran and Jaralis
even fought together
to quell the rebellion.
[♪ Intense
dramatic music]
[scream]
You're mine!
[battle screams]
[gasp]
[exhalation]
He probably won't be able
to stand for a bit.
You see
Huh?
I'm not done yet!
I can tell you're
a seasoned warrior.
And you're not going to let me
defeat you that easily, are you?
You have the bearing
of royal blood.
So is it his blood
that makes you so bold?
Lyceras!
Why is it taking you
so long to defeat her?
[FOHL] Eyes on me!
[panting]
Little brat!
[grunts]
Why? You're nobody.
[gasps]
Lyceras!
Finish her off already
and come help me over here!
Hey! Lyceras!
[NAOFUMI]
Starting to panic?
[grunt]
You need somebody else
to save your ass
cause your dirty tricks
weren't enough.
[NAOFUMI] I
bet the truth hurts
[NAOFUMI] I'm gonna
make this clear
so you can't talk
your way out of it.
If we win, you're going to obey
whatever orders we lay down.
You're a man
of your word
You don't have to worry.
No one can overturn the results
of a sacred duel.
No matter who they are.
The terms are
unchanging.
That means you're preparing
a ship to Q'ten Lo
for us to travel
in, correct?
Then it's official.
We're in agreement.
[grunt]
[FOHL] Jaralis!
Don't you forget
our deal either.
[♪ Intense,
battle music]
Now it appears
it's time to end this.
Good then.
I'm going to hit you with
the strongest technique I have.
Secret technique.
Big Bull Charge!
[roaring]
My imitation
of Hengen Musou Style.
[battle scream]
Jewel!
Well done…
Heir… of Tyran.
My dear father
[grunts]
[gasps]
Hengen Musou Style
Destroying Tiger...
[hard breathing]
[panting]
No, Fohl!
What happened? He looks like
he's in so much pain.
Raphy!
[gasps]
[Naofumi] Poison?
[♪ Violin music]
Well, that worked
like a charm
That is so unfair!
This has to be against
the rules, right?
Oh no.
In any of our historic
Siltvelt duels
the last one standing
is the winner.
[ELDER] According to
the rules, it's allowed.
You've got to
be kidding me!
[FOHL] Shield Hero!
[hard breathing]
I'm fine.
I can still fight.
[harsh inhale]
You can rest now
from the battle, brother.
For I will fight
on your behalf.
[FOHL] Atla!
I will defeat him.
[FOHL] If I
can't defeat him
[FOHL] I'll never hear
what happened to dad.
Oh, there's nothing
much to tell.
Your father brought
shame to Siltvelt
by fleeing it when confronted
by the enemy.
That's not true!
My father was not a coward!
Oh, but he most
certainly was.
Sacrificing his men
just to guarantee his own
personal survival.
You're lying!
[JARALIS] I
speak the truth.
[JARALIS] He
was no warrior.
[grunt]
And then he died
so pathetically.
He was actually begging
for his life.
Hust shut up!
[gasps]
What's with this kid?
He was almost dead
second ago.
You're lying!
Liar!
[gasps]
Tiran?
[Fohl roars]
[gasps]
[panting]
Now take it back.
Admit it!
He wasn't a coward!
[evil laughter]
Well then, if you want
to know that badly
[JARALIS] I'm
going to tell you…
How your
father really died.
It was during
that battle
the awful one
against the third rebellion.
The battle where
my father died.
[laughter]
[JARALIS] If only he'd done
what he was supposed to.
[JARALIS] If my plan
had come to fruition
[JARALIS] I could have
restored my honor.
[chattering]
[JARALIS] But he just
happened to ride in
with his reinforcements and
figured that made him a hero.
[♪ Tense music]
He stole the glory that
should have been mine.
Over and over again!
You will never
understand
how much humiliation I endured
when your father was alive!
He was always the bane
of my existence.
So I...
Don't tell me.
Hmm.
[♪ Dramatic
music intensifies]
[sword cutting sound]
[gasping]
Don't tell me!
It's the truth.
The only way to be rid of him
was to kill him myself.
Lucia.
Fohl.
Atla.
[sword cutting sound]
[♪ Somber music]
I can still remember
how incredible it felt to steal
his glory-grabbing
life away.
[JARALIS]
I'll never forget
the final, miserable look
on his face.
Why now?
Why is he suddenly
confessing this to us?
[sighs]
Oh, that's the face!
That's the face, yes!
And it's exactly
like your father's!
You and your father both provide
endless entertainment for me.
[FOHL] Shut up!
You bastard!
[evil giggle]
[bowel Sound]
[startle]
It's the beast
transformation!
[gasps]
What's that?
Well…
There's a well-known legend
existing only within Siltvelt.
[WERNER] Just like
a Demi-human
can change into a beast man
to grow stronger
the legend says that beast men
can transform as well.
And you're telling me that's
what just happened?
Most likely.
The power is
overwhelming.
It's more than
I imagined.
With a power
such as this
there'll never again be
a need for the Shield Hero.
The whole world can just
worship me as a god instead!
Did he overcome
the poison?
[roar]
[NAOFUMI] Meteor Shield!
Elder, Werner
[scream]
Shit!
Father, I promised.
[♪ Gentle music]
Fohl!
While I'm away
from home
you take care
of your mom and Atla.
I'll protect them.
I promise you.
[roar]
[gasps]
Back then, I...
[FOHL] I was weak.
[♪ Gentle, sad music]
[FOHL] I couldn't
do anything.
[panting]
I couldn't protect
[FOHL] my mother.
[panting]
[battle scream]
[♪ Gentle, sad
music continues]
[gasps]
[roar]
[grunt]
After you, I'm going after
that little sister of yours.
Atla…
[hard breathing]
[gasps]
Time to die as a failure
No! Fohl!
[gasps]
Brother!
[deep inhale]
I know that form!
[♪ Epic music]
Oh my.
Look at Fohl!
He seems to be quite
manly out there.
And look
Raphy!
Master Naofumi!
[NAOFUMI] Looks like his stats
have all gone way up.
Is that from
the beast transformation?
It's unbelievable.
For two generations
you and your family are still
getting in my way!
[all angrily roaring]
Is he really going
to destroy everything?
[NAOFUMI] Raphtalia
Right!
I'm on it.
Hooray! It's Filo time!
Yay!
Let's go.
[TIRAN] Fohl.
[LUCIA] Fohl.
Brother of mine.
[FOHL] Everyone.
Watch me.
[♪ Closing music begins]
[♪ Closing music ends]
WHITE TIGER