[♪ Dramatic
orchestral music]
My name is
Naofumi Iwatani.
Before I was summoned
into this world
I was like any other
college student.
But here I am, one
of the four Cardinal heroes.
The Shield Hero.
The four heroes have never
gotten along.
But as of late, it seems like
that might be changing.
Not that we can
take advantage of it.
Because just when things
were looking up for once
Raphtalia's
parents' homeland
sent assassins
into my lands.
It all happened so fast.
The second Raphtalia
put on the miko outfit
that resembled the clothes
worn by their emperor
they attacked.
[♪ Dramatic,
triumphant music]
Now I'm on my way to Siltvelt
to try and catch a ship
to Q'ten Lo, where hopefully
I can talk some sense
into these fools and get
to the bottom of all this.
On top of all that
But before it does
I need to deal with Q'ten Lo
for Raphtalia's sake.
Her future
depends on it.
[panting]
[growl]
Yeah. All right.
I think it's time
we take a break.
[birds chirping]
[growl]
Thanks for
checking on me
[sneeze]
Seeing as we'll be approaching
the border soon
it's probably best
I head back to my land
and regroup my forces.
[growl]
Gaelion?
What is it?
¡Drifa Aqua Blast!
[water rushing]
[panting]
[growl]
Did you miss me, Master?
¡Raphy!
Huh?
What the hell?
Why are you here?
[giggles]
At least pretend
to be happy to see us.
How did you
expect me to react?
You three are supposed to be
off training right now.
Why, yes, and that's exactly
what we were doing.
So you're telling me
it was just a coincidence
that you ran
into me here?
Well, um.
So you see
we were busy training
when we met Fitoria.
Wait. Fitoria?
She told us
if we headed this way
that we would eventually
run into you.
She also mentioned
she had a request for us
she wanted me
to tell you about.
Tell me later.
I've got my hands full
at the moment
dealing with something
that can't be ignored.
Raphy?
Huh?
Can't you at
least hear her out?
Not only did she already pay
in advance
but she also did
a lot to help us.
Oh, really?
And how exactly
did she do that?
Just look.
In exchange for lowering
our levels a bit here and there
she gave our
stats a huge boost.
She isn't kidding.
From the looks of it
all of their stats
have more than doubled.
It doesn't matter.
Will you hold
on a second?
She also helped us with
acquiring a new class.
If you want
to help her out
It's not something
I can do!
Let's see.
It sounds like it has to be you
and me to help Master.
Are you two
talking right now?
Yep.
I see.
So you're off
to Q'ten Lo.
[FILO]
Um, Master has a question.
He wants to know if you're going
to kill off the Cardinal heroes
if he decides to ignore
the request you have.
I suppose my
request can wait.
But don't blame me if you
end up regretting it later.
[FILO] Whatever he says.
[♪ Dramatic music]
[NAOFUMI] Siltvelt.
[♪ Opening music begins]
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
[♪ opening music ends]
EPISODE 1: SILTVELT
[♪ tranquil music]
My imitation of the Hangen
Musou Secret Technique.
First dance, sun!
How in the world
is someone like Atla
able to fight like that?
That's incredible, Atla!
I guess Claire
was right then.
She really does have a talent
for Hengen Musou.
I have to train harder
from now on.
[WOMEN] The Shield Hero and his
party have returned, everyone!
The plan is for us to reach
the Siltvelt border by tomorrow.
Once we're past it
Does that mean I get to pull
the carriage again?
Sure does.
But we're not going to be able
to take it through the portal.
Hey, Melty.
Can you contact the Queen
and have her prepare
a carriage near
the border checkpoint?
You make it sound like
an easy thing to do.
I suppose it couldn't hurt
to ask her.
Understood. I dare say.
So. I know that
Filo's coming.
But who else?
Well, it's a
Demi-human country
so taking a royal
like Melty with us
probably
wouldn't be wise.
I'm well aware of that.
Besides, someone has to stay
here and watch your lands.
Appreciate it.
How about bringing
Fohl and Atla?
The two of them
have been training every day
and pushing each other
to be stronger.
They've come a long way
from when you picked them up
in the arena,
haven't they?
No kidding.
And their rate of improvement
has been quite unbelievable.
Seeing as they're
from Siltvelt
they might be useful
in this scenario.
[REN] Now, for me.
What about
the two of us?
[NAOFUMI] I'd love for you
to come along with us
but not when your curses
haven't fully healed yet.
But they've both gone
out of their way
to bathe in the Carmina
hot springs
so shouldn't their curses
be lifted?
Well, the hot springs
are helping
but it's still going
to take some time.
Exactly.
Just focus on recovering
so you're ready to go
when the Phoenix revives.
Understood.
I'll stay and help with
the recovery process
if that's okay.
So our party
going will be me
Raphtalia
Filo
Sadeena, Fohl, and Atla.
[RAPH] Ra…
And of course,
you too, Raffy.
Raffy.
So
did any Q'ten Lo assassins
attack while I was away?
It's actually been
rather quiet here.
There hasn't been
any sign of them since
that first attack
happened.
What?
The people...
The people from
my master's world
should be after
this village too
but there is no sign of them
either. Think what you want.
What the hell is
going on here?
Are they being cautious since
their scouts were eliminated?
I hope that's
what this means.
I was looking forward
to helping fend them off
but things here
have been peaceful.
I guess I'll have to be useful
in other ways.
We just have to be ready
when they attack.
Um, by the way.
Does anyone know
where Motoyasu
could be or what
he might be doing?
As weird as he is
he'd be useful to have
here right now.
[screams]
[MOTOYASU] You
have some nerve
thinking you can invade
my father's lands.
You're not
the first, either.
There were also some dudes
dressed like ninjas earlier.
For my father and
for my beloved Filo
I will destroy you
and obliterate your souls.
[screams]
Please stop.
I don't want to die
at the hands of some weirdo.
Bye, bye now.
[♪ Heroic music]
Onward!
The next group of evil doers
demands my retribution.
[evil laugh]
Well, how do you like
the carriage, Filo?
It feels like they used
a different wood.
Does it really make that big
of a difference?
Mmm…
Maybe a little bit.
Not sure what
that means.
[GIRL] It's the
shield hero!
[RAPHTALIA] Looks like a
crowd starting to gather here.
I'm guessing that when the Queen
arranged this carriage for us
rumor must have spread through
town that we were coming.
Make sure to stay
on your guard, everyone.
Right.
Why don't we
take a break?
I think all of us
would be in better spirits
with a little drink.
Pardon me, Your Majesty
The false Empress
and her companions
have just
arrived in Siltvelt.
I understand that this news
might be worrisome.
But I assure you, I'll take
care of everything.
I shall cut down the Shield Hero
and this traitor
who seeks to rob you
of your throne.
You have my word.
The two of them won't live
to see Q'ten Lo.
You put your trust in me
[thunder]
[evil smirk]
[♪ Joyful music]
[NAOFUMI]
What do you think, Fohl?
Feel like home yet?
Not exactly.
I've never been to this part
of the country.
I don't remember being here
very much either.
Something
isn't right here.
We made it through
the checkpoint way too easily.
Wonder what
that's all about?
[RAPHTALIA]
What does that banner say?
Can anyone read that?
[SADEENA] You don't need to know
how to read it.
Just look around
at everyone's faces.
[FOHL] Oh,
that big banner.
It looks like someone's written
welcome Shield Hero.
Oh, interesting.
So you can read it?
Being able to read
stuff like that
is the one useful skill
my brother has.
Not true.
[laughs]
Just keep going, Filo.
Okay.
[GUARD] If you
don't mind, sir.
The Royal Guard would be
honored to escort
the Shield Hero and his party
to the palace.
Follow me!
[cheering and galloping]
Even though I expect to see this
kind of thing from Siltvelt
it's nice to see them treating
Master Naofumi this way.
He deserves this
kind of treatment.
Easy there.
[NAOFUMI] I feel like I'm the
star of a parade or something.
Even I'm surprised to see
a turnout for you like this.
You've become quite
a revered hero, huh?
You know, I
just remembered
what the Queen of Melromarc
once told me about Siltvelt.
Oh dear.
What did she
say about Siltvelt?
First off…
First off
You're going
to be welcomed
and then approached
by noble women.
After that, they'll attempt to
form a type of harem for you
with women from any
number of species.
A harem?
After that
fall victim to
an unknown disease.
And once it becomes
too much, you'll…
What?
Something like that
is impossible.
If it isn't
obvious already
the people of Siltvelt worship
the Shield Hero as a god.
I would never do something
like that.
Yeah, well, I sure hope
you're right.
Raphy.
[NAOFUMI]
Well, either way
we need to try and get
through this country
as quickly as possible.
[♪ Soft music]
[MAN] It's a pleasure to
meet you, Shield Hero.
Welcome.
On behalf of Siltvelt
Allow me to
introduce myself.
My name is Werner
of the Shusaku race
here in Siltvelt.
I'm happy to help
however I can.
Shusaku?
Well, then, my name is
Naofumi Iwatani.
And this is.
I am Raphtalia
Oh, and my name's Filo.
Nice to meet you.
Raphy!
My name's Sadeena.
My name is Atla.
And I'm Fohl.
Know that you are
all welcome here.
Believe it or not
I purchased those two back when
they were slaves in Zeltoble.
But they're not pure
blood Demi humans.
I don't plan on getting involved
in any power struggles
in your country, or letting
them get involved.
I appreciate
your reassurance.
Please, I'd like you to join me
inside the palace.
I'm sure you must be exhausted
from your long journey
Shield Hero
but if you wouldn't
mind me doing so
I'd like to request
an audience.
An audience?
Between who, exactly?
[WERNER] I'm afraid
your servants
aren't allowed past this point.
[WERNER]
As you see, Shield Hero
the races that have ruled
over Siltvelt until now
have gathered here
before you in order to
properly welcome you
into our city.
I'm Solea of the Genmu race.
Honored to meet you.
And my name is Tsualon.
I represent the Aotatsu.
It is a privilege to meet you.
Right.
Thank you for
that, I guess.
Your words honor me.
So is this how an audience
is supposed to work here?
Yes.
You must understand we're
overwhelmed with joy to see you.
Then… I'll just come out
and say exactly what I need
from you all.
Yes, Sir.
I don't have any interest
in taking over Siltvelt.
So rest easy
knowing that
I'm merely passing through
on my way to Q'ten Lo.
I don't intend on getting
in the way
of how you
do things here
or how you
rule this country.
On that note
I'd like you to prepare
a ship to Q'ten Lo for me.
And as soon as possible
I see now.
You seem to be
misunderstanding
the situation before you
How so?
First, I would like you to rest
from your long journey here.
After you've gotten
enough rest
and participate
in tonight's banquet
we'd be more than happy
to hear any requests
that you might
have for us.
I don't have time
for any of that.
And I'm sure it's safe to assume
some of you want me out of here
as soon as
possible, right?
[WERNER] I
can't deny that.
But please know we don't share
in that way of thinking.
That is a sickness in our
country that must be purged.
Anyone who doesn't want
Master Naofumi here
is a traitor to
his country.
We should round them up
and execute them all.
While your name evokes
discourse in some
please know our undying loyalty
to you remains unaltered.
It's important to us
you remember that.
What a pleasant thought
to swear my loyalty
to Master Naofumi.
If you're loyal, then
shouldn't you be trying to grant
my wish as soon as possible?
We'd be more than happy
to prepare a ship for you.
But please.
You must understand
that we'd be heartbroken
if the God we worship
left in a hurry.
I mean, after all, you've only
just arrived here.
Is this country really just
a stop on your journey?
You saw how the people in the
streets worshipped you, right?
If you were to leave us
so suddenly
our city and all of its people
would be left thinking
that you abandoned Siltvelt. Is
that really something you want?
Of course not. But I don't
have time for...
I'd go so far as to say there
may even be riots
and a military coup
d'état if you left us.
I hope that helps you
to understand
just how much you mean
to this nation of ours.
So please, I beg you
please be the Shield Hero that
all of us have waited for.
All right, fine.
I will attend this banquet of
yours, if that's what you want.
Thank you.
You'll be delighted to know that
we've planned a room for you
and a room for each one
of your followers.
We ask that you please remain
there until the banquet begins.
I don't want us
in separate rooms.
I can't imagine
they'll try anything on me
at this very moment
but I don't want to be alone
just in case they do.
I understand
your concern, sir.
But we cannot treat others
in the same manner
we would treat
the Shield Hero.
Doing so would be a mockery
to the faith we believe in.
[ATLA] Um…
If it isn't too
much trouble
a room next to Master
Naofumi for me?
Who gave that white tiger
permission to talk?
What an absurd
request to make.
[WERNER] Very
well, Shield Hero.
I'll have it prepared
immediately.
While there's still time
before the banquet
I'd much rather go out
and explore
the town than stay cooped up
inside of a room.
The people of Siltvelt would be
honored to see you.
How wonderful.
Okay, then.
Let's get going.
[WERNER] However
I'm afraid it will take
some time to make
the necessary arrangements
for a royal visit.
Understand,
a sudden visit
from the Shield Hero might
catch people off guard.
If that happened
they'd regret not offering
you a proper welcome.
Such a major event requires
preparations to be made.
The people must be told in
advance of your arrival.
[NAOFUMI] All right, fine.
I'll stay inside the palace.
Am I at least allowed to walk
around inside?
Why, of course you are.
I mean, after all, this is
your palace we're in.
[NAOFUMI] Yet
I'm on a leash.
And I'm not allowed in
any of the rooms
as they're
being renovated.
So much for this
being my palace.
You gotta be kidding me.
How many days are we gonna
waste in this place?
[SADEENA]
Seeing how that went
we'd be lucky if we weren't
stuck here for months.
If that happens
we won't have time to get ready
for the Phoenix.
[laughter]
I guess you're right.
I respect their loyalty
to Master Naofumi
but they're too
strict with him.
If they really
do worship him
This must be how
the other heroes felt
when they were worshipped
as gods in Melromarc.
But even if that's true
they certainly
didn't act the same.
They were a lot more free
spirited than you.
[SADEENA]
I don't know, you'd have to be a
pretty free spirit to ask them
to give you a ship
without first serving your duty
to them as Shield Hero
wouldn't you say?
I can't believe you
were able to say that
to them with
a straight face.
Look, I know it sounded
a bit harsh
but we don't have the time
to waste parading around here.
Cut him some slack.
The only reason
Master Naofumi is hurrying
things along like this
is cause he wants
to help Raphtalia.
I know, you don't have
to tell me.
[RAPHTALIA] I'm sorry.
I feel like I've caused
everyone trouble.
[ATLA] Has something
like this happened
you would do
the same for me
[RAPHTALIA]
Where did that come from?
[MAN] Well now.
If it isn't the Shield Hero.
Who might you be?
My name is
Jaralis, and I serve
as the representative
of the Lyle race.
It's a pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
A lion Demi-human?
I hope you're able to forgive me
for only now
being able to come down here
and introduce myself to you.
No need to mention it.
Allow me to be frank
Most of us caught wind
of what you mentioned
during your audience
earlier with Werner.
If you wish to have a ship
arranged to Q'ten Lo
please know I'm able and willing
to do such a thing
for you, if that is
what you desire.
I find it troubling you weren't
present at the audience earlier.
I have a hard time believing
that someone who wasn't there
would be capable
of such a thing.
Very well, then.
I will look forward
to seeing you at
tonight's banquet, Shield Hero.
I apologize if I've troubled you
in any way.
Wow, we're so high up.
Hey, Fohl
do you know anything about
that Jaralis guy we met?
Nope. Sorry.
It's my first time seeing
this Werner guy, too.
I did warn you all he's good
for his reading.
Atla!
Honestly, I don't trust
either of them.
But if Jarlus is willing
to prepare a ship for us
I think it's pretty safe
to assume
he's probably not
on the same side as Werner.
He may not be important enough
to serve an audience
but I get the feeling that
he does have some power.
So we should probably
keep an eye on him.
That's my impression. But what
do you think?
Well, there's no telling when
we'll be able to leave Siltvelt
if we continue letting the bird
guy boss us around like this.
But the lion's offer almost
seems too good to be true
doesn't it?
If we were to side with one
of them, I have a feeling
it would lead to making
an enemy out of the other.
Well, in that case I guess we'll
just have to wait and see.
This is all too
complicated for me.
I'm hungry. When
are we eating?
[NAOFUMI] Soon enough.
Q'ten Lo is a
long way off
OFFICIAL WELCOME