[melancholy music]
♪♪
[TRASH] Thank you.
This is for me?
[FOHL] Sure is.
Atla and I made it
for you this morning.
Hm.
Huh?
I sincerely hope
you'll enjoy it.
[murmurs]
Hold
on, could this be...
Mom used to make this.
Brother told me.
[exhales deeply]
It's not too
salty, is it?
No it's fine, really.
[chuckles]
It's so good.
Very good.
It's wonderful.
[MIRELLIA] Trash's little
sister is named Lucia.
Turns out her children
are Fohl and Atla.
If that's the case, shouldn't
we tell the two of them?
Trash is happy
with how it is.
Changes could possibly
disrupt things.
Anyway, how
was Siltvelt?
I'm told you may have
faced some trouble there.
Everything happened exactly
the way you said it would.
Well, it sounds like
things worked out in the end
because thanks to you
are going to be helping
in the war against the Phoenix.
[NAOFUMI] You wasted
no time setting that up.
[MIRELLIA] Preparing
for the battle with the Phoenix
is the number one
priority right now.
So what's next
for you, Shield Hero?
I'll continue preparing
for the Phoenix.
But first, I have to settle
things with Q'ten Lo.
I can't focus on what's
in front of us
if I'm worrying
about another attack.
Then do as you wish.
Oh, and Raphtalia.
Yes?
[MIRELLIA]
Depending on how things go
the next time we
meet, I may very well
be welcoming
you as royalty.
[RAPHTALIA]
I'm sorry.
I know this is
an important time.
It's not your fault
Q'ten Lo attacked.
And I'm just doing
my job as any Lord would.
Master Naofumi.
What did he think
of your home cooking?
Go ahead and see
for yourself.
I only wish
we made more.
If you're finished
with things here
then we should
get back home.
As soon as we're ready
[ALL] Right!
[theme music]
♪♪
♪ Hey ♪
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
♪ Nothing standing
in our way right now ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ The reason that I choose
to fight when I travel ♪
♪ Proof that I exist ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Live with no regrets ♪
♪ It seems like
a never-ending genocide ♪
♪ What's the way
to becoming ♪
♪♪
♪ The choice is yours ♪
♪ If the pieces
of your story cross ♪
♪ Don't let them go
Don't let them go ♪
♪ Cause you
don't want me
♪ No limit to
where we go ♪
♪ I will protect
your resolution ♪
♪ No matter
what comes next ♪
♪ Cause every time again
♪ We'll never
lose and cry ♪
♪ Now nobody can
stop us, no way ♪
♪ We'll back
you every time ♪
♪ It was just pushing
through the flame to some ♪
♪ That we
can stake out ♪
♪ Even if there's no
end to this road ♪
♪ We protect
our resolution ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ No need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Nothing standing
in our way right now ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ No need
for hesitation ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ go now ♪
EPISODE 6: LEAVING PORT
[RATOTILLE] My goodness
Why are you back?
To choose who's going
to Q'ten Lo with me.
Are you taking these?
Thanks to everyone
in the village
they're super
strong now.
Hmm. I want as much fighting
power as I can get.
But we have to be able
to defend the village, too.
It'd be good to have
Sadeena with us.
She knows the area.
Hm, that's true.
I'd forgotten about that.
Who else?
[RAPHTALIA] We could bring
Atla and Fohl as well.
[NAOFUMI] They did help out
a lot back in Siltvelt.
By the way
They're out training
Even if the curse is still
affecting both of them
it doesn't mean that
they're not cardinal heroes.
At least one of them
should come along.
[SADEENA]
If you're going to Q'ten Lo
you should
take him as well.
But why Gaelion?
You may not know, but
Q'ten Lo has a Water Dragon.
As a fellow dragon
be able to sense him before
he poses any sort of threat.
Yeah!
Sure.
Let's bring him.
[WYNDIA] No fair!
I wanna go!
I can fight
too, you know?
Do you remember what happened
when the village was attacked?
Mm.
We don't know if or when
they'll come back.
Making sure everyone here is
safe is really important, too.
You up for it?
Mm.
Now, then...
[ERHARD]
Hello? Anyone in there?
Huh?
Hey.
What is it, Erhard?
Room for one more
on your trip to Q'ten Lo?
I went ahead and took
a good look at the weapons
those guys were using.
And if I'm not mistaken
Are you positive?
Yeah, that's how
it seemed to me.
They've been
missing for ages
to finally find them.
I'm begging you.
It's bound to be
dangerous there.
Sure you wanna go?
I was an adventurer
My level is 87
[NAOFUMI]
Wait, seriously?
[ERHARD]
Take me along with you
and I'll keep
your weapons maintained.
All right, fine.
You can join us then.
You won't regret it.
[laughs]
[chuckles]
That explains why he was
so proficient
with a sword.
Him being able to train
you makes sense now.
Anyway, we'll discuss the rest
when Itsuki and Ren get back.
If possible, I'd like
to leave tomorrow.
[KEEL] Big sis!
[ALL] Huh?
You gotta help me!
Why in the world are
you dressed like that?
Those two made
me wear this.
A cross-dresser, huh?
I don't know
if you can say that
especially since
Keel's actually a girl.
[ALL gasps]
I found out when we were
taking measurements
for her to work
at the shop.
I just always
thought I was a guy
so I never
questioned it.
Yeah, same here.
But why that outfit
in particular?
She was creatively
inspired, she says.
Not to mention
everybody loved it.
[KEEL]
Well, I hate it.
All right.
Master Naofumi?
Keel, from now on
that when
you go trading.
[shrieks]
The more
attention you get
the more sales
you'll make.
Use that talent of yours.
Don't waste it.
I want to be
a strong man
Forget about gender.
You have to be useful.
Understood?
All right, if
you say so.
Master Naofumi, you've got
money symbols in your eyes.
[ERHARD] It's nice to know
that some things never change.
[MELTY] Naofumi!
It looks like
you've returned, huh?
How'd it go?
I heard you ran
into trouble in Siltvelt.
[NAOFUMI]
To put it lightly.
Did anything of note happen in
the village while I was away?
Well, we haven't had to deal
with any more assassins
but we did find
explosion craters nearby.
They might have tried
to set a trap for us.
Either that or they got
in a fight with someone.
The real
question is who?
[eerie music]
♪♪
[MOTOYASU]
Found you, villains!
[MONKEY ASSASSIN]
Who's there?
[adventurous music]
Your nightmare!
[explosion]
[grumbles]
Ahh. My spear didn't work
as well as it should have.
No matter.
As source of thy
power, I order thee
decipher the laws
of nature and burn my foes
until only ash remains.
Drifa Firestorm!
[explosion]
[yelling]
Filth must be
cleansed by fire.
Now, on to the next one.
[ITSUKI] We really don't
know what to make of it.
[NAOFUMI] I'll look
into it when I have time.
[MELTY] Hey, Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI] What is it?
I know that you've been
busy lately, but don't forget
you need to do what
Fitoria asked you.
I will, once we're done
with things in Q'ten Lo.
And just remember, she gave
you the reward in advance.
[NAOFUMI] I know.
- [FILO] Melty!
- Huh?
I'll be there
in a second.
It's time to play.
[MELTY]
I wasn't done talking.
Fitoria, huh?
She said she wanted the four
heroes to get closer, but...
Sir Ren, is there anything
missing from the shopping list?
How about adding
some dried jerky?
We're running low.
Will do.
Thank you so much.
Looks like you've
been helping out.
It's not much, but I'm
doing everything I can.
I am a part of this
village, after all.
Naofumi, do you think we
should come along to help
you guys fight
in Q'ten Lo?
It's hard to say.
I honestly don't know
if the Cardinal Weapons
will even work on them.
But we're taking
a ship to get there.
If we have to fight
a battle at sea
long-range weapons
will definitely help.
Itsuki, Rishia
Absolutely.
[squeals] I'll
do my best.
But I want you
staying here
Are you up for protecting
the village with Eclair?
Sure, but...
[NAOFUMI] I only ask
because it seems
like the villagers
trust you.
For now, just focus
on breaking the curse.
I'll call you with
the portal when we need you.
Yeah, you got it.
[knock on door]
[RAPHTALIA]
Um, Master Naofumi.
Hmm?
The emperor, who
exactly are they?
What kind of person
sends assassins
to protect
their position?
It's human nature
to try and cling to power.
So they're no different
from anyone else.
I have no interest
in those things, though.
Don't tell me.
Tell it to the people
of Q'ten Lo.
Right.
I have my doubts
they'll be convinced
but we have to try.
[folk music]
[chattering]
Has everything I
requested been prepared?
Yes.
Everything's
almost on board.
The last 10% is
being loaded now.
[RISHIA]
All of this is just 10%
of what we're
bringing along?
Well, we can't
have anything happening
to the Shield
Hero, can we?
So we went ahead and added
a little bit extra.
Incredible.
That's so kind
of you to do that.
Am I mistaken, or do they
not seem happy to see me?
[RISHIA]
No, I think you're right.
[grumbles]
[yelps]
OK, it's time to board.
When everything's
loaded, we're leaving.
[MAKINA] I have some
troubling news to report.
Only just a few moments
ago, the false emperor
left port for
our nation.
But there's no
need to worry.
They'll never make
it to our lands.
You have my word that they'll
perish at sea before then.
You just leave the dirty
work to me and me alone.
Someone with a kind
heart such as yourself
shouldn't have
to worry about staining
their hands with blood.
[chuckles]
[adventurous music]
[boat whooshing]
♪♪
[RAPHY]
Whoo-hee!
[FILO]
It's like we're flying!
Hey, don't do that.
It's bad luck.
♪♪
[retches]
That's a strange
light, isn't it?
Yeah, it sure is.
But we can't reach
Q'ten Lo without it.
Look there!
♪♪
Are those whirlpools?
If you don't keep
following the light
the whirlpools will
block your path.
We've got a whirlpool
right in front of us.
Hard to starboard!
[creaking, whooshing]
Whee!
♪♪
Your parents
and Raphtalia's parents
made it through
these conditions?
That's right.
My mother and father
did this, just like us.
These whirlpools
are a headache.
Yeah. Why do you think
your master went to Q'ten Lo
in the first place?
No idea.
He was always
on the move, whether it
meant chasing skirts or running
from debt collectors.
He sounds like a loser.
[ERHARD]
He has a lot of problems
but also
top-notch skills.
After falling in love with one
of his weapons at first sight
I started
learning from him.
[NAOFUMI]
That good, huh?
[ERHARD]
If I can meet him again
I can take my skills
to the next level.
If he's as talented
as you say
maybe I should just
hire him instead.
Come on, don't
be like that.
[laughter]
[squawks]
Anything to report?
I'm not able to see
it, but I can sense
a dragon in
the far distance.
Let me guess
Hmm. I tried to get
closer to see
but I was blocked
by a barrier.
That dragon must
have put it up.
We're almost
to Q'ten Lo's waters.
[panting]
This fog.
I hope we're able
to get there unscathed.
These guys were
willing to come
all the way
to our village.
They won't let us reach
land without a fight.
Stay sharp, everyone.
[water shushing]
Something is approaching
from our rear starboard!
Another ship, it's going
to collide with us!
[bell ringing]
[adventurous music]
[arrows thudding]
[squeals]
Wind Arrow!
[explosion]
Master Naofumi!
Let's go!
Oh, what's
going... [squeals]
[explosion]
♪♪
[arrows thudding]
[MONKEY ASSASSIN] Death
to the false emperor!
Tornado Throw!
Meteor Shot!
[BUNNY ASSASSIN]
Death to the false emperor!
[FOX AND MONKEY ASSASSINS]
[SADEENA]
I'll handle this.
As source of thy
power, I order thee
decipher the laws of nature
and let the lightning I command
pierce the
foes before me!
All Drifa!
Chain Lightning!
[BUNNY ASSASSIN groans]
Be careful using that.
Zweit Aura!
Good timing.
Thank you.
♪♪
We need to take them
alive and question them.
♪♪
They might
self-destruct.
Take them
out before then.
- Right.
- Roger.
Understood.
Brother, please, we don't have
time for you to be seasick.
Yeah, I know that.
Stardust Blade!
[smack]
Knew it. Hero attacks don't
have an effect on them.
Die, false emperor!
Air Strike Shield!
Raphy!
[whimpers]
[grumbles]
[thud]
[groans]
[shrieks]
[splash]
[explosion]
Hey! Wait!
Stop!
You're no good underwater.
Let's push them
back, Gaelion.
Lightning
Strike Harpoon!
[yelling]
OK, we're almost done!
[MONKEY ASSASSIN]
Glory to the almighty emperor!
Crap!
[explosion]
[squeals]
No, you don't.
Shield Prison!
[zapping, crashing]
[thump]
Nice job there.
But are you OK?
Yeah.
We're clear
to starboard and to port.
[ITSUKI] Looks like we
should be OK for now.
As long as we servants
of master Naofumi are here
they'll never stop
us in our tracks.
This one, too, huh?
To think they attacked
with the whirlpools here.
That's how bad they wanted to
stop us from reaching Q'ten Lo.
[SADEENA] I hope we can make it
there without any more trouble.
[rumbling]
[splash]
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[squeals]
Naofumi!
Raphtalia!
[squawks]
Master Naofumi!
Atla!
[explosion]
[intense music]
♪♪
[grunts] Where are we?
Are you OK?
Yes.
Thank goodness.
I found you two!
[meeps]
I guess you got caught
in that thing, too?
Yes. It seems the Water
Dragon's brought us here.
[GAELION] I could feel it
in the whirlpool myself.
The Water Dragon.
Surely there must have been
another way to get us here.
Yeah, you're right.
So why would
they do all this?
They must have wanted
to share something urgently.
[NAOFUMI]
What's this?
A dragon
emperor fragment.
And it appears to contain
a direct message
from the Water
Dragon itself.
Are you sure about this?
You might go out
of control again.
[GAELION]
I sense no evil.
It should be fine.
[bright flourish]
Hmm, I see.
Did you learn
anything new?
The Water Dragon wishes
for you to return this nation
to its rightful form
say anything
more than that.
What do you mean
"rightful form"?
[GAELION]
For many years
this nation
was protected by a barrier.
This barrier
existed to protect
the Pacifier
of Spirit Implements.
Oh, what do you
mean by "Pacifier"?
[GAELION] I'm afraid I don't
have more information on it.
But it seems
your clan fulfilled
that role for
generations.
Huh?
Hey, Raphtalia
anything about
that to you?
Never. I wish that I could
be of more help.
He probably thought
it was something
you didn't need to know.
Yes.
"Spirit implements."
If I had to guess
to the Cardinal Weapons.
I was just thinking
the same thing.
Then pacifier
must mean...
Judging by the name
who keeps a tight leash on
the wielders of those weapons.
For example, if a hero
misuses the power of a weapon
having somebody who's
immune to its effects
would prevent the worst
from transpiring.
The weapons they've
been using must
be an application
of that art.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
All right, Gaelion
are we supposed
to do then?
It's important to note
the emperor has control
over Q'ten Lo's barrier.
Our first order of business
should be to take care of that
or our friends
can't make landfall.
Seriously?
Raphy?
Raphy!
Huh?
Raphy. Raphy.
Raphy!
Raphy. Raph-Raph.
Raphy.
Raphy!
Whoa!
- Raphy.
- Huh?
I'm told they're stuck
going around in circles.
They can't
go any further.
It's just like
the Water Dragon said, huh?
So even if
we'd kept going
we never
would have made it, huh?
It would appear
there's a base nearby
that controls
the barrier.
[footsteps]
I hate the idea that this
thing is manipulating us
but we don't
have a choice.
[RAPHTALIA]
What's this?
The Water Dragon
prepared these.
You will have to wear them
to hide your identities.
They're
well-prepared, huh?
[calming music]
[gasps] A shining
cherry tree?
[SADEENA] The Sakura Lumina
are unique to Q'ten Lo.
♪♪
Well, it wasn't easy
at least we all
made it here.
This place
and father
were both born.
♪♪
[singing in Japanese]
ARRIVING IN Q'TEN LO