[♪ Solemn
orchestral music]
[sighs]
I mean, after all
it's thanks to Master Naofumi
that I'm even alive right now.
Yeah, that's right.
Atla was getting sicker
by the day.
She never would've recovered
without his help.
[gasps]
[MIRELIA] I figured I'd
find you here.
[gasps]
How have the children
been faring?
The white
tiger siblings.
Last I heard
accompanying
the Shield Hero's party.
[gasps]
You mean to tell me
you let them go?
And to Siltvelt?
Their kind is
hated there.
[war sound, screams]
Magic Prism!
[magical charging sound]
Now's our chance!
Give it your all!
Drifa Shine Ray!
[magical charging sound]
[♪ Angelical chorus]
[screams]
[roars]
[♪ Gentle music]
[AULTCRAY] In my nation's
war against Siltvelt
countless
lives were lost.
And one of them
was their leader, Tyrant.
The white tigers were forced
to bear full responsibility
and lost any position
they had in their country.
Those poor kids.
They carry with them
the burden of Tyrant's blood.
Siltvelt doesn't take
kindly to that.
Yes, but those children have
their own path to follow.
[gasps]
But...
Need I remind you
I have every confidence
he'll ensure their safety.
[sighs]
I'm not listening to another
second of this!
Huh?
[♪ Opening music begins]
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
[♪ opening music ends]
[♪ Tense, playful music]
EPISODE 3: A TRUE PEOPLE
[MAN] That white tiger needs
to be put in place.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[JARALIS] The girl
carries tainted blood.
What? But how?
Do you mean to tell us this girl
bears human blood?
Could it be
she's Tyrant's?
Look, brat.
You have no right to
speak amongst us.
Be gone with you.
Bears tainted blood.
No right to speak?
How absurd.
How could you say such a thing
after poisoning us?
Your accusation
means nothing.
The citizens of Siltvelt
and especially you.
[JARALIS] Hold
your tongue!
This nation…
Has forgotten the one thing
that still unites it as one.
If I were to stop here
I would never be able
to forgive myself.
Atla…
As Master Naofumi's shield
who's sworn to protect him
you're wrong!
I declare all of you
to be completely wrong!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[JARALIS] And how exactly
are we the ones in the wrong?
For starters
are disrespectful
to the Shield Hero.
[LADY] You
take that back.
[MAN] We would never
disrespect our Hero.
Ever since he arrived
within our power to welcome him
here with open arms.
If that's true, then why have
you continued to deny him
his very simple request
for a ship?
[gasps]
Even worse, your behavior
towards him has been
disrespectful since
we arrived here.
It's disturbing
But the worst part
about all of it
is that it took me
so long to realize
how rude all
of you were being.
Now then, I have
a question for you.
How was Siltvelt founded
in the first place?
Hm.
[sigh]
I believe it was the Shield Hero
who made it possible
for Demi-humans and beast men
to live side by side.
Correct.
And in the same way
Master Naofumi's gone
and founded his own village.
It's like
Lurolona Village.
I'm welcome there.
[♪ Gentle,
emotional music]
Well, we are
still slaves.
You see?
Master Naofumi welcomed beast men
and Demi-humans alike
giving them not just
a place to live
but a place they can
finally call home.
All of us are forever
in his debt.
Not only do I serve him
[sighs]
We all should
be thankful.
The same way
he gave me a home
he gave each of you
the wonderful country
of Siltvelt to call home.
It's so easy to forget.
But we really do owe everything
we have to the Shield Hero.
Everything we do
Then it sounds like
we're in agreement.
We owe the Shield Hero
our lives.
Does everyone concur?
[CROWD] I concur.
Yes!
We're of
different countries
but the feelings that
we share are the same.
But our country
is much bigger
than a tiny village
like your own.
Tell me.
Was it always that way here?
Or did you also start out small?
[ATLA] Are you saying
the village Master Naofumi
has brought back to life
is too small to matter?
[MAN] No, but…
But think about why
we have our power.
Our claws.
Our fangs.
Is it to take from people
who can't defend themselves?
[ATLA] Or to stand up
and protect them?
The answer lies
at the center of our being.
Well, it's because...
You're not thinking!
We have these
for one purpose.
To serve the
Shield Hero.
[ATLA] Even if you mock me
for having tainted blood
the blood that
resides in me
my heart, my soul.
Each of them
cries out to me
to express my undying loyalty
to the Shield Hero.
[ATLA] The waves of calamity
you fear wait for no one.
Only the Shield Hero
can help us fight back.
[ATLA] We must not
forget who we serve.
[MAN] She's right!
Only he can bring us together.
[MAN] The man before us is
the hero of the time to come.
[murmurs]
[deep exhale]
[JARALIS] Disgusting
white tiger.
That was
certainly a lot.
But none of it
sounded wrong
so I don't know if there's
anything to add to it.
Right, Master Naofumi?
Yeah.
She's got a
way with words.
[WERNER] Our
sole objective
is to support the Shield Hero
and do all that we can
to save the world
from the coming disaster.
I'd like to thank you
for helping us remember that.
[WERNER] And yet
you would try and poison
the Shield Hero!
What you did
is unforgivable.
Give them the
death sentence!
Why would you commit
such a heinous act?
You dare
accuse us of that?
Where's your proof
we did anything anyway?
Filo, Sadeena!
Don't worry!
We made sure to bring him
here with us.
Oh, hey there, Master.
[chuckles]
[♪ Suspense music]
[murmurs]
Right this way, dear.
[groans]
Hi. My name is Denny.
I was the one
given the honor
of preparing breakfast
for the Shield Hero today.
I'm a court chef, so it
should've been smooth sailing.
[gasps]
[grunts]
I'm still hungry.
Can we go back
to breakfast, Master?
I don't mind eating it
if it's poisoned.
Once we finish dealing
with stuff here, you can eat.
Fine.
Let me explain.
Over the last three days
I've had Ethan keep an eye
on things in the palace.
[gasps]
[MAN] A white tiger
working with the hero?
The welcome was
more than enough to
to make me suspect each
and every one of you.
While I was doing recon
I saw him add poison
to today's breakfast.
[sigh]
You have to forgive me.
I swear, it wasn't me.
It was…
[sigh]
I had to do it.
[NAOFUMI] Don't worry.
Your family is safe.
[gasps]
You're free to
speak your mind.
No harm will be coming
their way now.
Oh, thank you,
Shield Hero.
Who told you
to use poison?
[hesitates]
[gasps]
Jaralis told me to.
[grunts]
[sighs]
But I only did it because
he threatened me and my family.
Look, he's telling
the truth, Master.
Explain yourself.
Hm.
How strange.
I don't believe you
and I have met before.
Are you sure it was me
who instructed you?
You weren't just given my name
to say at this time?
Well, uh...
Look, Shield Hero.
I can only assume that this is
a plot to ruin my good name.
I've yet to see
any proof I did this.
Yeah, where's the proof?
There must be something, right?
He is the proof!
Just drop the
act and confess!
I figured he'd say that.
[people chattering
indistinctly]
That's enough!
Let's go, Filo.
Okay.
Well, either way
I'm not staying in a country
that tries to poison me.
Deal with the
rest yourselves.
Shield Hero!
[JARALIS]
Before you leave.
Huh?
There's something I think
everyone here should know about.
I believe with
all my heart
the Shield
Hero before us is
not the hero of the time to come
we've been waiting for.
That's enough, Jaralis!
You go too far!
Like all of you here
for the future of Siltvelt
and want to see it prosper.
Making the wrong decision could
spell the end for our nation
and that is why
I am now forced
to speak up against
the Shield Hero.
Master Naofumi
our god, is not one
to make mistakes.
Raphy?
Tell me then
are you so foolish that
you would suggest
he isn't the real
Shield Hero?
Well, I wouldn't
go that far.
However
I want to call into question
if what we're experiencing
truly are the
waves of calamity.
If they really are meant
to destroy the whole world
then why was the Shield Hero
summoned to Melromarc?
And not the country
that worships him as a god?
That fact alone is
all the proof you need
to know he's not the hero
we've been waiting for.
So I ask again!
Is he truly the hero
of the time to come?
I believe it
remains to be seen.
[gasps]
[MAN] You mean…
The Shield Hero isn't the hero
that we've been waiting for?
I always have
found it odd
that he was summoned
to Melromarc instead.
I get it now.
So this is why
Jaralis was so calm.
[♪ Suspense music]
The answer to
that is obvious.
What we're facing now
are the waves.
It's because of that
impending danger
the Shield Hero was summoned
along with the other three.
While each one of them
is powerful, their strength lies
in how they can
work together.
Because of that
it only makes sense he was
summoned to Melromarc.
It was his best chance to work
with the other heroes.
That fact alone is proof
that the world is in danger.
Sounds like nonsense.
I'm telling the truth.
I'd expect anyone
who's sworn loyalty
to Master Naofumi
to understand that.
It seems I'm not the only one
who's sworn loyalty
to him that holds doubt
for him in their hearts.
[gasps]
Err…
Didn't you all find it
to be a bit peculiar?
If Werner had sworn loyalty
to the Shield Hero
why hasn't he been able
to procure a ship as requested?
[JARALIS] It's because if he
does not stay in the country
those who doubt that he is
the hero of the time to come
will not be satisfied.
Am I wrong?
It's just...
You're all so selfish.
Why?
After everything
Master Naofumi has done
why do you insist
on prioritizing
your own agendas
over him?
I believe this girl's words
to be the truth.
[gasps]
Young, but with a will
as strong as any.
Weak in appearance, but fierce
in everything that she does.
Look at her.
She might not
be from here
but she exudes everything
our country stands for.
I believe her to be the only
true citizen of Siltvelt here.
What are you doing here?
Pff.
[MAN] I can't believe
you really came.
Who is this?
[WERNER] The
Elder of Genmu.
He's been retired
for some time now.
Despite that
he holds a lot of influence
with all the different factions.
[♪ Smooth music]
It's an honor
to meet you
I never thought the day would
come you'd stand before me.
I'm Elder Genmu.
But you can call me Elder
if it's too much trouble.
Elder, your appearance.
You do stand before
the Shield Hero.
Ah, yes, my apologies.
Understand, it's required
I take this form
in order to better
protect myself.
It's practically
a habit now.
[vibrant sound]
I didn't mean
to eavesdrop
Does anyone here disagree with
anything this girl said earlier?
How could you
when she speaks the truth?
It's utter foolishness to
prioritize your own desires
over those of the Shield Hero
who now stands before us.
The Elder's
absolutely right.
So you would listen to the words
of someone with tainted blood?
No true citizen of Siltvelt
would ever do such a thing.
I've heard enough.
If you insist
on continuing to be
an obstacle for Master
Naofumi's endeavors
then I shall
eliminate you by force.
Atla!
[grunts]
If it's a death wish
you have
I'll kill you and stain my hands
with your cursed blood.
I accept your challenge.
Silence, both of you.
[grunts]
[disdain]
Yelling at each other isn't
going to do anyone any good.
Now let's see
what to do.
Ah!
As is Siltvelt tradition
to do so
why don't we settle things
with a duel?
[murmurs]
A duel?
Elder!
Is that not
a bit too far?
If there is doubt that he is
the hero of the time to come
then this must
come to pass.
If it didn't happen now
[sighs]
If you say so.
Well, in that case
I volunteer to serve
as second
to the white tiger
Demi-human, that is.
Jaralis!
[WERNER] If you intend to prove
what you believe to be true
then you must
accept the duel.
[grunts]
For the sake
of what is fair
I hope someone
of my stature is up to par.
Are these terms
satisfactory for you?
After all the lies
you've spoken till now
I'm sure you're willing to take
the risk of what
will happen if you find yourself
on the losing side of this.
Of course I am.
Ha!
I accept the terms
of this duel.
[crowd gasps]
This whole situation's
gotten out of hand.
Yeah.
I thought the poison would be my
trump card to get to Q'ten Lo.
So why are we having
a duel now?
Now, if I win
this little duel…
[JARALIS] First
we shall strip the white
tiger Demi-humans
of their position as one of the
four great races in Siltvelt.
And in their place, we Laio
shall rise to power.
[grunts]
Furthermore, the Shield Hero
shall belong to our country
and our country alone.
Finally, the girl with tainted
blood shall face punishment.
[JARALIS] Are these terms
okay with you?
Hell no! The results of the duel
are weighted in your favor.
Sounds good to me.
You needn't
worry. If I win
So be it.
Well, if I win the duel, you're
to do whatever I want, Jaralis.
It would be my pleasure
However, I don't think
that will be happening.
[gasps]
All right.
If the Shield
Hero's party wins
Siltvelt will grant
whatever your heart desires.
Is that satisfactory?
Fine by me.
Very well.
I permit this duel.
The white tiger Demi-human
versus Jaralis.
Hold on.
Huh?
Brother, please.
Let me fight.
I can take her place.
I should be the one
to defeat that monster!
Huh.
I can't allow that.
Master Naofumi's future
is at stake
and I can't trust you
to win this duel.
[gasps]
Atla dear
why not give
him a chance?
After all, I've never
seen him so certain.
I know, but...
There's something
I have to ask him, Atla.
And I'll do it
after I defeat him.
It has to be me.
I'll beat him for
me and Father.
Hm.
If you're so determined
[exhales nervously]
Nothing would
make me happier
than to show you what noble
blood is capable of doing.
Don't be daft.
Duels must be fought with equal
participants on either side.
Yes, you needn't
worry though.
I'll happily bring
another person.
Is that all
right with you
[sighs]
Master Naofumi
Even if my
brother does fail
I'm able to defeat them
on my own.
Atla, have faith in me!
[ATLA] Going along
with the enemy's plan
and still winning
is a sign of strength.
I promise you, I'll win.
Please agree,
Master Naofumi.
Come on.
[sighs]
If that's what you want.
[chuckles]
[♪ Smooth music]
Raphy, Ra-Raphy!
[ATLA] Master Naofumi.
Are you positive
about this?
I am, and it feels like it's
important to my brother too.
This is my chance to prove how
strong my loyalty is for you.
Nothing makes me happier than
you knowing you can rely on me.
Above all else.
I can't exactly
call myself your shield
if I can't overcome
a little duel.
[approval]
I'm counting on you.
Thank you.
That's all I've ever
wanted to hear.
[MAN] Both parties
[♪ dramatic music]
[gasps]
Hold on.
Who the hell is
that buff minotaur?
Oh my.
Incredible.
He's called one
of the heroes
from the last Great War
to fight alongside him.
Yes.
Seeing how this battle will
decide the Shield Hero's fate
it would be foolish
to entrust
such a matter to anyone
but the best.
Mark my words.
I will be victorious.
And my daughter shall marry
the Shield Hero.
[gasps]
That wasn't a condition.
[glimmering] [smirk]
[giggles]
[gasps]
How dare you use Master Naofumi
in your arranged marriage?
Atla! Fohl!
You have to win!
Just leave it to us.
Yeah.
Jaralis, your
fight is with me.
And if I win
you have to tell me everything
you know about my dad.
Hm.
Happily, filthy
white tiger.
Before we start the duel
[♪ epic music]
[MAN] Begin!
[gong]
[♪ Closing music begins]
[♪ Closing music ends]
ENTRUSTED POWER