[♪ Joyful music]
[NAOFUMI] This room
should be more
than big enough for all of us.
[RAPHTALIA] Even so
I'm afraid this room is for you
and you alone, Shield Hero.
No fair!
I want to stay
right here with Master.
[SERVANT] We've already prepared
another room for your servants.
I'm sure you're
wondering
what you'll be doing
for the rest of the day.
Once you've gotten acquainted
with everything in your room
we'll have you change
into Siltvelt formal wear.
It's customary when attending
a banquet like the one tonight.
[sighs]
But before all that, we'll have
a bath drawn for you.
It shouldn't take more
than a few minutes.
It feels like they're pretending
we don't even exist.
It sure does.
There's still time
till the banquet.
We should go out and
explore the town while we can.
Thanks, but I want to be on
standby in the next room.
If something happens to Master
Naofumi, I have to protect him.
Oh, come on. It'll be just fine.
Let's go see the town.
[sighs]
You know what?
I think that's
a great idea.
Yay!
I wonder if the booze
is any good around here.
[FILO] What are we waiting for?
Let's go!
[RAPHTALIA] But…
[NAOFUMI] But?
[startled gasps]
Raphy stays
here with me.
Raphy!
[♪ Opening music begins]
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
[♪ opening music ends]
EPISODE 2:
OFFICIAL WELCOME
What a pain.
The way things stand
this country might be more
of a headache than I thought.
Right, Raphy?
[squeaks]
What is it, Raphy?
That's a cool shield.
Let's see.
Its skills are
beast transformation
and territory reform.
[gasps]
[bells chiming]
[♪ Joyful, chill music]
Wow! That looks yummy.
This town is fabulous
[giggles]
Anything catch your eye?
Judging from this statue
it seems like they know
how to show respect
for Master Naofumi.
I hope he's okay.
These all look
really yummy too.
I don't know about you
If things keep
going smoothly…
Master Naofumi's territory
might look like this someday.
Just let me know whenever
you're ready to order.
- Okay.
Huh? They
forgot their waters.
[people whispering]
Disgusting.
I wish they would
get out of here.
Now I understand why you were so
reluctant to leave the castle.
He's been acting like this
the whole time we've been here.
You let it get to you
too much, brother.
It's wonderful to have
so many types of people
living together, but I'm sure
things are complicated.
Things are never quite
as simple as they seem to be.
We need to learn
all that we can
And then report back to Naofumi
everything we find out.
[sighs]
Feels relaxing,
right, Raphy?
Raphy.
[bubbling]
Ah?
APHRODISIAC DETECTED
[gasping]
Aphrodisiac?
What the hell is that about?
So much for relaxing.
[female laughter]
[gasping]
[women clamoring,
approaching]
Shield Hero!
Wait, wait, wait!
Stay away from me!
Meteor Shield!
[women clamoring]
Open up!
I thought you want someone
to wash your back?
Portal Shield!
PORTAL SHIELD
UNAVAILABLE
Unavailable?
Raphy!
Raphtalia! Is
everything okay?
Master Naofumi!
[panting]
Well, I guess that's
our cue to get going.
I've never been so full.
Hey, not all of us are done
eating, you know?
[women clamoring]
This must be what the Queen
was talking about.
First off
you're going to be welcomed, and
then, approached by noblewomen.
After that, they'll attempt
to form a type of harem for you
with women from
any number of species.
A harem?
[screams]
All right.
Great Dragon Vein
we call upon thee
in our time of need.
The source of thy power
Decipher the laws
that govern nature
and call forth an illusion
to deceive our foes.
Emptiness manifest form!
[whooshing]
[squirming]
You're amazing,
Shield Hero.
Wow! He's even stronger
than he looks.
[women clamoring]
What the hell kind of illusion
are they seeing?
Wait a second, isn't it
"form manifest
emptiness"?
Master Naofumi,
are you okay?
[gasps]
Oh, why? I came when
I heard the SOS signal.
What's going on here?
Exactly what it looks like.
An emergency.
Oh my.
You seem to be
enjoying yourself.
Shoot, they got to you
ahead of me.
They're seeing
an illusion
Now let's get
out of here.
You've got
some explaining to do.
I'm truly sorry
if they troubled you.
It's a service
we've provided
for the Shield Hero
for generations.
I had assumed
you would enjoy it.
Are you insulting me
right now?
Not in the slightest.
Please, forgive me
Enough empty apologies.
If you want
my forgiveness
then you'll get me
on that boat to Q'ten Lo.
Yes, of course.
We'll hold a conference
within a few days
where we'll vote
on the matter.
If it takes
you that long
I suppose I'll just have to head
back home using my portal skill.
Please, you
must be patient.
All I require is
a little more time.
I promise I'll have
a ship for you.
All right, fine.
That said, if you keep
treating us like this
don't be surprised if we do
something about it.
I just don't
trust Werner.
Who knows if he can
even get us a ship.
Raphy.
[suspense tones]
[gasping]
[chattering]
[♪ Fun, elegant music]
Oh my!
What a magnificent outfit.
That outfit must have some
deeper meaning to it, right?
Tell me
everything about it
[giggling]
Attention! The glorious worship
ceremony has come to an end.
However
our pleasant evening of dinner
and sweets has just begun.
[crowd gasps]
I can go and put a plate
together for you if you want.
Sure. Sounds nice.
Thanks.
[giggling]
Did somebody say "food"?
[guests whispering]
Don't pay attention to them
so much, big brother.
Atla's giving you
some good advice.
Just try and keep
your head up.
It's a rare opportunity
An opportunity?
Nothing is as it seems.
Just take a look around.
This is supposed
to be an elegant banquet
to worship the Shield Hero.
But there must be some people
that are here for other reasons.
And if you were
to find those people
I have a feeling this party
would be over in no time.
[gasping]
Can I get another
drink, please?
People here for
other reasons, huh?
[gasping]
[JARALIS] Shield Hero.
Are you enjoying the party
as much as it seems you are?
I know you.
Jaralis, right?
Words can't describe
how pleased I am
to know you remembered
my name.
About our discussion
yesterday…
Fohl. Atla.
[gasps]
I need to
speak with you.
Wait a second.
It's been a
while, hasn't it?
Many years.
Look at you two.
You've both grown so much.
It is you.
You know this
man? Who is he?
But of course.
Ethan worked for our father.
Worked for our father?
Yep.
You may not remember
this very well
but Ethan used to stop
by our house and play
with us all the time.
Your parents died
I've been worried sick thinking
about the two of you.
Seeing you here now
certainly calms me.
As you've witnessed
us white tiger
Demi-humans
are often looked down upon
by others in this country.
It's humiliating.
However, there is something
urgent I had to tell you.
[swallowing]
The two of you should avoid
Jaralis, the lion.
You see
it's suspected that he had
a hand in your father's death.
Seriously?
Rumor has it
he was present during
your father's last moments.
That being said
people in the military that
claim this rumor to be false.
Well, was it?
Yes.
His report of Master Turen's
last moments didn't make sense.
I told the military
to investigate.
But they refused
claiming they already
looked into things.
Even now
I regret not fighting with
Master Turen until the end.
I should have been there
to protect him.
But now, I have a chance
to atone for my sins
by doing whatever I can
to help his children.
Know that I'm here
to serve you however I can.
So, are things
proceeding well
with Lord Werner
concerning your ship?
As I thought.
Werner has little to no desire
to do something
like summon you a ship
if it would mean you're leaving.
After all, the longer
he keeps you here
the more favor he garners
from the masses.
Public opinion is very important
for someone like him.
Why does it
even matter at all?
Because the people's faith
in the Shield Hero is
so strong in
this country.
People began
asking themselves
why you protect
other nations
as opposed to protecting the
place where you're worshipped
Siltvelt.
You see
more and more people here are
beginning to share that thought.
Werner's concern
is that the people who
share this sentiment
might do something rash if the
opportunity presented itself.
Which means
no matter what
you say to him
[disagreement]
However, I'm offering you myself
as an alternative.
Say the word and I'll arrange
a ship to Q'ten Lo for you.
Unfortunately, I'm not able
to do so officially
due to the limits
of my position here.
That being said
I'm willing to do
whatever it takes
if it means me helping out
the Shield Hero.
You are our people's god
and this is your wish.
Believe me when I tell you
it saddens me to say
but letting me help you is
the only way to Q'ten Lo.
[birds chirping]
Wow!
[FILO] Looks yummy.
It certainly does.
[WERNER] Oh, there you are.
Good morning, Shield Hero.
If you don't mind, I'd like you
to attend a conference
after you've
finished eating.
Followed by a lunch
All right, all right.
I'll be there.
Great.
I will come and get you early
to show you the location.
As expected.
Werner keeps throwing
meaningless ceremonies
and useless meetings my way
to keep us stuck here.
Jaralis is
right about that
But the way he's been sucking up
to me doesn't sit
right with me either.
From what Fohl
and Atla told me
it sounds like this guy
could be dangerous.
[sighs]
Seems neither of them
can be trusted.
Which means…
Offer up your prayers
to the Shield Hero.
It is the will of the Shield God
that determines all.
It is thanks to him
that we have food.
that we are here.
Let this food before us
and our lives
become the power
to enact His will.
Let it become power!
Even the prayers they say
here are wonderful.
Now then, it would be
our pleasure
if you were to eat first
Either way, this country
is starting to creep me out.
I've got to find
a way out of here.
All right. Let's bring this
special meeting to order.
To begin, as we work
to strengthen our military
in preparation
for the next wave
we need to reorganize
our forces
with the Shield Hero at the
center in order to bring out…
Let me stop you there.
You talk like
I'm staying
abundantly clear that
I'm only passing through here.
And we acknowledge that.
Which brings me to our next
point to address here…
The budget needed to have
our finest shipyard build
a vessel worthy
of the Shield Hero.
You know that's not
what I want.
[sighs]
Listen, I'm not stupid.
I understand you need me to stay
right here so you can use me
to expand your military and
unite the people of your nation.
[gasps]
However, just like you want
to protect your country
I want to protect
the lands I govern.
The people of my village
are waiting for me to return
as we speak.
Yes, but…
Look, once the Phoenix and
Q'ten Lo are dealt with, I don't
mind acting more like the Shield
Hero you want me to be.
[clapping]
Spoken like a true hero.
A ruler should
always prioritize his lands and
people above everything else.
And in that sense
I could learn a thing or two
from you, Shield Hero.
Though I'm sad you
want to leave.
After all, I want
the same thing
for the Shield Hero
to unite our country
and quell
the people's worries.
But look what
we're doing here.
Can you not see we're ignoring
the wishes of our god
for our own country's
self-interest?
Shouldn't we honor his wish and
prepare a ship immediately?
As I'm sure you're
well aware of by now
only spokesmen of the four
great races can speak here.
Please know
your place, Jaralis.
[groans]
I apologize
for the inconvenience.
Your input on this matter is
very valuable to all of us here.
Please give us some
more time, so that
we may put together our thoughts
in light of your opinion.
Yet another delay.
Just how hard-headed
is this guy?
[hammer strikes]
[giggles]
Master Naofumi.
Let's do this quickly
while nobody's around.
Mmhm.
This is Ethan, the person
that I was telling you about.
It's such an
honor to meet you.
You have my thanks
for saving these two.
Please know you've done
more than I can ever repay
and so I'll be forever
in your debt.
I'll do anything. Anything
if it means helping you two.
That's enough.
I did it because
I wanted to.
In any case, Fohl told you
what I needed, right?
Yes, to keep a watchful eye
on the two of them.
Correct.
Werner and Jaralis
are a problem.
They'll both try to break out
of the stalemate they're in…
Which means they might
do something rash.
Share any information you get
with these guys.
Hello!
Nice to meet you.
And in just a few days
Wow.
On the surface, I played along
with their stalling tactics
while I prepared
in secret.
So that I'd be ready
when the time came.
And thus, my days
in Siltvelt passed by.
POISON DETECTED
It's not yummy anymore.
Really?
I, on the other hand
will eat anything as long
as there's beer with it.
That's gross.
The will of the Shield God
determines everything.
It is thanks to him
that we have food.
that we're here.
Let this food before us and
our lives become
the power to
enact His will.
Let it become power!
Shield Hero, please eat
before the rest of us.
[grunts]
[crowd coughing]
Shield Hero, what is
the meaning of this?
Just shut up
and drink it.
It tastes like shit, but it's
better than dying of poison.
Poison?
So he's playing
dumb, huh?
To poison a god is a crime
worthy of death.
It is blasphemous.
What's with the look?
Have something
to tell me?
All right, relax.
Seeing as you all
love to chitchat
what do you say we sit down
and talk about this?
[chuckles]
To think that someone would
try poisoning me.
I thought this country of yours
was supposed to be safe.
There's no doubt in my mind
that Jaralis did this.
Only he would do something as
shallow as betraying our own God
Without proof, I'm afraid your
words are as empty as your head.
For all we know, you could
have done it because
you knew the Shield Hero
was leaving our lands.
It makes sense
now, doesn't it?
Liar.
Well, I don't
care who did it
All that matters is someone
tried poisoning us.
To me, it's
unforgivable.
I can't cooperate with a country
that tries poisoning me.
Plus, I've got a
lead on a boat.
I'm not going to entertain your
shenanigans any longer.
You can't, Shield Hero.
Please.
You've only yourself to blame
for this, Werner.
You've upset our God and lost a
chance to help him out.
I would go so far as
to call this blasphemous.
That's quite the failure you
have on your name, Werner.
Know your
place, Jaralis.
I knew that you were up to
something underhanded.
If you say
I'm responsible for this
To make such an accusation
is unforgivable.
Everything you've done up until
now is all the proof that I need
I know you'd do anything
if it meant you'd gain power.
I'm not the only one
who's able to see that.
I knew it.
He's right.
Coward.
Shameful.
You're only doing this because
you're in danger.
Or should I say
your position's in danger?
Is this any way for a ruler
to be acting amidst a crisis?
This is what happens
when you let bloodlines decide
who gets to be in charge.
There are many
talented people
outside of the four great races
who are fit to lead.
[laughter]
How embarrassing
if you're referring to yourself.
What was that?
Shut up, Laio.
[fighting]
All of you, shut up.
I'm not listening
to another second of this.
[♪ Closing music begins]
[♪ Closing music ends]
A TRUE PEOPLE