[dramatic music]
[yells]
[moans]
[thuds]
[exhales]
[growls]
[whooshes]
[yells]
[thuds]
[grunts]
Go Lightning, and pierce
the foes that stand before me.
All Drifa Chain
Lightning!
[yells]
Well, that's
most of them.
Yeah.
Aw, are we
finished already?
That's no fun.
So what's the
plan, Naofumi?
Do you think we
should help those two?
No. This is their battle
to fight for now.
[grunts]
[booms]
[growls]
My father fought bravely
believing in those
who stood by his side.
[whooshes]
[growls]
And I'm never
going to forgive you
for the cowardly
thing you did to him!
[booms]
You insolent wretch!
I'll send you to hell
with him right now!
[thuds]
There's still
something I must do.
I have to kill a god!
[roars]
[gasps]
Huh?
Master Naofumi!
Oh, my.
They're better already?
There's no way!
[groaning]
[theme music]
♪♪
♪ Hey no need
for hesitation ♪
THE RISING OF
THE SHIELD HERO
♪ Fight it right now ♪
♪ A will to face it
♪ Gangster girl
stop that pass ♪
♪ The reason that I choose
to fight when I travel ♪
♪ Proof that I accept ♪
♪ Leaving no regrets ♪
♪ It seems like a never
ending genocide ♪
♪ No need for hesitation
♪ the pieces
of the story ♪
♪ Don't let it go
♪ 'Cause you're telling
me nor anyone else ♪
♪ No limit to
where we go ♪
♪ I will protect
your resolution ♪
♪ No matter
what comes next ♪
♪ 'Cause they'll
tell again ♪
♪ We'll never
lose and cry ♪
♪ Now nobody can
stop us, no way ♪
♪ Protect you
every time ♪
♪ Push it push it
until you break ♪
♪ Even if there's
nowhere to go ♪
♪ We protect
our resolution ♪
♪ Yeah, hey ♪
♪ No need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Nothing standing
in our way ♪
♪ Fight it right now ♪
♪ Hey, no need
for hesitation ♪
♪ Don't let it
cry go now ♪
[groans]
[gasps]
[buzzing]
[grunts]
[groans]
EPISODE 5: WHITE TIGER
Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
[grunts]
[groans]
Ooh, Master, I keep kicking
them, but it isn't helping.
I know.
They're acting
like zombies.
They're zombies?
It looks like
Jaralis must have
done the same modifications
to his men that Kyo did.
[groans]
[growls]
[yells]
He's so fast.
[booms]
[yells]
Ah, my eyes!
[thuds]
Brother, way to go.
That was amazing.
[gasps]
[low growl]
Blood, more blood.
No.
I need power!
[thuds]
[groans]
[gasps]
[chomping]
[evil chuckle]
What is he doing?
He's devouring
his own men.
[gurgling]
[booms]
[groans, yells]
[groaning]
[NAOFUMI] This isn't just
a duel anymore, Fohl.
[gasps]
It's time for us
to join you in this fight.
You understand?
[sighs]
- Let's go.
- Right.
Yeah!
Ah!
High Quick!
[grunts]
Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew!
Master, that was
icky, squishy, yucky.
[chuckles]
The more I eat, the more
powerful I become!
Hurry, everyone.
We must protect
the Shield Hero
and neutralize
the traitor.
What is that thing?
[gurgling]
It is Jaralis, but he's
transformed into a monster.
Atla, Raphtalia, Fohl!
Get back or he might try
to absorb you guys as well.
We'll stand back then.
Understood,
Master Naofumi.
And the rest
of you, too.
Don't take another step.
Careful, Brother.
[roars].
I'm supreme.
My power
surpasses a god's!
And with it, I will
become strong enough
to conquer the world!
Jaralis!
This is where I avenge
my father...
By taking you down!
[whooshes]
[blasts]
[gasps]
[dramatic music]
[groans]
[thuds]
[gasps]
That's not good.
♪♪
[grunts]
What?
GRANT YOUR POWER TO THE TARGET
TO MAKE THEM TRANSFORM?
[beeping]
[thuds]
[NAOFUMI] Fohl.
You ready?
It's time for you
to get even stronger.
Yes.
I'm ready.
For Atla's sake, and more
than anything, for my own.
I want to be strong
enough to beat him!
That so?
Then let's do this!
GRANT YOUR POWER TO THE TARGET
TO MAKE THEM TRANSFORM?
[heroic music]
[blasting]
♪♪
What is this?
What's happening?
Master Naofumi
This is truly
a divine miracle.
Then they were true.
The legends
were all true.
[uplifting music]
♪♪
This power.
Incredible.
Could it really be me?
This is impossible!
That's quite
impressive, Naofumi.
Your skill transformed
full into a beast too.
So it seems.
This form, it's giving
a buff to all his statuses.
He's stronger than Filo
and Raphtalia like this.
[beeping]
Although it looks like this
power comes with a time limit.
Hey, Fohl!
Hurry up and crush him!
[evil chuckle]
No matter what blessings
the Shield Hero gives you
it won't help!
I will destroy the remnants
of the old god.
And I will build
a new divine myth!
[thuds] What?
[grunts]
[groans]
You're kind of slow.
Is this a joke?
You cheated in order
to get stronger
and you think that
makes you special.
You don't have
the right to say that
you disgusting monster.
A monster?
You're really
calling me a monster?
That's impossible.
In this form, I
am like a god!
[groans]
No.
I'm the monster?
No!
This... this can't be.
It just can't be!
[yells]
[thuds]
Atla?
Listen to me.
Focus all your power
on a single point
and then break through.
All right, you got it.
[determined music]
♪♪
Now, whatever you
do, don't let go!
I see.
If I'm not mistaken
there is an
ancient white tiger
battle technique.
They call it Tyrant
Tiger Strike.
Tyran and Lucia.
Are you both
watching this?
[grunts]
[yelling]
[roars]
No!
It wasn't supposed
to be this way!
That drug was supposed to make
me the most powerful beast man!
How could they do this?
They all tricked me!
[blasts]
[yells]
[booms]
What the... [yells]
We did it, Brother.
We defeated
that old traitor.
Wait, your body.
It's back to normal.
[sighs]
[gentle music]
[ETHAN] Fohl!
Atla!
You did it.
You were able to get revenge
for your father's death.
[gasping]
Father, I finally
avenged you.
[gasps]
Oh no, Brother.
Is something wrong?
You're not
hurt, are you?
Atla, you should
probably get off him now.
Why would I do that?
[RAPHTALIA] Because I'm pretty
sure you're crushing him.
[ATLA] There's no way
my brother is that weak.
[FILO]
Wow. Fohl's all squished!
[SADEENA] Oh, my.
[NAOFUMI]
The following day, a search
began for whoever it was that
gave that drug to Jaralis
and talked him
into committing treason.
But they seemed to have
completely vanished
when Jaralis
was defeated.
Instead, it was decided that
we'd investigate the drug.
So I called
on Rat to help.
It seems like
this will certainly
be worth looking into.
[WERNER] I apologize once
again for our harsh words
towards the
white tigers.
You are true people of
Siltvelt, and because of that
we will give you the respect
you both deserve.
[relieved sighs]
That said, since
we won the duel
will you finally
honor our arrangement?
[WERNER] Yes. But I must inform
you that the duel doesn't
actually matter anymore.
Huh?
[ELDER]
There's an ancient legend.
It says that the one who is
able to reveal the true form
of the people
of Siltelt will be known
as "The Hero
of the Time to Come."
[WERNER]
All will be arranged for you
as you have requested
The ship to Q'ten Lo
is being prepared
and it will be
ready in two days.
[stammers]
And all we dare ask is
that you enjoy your time
in Siltvelt until then.
Now, may I suggest that
perhaps you take a tour
of the castle
town together?
[village chatter]
[SADEENA]
I'm so happy for both of you.
[FOHL] Yeah, thanks.
But I'm just happy I was
able to restore my father's
good name, you know?
And I'm just happy that
I was finally able to get
out of that damn castle.
Hero!
[giggles]
Werner and the others
were saying
something about
a big parade.
We can look
into things like that
once our business with Q'ten
Lo and the Phoenix are settled.
But more
importantly, Fohl.
Huh?
There's somewhere you
wanted to go, right?
Is that OK?
Where do you want
to go, Brother?
[somber music]
♪♪
This grave, it belongs
to our parents, doesn't it?
[NAOFUMI] Now that Fohl
and Atla's parents' honor
was finally restored
upon Jaralis's defeat
their graves were
scheduled to be moved.
But Fohl refused.
He said he knew
that they both would
have wanted
to remain here.
Fohl's sudden growth is
just something that happens
to Demi-humans, I think.
Becoming a beast man and then a
beast, but more than anything
defeating the powerful foe
that killed his parents
was the greatest
catalyst for it.
Atla was extremely
jealous of him.
Now, Fohl and Atla
There's another place
I need to show you two.
[gasps]
You're showing us
their parents' home?
Fohl decided
to sell it in order
to pay for all of Atla's
medical treatments
shortly after
their parents passed away.
I'm so sorry, Atla.
It's OK, Brother.
You don't need
to apologize to me.
But the new owner heard
what happened and would
like to return
it to you.
[SADEENA] Really?
What a generous person.
Yeah, it was someone close to
my father who bought the house.
And they paid
a lot for it, too.
That's very
kind of them.
[thuds]
[FILO groans]
The road was all
bumpy, wasn't it?
[FOHL] We made it.
All right.
So which one of these
is your house?
That big one, that couldn't
possibly be it, could it?
[FOHL]
Actually, it is.
[NAOFUMI]
Seriously?
[RAPHTALIA]
It's huge.
Somebody put a lot
of thought into these details.
Those windows
remind me of shoji.
[RAPHTALIA] Shoji?
It seems similar
to Chinese decor.
[FILO] Master, look!
Huh?
This tiger's eyes
are both missing.
[FOHL]
Yeah, that's right.
We sold anything
worth money.
Even though you
were a rich kid
you still had
it rough, huh?
Would you shut up?
This is my
father's study.
And they actually left
it exactly like it was.
Brings back so
many memories.
[gasps]
It looks like
a changing room.
There used to be traditional
white tiger clothing here.
But this is.
That's weird.
Didn't you say before
that you sold everything?
Yeah, so why?
You don't think they
returned it, do you?
I mean, from
my perspective
I had eventually planned
to make enough money
to be able to
buy it all back.
[NAOFUMI]
That's good, but...
Remember, you still owe me
quite a bit of money, too.
[grimaces]
Seriously,
Master Naofumi?
I know, Atla.
Want to try it on?
Huh? Raphtalia, do you
think it'll make
me as attractive as you were
when you wore your miko outfit?
Hmm. Is that really the only
time I've been attractive?
Who cares.
I'm going to check
out the kitchen.
If we're staying here
Come on. I'm
going to change.
So you need to leave
the room, Brother.
But Atla!
[NAOFUMI] Raphtalia, you stay
and help her change.
- Atla!
[RAPHTALIA] All right.
I'll come by so I can show
off my fancy outfit later.
Bye!
See you soon.
Whee!
[NAOFUMI]
Everything in the kitchen
has been well
maintained.
We can work with this.
Now we just
need ingredients.
[NAOFUMI]
Shield Hero.
Hmm?
If you'd allow me, I'd like
to make tonight's dinner.
Wha...
[FOHL] Unfortunately
remember much about her
life here or anything
about our mom and dad.
So if possible
I want to at least let
her try some of the meals
that Mom used to make.
[NAOFUMI]
Mom's home cooking, huh?
[gentle music]
♪♪
[sighs]
Oh, wow.
I've never tasted
anything like this before.
But it's good.
I see.
Are you going
to keep that on, Atla?
Do you like it
There were some
for Brother, too
that I can get
ready for him.
Hey, Fohl.
Mind if I try something?
Hmm?
[sizzling]
[NAOFUMI]
What do you think?
Hmm.
[NAOFUMI]
What's missing?
Not enough sweetness
or tang, I think.
The flavoring is off
It was more of a gentle scent
that you could feel right
in the back
of your nose.
Well, if we're going
to replicate flavors like that
with these
seasonings, then...
[sizzling]
[chomping]
[gasps]
It's amazing.
[satisfied sigh]
[FILO] Wow!
It looks delicious!
[squealing]
It's a little unusual
This is really
Siltvelt home cooking.
All we need
is local booze.
That's all you
think about, isn't it?
Atla, Fohl worked
real hard to make
this meal just
right for you.
Better eat it all up.
Whoa, hey.
I can't take
all the credit.
You helped a lot, too.
That's not
important now.
I'm really grateful
for everything
you've done, Brother.
But let's just eat, OK?
It's time to eat!
[murmurs excitedly]
[RAPHTALIA] It has
an interesting flavor profile.
[FILO] It's better than
the food at the castle!
Atla, will you try
the potatoes
just one more
time, please?
OK.
[FOHL]
So, what do you think?
It's good.
This flavor.
I like the
way it tastes.
[sighs]
Makes me happy.
Mom used to make
it all the time.
It smells a
little different.
Did you change it from
the first time I tasted it?
[NAOFUMI]
Not too much.
I just used a few
Melromarc spices.
That's all it takes
to change the flavor this much?
I just figured that if
your mother was a human
then these are some of the
spices that she would've used.
It's still hard
for me to believe
that she was able to figure
it out so quickly.
It's a combination.
It's a dish that blends
parts of both Demi-human
and human cultures
I see.
This just makes me
miss them even more.
Master Naofumi
and Brother
would the two of you
please teach me how
to cook food
like this too?
Huh?
I want to learn so I
can be as good as you.
[laughs]
Yeah!
Of course we can.
Mom would
have loved that.
[NAOFUMI] And so we
spent some time at Fohl
and Atla's family home.
[gentle music]
♪♪
Come on, Brother!
[NAOFUMI]
Eventually, we set out
because preparations with
the ship were almost complete.
Make sure that's
taken care of, too!
Huh?
Master Naofumi?
Yeah, we need to head
back to the village.
There, we'll decide
who's going to Q'ten Lo.
[non-English singing]
♪♪
EPISODE 6: LEAVING PORT