♪ opening song ♪
Attention all residents.
Every one of the facilities on
this island is currently
under our strict control.
Our purpose here is
to inspect and take over
the military forces
on the island.
We promise we will
not harm anyone
who complies with our demands.
However, that will not
necessarily be the case for
those who stand in
the way of our operations.
What should I do?
The island is
being occupied now.
I wonder if my Mom
and Dad are doing okay.
Oh, mother...
Grandma what's going
to happen to all of us?
There's nothing
for you to worry about.
Just be patient my dear.
Huh?
Listen up.
Until we've
completed our search.
Nobody leaves.
Everyone, sit tight.
Your meals will be ready soon.
I want you to keep a close
watch on the island residents.
Yes, sir.
Also...
...tell Kariya she needs to
hurry up and find the core.
I could get used
to sitting right here.
Where on earth did the core go?
Hmm...
Just how many times have
we played Old Maid now?
I don't remember.
I wasn't keeping track.
Hey! How much longer
before we get to eat?
Why wouldn't you let me
go out there and fight?
How could you just hand
over control of the island?
What about when
Mr. Mizoguchi comes back?
What? Do you not
wish to face Kazuki?
Is that it?
No, it's not like that...
You are not to
fight against humans.
Understand?
No matter what
ends up happeneing.
For as long as
blood has been shed,
you will be the one who
suffers when Kazuki comes back.
And what about you?
Tell me something, how much
blood have you shed?
I've shed far too much.
Listen Soshi, if you come
to learn that Kazuki has
shed another person's blood,
then do me a favor.
help him in any way you can.
I will.
I'm going to help him.
Thank you.
After all that he's done.
Do you still believe in him?
Yes.
However, he did leave
without talking to me first.
So I'm not sure whether
or not he believes in me.
Unfortunately that's the truth.
I understand.
Because I feel
exactly the same way.
We're taking off now.
We're going to be
tracking down that machine.
Got it.
Well once again...
I wasn't able to do anything.
That's not true.
You were able to do something.
The very fact that you
were there during the
last moment was a
salvation to Yoji, Maya.
You mean that I
helped by just being there?
That's right.
Now, let's go see Kazuki.
Mother, is that you?
It is yours now.
I'm handing over this Mark Sein
to you on behalf of Yoji Hino.
Mark Sein?
Mr. Hino?
Yoji Hino no longer exists...
Huh?
We have come to
the decision that
I shall no longer be
a separate entity.
Wait. Mom!
You're my Mom, aren't you?
Akane Makabe no longer exists.
I am the one your people have
been referring to as Festum.
Child of Alvis, I hereby leave
the MIR vessel in your hands.
Get on.
I must leave you now.
I don't understand.
How could she?
I have one final observation to
report to our collective mind.
It is over. We have
limited your existence.
We are beginning to understand
the concept of
human individuality.
What do you speak of?
We do not understand.
It is your own rejection
that is the cause of that.
How can it be?
I am us.
Then why are you using words?
I have stopped
the divergence already.
If you and I are
supposed to be one,
why are we having
a conversation?
How strange...
...when I'm inside of this thing
It feels totally different.
Mom?
As a direct result of the
existence of another MIR that
was supposed to
become one with us,
I have become a unique entity.
And that is identical to the
process of you becoming you.
I felt it was
important for us to
understand that
final observation.
Your existence
has been eradicated.
No! Wait. Don't!
It ate her...
It just ate my mother!
Kazuki...
where are you?
Hey.
Take a look at that!
That's the machine we're after.
It's Kazuki!
What on earth is
going on down there?
Kazuki.
It's been born.
Huh?
What do you mean?
It has only just appeared.
Although, you are
on the verge of causing
the core to be reborn...
Kazuki.
Why did she die?
Answer me.
Was she sick or something?
It was all my fault.
Dad.
She was right here.
Where am I?
What happened to Soshi's eye?
I heard he was playing by
himself and just fell down.
Oh the poor thing.
It was all my fault.
Ouch!
I did it to him.
I heard it will be difficult for
Soshi's left eye to heal.
It's a nasty infection...
Did he really get
it just from falling?
Why? You think
it wasn't an accident?
Why...
...why didn't you just
tell them I did it?
Soshi...
Because of that,
I haven't been able to
bring myself to
apologize to you...
It's been so long.
If I could...
I'd do it myself.
It's because of
your eye, isn't it?
That's why you can't
pilot Fafner, am I right?
It's my fault.
So why don't you blame me?
Why didn't you just admit I was
the one who did that to you?!
Is it because I ran away?
Is that why you stayed
silent all this time?
I was so scared.
And I was also scared of
myself for having hurt you.
That's why I ran away.
But you're still angry
with me, aren't you!
You hate me for it, don't you!
And that's why you're telling
me to fight and risk my life!
Soshi!
For a long time...
I wanted to disappear.
It would be better...
if I could just disappear...
But still at least I wanted
to apologize to you...
The first feeling of pain.
Who are you?
Just like the manner in which
the core woke me up to who I am,
you made Soshi the
person who he is.
His wound is important.
It is proof of who he is.
Believe it or not, Soshi is
actually grateful to you.
Grateful?
Kazuki...
Why did you hurt Soshi?
It's cuz...
I will help you remember
what happened.
The truth.
Are you there?
Soshi...
What was it you
were trying to do?
It' s called assimilation.
I heard we can become one.
Soshi...
Let's become one...
Kazuki.
It's swallowing up
everything that it touches.
Yoji.
Just what kind of
monster did you create?
Is Kazuki down
there with that thing?
I don't know.
Damnit!
What's it doing?
Trying to swallow us?
In the beginning,
We were one entity.
And we were in
a large deep place.
Every one of us
came out of there.
That's when we
all became separate.
I became who I am.
You became who you are.
And the words were born.
Everything is one.
There are no
strangers in this world.
And the desire to return to that
place is merely a new discovery.
Because you cannot have a desire
to go back there if you
don't exist anywhere.
That is how many of the
contacts came into being.
We even view hurting
each other the way we
are doing right now,
as filled with possibilities.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
Are you telling a fairytale?
Yeah...
It's a fairy tale about this
universe and the rest of us.
It is the one and only story
passed down to us from god.
A story that is
both happy and sad.
It's a phenomenon
called assimilation.
I heard it's a way to go
back to a far away place
that is marked in our body.
A way back?
The genetic code
is implanted within us.
It's in our genes.
Dad said so.
And he also told me
that I was born for the
purpose of protecting
the core of this island.
It means my life's not my own.
I can't live for
myself or anyone else.
But Soshi?
Right from the beginning
I never existed anywhere.
So I want to go back to that far
away place with you, Kazuki...
...and become one.
Soshi...
Is that why?
The assimilation phenomenon
is but one choice.
There's also another option.
You see, our bodies are
imprinted with a way for
us to go forward as well
as backward, Kazuki.
Have you come
to a decision then?
What's your choice?
I don't know.
What will you do?
Are you going to stay?
I...
Or perhaps...
you want to disappear?
All that I want...
...is just to...
...to be able to
talk to Soshi again.
Soshi?
It seems that you
have chosen to be here.
But why?
Why did I?
This conversation...
...is a proof of who I am,
and also proof of who you are.
Kazuki.
This conversation...
You have shown the
core which direction to go.
I thank you.
That's it!
We're getting outta here!
We can't!
What if Kazuki's down
there and needs our help?
Oh no!
Did you see that?
Was it Kazuki?
I don't believe it!
That thing is eating itself.
Isn't that?
It's Kazuki!
Wait a minute.
Isn't that Maya?
What is she doing here?
During the day,
you can find yellow jackets
or scarab beetles.
And if I want to
catch a stag beetle,
I usually set up a trap
in the early evening.
Then what do you do?
I actually hate using traps
because I think they're cruel.
I look for a tree that
has sap during the day,
and make a map so
that I can find it at night.
The guys in the biology club
always set up traps blindly.
But I bury all of theirs
whenever I run across them.
But they get upset
when they find out.
That's good of you.
I make sure to return the insect
after I finish my research too.
I see.
Oh, come to think of it...
I don't even know your name.
My name is...
Wh-What?
What's the matter?
They're coming.
If I don't do this now,
I'm afraid I won't
get another chance.
What should I do?
Michio!
What are you doing over there?
Shh!
You idiot!
Don't be shouting my
name in a place like this!
But you told me to
call you by your name.
Fine. Alright.
Why don't we just go now?
Looks like you've been
hiding all the good stuff.
You sure there
isn't anything else?
I don't know.
And if you don't believe me,
search for yourself.
What!
Will you let me go home now?
I have an important
deadline to meet.
The island's defense
system is still active.
That means the core is
still on the island, right?
Yes.
I'm positive of that.
But I need extra manpower.
We are about to intercept
the enemy right now.
Do you think I'm in a
position to spare any staff?
Why don't you just hurry
it up and get on with
your search so that you
don't hold us back.
And remember I'm
reporting the details
of your progress
to headquarters.
So you can be sure
that a certain man
you trust will be
seeing all of it.
He means Mitsuhiro...
Festum detected.
It's 120 meters away.
More Festums approaching
from the southwest.
This will be a good opportunity
to try out the Nothung Models.
You're actually going to let
these people get
into the Fafners?
But they haven't gone through
the mind alteration test...
It'll be too dangerous!
Don't you worry about a thing.
We've done extensive research
on the Nothung Model data.
And these girls have
been hand-picked.
Now hurry up and deploy them.
No.
You can't...
Come on. Let me in.
I'm afraid not...
This place is off limits to
everyone including you.
Do you really believe
that you'll be
able to handle that CDC?
It's okay.
You can go on and let her in.
I'll take full
responsibility for her.
Yes, sir.
It can't be...
Yumiko.
Have you been well?
It's been awhile.
Hey where do you
think you're going?
Who are you?
Do I know you?
Hey Triple six.
Time to take off!
I-I'll be there right away.
Hey, wait a minute.
Yumiko!
I don't know you.
So don't follow me.
What was that about?
Who was that woman?
Kazuki.
Thank goodness.
That you're safe.
Are you really here?
Maya...
...is it you?
Yes, that's right.
It's me.
I'm right here.
Thank you, Maya.
What about Soshi?
He's back on the island.
So don't worry.
And he's waiting for you.
I just know that he is.
This entire time.
He knew what was
beyond the island.
I wanted to see that too.
I had thought that...
...If I saw it I would
understand him better.
Of course.
But I didn't leave because
I was afraid of fighting.
I know.
It's just...
I was really afraid that I
wouldn't exist anywhere else.
That's how I felt.
It's okay Kazuki.
I understand.
I thought things would be better
if I just disappeared for
awhile, but I don't know.
Let's go home.
When we're there,
we can talk about it again.
Because if we don't,
I feel like it's not just you,
but I might disappear too.
So that's why...
we should talk things through.
♪ closing song ♪
I'm getting way
too old for this kind of stuff.
I'm surprised that
you didn't get hurt.
Mr. Mizoguchi,
did you already know?]
Huh?
About what?
What happened to my mother.
And why it is she disappeared.
Akane was trying to protect
Fumihiko and that's why...
...the Festum absorbed her...
I saw it all.
I was right there
when it happened.
I see...
So that's why Dad
said it was all his fault.
Kazuki.
Thank you for sharing that
with me, Mr. Mizoguchi.
Things are making much more
sense now thanks to you.
Now that that's all settled,
it's time for us
to go back home.
It's not exactly going back.
It's different now.
I just can't think of the island
in the same way as I did before,
when I didn't know
everything that I know now.
So perhaps...
rather than going back to it...
Tatsumiya Island is the place
where I'm going forward to.
The place that I'm headed.
Someone else once told
me something very similar.
He said that he couldn't think
in the same way he had before.
And that he had to do everything
in his power to
protect the island.
Who said that?
Could it be...?
Soshi.
The changing island.
Friends who
continue to get hurt.
And then there are her words...
which come from the skies.
Next on Fafner:
episode number sixteen.
"Welcome Home."
Are you there?