♪ opening song ♪
Come to think of it,
you used to wet your bed
when you were little,
didn't you Michio?
Shut up!
What are you talking about?
I never did anything like that!
Sakura!
Prepare for a brain scan
and radiation treatment.
Hurry!
Solomon has responded.
Three new enemies have
appeared eighty kilometers
off the southeast bank.
Deploying the number one and
number two Welle Shields.
They haven't
changed their patterns,
but they're attacking
more frequently.
Commander Makabe, I have news.
Attention all Fafner pilots.
We are changing part
of the formation.
So be sure to remember
your recent training.
Changing?
What does he mean?
What part?
Canon is taking
Sakura's position?
But why?
Where's Sakura?
Did something happen to her?
Sakura is...
She's fighting at
a different location.
Tsubaki!
It's too dangerous
for you out here.
What...?
All of these things are dead.
How come?
There are no more Festum left.
All the pilots are
in good condition.
The Fafners are
on their way back.
Commander Makabe.
Yes, what is it?
The pilots have all
been instructed to
head to the medical room.
I understand.
I'll leave you to
take care of them.
Where is Tsubaki
Minashiro right now?
It's strange.
I wonder why they want us all
to meet in the medical room.
Kazuki, do you have any
idea what's going on?
No.
Not a clue.
Soshi...
What happened, Soshi?
Do you know?
Please listen.
Try not to get too upset
when you go inside, Kenji.
Kenji, wait!
No. What happened...
to her?
Why the hell did this happen?
Even the tree is almost dead.
Why's that?
I would like to
know that myself.
Commander Makabe?
Commander Makabe.
This is the first time
that you've come see me.
Tell me something...
Mark Sein's existence,
the abnormalities we're
witnessing in nature, the
enemy's attack patterns...
...and the recent assimilation
of one of our pilots...
All of these things
are related, aren't they?
As well as...
the fact that I awakened.
And let's not forget how
you let Koyo Kasugai out.
That's right.
I did it so that the North
Pole MIR and our MIR
could understand life better...
Life?
In Japan...
a long time ago...
The MIR took the "power" of
becoming parents
away from you,
because it couldn't understand
what it's like to be born.
And so it tried
to protect humans
from death by taking life.
However now... The
MIR is relearning about life.
You mean it's learning about the
concept of life and death?
Is that why it made
all these flowers
on the island blossom suddenly?
Yes.
But there's still
a whole lot more
that it would like
to learn about.
Is that why you've
been coming out here?
So that you can teach
them that during battles?
Have you been
leaking information
about us to the enemy?
When you do that
the island is at risk.
After everything
we've sacrificed...
You're heartless.
Don't you feel
any sorrow at all?
How can you even say that?
Of course she feels sorrow!
Tsubaki wished that she
could've known her father
and mother like a normal child.
So why wouldn't she feel
sad about people dying?
How could you even
say such a thing to her?
A lot of insects died today.
And a lot flowers died too.
Commander are
you sad about that?
What is it that you're implying?
That we're like insects
and flowers to you?
Not at all.
You see insects and flowers
don't feel sad about themselves.
Animals don't really
know what sorrow is,
so then how can they feel sad?
How come... humans are the
only ones to feel sadness?
Yet they alone have the
potential to truly answer that.
The answer to that.
What is it?
So then the more
we pilot Fafner,
the closer we come to dying?
It's not death.
Your body crystallizes
due to the
chromosomal changes
it goes through.
And how can you
call that being alive?
You know what?
Maya's father was right!
We're nothing but batteries
to mobilize the Fafners.
And Sakura...
finally ran out of power...
If Dr. Tohmi research
succeeds, we can prevent
the assimilation from occurring.
Too late...
Sakura's already...
What are you doing?!
I'm taking her home with me...
Come on.
Mother's going to take
you home now, Sakura.
You can't!
She's not stable. If you--
Don't you think Sakura's
fought enough already!
Let her rest in peace.
You're not helping her.
Kiyomi!
Kiyomi! Please!
Listen to me!
Let go!
Kiyomi.
Kiyomi!
Sakura...
Kenji.
Kenji...
You and I still have
a fight to settle, right?
If a world where
there's constant
fighting fills you
with sorrow then...
What do you think
is the best way
for you to erase this sorrow?
To teach them.
So that the Festum can
better understand our sorrow.
Yes.
Akane Makabe was the first
to come up with the idea.
It's so simple a solution yet
very difficult at the same time.
I don't believe it!
Are you telling me that
that's what you've been
trying to accomplish
during the battles?
I'm afraid that,
if I don't do this they'll end
up choosing the wrong feeling.
A destructive emotion
that you can only
feel if you are alive...
That's hatred...
If that's true,
the enemy already
understands us fairly well?
How am I supposed
to believe that?
Because...
...I am the proof.
Akane Makabe
showed the enemy life
by treating them
like living things...
It was the same thing with me.
And that's how my mother
gave this island's MIR a life.
I know you have your doubts.
But it's true.
Because if this island's MIR
wasn't able to
understand life...
...there would've been no way
for me to have been born.
Makes me wonder...
Are we advancing
in the right direction.
We made the island
for our posterity.
And we used the enemy's power,
and to ensure our
survival, we've been
sacrificing our own children.
We should be ashamed.
The right power and path.
You shall find it if
you search for it.
And you're the kind of
person who can do that.
The fact that you came here
to see me is proof of this.
The path you
seek lies within you.
Now you must find it.
I see...
Poor Sakura...
Um...
May I ask you something?
Sure.
What is it?
About Shoko...
She wasn't your biological
daughter, am I right?
No.
They thought I had the
characteristics of someone
who'd be good at
raising children.
So the Albericht
Organization gave Shoko
to me to raise as my own.
And what about Kazuki and Maya?
They're different.
Shoko and Koyo
were the exceptions.
They were the only
children who weren't actually
genetically related
to their parents.
But they all have a
genetic component of the
Festum in them, don't they?
It was originally intended
to protect the genes
from being polluted by MIR.
If you don't
pilot a Fafner,
then the MIR
factor isn't dangerous.
I don't have it.
I'm missing the factor.
That's why my integration
with the Siegfried System
hasn't been completed yet...
And why I still can't
pilot the Nothung Model.
Canon.
I just want to...
be like everyone else...
There...
That's all of it.
I wonder what happens
at the end of this story.
You know what?
I'm positive it'll
have a happy ending.
After all, that's
what I'm fighting for.
The Mark Sein is able to
connect the best with the core.
But it's not because
it's more like the
Festums than other Fafners.
Then is it possible to
apply the power-gain
release
to other machines?
No.
In the simulation, the
pilot's senses overloaded
and weren't able
to keep up with it.
The sensory elements which
are buried like filament in the
Silicon Nanofilms body
become extremely unstable.
During assimilation
their numbers...
...shape and locale change.
So you see...
That's the reason why the whole
body feels like melted rubber.
Why didn't it happen to Kazuki?
Why's he all right?
I can only speculate that
his mind adapted itself...
There's clearly a higher sense
of self-consciousness from the
bond between Kazuki and Soshi.
Each one wishes
to better themselves
for the sake of the other.
And so perhaps, that is the
biggest factor influencing it.
It's impressive,
but Kazuki couldn't have
progressed to that
level on his own...
Right?
Which means we have no idea how
well the Mark Sein will do in
remote operations when
it no longer has direct
communication with the
Siegfried System.
Commander!
Does that mean we're
actually going to join
forces with the Neo U.N.?
At this rate, if the enemy
continues it's all out war of
attrition this may be a possible
solution we want to consider.
If we were to join them, it
would cause too many problems
such as the island's
defense during battle or
the chain of command between us.
Soshi Minashiro is
planning to do just that.
Huh?
In the event we were
to join the general attack
on the North Pole MIR...
...he asked whether
or not it'd be possible
to build the Siegfried
System inside a Fafner.
Build a Siegfried System
inside a Fafner?
That's absurd!
Why does he think we made the
two separate in the first place!
If he pilots a Fafner like that
he'll definitely wind
up assimilated!
That's pretty much
what I told him too.
So he asked for your
advice as well Dr. Tohmi?
Yes.
He wanted to know
approximately how much time
he would have before he would
completely lose consciousness.
It seems...
...that I don't have
much time left.
What are you
going to do, Soshi?
I have prepared myself for
the worst possible outcome.
I see...
We weren't able to
become actual
brother and sister
until the end, huh?
I saw you for the
first time ten years ago.
My father took me to see you.
I remember.
Ever since then, I have
visited you many times.
I know.
I lived to protect
you and the island.
At least...
...that's what I thought.
You thought that until you
were hurt by Kazuki, right?
Tell me what you
want to do Soshi.
If in the end, we join the
Neo U.N.'s
final battle operations...
...I want to fight
alongside all of my friends.
Therefore I'd like
to leave this island.
And so I need the
core's permission.
Don't you realize that you
already left me long time ago.
However...
...you won't be able to be with
them for a long period of time.
Even with the extra stress of
the Siegfried System
and Fafner placed on me,
I can still operate
for about eighteen hours.
And in that time, if you
are with the most important
people to you, you are
the happiest, correct?
That's right.
In that case,
don't worry about me.
Go right ahead.
I hope I'll still be able
come outside and watch,
so I can see you off.
I'm so sorry...
I appreciate this.
Thank you.
Now you have
no choice but to fight.
I hope someday you'll remember
that there's also
a different way.
I will.
Oh! And another thing,
don't forget me okay?
I won't.
I promise.
Canon Memphis?
Yes.
She demands to be injected
with alien biomaterial.
She's locked herself
in the medical room.
And she refuses to battle
if her demands are met.
She probably thought someone
was giving an order
when they weren't...
Then again...
Without knowing
your reasons for it...
...I cannot give
you this injection!
Please. Canon.
Just tell us who
told you to do this?
Uh...
Look.
Once you tell us the truth,
We'll inject this in you.
So just tell us.
No, stop it!
You can't!
Kazuki was the one.
What?
He did?
When was this?
It was back when I tried to
disappear along with the island.
Kazuki told me I had
to make my own choice.
But this is?
Not just him...
Mrs. Hazama said it too...
She said that I
had to live without orders.
Wait just a minute.
That isn't what
I was getting at, at all!
I've had hard times.
And I've thought...
quite a lot.
In the end...
there's only one solution.
I'm making a
choice once and for all.
And this here is my choice.
To be on this island.
I'm going now.
I'm going too...
...Sakura.
Enemy sighted
120 kilometers away.
It's on approach.
There appears to only be one.
We've identified it
as a Scarabee-type.
However it could be
a new mutation.
There's only one of them?
I guess as soon
as Sakura collapsed,
they changed their patterns.
I have no doubt that the
previous two hundred enemies
deployed were sacrificed in
order to exhaust our pilots and
increase their
odds of assimilation.
Attack the enemy
with full force!
Let's show them
just how ineffective
their war of attrition is.
Sorry I'm late.
You okay?
I'm all right now.
Ok, number one
and two Welle Shields
are ready to be deployed.
I've never fought
in a Fafner for real.
I've only done
it in the simulators.
Yeah. I've
never done it either.
There's no need to worry.
What are you doing here?
I'm gonna defeat
all the enemies.
That's right.
Here.
It's for you.
It's for luck.
Wear it and it
will keep you safe.
Mark Sieben, check out the
enemy's defensive capabilities
and determine if
this is a new type.
Mark Acht, Funf, and Babalon,
you three will come in direct
contact with the enemy.
Megaselion and Mark Sein
will analyze the enemy's
method of attack and try to
capture it from behind.
Whatever happens,
don't break this formation.
The Denial Defense Line
is about to be crossed.
All right Mark Sieben,
begin your attack!
Roger.
Huh?
Eject the cockpit bloc!
Did you see that?
What the hell happened?
Mark Funf, retreat.
Babalon and Mark Acht,
keep your distance
and intercept it
from both sides!
How did it...?
Why isn't the pain
inhibitor working?
This makes no
sense the data isn't
showing any damage anywhere...
Canon!
Got it!
There.
We're back online.
Why...?
...why isn't it attacking us?
The enemy is merely sending all
of our attacks back towards us.
It isn't attacking
or assimilating us?
That means...!
Yes.
That's right.
It has understood your pain.
Mark Funf, launch
the Aegis equipment
and try to hold off the enemy.
Roger!
Here I go!
Mark Sein, approach
the enemy from behind
and try to immobilize it.
Understood.
Good.
Now keep on crushing it.
Kazuki!
Assimilation...
Oh no.
The enemy is beginning
to spread its roots.
Soshi...
The enemy has now
reached the Keel Block!
What?!
Was it trying to take over
the system from the start?
Assimilation with the
Siegfried System has started.
Separate the enemy's
main body from its roots!
You bastard!
Soshi...
Ask Kazuki...
if he can lend me a hand...
Kazuki!
I need you to try
and move your hand?
Good enough!
I won't let them feel
sad any longer...
I'll protect you!
Eject now!
♪ closing song ♪
Power that's been taken.
Hope that's been taken.
Yumi... ko...
Next on Fafner episode
number twenty-three.
"Decoy."
Are you there?