♪ opening song ♪
I just need to hear
the answer for myself.
Between Fafner
or the rest of us,
when it comes down to it,
which one's more important?
It would be Fafner.
You sure have changed.
You know that?
The one who's not
willing to change...
...is you, Kazuki.
Are you there?
Have one shred of
doubt about the battle
and you will for sure
be its next victim.
You should try and forget
about Shoko and Koyo.
You're not...
You're not being
serious, are you?
I'll tell you what I
need from you right now.
What I need is someone who can
act as if they were my left eye.
So, how did you like my work?
I did all right today
didn't I, Maya?
Well I thought you did a
pretty good job today.
I'm so glad.
I'll be sure to keep on
working harder from now on.
Good for you, Rina.
Because I'm determined
to be a good pilot.
I'm not selfish like Shoko.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Huh?
Well I had heard that Shoko
ignored direct orders and as
a result of that the Mark Zex
ended up getting destroyed.
Who would say such a thing?
Where did you hear that?
Well...
they all say it.
You have no idea about anything!
Wait, Maya.
What's the matter?
Please wait a minute.
Please don't go yet.
Are you there?
I wish I knew.
The truth is, you are
not here, Kazuki.
No because you are nothing
like the rest of them here.
I overheard your
conversation with Soshi...
...about his left eye...
It was me.
I was the one who did it.
When I was little.
Right here.
This is where
he lost his left eye.
And it was cuz of me.
I wonder, why did
I do such a thing?
I guess, I just wanted to try to
be his eye so badly that...
...but. I...
Perhaps you aren't able
to keep up with him...
It makes me wonder.
It's only natural...
after all...
...he knows what it's
like in the outside world.
The world beyond this island?
Dad?
Are you here?
Do you know where
Commander Makabe is?
The Commander?
Oh.
Your father is in a meeting
with Soshi right now.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Do you want me
to page him for you?
No.
It's all right.
It was you.
You called me here
that time, didn't you?
I thought you wanted me
to fight alongside Soshi.
But is that what you
really want me to do?
What did he see?
In the outside world?
What could have made him change?
Sis!
The rumors about
Shoko are just awful!
I know and I'm sorry.
But there's nothing we can do.
We can't control
what people think.
But Shoko did everything
to protect the island.
Rumors are like that.
It's best to just ignore them.
Excuse me, Miss Yumiko.
can you come here?
Huh?
What's going on?
What on earth happened?
One of the students has decided
to lock himself
inside of the studio.
Huh?
What student was it?
An eighth grader
named Hiroto Douma.
I think he's in
Miss Kaname's class.
Uh...
'Scuse me.
Hi, I'm Hiroto's father.
I didn't expect things
to turn out like this...
What do you mean?
Do you know
what made him do this?
Well you see... we
were discussing what
he would be
doing after graduation.
Why Miss Kaname,
he's going to be taking over
my restaurant of course!
Mr. Douma, that is
only secondary
to his real obligations.
This survey we're
conducting is to find out what
he wishes to do
as his primary duties.
It doesn't matter as
long as he's not a pilot.
Miss Kaname, Do you think
it would be difficult for him
to join the maintenance
crew on Takeru Island?
We will need to verify whether
he's suitable for that position.
I'm currently
assigned to the hanger.
I would sure prefer it
if he were able to work
in a safe environment
like me, you know?
Yes...
Hiroto, Is there somewhere
specific you'd like to work?
Listen, Can I be
honest with you here?
Of course.
In Tokyo!
That's where I
really want to work!
I want to go to Tokyo
and be a superstar!
Yeah!
I'll perform in concerts
or even appear on a...
Fine I guess I'll
have to decide for you.
And I know just the place...
...on the thirteenth
floor below Alvis.
The thirteenth floor?
What's there to do there?
You can wash uniforms!
How does that sound?
No!
And this is a result of that?
Despite his looks,
Hiroto can be pretty sensitive.
Yes, I see.
You could have
shown a bit more
consideration
wouldn't you agree?
Of course, you're right.
And you would
understand since you went
through a similar situation.
Didn't you, Miss Yumiko?
As I recall, some girl
wanted to become an idol.
And so she climbed to
the top of the lighthouse,
isn't that right?
I will go to Tokyo
and become an idol!
I will!
Hey Sis, did you
actually do all that?
Stop talking about it!
Hiroto, hurry up and
come out of there!
Let's discuss this properly
with the teachers.
I don't have
anything to discuss.
Everyone!
Listen up!
Ask yourselves this...
why should we have
to carry on with
the Arcadian Project?
I know that voice...
Is it Hiroto?
--Huh?
--Just now... what was that?
Hey come on you guys.
Try and stay focused here!
It's not...
It's not fair...
I want my innocence back!
Give it back to me!
Give my innocence back to me!
Wait a second.
Are you done already?
Do you know what?
It looks to me
like it's my turn.
What the heck are you saying?
Come on, Sis I thought you knew
my position on this already.
Huh?
Hey!
Mamoru, you better stay
right where you are
and finish your homework,
you got that?!
Kenji!
There's no running
in the hall way!
Hey wait for me!
I wanna go with you guys too!
What should we do?
Excuse me, teachers!
Oh! Kenji.
If you would please, just
leave everything to me.
After all I am the president
of the student council.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Isn't Soshi the president
of the student council?
You're wrong!
I am.
Mom!
That's weird.
I was under the impression
that it was Soshi as well.
Uh...
Come to think of it,
Soshi's really the class rep,
and Kenji's the student
council president.
Really?
I always thought Soshi
was president too.
I can't believe you guys!
Well, I guess you can
do what you want then.
Not that I would have
faith in whatever it is.
Hey...
Hiroto Douma.
This is Kenji Kondo,
the president of the
student council.
What do you want,
idiot son of Mrs. Kondo?
Idiot?
I'm not the one who locked
myself in a classroom!
As your senior in life,
there's something important
I want to say to you.
In order to live on this island,
each one of us must...
Hey, Kenji.
Seri told me
something interesting.
Know what she said?
She told me you tell girls you
killed Festum with Fafner.
And that's how you try
to pick up girls, right?
Is that really true?
Uh-huh.
He's the worst.
But you know what?
You've never fought
in Fafner, have you?
That's the truth, isn't it?
I'm afraid that's not
very manly of you, Kenji.
But I have fought in a Fafner!
So what if it was
just a simulation?
Good grief.
Whose bright idea was it
to make him the president?
Unfortunately, he was the only
one who ran for the presidency.
Oh, that's right.
I remember now.
He's such an idiot!
Listen, Hiroto!
Think about it!
Do you really believe
you have what it
actually takes to
become a superstar?
How am I supposed
to know if I don't ever
get the chance to get
off of this island!
The teachers, my Dad,
and the rest of the
adults here are all liars!
How can I believe
anything liars say!
I know I'll probably
never become a star.
But still...
I just...
I hate the fact that
we're not allowed
to ever set foot
off this island.
Because...
for some reason...
I feel like I'm
trapped in a cage.
And just once...
I would like to
see the outside world.
Because I...
I...
I have something that I want to
do that's always been
important to me...
After all, there's a sign that's
hanging in our classroom...
it has "Hope" written on it.
We apologize for keeping
so many secrets from you!
But there was a reason.
It was because we wanted to make
sure that you understood
the importance of peace!
Before living on this island,
all any of us knew was
the tragedy from wars.
And we're so glad...
...that you have
something more you
want to do with your
life or become.
Because none of
us adults could afford
to have those kinds
of hopes and dreams.
But not now you need to focus on
surviving before
you can do that.
You children represent hope.
Do you understand
what I'm trying to tell you?
You are our hope and our future.
We want you to live
to inherit the island!
I'm really sorry...
for all the trouble.
Come on in everyone,
welcome, welcome.
I've got it all.
Mackerel, sardines, tuna...
Say, which one of
these fish tastes the best?
Everything is fresh because
it was caught in Barnzveck.
They all taste good.
So you can have your pick.
Well then I guess the question
would be, which one I can cook.
Well since you're gonna be
the one cooking Maya...
I guess they'd all be
a bit difficult to make.
Hey!
You ditched school
today, didn't you?
I had things to do...
...at Alvis.
I'm just on my way home
to make some dinner.
What are you up
to tonight?
I probably won't eat.
Huh?
I don't really
feel like cooking...
...not today.
Then I have an idea.
Why don't you come over?
Huh?
Here.
Have a taste.
This is no good at all.
Hey uh...
...is there anything
I can help out with?
No. No.
You're supposed to be a guest.
Okay.
Oh, sweet sis!
Will you help me out?
Please. Please.
Well I guess I
don't have a choice.
Aaah!
Don't put that in!
Um...
then what about this?
No. No.
Make soup stock first.
So...
you invited Kazuki...
What's with that?
Huh?
No reason.
It was nothing special.
Hmm?
It appears to me that
my little sister likes
Kazuki rather than
Soshi, am I right?
Hey now!
Cut it out!
Don't get any funny ideas!
Uh...
You sure I don't need to come
in and lend you guys a hand?
Ah! No. It's okay.
Never mind us.
Just wait there.
Okay.
I know what you're thinking and
it has nothing to do with it!
Mm-hmm...
Oh, hi.
Hello.
Good evening.
Welcome, Kazuki...
Were you ever able to meet
with your father earlier?
Yeah.
I see.
Okay guys, dig in!
--Bon apetit everyone!
Hey Kazuki,
aren't you going to eat?
Oh right.
Thank you.
So?
How's it taste?
Mm.
It's real good.
I'm so glad.
That means all my
hard work was worth it.
Why my goodness, Maya.
This fish cake soup
tastes just like my recipe.
Well that concludes today's
broadcast of
Tatsumiya Island news.
And coming up next,
we are departing from our
regular scheduled programming,
to present you a very
special concert.
Yeay!
Good evening everyone.
I'm Hiroto Douma.
What in the world?
Well don't look at me.
Yeah...!
Thank you for everything.
I appreciate it.
You're welcome.
It was nothing.
Hey Kazuki,
did you hear about it yet?
The rumor about Shoko?
No but...
I can pretty much guess it.
'Cause you know...
about both Shoko and Koyo...
They always fought so hard...
It doesn't matter
what other people say.
It doesn't matter at all.
We know the truth.
Because we'll always
remember how they really were.
I know.
You're right but...
Hey Maya, what about me?
Will you remember what I'm like?
Kazuki?
What are you talking about?
Are you saying that you think
you're going to
end up like Shoko?
No.
I'm pretty sure
I'll be all right.
But still...
Still what?
I'm just worried that over time
I might get too
used to fighting.
And it scares me.
'Cuz you see...
I feel like I'm
already gradually
changing into
something different.
I think that...
everyone's been feeling uneasy.
Ever since that day...
when Festum attacked us.
And we discovered that
the place we trusted in
was just a fake, I
guess we all felt betrayed.
And nothing's been
the same since.
I don't think any of us
will remain unchanged.
It's okay.
We all have to go on living
on this island don't we?
So you see, that's why...
Oh, Maya...
Don't worry...
it doesn't matter if
you change; Kazuki,
I will always remember you.
I promise I will.
Thank you, Maya.
What's the matter?
Don't worry--It's nothing.
Something must be wrong, Kazuki.
You look really pale.
Sorry, I'm fine now.
You should head back.
You sure?
Why don't you go let my
mom take a look at you?
No, it's okay.
I'm all right.
Are you positive?
Yeah.
Please, you should go back.
I want to be alone.
All right...
I'll see you later then.
Feel free to come
by for dinner again.
You'll always be welcome.
That's great.
Thank you.
I'll talk to you soon.
Kazuki...
I wonder where
are you right now?
Huh?
Was that Kazuki?
What is it?!
Looks like he's
taken the Mark Elf.
What?
Was this your doing?
Did you order him to take off?
Of course not.
Why would I give
him an order like that?
Then why?
Do you have any
idea where he's going?
I've absolutely
no interest in this.
Not in someone
who's leaving the island.
You're doing a very good
job, Kazuki Makabe.
So where are we
headed, Miss Kariya?
Tell me.
To somewhere nice.
A new paradise.
We were searching
for answers although
we couldn't even see
each other clearly.
How were we to
understand each other?
We couldn't understand.
But we didn't want to
make that our excuse.
So then...
we lost something...
...again.
♪ closing song ♪
A world that shows
off its old scars.
The shadow of a new battle.
And a trap called...
betrayal.
Next on Fafner episode
number eleven.
"The Neo UN Force."
Are you there?