These are the children with
high synergetic code
formation values.
Some of those children will have
to depart again, won't they?
By now, I'm sure you have
already heard about the neo U.N.
recon planes conducting frequent
searches over the island.
And...
I'm thinking of
moving the island,
temporarily to an
archipelago in the northwest.
Lindwurm?
According to him the
Mark Elf is more compatible
with Lindwurm than the Mark Zex.
Increase gravity pull to
120 at a heading of 9 o'clock.
Neo U.N. plane spotted at
6 o'clock, 60 kilometers away,
approaching the
island rapidly.
What exactly's going on?
We're in a battle.
♪ opening song ♪
A Neo U.N. search
plane is approaching.
It will pass over the island
in about 25 minutes.
That's right.
The Neo U.N. plane
is going to be our decoy.
Meanwhile, we'll start
moving the island.
All staff, report to stations.
LDA is unfolding.
Locking Gewitter
units one and two.
units three and four.
Releasing Fafner cage.
Transfer AVC Lindwurm
to the turntable.
Move the block.
Final safety check all green.
Secure Fafner
to the contact position.
Lock Contact Arm.
Fafner has made contact.
This is Lindwurm!
Take off!
Now let's go!
This is the location we
received from the contact.
The coordinates were
definitely for Tatsumiya Island.
Something moved just now.
What?
Isn't that an API 1?
It's Festom!
May day!
Do you read me?
Young Star 2 reporting!
Sphinx type found
at point N Zero Two.
The Sphinx Model
is following us!
The Neo U.N.
recon plane has come
into contact with the Sphinx.
The key is how far they'll
be able to get from it.
We'll see.
What's the sailing phase status?
Phases eighty-two
through ninety-six
of the alpha line have
been all cleared.
The beta line is
currently at phase 63.
It's not even half way yet.
I see.
Attention all island residents.
The relocation of Tatsumiya
Island has been re-scheduled
from 1000 hours tomorrow
to 1900 hours today.
Repeat.
The relocation of Tatsumiya
Island has been re-scheduled...
It looks like we'll
be leaving earlier.
They're just a bunch
of selfish old bastards.
They never even
think of other people.
You're absolutely right.
And so we have lots to prepare.
Load on as many
supplies as possible!
It's no use!
We can't get away from it!
Don't give up!
Listen Kazuki.
Just remember
to keep your nose out.
We're not going to be conducting
a rescue mission here.
Festom is approaching.
It's extending feeler-like
objects toward us.
What the hell?
Are you there?
The output is increasing.
Get away from it!
We can't!
We're screwed!
No!
Are you there?
Hey! That's...
Kazuki
Don't do it, Kazuki!
But... I...
I must save them.
We've no choice.
Kazuki.
There's no way
we can go back now.
You're going to need to
follow me from here on out.
Do you think
that we'll get away?
If we gain some
time we'll be okay.
Sphinx model appears to now
be targeting to Lindwurm.
I instructed them to avoid
contact with the Neo U.N. plane.
Saving them is
only going to bring
about a whole world
of trouble later.
Alpha line phases one
hundred thirty-eight through
one hundred seventy-seven
have all been cleared.
Beta line has also cleared.
All components of
the Brunhilde System
are greenlit and ready to go!
Good.
Release Dux Stopper.
Miss Kariya!
Please, you have to let
us all go in there too.
The reality is that none of
you would be of any help.
What's happening
to Kazuki and others?
I don't need to explain the
details of our tactics to you.
What's going on, Miss Kariya?
You usually answer
the questions we have!
This is different.
We're not at school!
All of them...
What do they think
that they're trying to do?
I can't believe
we're really at war.
Are you there?
Amazing!
Who does that plane belong to?
Could it have possibly
come from API1?
The relocation of Tatsumiya
Island is about to begin.
Those citizens who
live along the coast,
are advised to watch
out for high waves.
What?
Huh? Bastards!
Commence with the
final phase to set sail.
Attention. Notice to the
personnel of all departments.
Release the outer
rim attachments now.
Today's the last day that
Guren Island serves as
a resource center, right?
Elimination of Guren
Island complete!
Unfold Walle Shield, and begin
transmitting dummy Beacon.
Guren Island is going to serve
as a decoy for us from now on.
Connect propulsion power.
Confirm systems
to begin sailing.
Brunhilde System
operations report.
All normal.
Purge outer rim anchoring axle.
So, we are finally
leaving this place.
It has been a long time.
All of the pre-sailing
phases have been completed.
Start the engines now!
Preparing to start the engines!
Internal pressure
of engines increasing.
Engine numbers one through
six are showing no problems.
Move forward at slow-speeds!
Move forward!
Guren Island is separated.
No problems with
any connecting joints.
Maintaining speed at 5 knots.
Good!
Make sure the tide
control level is secured at 7.
Maintain control levels at 7.
Expand the warning area
to a circumference of 200.
We've got to try and take
a picture of this plane!
Why won't they leave!
Kazuki!
It's attempting
to assimilate again.
I didn't know we could do that?
It's no big deal.
Don't act so surprised.
All right.
It's time for us to leave.
Soshi look!
Did that plane just save us?
Lindwurm's field
of combat is in the
middle of Tatsumiya
Island's direct path.
At this rate, they will
be entering the number
two defense block
in about 5 minutes.
Just what do those two
think they're doing?!
Mrs. Kaname, why don't
we trying changing
the course
of the island?
Because that would
take us over half a day.
All of this is meaningless
unless we destroy the core.
If that's what needs to be
done, I'll go there and do it.
Release me into that thing!
There's been an impact
on the island's surface.
It's inevitable now.
We'll have to blow our cover
if we want to save the island.
Are you sure?:
Disable the
camouflage surface.
Set up Walle Shield.
Kazuki!
But, that's...
Uh... A song.
I can hear it.
What are we hearing?
Do you hear that? Who's singing?
You know what to do, right?
Sphinx type has vanished.
It seems that she
has completely awakened.
That island...
Was there an island here before?
I don't see anything on the map.
Recon plane
Young Star 2 reporting
to Headquarters from area 17.
We have located an API1.
Repeat, Young Star
2 has located an API1.
Do you think we'll
be able to land?
We landed.
Seems to me that we fell.
Why did you
ignore the order and
rescue the Neo U.N. recon plane?
I apologize.
It was all my fault.
Is it really such a bad thing to
rescue someone
when they're in need?
Well that all depends
on the situation.
So what do you think?
Was I too lenient with them?
Well, you are the commander.
Soshi!
Good work guys!
The two of you
were simply amazing!
You really did it.
You guys saved us.
Anyway, I'm glad
that the both of you
made it back here
safe and sound.
That's right.
I think it's great...
Don't mind me,
I'm just happy that's all.
All right then guys,
I better take off.
I still have my training to do.
I gotta learn how to become
as useful as you two.
Otherwise I might just
get kicked off the island.
He said we saved all of them.
But the truth is
we were rescued,
by those small flying machines.
Koyo!
And where have
you been all this time?
Mamoru.
Kazuki and Soshi
fought this battle.
You should've seen it.
It was awesome!
Is that so?
I expected that.
This awesome thing
came out at the end
and did this incredibly
awesome stuff.
The whole thing
was just so awesome!
You know what?
I'm sure that they have
some awesome footage of it.
You should go and ask
Miss Kariya to show it to you.
I think I'd better not.
I might get nervous and
lose confidence.
These are the coordinates that
were reported by Young Star 2.
So we finally found it.
The island of Giants.
When I started this
day I never expected
that it would end up like this.
It takes a mature sailor
to move an old ship,
not a young sailor.
But, the one to find a new
route is always a young sailor.
However, the sailing map we
found was a journey
filled with hardships...
...which fell from the sky.
♪ closing song ♪
Tatsumiya Island set sail.
We don't know where we're going.
We can't see what's ahead of us.
And yet we're forced
to take a new step.
And at that time,
two people exchange words.
Next on "Fafner"
episode number five...
Pledge.
Are you there?