Attention all Fafners.
Six Arfenotheles, and three
Sphinx types have been spotted.
We've determined
they are all B-types.
Prepare for their
incoming approach.
We are going into battle.
The plan is to intercept
them as they land!
Confirming there
are no enemies left.
None of the pilots were harmed.
It only took them
seventeen minutes
to completely destroy the enemy.
That's a new record.
This one is the sixth straight
successful
interception this month.
It's great.
Hard to believe we used to have
such trouble against
just one Sphinx type.
Yeah, but now we can
maneuver up to seven Fafners
simultaneously in addition
to the entire island system.
That's great!
Today's battle
brings the total number
we've defeated to
over two hundred.
This is almost
too good to be true.
What do you think the secret to
our victory has
been, Miss Yumiko?
It's communication and unity,
as well as trust among
those in the fighting force.
Where is Tsubaki Minashiro?
She's in the southwestern
region of the Island.
She appears to have
been watching
the entire battle from there.
I'm so comfortable I wouldn't be
able to fight if the
enemy showed up.
A nice long bath
after a hard battle.
Now this is the good life.
Goubain, taking off!
Oh please...
...will someone just
take his helmet off?
Huh?
Oh, I'm in the bath.
Where'd the enemy go...?
We already defeated
them a long time ago.
Well now that's interesting.
You really don't remember
anything that happens in battle?
Soshi!
What do you think?
If you decide to go into
battle with that mask on,
you're gonna be on your own.
What are you doing?
Hey! That thing
looks good on you!
Hey, does this mean
our commander's
got a new look going on?
That's mine.
You can't have it.
Good, cuz I don't want it.
I'm so comfortable
that I wouldn't be able
to fight if the enemy showed up.
Good work today, you guys!
Sis. You can't
be in here.
It's only for the pilots.
Relax will ya?
It's fine.
Besides, I am
your leader after all.
Is Canon here?
She's over there
in the corner, hiding.
Hm?
What's she doing way over there?
She says that she's not used to
being naked in front of people.
Hearing that just
makes me wanna drag her
out into the open even more.
So then why don't we?
Hm?
What are you guys doing?!
Don't fight it!
Oh, your boobs are pretty big.
I'd say they're about the same
as Sakura's, aren't they?
Yeah, you're right!
I wonder if they feel the same.
Hey!
Cut it out!
You feel Canon's
and I'll feel Sakura's.
Hey!
Why me?
I thought this was about her.
You guys are perverts!
What are those
girls doing, over there?
--Ohh! They're soft!
What is it?
I dunno.
What?
I gotta question for you.
When I'm out there fighting with
you guys, what am I like?
What do you mean?
Sometimes when I'm
sleeping I have dreams about it.
...but those dreams
I have make me scared.
During battles, you always
take the lead, and prevent the
enemy from advancing
by creating a diversion.
So it's thanks to you, that the
outcome ends up in our favor.
Really...
Essentially, it means
you're positioned
in the most dangerous location.
Being scared is only natural.
The way I see it,
you and Kazuki are what holds
our fighting force together.
Oh, I see.
Would you prefer us to
change the current formation?
How bout a two top formation?
Then you'd be leading the
offensive with Kazuki...
Nah that's okay.
Besides I like working
with Kenji and Sakura.
I see...
What are you staring at?!
Yeah, right.
I wasn't staring.
This weekend, we are
going to be conducting
a training camp
for all the pilots.
Make sure to bundle up
so you don't catch a cold.
All right?
--Alright.
I bet you tried to
sneak a peep at us
while we were
bathing, didn't you?
Yeah right.
Nobody even cares.
And I'm supposed
to believe that?
Are you okay?
What happened?
I'm just a little...
flushed I guess, that's all.
Hey, were you
trying to cop a feel?
No, I wouldn't do that.
You try anything
and I'll kick your butt.
Aw, come on, don't be like that.
Fieldtrips to the
beach, a festival,
and now a training camp...
Those are all
the things we tried
to do but couldn't, aren't they?
It's a difficult
time for everyone.
Besides they should have as
many good memories as possible.
You're probably right.
Um... by the way,
it's been awhile, and...
I think I'm late.
I don't quite follow you.
Late for what?
I thought it was rather odd,
because I'm usually
pretty regular...
But I should probably
wait a little longer
before talking
to mom about it.
Wait a minute,
are you telling me that yer...
If I am pregnant...
...do you think everyone
would be surprised?
Of course!
It would be the first natural
conception in thirty years.
Everyone would be thrilled.
If it turns out that I'm wrong,
I wonder if I'll have to use an
artificial uterus
to have a baby?
When my mother found out she
wasn't able to have children...
...she must have
been devastated.
Have there been any changes in
Koyo since we got him back?
No.
But I've been able to study his
chromosomes and figured out a
way to slow down the
effects of the Festum
component in the other pilots.
If I didn't have access to it,
there's no way the pilots
would've been able to
fight this many battles
without being assimilated
by the Festum already.
I don't like the fact
that the enemy's been
launching an attack
every four days.
And that's exactly
what Mitsuhiro
said would happen
before he left.
The third Festum War...
In other words,
the final battle, right?
We told the Neo U.N.
that we wouldn't participate in
their Dual Attack Offensive
against the Festum.
Maybe somehow we're
still getting dragged into it.
No...
I don't think the Neo U.N.
will launch full-scale
operations until later.
In this current
string of attacks,
I can't help feeling
that the enemy
has a different agenda now.
What do you mean agenda?
These things don't even have a
concept of what an operation is.
The enemy cores
have a limit at the rate
to which they can multiply.
And though we've defeated
many of their kind they keep
dispatching more
and are maintaining
a certain attack pattern.
Military computer programs, when
running tactical simulations,
will often dispatch
additional soldiers
in order to make
up for the loss.
The Festum merely
optimize their battles
just like
a computer would.
Therefore it isn't like them
to favor a specific unit.
So if the enemy's
attack patterns
have changed
significantly then...
Are you suggesting
that the Festum we've
been fighting are some
kind of diversion?
That's right.
Which means that the
Festum now understand the
concept of "sacrifice,"
and are fighting with more
advanced strategic judgment...
Wow, your cheeks
feel so soft, Tsubaki.
When you do
that it tickles, Rina.
But the Festum feels
hard though, right?
Do parts of you feel hard
like the Festum too?
You keep your hands
off of her, you pervert!
Or else!
I bet your entire body
is soft, isn't it Tsubaki?
No fair!
She's touching her!
Yeah, Rina's always
like that with girls.
What?
A giant tailspin attack?
Absolutely not.
It would impose an excess
burden on our bodies.
Darn.
It's such a great move.
That's out of question.
Darn! And right when we got
to start school again too.
I don't believe it!
Take the primary post!
Those in work groups
gather at each bloc!
Get out of the way.
The pilots are coming!
Good luck you guys!
We're counting on you!
Way to go Maya!
You're so cool!
Don't you need to rush
over to the CDC too, Rina?
Right.
We're supposed to take shelter
behind the schoolhouse.
Huh?
Tsubaki?
The enemies this time
consist of eight sphinx-types,
and two long-range
battle D-types.
Give priority to
defending your five o'clock.
You'll land at main battlefield,
five kilometers
southwest from here.
Tsubaki, what are you doing?
It's too dangerous
to be out here.
You need to evacuate.
I have to watch
the battle right now .
There are no
more enemy units left.
The Fafners are returning.
It must've taken
longer this time because
they were those
long-range types, huh?
Hold on.
Wait a minute what's this?
What is it?
What is all this?
Are they fireflies?
Where'd they come from?
This makes no sense.
There weren't
any flowers before!
Wait...
what are these?
The entire island...
it's suddenly filled
with all this life.
Tsubaki!
Are you the one
doing all of this?
No...
All I am is a part of it.
I need to teach my
MIR about life and death.
The beginning of life, when
things stop being eternal.
Birth... it's what allows for
the existence of a life full of
happiness and sadness,
that only the creatures in
this world can experience.
It's beautiful.
Rather than having
a training camp,
I'd prefer to enjoy the view.
How can sunflowers
and cherry blossoms
bloom in
the same season?
Yeah and the
cicadas are shrilling too.
There doesn't seem
to be abnormalities in
the weather control or
life support systems.
Leave the problems with
the island to the specialists.
All we have to worry
about is doing our job.
Including subspecies,
we currently have
data on twenty different
kinds of Festum.
As long as they're the
A through D-types,
then it's possible for us
to defend against them.
Therefore, in the future,
our task will be to
do everything to prevent any
accidents from happening.
And train to deal with the new
types of enemies that launch
simultaneous attacks.
Hey Mamoru, who writes that
comic you're always reading?
Huh?
Do you know, Soshi?
Huh? No.
They're probably reprints
of old archived works.
Oh right.
Alright.
We're about to start the second
phase of our training today.
This is part of our training?
It's about time you
learn how to do this.
And Mom's always too
busy with work to teach you.
Why don't you just take
private lessons from Kazuki?
Why would Kazuki have
anything to do with this?
And what about you, Sakura?
I'll have you know
that I'm a great cook.
My mom taught me all about it.
Yeah right.
How are you doing Canon?
Hm?
Rapid absorption of nutrition
is the basis of this training.
Wow.
You sure are lucky Miss Yumiko.
You have someone to rely on.
I do? Who's that?
I'm talking about Michio!
He gives the impression
of being a real adult.
Like a real man, you know?
You think so?
It wasn't too long ago when
he was just a helpless
attention-craving coward, and a
good-for-nothing woman chaser.
Then...
...why did you agree to
go out with him?
Hmm...
Although he was a mess,
he was always
showing off and
then screwing up.
And I guess I
found that interesting...
That's too funny if you ask me.
And the fact that he's easy
to look at doesn't hurt either.
Besides, it was
obvious that he was
going out of his
way to woo me...
There aren't any
cases like this on file.
It's possible for it to result
in a sudden reactionary change.
Is that so...
You know, Commander...
I really don't mind going
to meet you next time.
No, it's all right.
Besides it's not really my style
to be summoning people.
Kyosuke's says that I
act too hastily and that
I'm not like a commander at all.
That's not what
I was getting at.
Besides,
I don't think that's true.
Yeah!
I got it!
That makes the fifth
straight loss for Kazuki.
Tough luck.
Kazuki...
You're really not very
good at this, are you?
No...
Now then, I'm going to
assign all of you cleaning
duties based on these
tournament standings.
Okay!
Check back on the
water in fifteen minutes.
Roger that!
Don't you still have
to go and help Kazuki?
He's going to have
to deal with his own loss.
Besides, I'm pretty
sure that someone else
is already helping
him out by now.
See what I mean?
How did you know that?
Just had a hunch.
Do you think Kazuki's the
reason Maya's fighting?
Did Maya tell you
that or something?
No.
Just call it a hunch.
If it's true then
it's news to me.
I thought the system allowed you
to sense the feelings of others.
Yeah, in a way I know what her
motivations for fighting are.
They're obligation
and loneliness.
It really bothered her that she
wasn't able to pilot a Fafner.
So you can tell
what we're feeling.
It would be arrogant of me
to claim I was able to
fully understand
others because of it.
Maya was the
one who taught me that.
My number is seven.
And your number is eighteen.
Whaddya mean?
It's the number of
Festum we've each defeated.
Kazuki's at sixty-two...
I'll never catch up to him.
I guess that I'm just no good.
I thought that I would be
able to avenge my father
by defeating as many
enemies as possible.
However, I didn't become strong
enough to do that in the end.
Don't worry. I'll do it.
I'll become like your father!
I'll become stronger.
Stronger than even Kazuki.
Yeah right.
It's not like
you're my boyfriend.
You don't have to be like that.
Fine.
Then let go of my hand.
You don't need to
go out of your way.
I'm not doing that.
You are, too!
You're a just helpless coward,
an attention-craving
woman chaser.
And you're nothing
like my dad, okay?!
So don't go out
of your way for me.
Cuz if I ever lost you...
I told you that's
not what I'm doing!
In that case then...
Could you...
...please hold my
hand some more.
Uh yeah, sure.
Operation creating
new memories...
I'd say the success rate was 50
percent, wouldn't you agree?
You know I can
just imagine it now,
the way you're going to
end up raising this child.
Shouldn't we be coming up
with baby names, just in case?
Before that we've got
something else to address.
The issue of your last name.
Huh?
Pretty soon I won't be able
to pilot a Fafner anymore.
If I manage to make it to
my retirement in one piece,
why don't we make
this thing official?
Stop it.
Don't be ridiculous.
You've always kept your promise
so you have to make it through.
If you don't you'd be a liar.
Yeah, you're right.
Hm?
Hey. I hope you don't
mind, I decided to help myself.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
That's the maintenance
record from the
facilities where
Koyo Kasugai is.
I'm sure it's been
completely altered.
It's far too clean.
It's just as I suspected.
She's the one who altered
the freezing procedure.
Then that means
that all of our actions
on the island are
being monitored...
Tsubaki Minashiro
knows about them all.
What a shame.
And after I went through
all that trouble to get it.
Festums and
humans co-existing...
Do you think that it's possible?
I don't know.
Our generation was different.
We hated the enemy too much.
And that's probably how
we ended up with a guy
like Mitsuhiro representing
our generation.
If I didn't have Kazuki,
I would've ended up
choosing the
same path.
His hand...
...it was bigger
than I thought it'd be.
Oh great.
He filled my mind with
such silly thoughts
that now I have a headache.
I'm home!
Where are they?
Did mom and dad
go to the hanger?
G-Goubain.
He didn't mean to
intentionally deceive you...
You have to understand
that he was merely trying
to do something for
you as a father.
You know, when you were
a babe there were virtually
no forms of entertainment
on the island.
So when you cried because
you wanted to read comics,
we were forced to
reproduce them from scratch.
Do you mean to say he was
copying old comics from memory?
Well, yes, at first.
But after awhile he started
talking about how it wasn't
a genuine gift if he didn't
actually create it himself.
He sacrificed many nights
of sleep in order to
perfect his craft.
Now, he draws the Goubain
series all by himself.
Anko Otsubu is the one and only
true cartoonist
from this island.
And he was born to please
just you and no one else.
I'm sleepy.
But I can never sleep
without my own pillow.
Kenji.
Did you confess your
feelings to Sakura?
Huh?
I don't think Sakura's
the kind of girl
who likes it when
things are vague.
Shut up, stupid!
And why are you
bringing this up now?
We don't know even
if we're going to be
coming back from
this battle alive?
You and Sakura will have
nothing to worry about.
You'll come back safe,
I'm gonna make sure of it.
Ms. Yazama!
What is it, Mamoru?
Something wrong?
I was wondering if you could
please keep this for me?
But that's your...
Are you sure?
I'd really appreciate it.
Well, that took l less time
than usual, didn't it?
And there were a lot
of them today too.
Hey, Mamoru.
What's wrong?
It was... scary...
Everyone...
...you always...
...do so much
during the battles.
Mamoru.
Hey, Do you think that I
can become strong too?
Do you think I can be
strong like everyone else?
Of course I do.
All right Sakura.
What?
What do you want from me now?
Uh...
Meet me after
school tomorrow alright?
What is it?
A love letter?
A challenge...
to Kazuki Makabe?
Looks like It's from Kenji.
It's been awhile since
I got one of these.
Do you always play along when he
sends you one of
these challenges?
Yeah, ever since
he called me a coward.
Why don't you
just try losing to him.
It's been Kenji's dream
to confess his feelings
to Sakura after defeating you.
So let him.
Hey Maya, I'm sorry but would
you mind leaving us alone?
Huh?
And why's that?
Because he said so, that's why.
What'd you say?
I'll be judging the match so
that you pilots won't get hurt.
We'll be playing by
the same set of rules
as in a simulation fight.
Is that all right?
Kenji challenged
Kazuki for you...
Hmm, I'm not sure about that.
I really envy you, Sakura.
You know the thing I really like
about you is your honesty.
You used to have a thing
for Michio, didn't you?
I'm not sure.
Maybe I guess.
And now you're starting to
like Kazuki a bit, am I right?
Why would you say that?
It was just a hunch.
But my hunches
are usually right.
Don't you have an appointment to
meet with Kenji right about now?
Hmm...
I don't think the fight's
over yet, but oh well.
I'll go there and cheer him on.
Just like if I was his girl.
I guess that's the way boys are.
Hang in there...
Hang in there boys...
What is this?
My mind... it's...
...it's disappearing...
No!
Please no!
Kenji! Kenji!
Kenji...
♪ closing song ♪
The light is gone.
Our feelings try to
make up for the loss.
I'll do something about it...
Next on Fafner episode
number twenty-two.
"Power."
Are you there?