Several objects are approaching
from the southwest.
They'll be arriving
in thirty minutes.
It's a large group of Festum...
But we can win if
we defeat their leader.
Start Vaffe Larden.
Engage!
Number one and two Gnosis units!
Intercept them off
the southwest bank.
Number three, four,
and five units.
Set up a defense line on the
southwest coast of the island.
Let's show these worms
of the universe what
kind of power the
human race is capable of.
Now we'll see if the Neo UN
Force has any skills.
I'm sure they won't
know how to use Solomon.
Barns is actually an
excellent commander.
I'm sure that he won't
be defeated easily.
I'm just praying that we're not
going to end up
like Moldova did.
Hey, Yumiko.
The CDC is now the
headquarters of Neo UN Force.
What can you even do in there?
I can't let people who
don't even understand
the system mess around with it.
Hey! Just what do
you think you're doing?!
This isn't the way I had
imagined meeting
you again either.
Trust me on that.
That really hurt.
Hey what are you doing?!
This'll all be over soon.
I need you to stay there, okay?
Just knowing that you were alive
somewhere out there in the world
was the only thing
that gave me the
strength to keep on
fighting, Yumiko.
It's what kept me alive.
I'm sorry...
We got left behind
because I was too slow.
Never mind that.
By the way, are you all right?
This is my first time outside.
So I still can't walk well yet.
That's alright we'll
take lots of breaks.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Hey...
Is it okay to ask you a favor?
Sure go right ahead.
You want to be
carried or something?
No.
I would be very happy if you
and I could become friends.
You see...
It's just that I don't
have any friends.
What are you talking about?
You've already got a
friend right here silly.
Thank you Seri.
That means a lot to me.
Don't think anything of it.
Huh?
Did I introduce myself, yet?
What's that?
It's the entrance
to the shelter.
Now, hurry in.
Okay.
I'm afraid I have to go.
Huh?
Seri, you stay down
there with everyone else.
But wait a minute.
Who are you?
Oh, that's right.
My name is Tsubaki.
It's Tsubaki Minashiro.
Minashiro?
Hey...!
Does that mean
you're one of Soshi's...?
It's a promise, okay?
You and I are gonna be friends.
The number one Walle Shield
has disappeared.
The enemy is still
headed right toward us.
They're advancing
in a straight line...
They've underestimated us.
Yes. The curfew
doesn't apply to me.
It's not like that.
It's for the people who are
physically weakened...
We humans shouldn't be
arguing at a time like this...
Hello?
Who is it?
Chizuru.
Are you there?
Huh?
I have a favor to ask
you since you're the
one who put me into the system.
It's really you...
But how can that be?
I still can't walk
very well because
it's my first time outside.
So please... would
you mind bringing me
something that you could
transport me with?
Sir, the Number two Walle
Shield has been breached.
Fire!
The colonel seems
pretty eager too.
Ain't that right, Kanon?
You're also livelier than usual.
Heh.
What do you expect?
I just reunited
with a lady friend.
It's that woman...
The Nothung Models are here.
One's landed on the
southwest side and detonated.
We've got a few
Pleiades-types on our hands.
Triple Six, go out there
and provide back up.
I'm already here.
Kanon!
Bring the number three
unit around to the left!
We're gonna come
at them from both sides.
Roger.
Watch out!
What do you think you're doing?!
Careful, damnit!
Don't you know how
to use your radio?
Mark Drei. Come in.
Do you read me?
It's cold.
The wind is so cold...
I can feel Fafner's surfaces as
if they were my own skin.
It's as if my body has
become really huge...
And it feels so heavy right now.
Those are the traits
of the Nothung Model.
Unite with it!
Accept the mind alteration!
Stop being an idiot!
If you don't stand up and fight,
you're going to die!
It is her.
Tsubaki Minashiro.
This is our first time.
Talking like this...
Chizuru.
We've made a direct attack on
three Serpent class Firma.
They've all sunk.
And what about
the head of the fleet?
We still can't find it.
Tell the remaining two
submarines to concentrate
all their attacks off
the southwest coast.
Hey wait a second.
Our allies are firing at us?
Tsubaki!
This is the first time
I've played in mud, ever!
How could they...?
Don't worry.
It's all right.
They're not burning everything.
It's just the surface.
The time has finally come.
They are about to choose now.
A third group has
appeared in the west.
Those alien bastards...
Disconnect the
island's southwest wing,
and engage its self destruct.
We'll kill the enemy even if it
means destroying the island!
The system has started
interception on its own.
It's rejecting all our commands.
How could that be?
Why are those
components moving?!
Who's doing it?!
Who's in control?
I don't know sir.
The door just unlocked.
Is it time to eat?
What the hell's going on?
Headquarters, come in?
It's no use.
I can't get through.
It looks like your chain of
command has been cut off.
Which means the
circumstances have changed.
Sorry but I'm not
staying here anymore.
Michio?
What the hell is this?
Who is the one doing that?
Kenji, are you okay?
Watch out.
Why is that section closing?
Someone is doing
it intentionally.
They're trying to
lead us in that direction.
Is that you... Tsubaki?
Re-establish our
line of defense!
Those who can
still move, advance!
A slew of Pleiades-types
have gathered
at the top of Mt. Tatsumiya.
They're directly above us!
They're above us?!
Tsubaki?!
I'm all right...
I was simply feeling
the island's pain.
I knew it.
Let's stop.
If anything happens to you...
The island will eventually
sink into the ocean
if I keep hiding like this.
And before that happens,
I need to allow everyone
to make their own choices.
Keel block...
Urdu fountain...
Even though my
destiny has been laid out...
...are you telling me
to choose what I want...?
Is that it, Tsubaki?
What the heck is going on here?
We have no time to lose.
Hurry up and get in.
You want us to pilot?
But we don't
even have any suits!
Kazuki got inside one
without the suit, didn't he?!
Besides...
If we don't fight now,
how can we ever face
Dad, Koyo, and the others again?
My job here is to
provide everybody with
something that all of them want.
And whether they
really want it or not.
I will let them choose for
themselves once again.
That is the same
with Festum as well.
I will also let them choose.
And it is for that purpose...
...that I was born.
Isn't that correct?
You should go back now.
It'll be safer in the shelter.
Thank you for coming all
the way here with me.
I appreciate it.
What is it?
I won't leave.
I'm going too.
But not as a system researcher,
as a resident as someone who
lives on this island, I want
to see it with my own eyes.
Yumiko. You too?
How did you get in here?
Well, I think I was led here.
Do you know what this place is?
It's the main body of Solomon!
That means that this is...
So we're standing
in Arthur's room.
And this is the second CDC!
Everyone,
take your regular posts.
The basic structure here
is the same as the CDC.
Confirm all systems.
We are going to take
back control of the island!
I am this island,
and this island is me...
What the people who
live here want to do
with the island is
completely up to them.
I will let them know what
it is they really want...
And the only way
I can do that...
...is by giving them a choice.
And through their choice...
...they will realize something.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to
let you choose for yourself.
But you're wrong.
I chose too.
I decided I wanted a heart.
That's what I ended
up choosing for myself.
And now look at me...
It's me.
I'm right here.
One hundred seventeen
of them have landed
on the island and the enemy's
power is still increasing.
It's a matter of time before
the Pleiades-types find us.
And the secondary
defense system?
I'm accessing it now.
Two minutes until completion.
The main body
producing the group
is invalidating the search.
I can't find it.
Can you use the Fafners
as a decoy to lure the
enemy head out?
It's going to be difficult,
but I'll give it a shot.
Someone's singing!
It's impossible...
Solomon has responded!
It's the enemy head!
Concentrate all power to
the interception system!
Where's that song coming from?
The lighthouse on the west
side of Tatsumiya Island.
Onscreen...
It can't be...
So that's where she is.
Tsubaki...
Are you going to let the Festums
make their own choice, Tsubaki?
The enemy has started making
its way toward the lighthouse.
Attention all Fafners!
Spread out and hurry to
the west end of the island.
Dodge any enemy units you see,
and gather at the
rendevous point.
We're going to
attack the main body!
You wait and see...
I'm going to defeat
every single enemy!
This is scary, really scary.
Go!
Goubain!
Wait, that's...
They're moving differently now.
Did they change
pilots or something?
Kanon.
I've located the enemy head.
We're moving west.
Roger.
Those who can
still fight, follow me.
Here we go!
Access is completed.
Let's give 'em
everything we've got!
Did we do it?
Here they come!
Mark Hguc, hold the
enemy in check with Aegis.
Mark Achat,
go around to the right side.
Mark Drei, confirm
the enemy core and destroy it.
Kenji get away from it!
I'm coming Kenji!
No, don't!
You'll break the formation!
You bastard!
Damnit!
We're too late.
Even the Nothung Models
were no match for it.
Above you!
You sneaky bastards!
They're such monsters!
It's too strong for us.
The target is making its way
back towards the
lighthouse again.
And Tsubaki?
She hasn't moved.
I see...
You have made
a choice as well...
A world without conversation...
...where everything disappears.
A path that leads to nothing.
However...
You are not the only one.
Other people have
also made their choice.
Tsubaki.
Let's try to escape.
Thank you, Chizuru.
Thank you very much.
But it's okay.
I'm going to be fine.
Welcome home.
That machine!
What the heck is it?
It caught the attack one handed!
That's what it did earlier!
This is not good!
It's gonna detonate!
My readings are showing that...
...the enemy core is
disappearing from the inside.
That can only mean
that the Festum are...
They're being assimilated
by something else.
The target is
disappearing again!
What?
Solomon's response
has disappeared.
You can find it if
you look for it. Try Soshi.
I will Tsubaki!
Vibrations,
temperature fluctuations,
electron dispersions and
spatial phasing...
This is it!
The wound that was created when
that machine counter attacked.
Whoever's piloting,
can you hear me?
I've locked onto the enemy.
It's up to you to defeat it.
It's Soshi...
Kazuki...
is that you?
We need to link our machines
and do a system crossing.
It should be the same as when
you do it with the Mark Elf.
It's already too late.
How could you...
Soshi, you once told
me that this island
was the only paradise left.
So I fought just like you said
I should, I went into battle,
without understanding
what you really meant by that.
After everything
I've been through...
I see things differently...
I understand a little better.
What is it that you understand?
That deep down inside...
...you have
suffered a great deal.
This whole time we knew nothing.
But you knew and tried
to protect the island.
In Shoko's case,
and in Koyo's case too.
You carried the pain alone.
And you never once...
What is the i.d.
code of that machine?
It's the Mark Sein.
I will register the unit
for system crossing.
Give me five seconds.
Are you all right?
It'll be done soon.
The enrollment has
been completed.
I'm starting the
system crossing now.
Kazuki, can you see what I see?
Yes I can.
I see it all.
Here we go!
What weapon is that?
It's the Mark Achat's
Garm Forty four,
but its energy levels
are tremendous.
I've never seen such power.
Is that thing a Luger Lance?
♪ closing song ♪
A conversation...
...with a girl who
wasn't anywhere.
There's not much time left.
Next on Fafner:
episode number seventeen.
"A Device."
Are you there?