♪ opening song ♪
I'm going to fight, as well.
Shoko.
If you feel sick, I want
you to tell me right away.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm gonna be just fine.
Checking the pilot's
physical condition.
There are no signs...
of any air sickness.
Maya is so amazing.
It's so beautiful.
What's remarkable is that her
emotions are unusually stable.
I guess she's insensitive
in a good way, huh?
So then, she should be able
to fight immediately, right?
I agree, but I think
she's more suitable to
handle back up
rather than the front lines.
That's because you don't want
her to be on the frontlines...
...isn't that right?
Let's see how she does with the
long range weapons simulator.
Yes sir.
I've begun the initiation of the
weapons simulation program.
You'll start the target practice
using Dragon Tooth.
I guess I should just try using
it the way Mr. Mizoguchi does.
Well she looks pretty
damn good with that thing.
Start her out at one thousand
two hundred meters.
I'm releasing
the target right now.
Just stay calm.
Concentrate on the rhythm
of your breathing, that's right.
Woah! I don't believe it.
She hit it dead on!
Move it two hundred meters
back each time she hits it.
She's still maintaining a
success rate of over 90 percent.
Target's current distance...
twenty-eight hundred meters.
Maya's naturally
really good at all of this.
You're right. She could
provide excellent back up.
We don't know how
she'll do in actual battle.
You know I've got a
feeling she'll do just fine.
And if we train her well,
she won't have any
problems shooting alone.
She's got the
potential of becoming
the best sniper here at Alvis.
Why won't you let
me pilot this Fafner?
The pilots of the Nothung Models
have special requirements.
And they're assigned
to their Fafners
according to
their genetic makeup.
And this Mark Sein
is so in tune with Kazuki
that it won't accept any pilot's
synergetic code except for his.
I'm so jealous of Kazuki.
I want to have a personalized
Fafner just like him.
Why don't we just
go ask the Neo U.N.?
Maybe they'll make
yours all special
like they did to Kazuki's.
I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
What do you mean?
This thing here...
It nearly assimilated Maya once.
This has three times more
Fenrir in it than the others.
It's to make
sure there's nothing
left of it if it needs
to be destroyed.
So do you still want to pilot
something like that now?
We don't know
her real potential.
So we shouldn't
use her in combat yet.
Are you afraid that
if Maya becomes a pilot,
she'll be in greater danger?
If Kazuki and Maya
were both in danger,
which would you
try to save first?
I thought you would want to go
watch Maya's
training session today.
I didn't have the time to.
I have to finish
this report by today.
Let's have a look.
Bon also known as Ura
Bon is a Buddhist
holiday celebrating the dead,
which island residents
are encouraged to take part in.
In other words,
it's on the Bon festival.
We're gonna have a
festival at a time like this?
Now's the more
reason to have one.
The whole purpose
of this island is to promote
a culture of peacefulness.
The training's over.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Rina.
It was incredible.
Maya was so cool.
Commander Makabe even said she
could probably start
fighting immediately.
So she's that good.
Yeah.
I see...
I'm sending you some data.
Can you confirm
each section for me?
Sure.
Michio...
Why do we need
to have so many pilots?
Because the Festum are
becoming more and more active.
A huge swarm of
them could suddenly
show up and just attack
us at any moment.
Well, it's not as
if I don't know that.
By the way,
we're still gonna go through
with that plan of
ours today, right?!
Uh, yeah right.
Maya and the rest of my family
are having serious issues.
Um, yeah.
Quite frankly,
the thought of Maya getting
in a Fafner terrifies me.
I'm sorry.
I know everyone's
had to make sacrifices.
The children are the ones
who are really scared.
If the adults
start acting anxious,
it will put unnecessary
pressure on them.
And we don't want that.
I understand.
We've been able to keep
him alive for a long time.
Yes...
Thanks to the new
data from Moldova
as well as his own strength too.
It's possible we'll be
able prolong pilots' lives.
And as a result,
perhaps our future too.
Both you and your
daughter have great vision.
You have the
ability to see beyond
the normal
limitations of science.
Your contributions
have not been in vain.
Oops!
Hey there, careful little
lady, you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
So many Mr. Mizoguchi
spinning round 'n round.
You all right Maya?
What good timing.
Come over here for a second.
Uh, what happened?
She's acting drunk from the side
effect of the synergetic code.
Did you say she was drunk?
I'm not drunk you guys.
You can see why they
call it beginner's high.
It's probably
this bad because she
was extra tense since it was
her first training session.
That's why I'm
leaving the rest to you.
Thanks.
Uh... Huh?
She's gonna be an important
fighting colleague to you.
So you'd better take her home.
A colleague...
I found you, Kazuki!
Hey Maya!
What are you two doing?
Soshi!
This really isn't
what it looks like!
Huh?
Oh Soshi and Tsubaki.
How ya doin'?
We're doing real great!
I'm so glad to hear that.
Soshi.
Help me out.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I'm busy right now.
What?
Be the responsible one
and take Maya home.
Consider this an order from
your battle commander.
Bye Soshi and Tsubaki.
See ya!
You're tough on
people, aren't you?
I'd save all of them.
Huh?
It's the answer to the
question you asked earlier.
I wouldn't put one over another.
However dangerous,
I would protect all pilots in
the Siegfried System.
Don't worry. 'Cuz you're
not alone in that. Soshi.
Are you feeling a
little better now Maya?
Yeah.
I can walk by myself now.
Sorry...
I got kind of carried
away back there.
It's okay.
I wasn't able to walk after my
first training session either.
No, that's not what I meant.
Perhaps I was like
that cuz I was so happy.
What do you mean "happy"?
I was finally able to see the
same things everyone else saw...
I'm sure that's
how Shoko felt too.
But instead of piloting Fafner,
it felt more like I
was becoming Fafner.
Like becoming a different me.
I'm going to do my best
to be just like you.
Oh, Maya.
Hey, you two!
What are you doing with
so many bags, Sis?
It's so that we can
celebrate your training!
Huh?
Kazuki, why don't
you celebrate with us?
Thank you but I'm supposed
to see my Dad today so...
I've got an idea.
We should invite Commander
Makabe to come too!
You're right!
I'll go contact him
and see what he says.
Wait a minute. What do
you think you are doing?
Don't you worry about it.
Let's get everything ready
before Mom comes home.
I appreciate
the invitation, bu--
Alright, quit your complaining.
Think of it as if you're
helping me out a little.
Oh.
Hey Kazuki's really
an amazing cook, isn't he?
I know he cooks
for his dad at home.
If you move in with him,
he could cook for you,
since you're so bad at it.
Whatever!
Not everyone's
like you are, okay Sis?
What's wrong with it?
Besides if you did it too,
maybe Mom would be
more understanding
about me doing it.
I wouldn't expect her to be.
But...
That's perfect!
This will be our primary weapon.
Now, onto the rest
of the culinary arsenal.
Oh no! The enemy approached
sooner than I expected.
Hm?
Is she here already?!
We must be brave and
face the enemy head on!
Man, what a rough day...
Huh?
Welcome home.
Mother.
What?
What's going on?
Excuse me.
I heard that Kazuki was here...
Do you come over here a lot?
Just every once in awhile.
What are trying to accomplish
by doing this, Yumiko?
Not so bad, is it?
I did pretty well here.
Didn't I.
What's that supposed to mean?
Mom, Mr. Makabe is the only real
person you confide in, isn't he?
I completed the
dish-washing task
and I'm ready
for your next assignment.
Thank you.
Here, have some tea.
Is that an order?
No. Of course not. Have a seat.
When I don't have any orders,
I'm at a loss as to what to do.
Then, go ahead and be at a loss.
That'll be the
only order from me
that you'll ever have
to follow, Canon.
That'll be quite
a tough mission.
This will be the first Bon
festival in which we honor Dad.
I will defeat as many
enemies as possible.
That way Dad's
soul can rest in peace.
Sakura...
I promise never to
run away from the enemy.
Thank you very much for dinner.
I apologize for
Yumiko's behavior today.
It's okay.
It's been awhile
since I've remembered
why this island was created.
If you don't mind
me commenting on it,
some people are simply trying to
start a new life for themselves.
It's just that...
Michio and Yumiko
are both good people.
And you should
be able to trust them.
Sometimes you need to let your
children go to see them grow.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Sure was an interesting
dinner, wasn't it, Kazuki?
Uh... is something
the matter?
I was just thinking that some
things never change, do they?
Huh?
You're probably right.
It's a notice about
the Bon festival.
What do we do for that?
We build this high wooden
stage and everybody dances.
And we'll have stalls too.
Is it like a dance party?
Not really.
It's kinda different.
It's the part of the
festival where we all pray
for the peace for the deceased.
So it's like a requiem.
Yeah, right.
It's more like that.
Don't forget we're
gonna need to prepare
something for Karin and Shoko.
Wait a minute.
What about Koyo?
What the hell you talking about?
He's still alive, you idiot!
Who's Koyo?
He's a good friend of ours,
and someone who
I wasn't able to save.
Oh, I see.
I know!
Let's visit Koyo again.
I'm sure he will wake up sooner
if we talk to him more.
You can't go!
Not over there!
I have Solomon's response.
It's ambivalent.
And it is unable
to determine the type.
It's not recognizing the
target as an enemy either.
I don't care!
I want you to
start the Vaffe Larden.
And get all of the pilots
onboard their
Fafners immediately.
If Solomon doesn't
think of it as an enemy,
I'd hate to imagine
what that means.
Even so, this'll be one
troublesome battle.
We may even lose a
few pilots with this one.
I'll position each pilot
in a different direction.
Make sure the
Mark Sieben is positioned
in the center
with the equipment.
Do you mean Maya?
It's gonna be a numbers game.
Our damage could be as
bad as it was at Moldova.
I won't let that happen.
Do your best.
Maya.
Mom...
I'll see you back at home.
No matter what it
takes I won't let
you have your way on my island.
We'll attack simultaneous
from five locales.
Everyone take your
instructed positions!
I'm ready whenever you guys are.
Okay, I'm in position.
I'm ready for your next orders.
Goubain!
Don't you think this
is all a bit sudden.
This is for you.
Okay Dad?
How are you doing?
You okay Maya?
Yeah thanks.
I'm linking all the audio
communication lines
to you so you'll
know what's going on.
But make sure that
you're only following
my instructions and
not someone else's.
Right. Got it.
The enemy is assimilating
with the Welle Shield.
I take it the Brunhilde System
is working, is that correct?
It has automatically switched
over to its the defensive modes.
I had a feeling it would
be one of those rare types.
As did I.
It just went down.
So did we defeat it?
Here comes the rare type.
Be ready.
Remember to watch
your back, Canon.
Use as much
firepower as possible!
Don't attempt hand to hand
combat no matter what.
That's weird.
Why isn't he attacking back?
Release the Aegis!
Mark Funf, you must retreat!
Mark Acht!
Attack when it's trying
to assimilate!
I did it.
I really did it!
It's the eye!
Everyone.
Aim for the eyes in the head.
Damn, that thing's fast!
I hate fighting
these kinds of Festum!
Now!
You're going straight to hell!
The enemies located
at nine o'clock,
one o'clock, and six o'clock
have all disappeared.
The enemy located
at three o'clock
is retreating to the
upper atmospheres.
They're doing pretty good.
It's not over.
All it takes is one
of those things
to destroy the whole island.
Outta bullets!
Damn you!
Don't make contact!
Mark Drei!
Retreat now!
Mark Drei is in danger.
She needs, back up.
No!
Help!
I'm scared!
Mom, help me!
Sakura, no...
Hurry up and eject
that pilot right now!
That's what I'm doing!
No... what am I
supposed to do now?
Do you want me
to shoot Sakura too?!
We've arrived at the scene.
We'll take care of this.
Once they stop moving that's
when I'm going in for the shot.
I'll do it.
I don't mind if
I take the blame.
You would...
If anything should go wrong, at
least I'm not from this island.
Stop it! You'll end
up killing Sakura!
I'm now disabling all
of Mark Acht's weapons.
--Sakura!
--No!
--Stop it!
Soshi, can you hear me?
--Ignore them, Canon!
--Are you listening, Soshi?
Why did you do it?
Why did you lock my weapon?
Answer me Soshi.
Because once you fire, the
enemy will advance toward you.
I don't care.
Besides... That's why I'm here.
Kazuki...
I'm going to draw the
enemy away from Mark Drei.
After that, it's up to you.
Draw it away?
And how are you
going to do that?
Mark Sieben
will take care of it.
Do you mean Maya?
Okay, let's do it.
They did it!
There is one more out there!
No!
Maya!
All the Festum have disappeared!
And our pilots appear
to be unharmed.
Way to go Maya.
She is so awesome.
Good job.
Instruct them all to land
at Mukoujima dock.
All right everyone.
Let's go give them
a hero's welcome.
Sakura!
Mom!
I was so scared.
I thought I wouldn't make it.
Welcome back, Canon.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm back again.
What is this?
That's weird.
Why am I just
feeling scared now?
We will celebrate by having
dinner together, Soshi.
Could you stop
taking charge of things.
I'm your big brother, after all.
That doesn't make a difference.
You'll always be Soshi, to me.
♪ closing song ♪
Tatsumiya Island is
bustling from the festival.
Memorial lights are everywhere.
Some memories never go away.
Next on "Fafner"
episode number twenty.
"Light."
Are you there?