Kenji!
Try dodging!
It's no use.
I'm going to die...
Don't give up!
Kenji!
Tsubaki!
What...
This thing...
What could this be?
That Festum...
is pain!
Tsubaki.
It's okay.
I'm ready... but...
I'm scared.
It's okay Tsubaki.
I'm really scared...
Take this!
Festum!
Would you like to
know the name of the
military tactic I taught you?
It is the war of attrition!
It is the tactic by
which to endure pain!
The pain that you
feel from fighting,
it is the pain of existence!
It comes from
the fear of disappearing.
Festum!
Chizuru.
What is it?
I want...
I want to stay here.
I want to stay
here with you guys.
Oh, Tsubaki!
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry, Tsubaki.
Mom.
You can't escape...
The enemy's attack
rate is slowing.
Many of our units have already
broken through their
defensive lines.
Push forward!
We can't waste this
opportunity!
Keep advancing as
far as we possibly can!
Thank you for everything.
Chizuru.
I get it.
I understand.
I'll be all right.
And this way...
I'll be able to
become the island.
Oh Tsubaki...
It's that time.
I'll be able to hold
all of you close.
Just like a mother would...
To do that...
I'll become
one with the island.
I don't want this.
I just want to go back...
to when we were nothing!
Everyone!
Retreat now!
Do you want to
be glad to be alive...
Because that...
...that is the joy that
only comes from existing...
Festum.
This is it.
It's Point C.
We're here.
Maya, use your Lacing Cutter.
Roger that.
This data...
...humans and Festum will now
be able to co-exist...??
Which means...
There's too much of it.
What if it overloads
our systems?
No.
Most of it is being
transferred to somewhere else.
And it's...
...Tatsumiya island.
My Mom...
Incoming data.
The Alvis servers and Urd's Well
are automatically receiving it.
It's being sent
from the North Pole.
Look at the size of that thing.
The data far exceeds any amount
we've ever received before.
They have reached Akane's core.
So now, they can have hope.
As can I.
The course is clear.
All systems are greenlit to go.
Something's updating our system.
It's navigational info coming
from somewhere near the target.
Do you think it's
possible that it's from...?
Akane Makabe...
A long time ago, when
most of us had lost hope,
she was the one
who reminded us to live.
Somewhere inside here...
Is where we'll find Soshi.
Oh Kazuki...
Soshi...
Kazu... ki...
They're here!
You won't get by...
...no matter what.
We're about to begin the
core's re-synchronization.
Oh Tsubaki...
You're not getting by me!
Am I being clear?
The lives you took away...
we want you to give them back.
No.
Kazuki...
Don't resist it...
Alright then.
I am you.
And you are...
...me.
The pulse of the enemy's MIR...
Yes Kazuki...
...you've assimilated
with the enemy's will.
That's right.
Acceptance is a kind of power.
Kazuki...
Thank you... Everyone...
Tsubaki...
Soshi.
Are you still in there?
Soshi!
Kazuki.
You're really here...
aren't you?!
Yeah...
I'm not gone yet.
I'm still here.
Thank goodness!
Soshi.
He's alive...
Kazuki, what's the matter?
My eyes...
His body is reacting that way
because he's already
been assimilated.
It can't be.
He'll be all right...
I'm sure it'll go away when
he receives treatment.
Let's go back...
...back home...
Kazuki.
What is going on now?
The MIR...
it's started to move...
Fire!
Do it now!
The enemy's right
in front of us!
Oh Tsubaki...
The final assimilation
is about to begin.
Oh no...
Tsubaki!
Is that it?
That's the enemy's MIR.
It's trying to
link to the sky...
It plans to cover the
whole earth with Festum
by invading us from the
outer atmosphere.
We still have some time.
Assimilate with Mark Sieben's
weapon and shoot it down.
I understand.
Maya...
you'll pull the trigger.
Roger that.
Release Mark Sein's energy when
it reaches it's maximum level.
You only have one shot.
Kazuki's body won't
last longer than that.
Because after all... To them,
that might have been the
only hope that they ever had.
Even if so...
it is not the last hope.
Tsubaki...
That MIR and I...
we are the same.
To show that life and death,
existence and nothing
continue as one...
...we were born into this world.
Tsubaki?
Did you go back?
Are you with the other MIR?
Tsubaki...
I just can't believe it.
The Festum are falling.
Mr. Mizoguchi.
The Fafner team
has just reported in.
Everyone is safe.
They really pulled it off.
Those kids actually
managed to do it.
It's wind.
Down here?
It's the core.
She has now become
one with the island.
A breeze...
I am not gone...
I am here...
Good work, everyone!
We'll be home
before you know it.
Kazuki!
It's the Mark Nicht!
I see.
Upon dying the MIR gave the
Festum a physical body.
At this rate, everyone
will be sucked into it.
Kazuki!
Right!
Kazuki, no!
Maya!
Maya, stay back!
Don't worry...
I'll make it back.
No!
Kazuki... don't!
Calm down!
The crossing is still in effect.
If any one of us died,
we wouldn't be able
to communicate.
Remember?
You were the one
who told us about that
before we went into
the battle, Maya.
Which means...
Kazuki...
he's still alive.
I don't exist anywhere...
Yet I am here.
Existence and oblivion.
They are two sides
of the same coin.
I am nowhere...
And I am here.
Kazuki... Soshi.
This...
It's the Festum's blessing.
It returns everything
to nothingness.
It makes you
wonder what reality is.
Perhaps we no longer exist
out there in the real world.
Kazuki.
But it's... too soon.
We still...
We still exist!
Kazuki.
Soshi!
We're here!
--Koyo!
I am... here!
I exist!
What's that?
Those are the space fleets
and the cores of the Festum
that were in the
outer atmosphere.
They are burning up
and falling from the sky.
Look, Kazuki.
Before it could take off,
the entire vessel was hit.
But the engine remains intact.
Try to assimilate with
the structure of the body.
I'll transfer over
the controls of the system.
Once we're in the air
I'll be able to pilot it.
Think you can fly...
Kazuki?
I can fly...
as long as we do it together.
Isn't that right?
What is that?
The MIR...
...it finally understood
the cycle of life.
Is that, Tsubaki?
No.
The same person
can't just be reborn.
If you could we would just be
identical copies of each other.
And we would lose all the
essential qualities of life.
So the being we knew as Tsubaki,
is being reborn
into something new.
Eventually, it will
grow up to be the core.
And I'm sure we'll be able to
have conversations with it.
As long as we
keep this island here...
...as a source of hope.
Continue on your current course,
and you'll hit the island.
You know,
when it came down to it.
You still saved me
in the very end.
Kazuki...
I taught the Festum about
pain and about existing.
And in the process...
I learned their blessing.
It was the cycle of
existence and nothingness.
The cycle of existence
and nothingness?
What are you talking about?
My body...
most of it is already gone...
Kazuki.
No!
Don't say that!
Once we get back to the island
I'm sure they can
do something.
You go on without me, Kazuki.
In a very short while...
I'll disappear.
Soshi!
What are you talking about?
Don't be like this, Soshi!
It will be alright.
I am going to return to
the Festum's side.
And from there, I will once
again create a life for myself.
I have no idea how
long this will take me.
But I will do it.
Soshi!
You're still here, right?
You're still there, aren't you?!
Soshi.
Soshi!
I'm still right here.
Until we meet again.
Goodbye friend.
Soshi!
Mark Sieben's all patched up.
It's prepared for take off.
Understood.
The pilot's mental condition
has also stabilized.
He's here!
Open the Number
seven Night Helle.
Do it now!
Fafner Mark Sieben you
are all cleared for takeoff!
♪ closing song ♪
Soshi...
I will stay here.
I will wait for
you... right here...
...forever.
I understand now.
Even though life
is filled with pain,
I can endure it and
I will choose to exist.
I will do it all again..
in order to see you once more.
As long as you believe in me...
I will return to you someday...
No matter what.