Hey, Maya, what about me?
Will you remember what I'm like?
Kazuki...
I'm just worried that over time
I might get too
used to fighting.
And it scares me.
'Cuz you see...
I feel like I'm already
gradually changing into
something different.
I think that...
everyone's been feeling uneasy.
And nothing's been
the same since.
I don't think any of us will
remain unchanged.
After all, we all have to go on
living on this island don't we?
So you see...
it's okay.
Oh, Maya...
Don't worry...
...it doesn't matter if
you change; Kazuki,
I will always remember you.
I promise I will.
Thank you, Maya.
♪ opening song ♪
You came.
It's not too late.
You can still change your
mind and quit, you know.
No. I've already
made my decision about it.
Let's go then...
Let's leave this island.
Is this...
the right choice?
I wonder.
I haven't seen Kazuki
around anywhere.
I wonder if he's stuck over at
Alvis, working or something?
You haven't heard?
Well I don't know if it's true,
but there's a rumor
going around that...
Kazuki and Miss Kariya...
...well...
...were...
...you know...
You're kidding!
I didn't know they had
that kind of relationship!
Forbidden love! And with
such a large age difference.
Now they've run
off too... elope!
I can't believe it!
That's awesome!
Shut up!
I don't find it a bit amusing.
All that really happened was
that he got scared and ran away.
He's a deserter in my book.
What do they do to you if you
desert in the face of the enemy?
I don't know...
You've done
such a foolish thing...
Yukie...
Where are we?
What exactly is this place?
It's a place where a few
billion humans used to live.
This was one of their cities.
Soshi...
He was here and saw
this world too, didn't he?
Yes.
That's what I've heard.
Now prepare for landing.
Got it.
Where have you gone to?
You're a good pilot.
That supposed to
be a compliment?
No. I didn't mean
anything by it...
I-I was just...
Believe it or not,
I was a Fafner pilot
candidate a long time ago.
Really? You were?
I verified the stats on the Mark
Elf pilot and there were no
abnormalities in the
synergetic code
formation rate or his
state of mind...
...except for the motive...
After careful evaluation,
I realized the only
possible conclusion
is that there must have been
some external factors involved.
More specifically one external
factor called Yukie Kariya.
I'm sorry.
Can you leave Kazuki Makabe
and Yukie Kariya to me?
I'd personally like to determine
what to do with them.
Kozo Minashiro and I've been
aware for some time now
of the fact that Yukie
Kariya is a Neo U.N. spy.
We decided not to apprehend
her until we could discover
her true intentions,
so I take full responsibility
for not being able to prevent
the current situation.
Leave it to me.
You let yourself
be double-crossed
by a younger woman.
You better watch out--people
gonna start calling you easy.
Well and your
son siding with her.
I'm sure you
didn't expect that either.
Do you think Mitsuhiro
was involved with this?
Who else would have come up
with such a complicated scheme?
If that's true, then we haven't
seen the worst of all this yet.
Yeah.
And knowing the way you are...
You're prepared
for that, aren't ya?
By any chance...
...are you regretting
what you've done?
No I'm not.
Because I felt like if I
stayed that way any longer,
I was going to lose myself...
...for sure.
I agree.
You didn't belong.
That island wasn't
the place for you.
You shouldn't just be
protecting that small island.
You ought to be protecting
the entire world.
Protect the world?
You mean me?
It's only natural for a
Fafner pilot of your caliber.
If we can use this
and destroy Festum,
I don't care what kind
of price I have to pay.
He used to always say to us...
...that we needed to
know the true meaning
of why Fafner was
originally created...
Make the people on the
island understand, Kazuki!
You can do it!
Miss Kariya...
...who is the "he"
you're referring to?
What?
This is bad timing!
It'll find us if we stay here.
We need to hurry up and leave!
No, that's out of the question.
We can't leave here yet!
Huh?
Get ready to fight, Kazuki!
That is a direct order!
Are you there?
It didn't work!
What do you think you're doing!
Destroy it now, Kazuki!
I'm trying!
Kazuki.
Land and then stand by.
Got it.
Could it be?
Is that Fafner?
That Sphinx type seems
to be a little too easy.
So this should be a real breeze.
Triple Six, have you
confirmed whether
or not the target has
been assimilated?
How the hell am I
supposed to know that?
Kanon!
This one's mine, you understand?
Don't you dare try to interfere!
I couldn't anyway.
I have my orders.
I'm coming to secure
the Nothung model.
Are you there?
I'm so sick of that.
Oh, just you wait.
Oh well...
Too bad.
You got here right in time.
Are you there?
I was before.
However, I'm afraid I'm not now.
You know what they say, a beast
with ten horns hates all women.
It will strip her naked...
...eat her flesh...
Then it'll...
...burn her down.
Sorry about that.
Awesome.
Miss Kariya...
What kind of Fafner is that?
Miss Kariya?
What's the matter?
Wait a sec...
it's an enemy?
Whoever that pilot is,
he sure is quick to move.
Oh no!
Who are you anyway?!
Well?
Answer me or I'll...
Now then...
Don't give me any trouble.
Kanon, I told you to
keep your nose out of this.
You're putting a damper on
things by ruining all my fun.
My duty comes first;
the order to have fun is
only secondary to that.
Tch!
Well, I can see that you're
as stubborn as usual.
Move it!
Get onto the boat.
I never dreamed that
Kazuki was the pilot.
Listen. Kanon.
As your superior...
Next time think of your duty
only after I've had my fun.
And that's an order!
I'm sorry.
That's not part of the rules.
Heh!
You sure are
one inflexible girl.
You're late.
I was waiting.
It's hard to get motivated
when you don't know
if there's gonna be a payoff.
Don't you agree?
My old friend.
Hey!
Aren't you Michio?
Oh now that hurts.
You mean you
didn't recognize me?
It really is quite a pity...
...for the Nothung model to
have ended up like this.
You tricked me, didn't you?!
This whole time, all you wanted
was Fafner, am I right?
Please don't misunderstand me.
I promised that I would
take you to a paradise
and that's exactly
what I'm going to do.
Well, I don't believe you now!
It's all a lie!
You're entitled to form
your own opinions,
but the place we're headed
to is a paradise to me.
You'll just have
to be patient and
sit tight for a while,
until we get there.
So are you satisfied now, Yukie?
I'm afraid that boy
is still a bit too green.
You're right...
But so are you...
Hm?
We know about you
and Kozo Minashiro.
You got a little
too close to him.
But that was just...
Everyone here suspects you.
They're all saying you
might be a double agent.
I'm just doing my job.
So no offense.
I'll make you pay for this!
You have to let me see him!
Then ask him
about me, you'll see!
You'll regret
treating me like this!
You listening to me, Michio?!
Michio Shino!
That woman's so noisy.
It's annoying me.
Looks like she hasn't
changed a single bit
since when I knew
her on the island.
Listen, if she
doesn't quiet down,
you have my permission
to put a gag on her.
At last, the Nothung
model is in my hands.
On behalf of the entire
world I must thank you.
You were a great
help Doctor Bertland.
It'll surely aid
the Arcadian Project...
...so that it may contribute
a little to the human race.
Are you positive about that?
Replacing these two
is the only way I know
of to ensure the
survival of the island.
Besides I've received a
report that the preparations
on Fafner have
already been completed.
I feel somewhat responsible for
dragging Kazuki
into this mess...
...and now these two...
Seems I'm the one
to blame for everything.
Don't think that way.
This incident is not your fault.
And neither is what
Mitsuhiro did in the past.
Everything was supposed
to have been settled.
I somehow think
he still believes
he can change the world.
And he's got it in his mind that
he can achieve this with Fafner.
Mitsuhiro left Tatsumiya Island
in order to go defeat Festum.
However, fighting battles with
nothing to protect
is meaningless.
I guess you could say that
Mitsuhiro's heart was
assimilated by Fafner...
He chose Fafner
over this island...
...and us...
I don't know why
I'm so tired today.
Welcome back, sis.
I just got home.
What's this?
It's the school event calendar.
Looks like we're still having
a graduation ceremony.
We have to, don't we?
We usually do...
Yeah, you're right.
The rumor about Kazuki...
have you heard it?
Oh, Maya...
Hey, Maya, what about me?
Will you remember what I'm like?
Kazuki...
I wonder where
you are right now.
I heard that you
were the last person
Kazuki talked to
before he left the island.
Soshi...
So what was it that
he talked to you about?
Well he...
Did he say he wanted
an escape from fighting?
Or was it...
...maybe he just
wanted an escape from me.
You're wrong.
All he really wanted was for me
to keep on remembering him.
I see.
There's something that I've also
wanted to ask you too.
What about you?
Did Kazuki tell
you anything, Soshi?
No...
nothing...
Well then why...
Then why did you
say that he escaped?
You should have helped him
and discussed more
things with Kazuki!
You're the one
who's running away!
Yeah? Well, you don't even
have a clue about it!
We did...
I thought we did...
I was under the impression that
we understood each other.
And so was Kazuki...
It's obvious that he felt
the same way about you!
We shared our
feelings many times.
Our pain and even our
wounds formed one bond.
But we wanted to understand
ourselves so much...
...that we forgot
about the others.
How could we take it back?
We had no idea.
♪ closing song ♪
The children who
are forced to fight.
The adults who can only watch.
And now...
he is no longer here.
Next on Fafner
episode number 12.
Desperation.
Are you there?