Initiating Fenrir.
Split into two groups.
One will be on standby.
The other will rescue the people
who're still underground.
How are we supposed
to get to them?
Through the ocean.
I'll go!
I'm going to accomplish what
the two of you weren't able to!
Soshi, you should at least check
that there's no
enemy down there!
He's never fought underwater
before, much less in the ocean!
If he gets attacked there...
Kazuki fighting them is going to
be your share of the duties.
I'll get there soon...
And when I do I'll
be ready to fight.
So, did I get it?
Here they come!
Hurry up and
load Gegner's energy.
What?
They're retreating?
What on earth is happening?
It's original shape has
been restored?!
I suppose this spot
here will just have to do.
Does that mean that
we're gonna be all right now?
Don't worry I think
we should be just fine.
Come on, budge!
You old piece of junk!
There's thirteen
minutes until Fenrir starts...
You need to stay hydrated.
But minors aren't allowed
to drink that stuff remember?
Drink it.
It's an order.
Hey--Wait a minute,
it's just water.
All we can do now,
is simply leave our fate in
the hands of providence.
That must be it!
Hurry up, we're gonna
need to jump on it!
Confirming that there
are two on board.
I'm counting on you.
Koyo.
I really did it.
No.
I can't wait.
Come on!
This way!
We've rescued the survivors.
Get out now, Kazuki!
What about Koyo?
Is he all right?
You should worry
about yourself right now!
I'm not gonna leave here without
Koyo, do you understand?
Kazuki!
We simply cannot afford
to lose any more Fafner!
Please understand.
You must try.
But Soshi I just...
Get out of there immediately!
No! Koyo!
I rescued them.
I know I did.
Kazuki.
Koyo! No!
Everything is
going to disappear.
I don't get it.
Why hasn't Fenrir
been activated?!
If I always did things on time,
I'd probably need another
life right about now.
Mark Drei, listen!
You can still make it.
Hurry up!
You don't need to tell me.
I'm going as fast as I can.
I can do this too.
I know that I can.
Tell me...
the people I rescued...
...who were they?
It was Maya and Mr. Mizoguchi.
Maya...
Who is that?
I can't remember.
Why can't I remember?
Koyo.
I wonder...
Is this what it's like
to be assimilated?
I don't feel anything...
I know deep down that
something sad happened...
That's right...
Someone named Shoko...
Rescue is on the way.
Hang in there.
That girl named Shoko...
Who was she anyway...
Koyo.
I've spotted Koyo!
Just hang on, Koyo!
I'm here to rescue you now.
I did it!
I recovered Mark Vier's cockpit!
The island has
completely vanished along
with the Alfenotheles
and Grendel types.
Seventeen members of the
scouting team are
unaccounted for.
And we've also lost one Fafner.
However we were able to
successfully rescue the pilot.
Maya is all right.
You must hurry.
See to the injured once
the convoy returns.
Oh, thank you so much, Sis.
You did a good job today Maya.
I don't know.
The truth is I really
didn't do anything.
And then there's Koyo too...
He's going to be
all right, isn't he?
Let's leave him in
Mom's capable hands.
There's no need to worry.
I'm sure he'll
be showing us that
bright smile of his
again in no time.
Good morning.
I was so glad to hear you
weren't hurt Maya dear.
I can't tell you how
good it is to see you.
Uh, someone told me that
she was here so I came over.
Yes. That's right and she's been
lifting our spirits up everyday.
Regarding this case, I really
don't know what else to say...
What's done has
already been done.
So there's no need
to say anything else.
How pathetic.
He wasn't of any use after all.
He's nothing but a big zero!
Now this just goes to prove it!
Miss Kariya, did you
find the treasure you
were looking for on that island?
Because...
I sure as hell found it.
I must say I'm
surprised that you came
all the way over to my house.
Is this the treasure that
you were talking about?
The unit serving directly under
Miss Kariya had
possession of it.
I'm sure she was going to
give it to the Neo U.N.
So what are you gonna do then?
Be honest for a second,
just how many of 'em
do you think there
are on the island?
I think that you should
hunt 'em all down at once.
We're dealing with humans here.
I'd like to show some prudence.
All right.
If you say so.
I know you wanna
let 'em remain free for now,
but if Kozo were here
he'd get rid of 'em.
I don't have any intention of
fighting against humans.
I know.
That's why I'm here.
Although, if you're
ever in danger,
I will do everything I
can to hunt them down.
Got it, Makabe?
Seriously!
They shouldn't make
us stay after school
if they want us to work.
You know, I noticed
something this morning.
Was the classroom
always this big?
Isn't it just because we have
fewer students right now?
Most of them were gone cuz they
had to work or were injured.
What I don't understand is why
they'd cancel the classes!
Aw man, I don't
understand these!
Hey!
Have you heard
anything new about Koyo?
I heard that he wasn't injured.
So I'm guessing that he's
just sleeping or something.
Do you think you guys could
run a little errand for me?
Maya!
Rina?
Will you be going to CDC today?
No, I'm actually going home.
Oh, I see.
I guess I'll be looking
forward to it next time then.
Huh? You'll be looking
forward to what?
You mean you haven't heard yet?
I'm real sorry,
but I have to go now.
They told me to
get back right away.
I'll see you later.
There you are.
Maya!
I'm really glad that
I finally found you here.
What do you guys want?
It's about Koyo.
I'm partly responsible
for what happened too.
Responsible?
It's not part of my
nature to ask a favor
from anyone but in this
case, it's a little different.
So then what do you want?
I was just wondering if you
would ask your mom for me,
if it was okay if
I went to see Koyo.
Yeah, sure!
I'll ask her for you.
Excuse me!
Would it be okay with you if
all of us went to visit Koyo?
What's the matter?
Did something bad happen?
I think that you should go.
It'll be a good lesson for you.
Hmn?
If you'll excuse me.
You sure about this, Yukie?
They need to know
what happens to people...
...after assimilation.
Hey, aren't you gonna
come and visit Koyo with us?
I'm not going.
Why not?
Is it because you feel partially
responsible for Koyo's injuries?
If that's it, then you should
go visit him even more.
Now, come on, let's go
over there and see him.
Hey. Wait.
Let go of me.
There's no use fighting!
What's up with you?
Do you have a problem
with dogs or something?
Why did you bring a
dog with you here anyway?
Because she's so darn cute.
It's all right, isn't it, Sis?
Huh? Aren't we going
to the medical bloc?
We're almost there.
You're kidding...
right?
I'm sorry...
but that's the reality.
Woof!
Chocolat!
Why did it have to be Koyo?
Why is he the only one
who became like this?
During the battle,
his central nervous
system was assimilated.
Assimilated?
Those are their tactics.
They take away
everything from us.
Is it my fault?
It's because of me...
If only I had gotten to
the cockpit block sooner...
That's...
Then...
it must be my fault too.
The reason that all this
happened was because
Koyo had to come to rescue us.
What happened is not your fault.
So there's no use in
blaming yourself for it.
This is a result of what
Koyo did to himself.
Thanks to him, we lost a Fafner.
So we don't have time
to be all sentimental.
How can you say
something like that!
You were the last person
Koyo was able to talk to.
The only one he had in the end.
Are you really that heartless?
When does the next
foster child arrive?
Unfortunately we cannot
approve a new delivery.
But why not?
Koyo's practically dead already.
As I explained,
Koyo Kasugai is in a coma
due to semi-assimilation.
Therefore he is
considered to still be alive.
According to the
rules and regulations,
I'm unable to grant
you a new foster child.
You can't do this to us!
What are we supposed to do?
We'll forever be
labeled as the ones
who raised the loser
on this island.
We're not going
to stand for this!
The issue at hand
is not your reputation.
May I remind you
that your son is still alive.
What is it that
you think you're doing?
Our reputation is
in ruins because of him.
So isn't it only natural for us
to hope for a new child?
We don't want to be
looked down upon because of
this like how the Hazama
family is now.
Alberecht was
able to recognize
Ms. Hazama's dedication
and achievements.
But unfortunately, it's clear
that the two of you are...
Please, you must
apply to Alberecht
for another child on our behalf.
We promise to raise
an excellent pilot next time.
Please.
Ugh...
It has come to our
attention that you have
been leaking information
to the Neo U.N.
Regardless, you both ended
up raising one hell of a pilot,
and I must thank you.
However...
Your current attitude proves you
are not qualified to be parents!
I want you off of this
island immediately!
I should have done
this a long time ago.
Hey there, Maya.
How's it going?
Mr. Mizoguchi...
I thought this store was...
Starting today, I'm no
longer just a customer.
I've been promoted to owner.
I heard that Mr. and Mrs.
Kasugai left the island.
And it wasn't a way to make them
take the blame for
losing the Fafner.
It had to do
with something else.
Where are they going
to live in this time of war?
What's the use of
answering such a question?
I just need to hear
the answer for myself.
Between a Fafner or us,
when it comes down to it,
which one is more
important to you?
What answer do you
expect me to give?
You're late, Maya.
You have to be sure to be
on time for your shifts.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Looks like you
just lost a point.
What are you doing here?
Why hello again Maya.
How's it going?
There was something
I just couldn't lose.
But in order to protect it,
I would have to sacrifice
the smaller things.
I didn't know it at
the time, but it would
lead to losing
everything in the end.
Yet I had to
keep protecting it...
♪ closing song ♪
I thought he understood.
That's what I believed.
And likewise...
I thought I understood.
But when it came to Kazuki,
I just couldn't...
Next on Fafner
episode number 10,
"Crossing Paths."
Are you there?