♪ opening song ♪
Calm down, Michio!
They're only just kids.
The next time either one of
you shoot one of our own,
I'll treat you like
the enemy out there!
Your actions were
reckless and foolish!
That is quite enough.
I can handle the
rest from here on out.
Hey!
Thanks for being the
bad guy for all of us.
They were actually
trying to protect
someone who'd already been
captured by the enemy.
But the truth be told,
I wish I had a
few more friends
like the two of them.
Yeah.
Don't we all.
I must confess...
To defeat the enemy, I was
going to sacrifice the pilot.
It's okay.
We've survived under those
same principles as well...
But at the same time we've been
searching for a
different way to live.
I never considered that before.
Kazuki.
Have you heard
about Maya's results?
They should be
ready any minute now.
I'm all right...
I've prepared myself for this.
Are you sure Maya?
Thank you for
telling me about it.
And not hiding it from me.
Listen Maya.
Mom will do whatever it
takes to protect all of you.
The better the pilot,
the faster they got assimilated,
at least I believe
that's the way it works.
I'd heard that those from your
generation had it the worst.
Is that true?
Well we really didn't have
any other ways to fight.
They died one after another.
It wasn't 'til after
I came to this island...
...that I even started
thinking about living my life.
That's how it was for me too.
Oh, is that so?
Hey, Kazuki.
We should probably
get going now.
But I thought we
were here to see Maya.
Let's give her
some time with her family.
I've just completed the routine
updates of the
Brunhilde System...
With the core mobile,
we've collected a
ridiculous amount of data.
I wonder if she is
going to remain like
this or eventually return
to Valkyrie's Coagula.
The Commander ordered us to
let her do whatever she wants.
And as long as
Solomon remains quiet,
the core's really no
different from any other
normal human being
like you or me.
Now then!
Shouldn't we be heading
back to the school now?
Don't forget we have that
special meeting to attend today.
I'd like to present my report
on this year's U Project.
I compiled the most appropriate
elements from 1,500 customs.
And I've come up with
the most feasible plan.
I also modified the
Bon festival dance a little.
You may refer to
the manual for details.
And the Spirit Lantern Ceremony
is scheduled at 2000 hrs.
And we'll be using
a low temperature
light source in the
paper lanterns.
They look no
different from candles,
but they'll burn for at least 49
hours at 60 degrees Celsius.
Sakura!
I have a confession
to make to you.
I was prepared
to allow you to die,
in order to defeat the enemy.
I thought I was
gonna to die too.
I didn't have the
courage to blow myself
up in order to save my friends.
I thought I was
prepared to die as
long as it meant I
could avenge my father.
But I was wrong.
I can't tell you
how glad I am to be alive.
I've never felt as
strongly as I do now.
And yet still...
I feel ashamed...
And I don't know
what I should do.
I wonder if I should've died.
If it would have
been better that way.
Don't say that!
I...
I had very specific
orders to kill anyone
who had been
captured by the enemy.
And...
Well I...
I'm glad I didn't
shoot you in the end.
But I would've done
it without hesitation.
And I feel bad for that.
Thanks, Canon.
I really envy you, Sakura.
You know that?
Huh?
Kenji and Mamoru
care so much for you.
They would've done
anything to save you.
No!
It's not like that!
I mean...
Those guys are
a bunch of idiots.
Besides I'm sure they
would've done the same thing
for you too if you'd been
captured by the enemy out there.
You think so?
Yeah, I know so.
Because you're a friend now.
And if there's one thing those
two hate, it's losing a friend.
I'm really their friend?
Oh, there you are.
Hey, there!
What is it?
What do you want?
Uh...
Everyone's about to
make the paper lanterns.
You should come too Canon.
Are you sure?
Hey Canon...
I need to tell you
something, It's about...
You know when you...
what I mean is...
I think Kenji's trying to
apologize for shooting at you.
Yeah.
That's right.
I swear I didn't
mean to hit you.
And anyway, I missed, didn't I?
That's the truth.
Tell her Sakura...
Whatever! Look!
You're an idiot.
How are we supposed
to trust you anyway?
You're such a bad shot.
Ha!
I knew she'd say that!
Please!
You have to believe me...!
Don't worry.
I believe you.
We'll make sure he's
completely immobilized
before the festival begins.
I want to believe that
we can still save him.
But he himself wants
to return to the Festum...
That's why the Coagula
type attacked, to retrieve him.
That's our proof.
Thebon dance?
Tsubaki, this is your
first bon dance, isn't it.
All right!
Don't worry I'll teach you
all the different moves.
Yeah, but you don't even
know how to do a bon dance.
You are looking at the guy
in charge of the songs.
I'm on the Alvis public
entertainment team.
Wow, that's awesome.
Great!
Okay, let's not
get too carried away.
Oh boy!
I'm really hoping that
I get the chance to
dance with Maya
while we are there.
What are you talking about?
That makes no sense.
It's not like it's square
dancing or anything.
It's totally different.
I'm sorry for having
to make you suffer.
But I have to do this.
It's weird. I hardly remembered
any of them when
I was at the Neo U.N.
But now I can see everyone's
face so clearly in my mind.
Promise me
you won't die, Michio.
You never know.
If you were planning
to die anyway,
why'd you bother
coming back here?
Huh?
When I found out that
you had left the island...
I was so sad.
I couldn't stop crying.
Well...
I just won't die then.
I promise you, Yumiko.
The people of this island
seem to respect the dead.
They don't just forget them.
And what about you?
Do you remember
your old master too?
All right, I'm
done with this row.
Good.
Turn on the electricity!
Tamotsu's done a mighty
fine job hanging all those
lanterns, hasn't he?
Will you be having
your own stand too?
Yes, I will.
Those are your very own hand
made ceramics aren't they?
Yeah.
Although I'm not as skilled
at it as Akane of course.
Are you in pain?
Do you want to
give up your life?
Is that it?
I had to think about
that for a long time too.
Choose carefully.
Finally!
There they are!
So, how do I look?
--You look great Maya!
Is something wrong?
Huh?
What did you say Soshi?
I didn't know you
had Yukata, Canon.
Ms. Hazama was the
one who insisted I wear it.
Does it look weird?
No way!
You don't look weird at all!
Don't worry,
You look really good.
Oh that sure is good to know.
Tsubaki didn't come with you?
She had to do something,
so she'll be here later.
Are you going
to be selling those?
Probably not.
Excuse me.
If it's okay.
I would like to buy one.
Gobain!
Uh...
So then I say "Gobain?"
Right.
Just like that.
Is this one of the
Bon festival dances?
That's his own dumb thing.
Stop teaching her your
stupid games, Mamoru!
Aw man.
I was just about to teach her
the ultimate fighting move too.
That one's a seret.
Wait a minute if there's some
kind of ultimate fighting move,
then I want to learn it too.
Forget about it.
You don't need to.
Mamoru and I will
handle the fighting.
You should just go ahead and
take it easy, try and relax.
--Gobain!
And why's that?
Are you implying that I'm
useless or something?
No. I didn't mean
it that way.
I just wanted to--
What is your point?
I'm going to become
even stronger than Kazuki,
and then I'll always
be able to protect you!
You're such an idiot!
What are you trying to say?
You make no sense.
It's not necessary, okay.
Here's a candied apple.
It's the consolation prize.
I think it's rigged.
No one can make that shot.
My turn!
I wanna chance at it.
--Woah, she got it.
What do you want
to do now, little lady?
Do you want to take
it home as your prize?
No.
Can I just have a candied
apple like everyone else?
Sometimes when
I think about Dad...
I think he's laughing
at his coward daughter.
I doubt it.
I'm sure he's smiling,
relieved at what you've become.
I want to thank all of you
for making these lanterns.
I'm sure that Shoko's
feeling very happy right now.
And I wanted to thank
you especially, Canon.
It really means a lot.
Do you think all of our thoughts
and prayers will reach Shoko?
Yeah.
That's right.
If you would please follow me.
Welcome, I'll be right th--
Hello. I'm... back.
Hello.
I've come back.
I've come...
This is certainly a surprise.
Be quiet!
It's too early for
your walk, Chocolat.
Guess I have no choice.
Alright, I'm coming.
That's weird.
I wonder where Kazuki
and Canon could be.
It's not like either one of
them to be late to anything.
Maybe they're like Soshi,
and got here really early.
So there wasn't any problems
with the security system?
No, there wasn't.
And I'd only just finished the
freezing procedure last night.
Koyo!
Where is he?
They were planning on
freezing all of Koyo's cells
so that they could
seal him inside of there.
Don't tell them that.
What?
Seal him?
But somehow he got out and
now he's walking around.
So we'll have
to take care of him
just like we would
any other Festum.
Yes?
What is it?
It's an emergency.
Koyo has just been spotted
in the number seven bloc.
Wait!
Come back!
I think we all have a pretty
good idea about
where Koyo's headed!
Come on! Let's go!
Kazuki.
Koyo...
I have Solomon's response.
It's ambivalent.
But it can't seem
to determine the type.
It doesn't recognize
it as the enemy.
It could be treating
it like a Coagula type.
It's because this Festum was
at one time a human being.
Incoming transmission
from Mr. Mizoguchi.
I'm in the number seven bloc.
I've got a clear view
of Kaname's house.
It looks like
they're trying to negotiate.
Stop acting like such an idiot!
Hurry up and
come out of there now!
Come on out Mamoru!
It isn't safe to be in there.
I know he looks like Koyo,
but he is not the
same person anymore.
Stop saying that!
I don't care if Festum is
Koyo or Koyo is Festum.
Koyo is still Koyo!
Oh crap!
I don't even know what
I'm talking about anymore!
Anyway, the point is,
we're not handing him over!
Come here Soshi!
You should be in
here with all of us.
Oh Sakura...
She's always hated the Festum.
Why is she doing this...
If it's all right with you,
I'd like to borrow something
of yours Mrs. Kaname.
What is it, Chocolat?
Are you trying to
lead me to something?
The assimilation center is
located right at the brain stem.
So you should be able
to destroy it with one shot.
You heard that,
didn't you, Kyosuke?
Yeah, I sure did.
I got a problem though.
If I shoot that kid,
Maya probably won't
ever talk to me again.
We'll never hand
him over to you!
Thank you...
For...
saving me...
I appreciate...
it a lot.
Don't worry about it Koyo.
No big deal.
It's the Ocean...
the Ocean...
The girl Maya...
I saved her.
I saved her, didn't I?
Kazu... ki...
Oh Koyo.
It's...
It's all my fault.
Because I couldn't
save you in time Koyo.
No.
That's okay.
Thank you.
Sakura.
Thanks.
I feel so...
It was you, Koyo. You were the
one responsible for saving Maya.
Thank you so much.
At this rate, it looks
like we may have
to force our way in there.
No one is to open fire on
the children, understand?
Yes Ma'am.
No.
Wait a minute.
Please let me handle it.
Using those wooden swords?
What are you planning on doing?
Fine.
Go ahead.
I'll let you try your way.
Thank you.
Kazuki!
Come out here.
Michio.
Stick to the plan.
Move to the southeast
side of Kaname house.
Roger that.
I want you to fight
against me. Kazuki.
Right.
Are you idiots!
You guys are gonna
get yourselves killed!
Yeah? So?
I guess we are
a bunch of idiots!
And we're not going to
change the way we are
no matter how many
damn times you beat us up!
And if you got assimilated,
we'd do the same thing!
We'd still be protecting you!
Unbelievable.
They really are idiots.
All right.
I'm locked in and
ready to shoot at anytime.
You just need to decide
whether or not you want me to
blow off his head in
front of all those children.
Why would they
send the Megaselion
to fight against Koyo?
Mr. Mizoguchi...
Aw man, that's great.
Just what do you think you're
trying to do there, Missy?
Hey Chocolat!
Hazama...
I appreciate you
protecting Koyo...
Kazuki.
But that isn't him!
Koyo's already gone!
That thing over there
doesn't have any feelings.
If he doesn't feel,
how could he thank us?
So what you're trying to tell me
is that Koyo is still
living inside of that thing?
You're not listening.
Koyo said "thank you" to Sakura.
But he's already
been assimilated.
How could he say "thank you"?
This is impossible!
They even have
the Megaselion out.
It must be a big deal.
I wonder what's going on inside?
Aren't you guys curious too?
There's a Festum inside there.
--Huh?
Well, he was being locked up, so
I decided to help him get free.
But, why would you do that?
I was the same way.
So I knew how he was feeling.
Huh?
What do you mean
you were the same way?
I am what's called a Core type.
And so you see...
Us Core Types are branched
off from the Coagula types.
There are only a few
of us in the whole world.
A blended independent body
of a human and Festum.
Are you there?
Koyo you...
I've got a clear shot!
Should I take it?
No, wait!
It's Chocolat.
Chocolat!
Are you there?
Tell me, are you there?
I left it at home!
Kyosuke do it!
There's no shot!
You'll never hit him.
You're too far.
Tell me, are you there?
Are you, are you there?
I was here before,
but I am not any longer.
No Canon!
What is she trying to do?
No Kazuki!
Just trust her...
Can you do that?
Sho... ko...
Shoko...
She's not here...
...anymore...
Shoko...
Koyo.
I feel so sad.
Shoko is really gone...
Shoko is...
I know.
Shoko's...
She's really...
Shoko is...
Now is my chance...
I've got a good clear
shot of the target again.
There's no need, Kyosuke...
Why not?
We no longer need to worry.
Because Festum don't cry.
You have a point...
Solomon has responded.
It's determined
that it's a slave type.
It's just so hard to believe.
That a Festum would destroy...
its own assimilation abilities.
That means our
ideas are not wrong.
We were on the
right path after all...
...and that path
which leads to the
coexistence of
Festums and humans...
Is just the first step.
But now is not the time.
It is still too early.
And until that day comes...
Good night...
Koyo.
♪ closing song ♪
The present becomes a memory.
We rush to see
our lives blossom.
It's beautiful.
Next on "Fafner"
episode twenty-one.
"Future."
Are you there?