I'm alive.
Kazuki.
Why? He was
such a nice boy.
Sis...
She's crying...
What happened?
Did we lose someone?
♪ opening song ♪
Mamoru...
Mamoru, please answer me.
This can't be!
Oh Mamoru...
We have less than
two weeks until the
final battle at the North Pole.
This test is going
to be the last one
we will run at this base.
I didn't expect you
to be able to handle
the Salvator Model
this well Yukie.
Nice work.
Thank you for
the compliment sir.
I have entrusted you
with my lifelong dream.
The human race's
fate is in your hands.
Yes sir I understand that.
You may begin now.
I'm sorry sir.
The pilot's
bio-graph is abnormal.
We should wait.
Of course it is.
After all, we've
administered her with
sub lethal doses of
the medicine...
We did it to accelerate
the affects the Festum
elements
would have on her.
Yes sir...
but still...
It was the only way for her
to operate this machine.
She knew full well
the consequences.
Her life may not last very long.
We don't have any time to waste.
I've earned the right to pilot.
It makes me so happy.
What's wrong?
Why is there a delay in
releasing the cage?
We are finished.
I am the vessel
through which we have
come to understand this place.
What!
I am the one
through which we have
learned about your emotions.
And we will now take
your newfound power.
He's gone!
Terminate the test now!
I want a complete
shutdown of the Fafner core!
What?
The Festum's doing it.
Disable all the
cockpit functions!
I have no control over it.
It's rejecting all the codes.
You bastard!
You're destroying
all of our work!
No. No.
No!
You are me now.
And we are one.
No... Wait!
You can't do this!
Oh Mitsuhiro...
Help.
This is hate...
I feel it now.
This is hate!
The machine I built myself
couldn't save my only son.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
I think the boss is
calling it quits for good.
Don't be an idiot!
He just needs a little more
time to recover that's all.
You better not slack off.
You wouldn't want the Boss to
yell at you when he gets back.
All right!
We have three hours!
Let's finish changing
all those parts!
Yes sir!
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
Oh. Right.
You've managed to keep
everybody's spirits up.
It's thanks to you that
I don't feel depressed.
You think so.
I didn't do that much .
I'll follow his example.
Chisato...
What are you doing here?
You should still be resting...
There's much to be done here.
And besides, my grief can wait.
Twenty hours has passed
since communication was
cut off between us and
the Siegfried System.
We have no
way of knowing
what the conditions are inside.
But according to the report...
...we do have reason to believe
that he is still breathing.
That's only because they
have no use for the air.
Are they attempting
to assimilate
Soshi while he's alive...?
No.
It's not that.
They lost the core
mid assimilation,
when the main body was
severed from the roots.
So there's still a good chance
that Soshi wasn't harmed.
Prepare to carry out the rescue
operations that were designed by
Ms. Kondo within the next hour.
I just hope it
works, for all our sakes.
Ms. Kondo is an expert in the
field of Festum analysis,
and the person responsible
for the design of Solomon.
We have no options
other than her plan.
The problem though
is Kazuki's body.
Are you really going
to let him do it?
He has agreed to it.
And Kazuki wants this.
Kenji, open up.
Come on, the four of us
are the only ones remaining
who can still fight now.
You must fight.
If for no other reason,
do it for Mamoru and Sakura?
I don't want to die...
I don't want to die!
Hey Kenji...
...haven't you
forgotten something...
Our fight we
haven't settled it yet.
Kenji...
I want to let you know...
...I'm actually feeling
somewhat relieved right now
because the truth is you
probably won't have to fight
if you stay locked
in there like that.
However...
...keep in mind that
it means somebody else
will have to pilot
a Fafner in your place...
Try not to forget that okay.
And if you still
don't want to fight...
It's alright son.
Mom will make
sure to protect you.
I can't bring myself to...
I can't do it.
Yumiko.
Megaselion is
damaged beyond repair.
And I can't pilot one of
the Nothung Models
in my current state.
But you've piloted a
Fafner and fought bravely
up through the
maximum age limit.
Nobody is going
to give you any grief
if you decide to
retire now, Michio.
They need me.
I can't retire.
At least not until the
new pilots are ready.
Cause if I retire now,
I won't be able to justify
all the lives I've taken.
Listen, when the
medicine's effect expires...
...we'll get married.
Michio...
May I have your permission?
Yes. May you
be happy together.
I wish you both the best.
Thank you, I'm so honored.
Now.
Please, let's do this.
Promise me...
...you won't die.
I'm next.
Give me the injection.
So...
how did it go?
Not good.
Looks like we're going to
have to fight without him.
Oh, I see...
Well...
I guess I'll be going now.
I'll go with you.
Maya, you should stay here.
Huh?
You should wait...
for Kazuki.
Once it enters your blood
stream, the medicine will
activate and promote
unification with your Fafner.
And my eye...
can it heal it?
Yes, but temporarily.
However after the medicine
wears off, you may go through
an unusually strong
assimilation process.
I'm prepared.
Please do it.
Do it while I can
still save Soshi...
I was wondering
something Canon...
...were you trying to be
nice to Maya back there?
I wasn't trying anything.
It's just...
I wanted to leave.
'Cuz I never have
anything to say to Kazuki.
Nothing important.
That's not really true.
Hey... Kazuki...
Do you remember...?
...that time when
we played cards at Alvis?
Shoko and Koyo were
there with us too that night.
Yeah...
And I, remember that you were
the one who came and got me.
When I think about the things
that happened back then...
...I feel like I
can understand why
mom and the others were hiding
the island's secret from us.
It was for our own good.
To teach us...
all about peace.
You know what I also think?
I think they didn't want to
rob us of those memories.
What do you mean?
You become afraid of good
memories cuz you know
how easily they can be
taken away from you.
However without those good
memories to hold onto,
all you end up left with
are the horrors of battle.
I think that's why
you push yourself
so hard to keep
fighting, Kazuki.
You know...
I won't forget what you were
like before you were a pilot ...
I could never forget that.
That's why I refuse
to forget about
what things were like before.
When things were fine.
Try to remember those
times, okay Kazuki?
You know, Maya.
You're pretty remarkable.
You take such good care
of people's memories...
That's why...
...whenever I'm with you...
I always feel so relieved.
You really feel that way?
You attempted to do
the same thing against
Kazuki Makabe that
the Festum does.
That is a betrayal
against the human race.
That wound is the punishment.
Justice was served.
You got what you deserved
for your deplorable actions.
You're wrong...
You're mistaken.
This wound...
...made me who I am.
Imagine how you'd feel if you
could stop being yourself.
How relieved you would be.
I don't think like that.
At least not anymore.
But I know the actual truth.
You're jealous of the
Festum aren't you?!
You Festum are capable
of many things now...
I see you know how
to read my mind...
Is that how you try to lure me?
Just because you've learned
to understand people's pain,
you think you
understand everything?
And what about you?
Do you even know what
it's like to feel pain yourself?
After everything you've done...
I'm here...
I'm still here.
Kazuki!
Tsubaki Minashiro has
responded from the Keel Block.
Begin releasing each barrier.
Kazuki.
Follow the orders I give you
and mobilize Mark Sein.
Roger.
After five minutes, bring up the
image on each of the monitors.
Yes, sir.
Disclosing that information
is a double-edged sword
If by any chance Soshi
isn't all right in there...
If we keep things from them
we'll lose the people's trust.
And as of now trust is
the only power we have.
Mark Sein has completely
submerged under water.
Alvis will release
the lower barrier.
We are closing off the Norn
hangar and number seven circuit
located near the Keel Block.
We will fill the decompression
chamber with seawater
and create a path
for the Mark Sein.
Is that water?
That's Urd's Well...
It's a type of liquid
computer that was
once used to analyze the MIR.
Its Solomon's master
server now and it tells us
when the enemies
are approaching.
If that's a computer,
is it okay to step on it?
Yes. You can
swim through it too.
Welcome...
...to where the island's
future will be determined.
I summoned you here to the
coagula one time before.
Do you remember that?
Yeah.
That was when you told me that
I should fight with Soshi.
At least that's what I sensed.
Yes, that's right, Kazuki.
And I thank you
for listening to me.
Where is he?
Is he okay?
He's right there. Inside.
Listen carefully, Kazuki.
That Festum that you're looking
at no longer possesses a core.
We've asked Tsubaki
to become its core.
Then she will lead the
Festum to self-destruction
with use of your Mark Sein.
In order to do this,
Tsubaki is going to have to
integrate with your Fafner.
Do not fight her existence.
Got it.
The integration was instant...
Just as I expected.
Are both of you
all right in there?
Now assimilate only
with the surface units
and approach the
opponent cautiously.
If you try to tear them off,
you will run the risk of
putting Soshi in danger.
Okay, got it.
Soshi...
Now I am you...
do you see?
And you are...
you are me...
Kazuki...
is that you?
Soshi!
Soshi, it's me.
Communication with the
system has been recovered.
So then he's okay.
Projecting an image from
the Siegfried's interior!
He's still alive!
Thank goodness!
Kazuki...
How many hours has it been...
since the last battle?
Twenty-one hours.
It's been that long?
My sense of time is dulling.
So I can't really tell.
Soshi, are you hurt at all?
I don't know...
The sense of
pain that I'm feeling...
...seems to be fading away.
Kazuki...
Are you really there?
Yeah I'm here!
I'm right here with you Soshi!
I'll get you out of there soon.
Kazuki.
Don't be too eager!
Leave it to Tsubaki's will.
Alright...
Sollomon is responding!
Move to Vaffe Larden!
Babalon, Mark Sieben,
Mark Eins, stand by to take off.
On my way.
I'll teach them that this
battle is far from over yet.
Good, I can do this.
I can still fight.
Canon and I will distract
the enemy in the front.
Maya, you get back and try to
prevent the enemy from landing.
You got it!
During battle, we can only
communicate with the CDC.
Good luck everyone!
The object is on approach
from a heading of 10 o'clock.
It's speed is...
M-Mach seven!
That's some amazing speed.
Was it assimilated by the enemy?
We identified it.
According to its I.D. code,
it's a Neo U.N. patrol plane.
What about Denial?
Do we have time for it?
There's no time.
Its about to hit the
number one Welle Shield.
It's broken through
both the number one
and number two Welle Shields.
It's going to
crash on the coast.
Here it comes!
Wait, that's the...
...Salvator Model!
So the enemy
got its hands on it...
What's that?
What's it doing?
What just...?
Is this...?
...an integration?
It's the machine code...
Mark... Nicht...
Is Festum trying
to integrate with it?
It's attempting to uproot all
the power we've gained!
Attention all pilots,
intercept it!
Take this, you bastard!
Canon!
Take this!
No Canon!
Retreat!
There's not enough time!
Canon! Michio!
The Festum is growing rapidly.
It's penetrating the entire
island from the Keel Block on.
All pilots standby!
I want all the Fafners
released from the hangers!
We can't let the
enemy have them!
No!
The Festum's roots have
penetrated the Main Bloc.
What?
Take cover!
Kazuki, block the enemy's power!
It's taking over the system!
Hurry!
Ayano!
There's nothing you can do!
Evacuate island residents
to the southeast.
Prepare to disengage N bloc.
Mrs. Kodate!
No!
Ms. Hazama!
Look out!
Please stop this...
You're wrong...
Humans are not
only filled with hatred...
Please!
Try to understand!
Damn!
CDC, do you read me?
Separate the block right now!
Disengage the N bloc.
Do it now!
Damn you.
I won't let you escape me...
Hold on... where do
you think you're going?
I won't let you...
My Yumiko...
...is over there...
Initiating Fenrir...
I promised her
I'd return alive...
And I keep my word.
Ejecting cockpit bloc...
Activating Fenrir.
♪ closing song ♪
Kazu... ki...
Soshi!
Soshi! Soshi!!
Soshi! Soshi!! Soshi!!
The amount of time we are given.
The challenges we are given.
The desire to understand.
Next on Fafner episode
number twenty-four.
"MIR."
Are you there?