♪ opening song ♪
It seems that
Kazuki's coming back
as quickly as he
left us, doesn't it?
We've just received
authorization to land.
Look at that.
Not a single enemy to be found.
Kazuki...
He did it, didn't he?
Even though he was so worn out.
One can do of a
lot for love, right?
In other words, thanks to you,
our island is now safe.
Not really.
Like always I wasn't
very much help.
No need to be so humble.
You took off with a
primary military apparatus,
leaking this island's
secret to the world.
With the consensus of Alvis,
you could be deported.
You will remain here until they
determine your punishment.
Mr. Mizoguchi told
me all about Mom.
You should know Dad.
It wasn't your fault.
Apologize when
you pay respects to her.
Don't ever leave without
saying anything again.
How you can lock your own son up
in a mental ward
like that is beyond me.
It was Dr. Tohmi's
recommendation.
So the kid was a bit impulsive.
It doesn't mean
he's off his rocker.
Um... What's going to
happen to Kazuki now?
Don't you worry about it.
By the way, don't you have
something to give to this guy?
Oh...
Mr. Yoji Hino wanted
you to have this.
And Yoji?
I'm afraid that he's gone...
He's gone a along
with all those Festum.
I see...
You've really been
a great help to us, Maya.
And I thank you.
No...
I...
Hello Soshi.
How do you do?
I had a hard time
putting on these clothes.
And I still can't move
my arms very will in them yet.
I got out of the Coagula.
Do you want to know why?
If that is your "will"
then I will respect that.
I'll do whatever
I can to support you.
Not will...
Actually...
it's my dream.
Your dream?
I wanted to see the
world with my own eyes,
and touch it with
my own two hands...
And now my dream
has finally come true.
Just tell me what
you want and I will
do everything thing that I can.
I want to live with
everyone else in the family.
There's no need to worry.
It's just a selfish
wish of mine.
Feel free to act
like a big brother
and tell me that
it's just not possible.
I don't mind at all.
Right.
It's called synchronicity.
Anytime we humans
acquire a new technology,
the Festum assimilate the
information to use against us.
We know that the
enemy is getting stronger.
But do we know for a fact that
it's all because of the island?
The Festom are using
Tatsumiya Island as a
conduit to the
human race's powers.
All right.
Well then why can't
we just use the island to
detect the enemy's
power as well?
You don't have any intention
of giving up the island do you?
Of course not.
And what is
your intention, Barnes?
This submarine
is scheduled to leave
the island tomorrow morning.
However the other one
will be staying.
What for?
Are you going to
use the sub as a shield?
I guarantee we
won't launch an attack.
I'm sorry but I
just can't trust you.
Hmph.
This conversation is over.
We will return both
of them to you unharmed.
That's a promise.
Don't you realize
that all you're
doing is putting
yourself in danger?
How are you?
It's been a long time.
This is quite a surprise...
Good to see you, Michio.
If you don't mind...
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
Your new Fafner model...
Would you mind telling me
who was piloting it earlier?
It was Kazuki.
You mean that kid?
So then you know who he is?
I know that he's a coward.
He called off
an attack mid-battle.
Called off an attack?
He did that?
I see...
Well then I must
remember to praise him.
Soshi.
Hello Maya.
How do you do?
Huh?
Hey, is Chizuru inside?
Goodbye Soshi.
See you later.
Who is that girl?
Tsubaki Minashiro...
and she happens to be my sister.
You have a sister?
I never knew.
Due to personal reasons she was
being kept at
a special facility.
Oh I see.
Hey, did you ever get
a chance to talk to Kazuki?
That has nothing to do with you.
But you promised me
you would, remember?
You're not a pilot, okay?
So just keep
your nose out of this!
I already know that...
I haven't forgotten.
It's just...
I really want everyone
to get along that's all.
Every single
time someone's gone,
we always end up fighting...
Please Soshi, will you
try and talk to Kazuki for me?
Oh, Soshi.
This here is my room.
Come in.
So then...
Does this mean that
you live inside of Alvis?
It makes going on
missions more convenient.
You can sit if you want.
Now.
Why don't we talk.
What did you want to talk about?
It's so empty.
This room doesn't
have anything in it.
No, look!
I have a bed over there.
I have a table and a sofa.
I also have a desk too.
And then there's that
picture hanging on the wall.
Is that...
your only picture?
And look.
I have my very own
small private bathroom.
Soshi. Are you
sick or something?
Don't touch anything!
These are pills I take.
They're to suppress flashbacks.
What kind of flashbacks?
Once in a while after the
battles have already ended...
I can still feel the pain that
you pilots felt while
you were fighting.
So these...
are like painkillers.
Soshi.
Wait! I haven't finished
showing you everything yet!
This is the vending machine.
It's located approximately 11
steps from the front of my room.
So it's very convenient.
You know something?
You're a bit strange,
aren't you?
I'm the only one...
missing from here.
I was the one
who took this picture...
So I guess it make sense.
If I were in this?
Where would I belong?
I'm surprised that you
came here to talk to me.
I'm actually here to complain.
Is this about locking
you up in that room?
Or could it be about
me leaving the island
back then without so much as
saying a word
to you before I left?
You having a reunion
that I can join?
What are you doing here?
Out of all those kids
who were our classmates?
How many of them
can you remember?
Because of all
the gene assimilation
all of them died. One by one...
And in the end the only ones
who are still alive
are the three of us.
After all, we were nothing
more than a few guinea pigs.
They needed to use us in order
to preserve their
future generations.
But I still don't
understand what this
has to do with Neo U.N.
The more a person pilots Fafner,
the more their
chromosomes mutate,
bringing them
ever closer to death.
Though it's possible
for the mutation
to increase one's
lifespan as well.
Or at least that's
what Dad told me.
But in the end,
his research was useless.
Hold on a minute.
So then how come you...?
Long ago,
I once knew a girl who's
dream was to
become an singing idol.
But I just couldn't bear
the thought of her growing sick,
I really wanted to save her.
Before I knew it,
I was fighting,
far away from the island.
If you want me to,
I can let you out of here.
It's okay...
...don't worry about it,
my Dad told me to stay here.
Oh, I see.
Hey.
Thanks for the drink.
Yeah
I'll see you then.
Oh, right.
Goodnight Soshi.
I see...
So I have three
months at the most...
I don't see that as a bad thing.
I'll be glad to live that long.
Oh Tsubaki...
I made the decision that
I wanted to live my own life...
I know it means that
someday it'll come to an end.
If I had chosen the same path as
the Festum things
would be different...
I wouldn't have
even wanted to be alive.
At least that's how
I would've felt.
Your body feels so warm.
it's really nice.
I could care less
for the island that
created me to
be their guinea pig.
It doesn't matter, does it?
If you're one of
the lucky ones, you die.
And if not, you
have to deal with surviving.
No...
that's backwards.
Everything becomes
backwards eventually.
That's just how it is.
Yeah?
Well, then I guess that island
must have some luck on its side.
Triple Six!
What is it?
I wanted to let
you know that I am
going to be
staying on the island.
I have no choice then.
It looks like I'll
be staying here too.
No, you can't!
Huh?
You're leaving... In fact
you're shipping out tomorrow.
Those are the Colonel's orders.
Yeah yeah.
If I hafta go,
it's better to do it asap.
This new model is the product of
Mitsuhiro and Yoji's research.
Those two must
have created this Fafner
to battle against the
MIR of the North Pole.
Kozo Minashiro was
preparing for that as well.
But we were attacked
by Festum before we
were fully prepared
to fight against them.
Has it really been
seven years already?
That's how long it's
been since the children
received the message
from the enemy?
And are these Fafner to be our
weapons in the final battle?
I've spent time with Tsubaki
Minashiro and she speaks
as if she and the machine
are one and the same.
What?
Tsubaki Minashiro...
Does that mean
she's gained free will?
Yes and she still maintains the
ability to control
the whole island.
What do you mean
when you say that she
and the machine
are one and the same?
Even when it was assimilated,
Mark Sein remained
as its own entity.
Just like Tsubaki Minashiro
who's still the core
of the island yet
human at the same time.
But how could
a Fafner just suddenly
start assimilating
things like that?
Because the entire
thing melted away.
I guess it changed
into something different.
This is simply unheard of, the
spontaneous rebirth of the core.
Dr. Nishio.
Do a complete diagnostic.
Understood.
It's like having a
whole new CDC isn't it.
It's a parallel all-in-one room
called Arthur's Room.
Believe it or not, this
place was actually built first.
Since it has
everything in one place,
it was too big of a
load on our systems,
which is why we
never used it before.
But now that the
core's walking around,
we're able to
use the system to link
and intercept as
many things as we want.
Then that means
this is even more effective
than our old CDC, doesn't it?
Good morning.
--Good morning to you sir.
Status report.
The Neo U.N. vessel
Midlight is heading northwest.
There's been no
suspicious activity thus far.
The vessel should be exiting the
Number One Welle shield shortly.
So it's a mirrored
camouflage system.
To the only home I ever knew.
Farewell.
And soon it will
disappear for good...
...and everything else
along with it,
including that girl Kanon.
I've begun executing the plan.
Protect the ship until
the explosion goes off.
Roger that.
It's finally time...
My chance to truly disappear.
They'll sacrifice the
crew just to blow them up?
Are you serious?
The Colonel plans to use
Fenrir and strategic missiles.
He's serious about
wiping out the island.
Why now?
And how long have you...?
If you take off to
try and save them.
I'm sure that the
Colonel won't hesitate
to attack Megaselion as well.
But I've set up a little device.
To make sure that won't happen.
I am no longer a
member of the Neo U.N.!
Megaselion has launched
without authorization!
He did come
from the island after all...
We'll just let him
join his father then.
There's something wrong with
the weapon control system.
We can't fire!
How could that be?
Sorry boys.
But information systems are
my specialty you know.
Alvis!
Come in, Alvis!
This is Megaselion.
It's Hino!
Sir, its Michio.
The island is in danger!
The remaining submarine is
going to use Fenrir to attack.
What?
Are you sure?
Did you hear what
he just said, Kyosuke?
And can you confirm any of it?
Your suspicions are correct.
The Fenrir warning system
has been completely destroyed.
It's safe to say
that no one in the
crew knew anything
about it either.
I'll see what I
can do from here.
They've figured us out.
Sacrificing their own
so that they can blow
all of us up is just plain
old tacky if you ask me.
Fenrir control has been switched
over to the
machine I.D.ed J-O17.
Damnit!
Fumihiko.
An enemy Fafner
has taken control of Fenrir.
Kazuki!
We need you to fight.
Launch an attack
in the Mark Sein.
We could contact
the Belicur for assistance.
They're currently
deployed in the Pacific.
Do it!
On behalf of the future
of the human race,
I want that island destroyed!
Their guided missiles are
headed straight for the island.
Impact in ten minutes.
The Welle Shield is almost...
No!
Don't close the shield!
If that submarine explodes
within our barrier,
it'll take the island with it.
You work on that sub.
I'll take care of the missiles.
What?
Canon is honest at heart...
Please, give her a chance
to change her mind.
Don't worry, I will.
Canon!
I need to talk to you.
About what.
Huh?
Oh uh...
I just wanted to
ask you something.
What do you mean by "something"?
Well uh...
I was wondering...
where is it you come from?
Moldova base.
No, uh, that isn't what I meant.
What I meant was,
where's your hometown?
It was a place called Dublin
until about four years ago.
But it no longer exists.
Dublin?
Let's see...
That was in Germany, right?
No it was in Ireland...
Is this your way
of making fun of me?
No, not at all.
I'm not making fun.
I swear!
Our little talk is over.
No!
Please wait.
Um...
what about your family?
I used to have one.
They don't exist anymore.
What about your friends?
I don't have any, the
festum assimilated them.
One last thing.
Why are you doing this?
No reason.
I'm just following orders.
An order?
You're telling me you didn't
have a choice in the matter?
Does that mean
you'll do anything
as long as you are ordered to?
That's right.
Will you listen to yourself?
It's like you've
lost your own identity.
I was like you.
But now I don't exist either.
You're simply the worst.
You know that?
What does that mean?
Look at the island.
A lot of people live there.
And not only that,
so many of them
mean a great deal to me.
That doesn't have
anything to do with me!
Of course it doesn't!
Because they don't exist to you.
And the reason for that is...
Because you
don't think you exist.
When you were
given this order...
...you were grateful,
you were relieved, weren't you?
Cuz... You're incapable of
making your own decisions!
You've been waiting so
long for this order.
Because all this time,
you've wanted disappear, right?
Is that Michio in there?
Hey thats...
That you, Triple Six?
Damn!
Can I not make this
thing fly any faster?
Thanks for the assist, guys.
Why are you
doing this, Triple Six?
Who gave you the order.
You don't understand
at all, do you?!
Huh?
Don't come closer!
When I'm this far from you...
I can't even see your face!
You're not lost.
You're still
inside there, aren't you?
I'll give you three minutes.
If you want to turn that
switch on, then go right ahead!
Kazuki!
What is this?
Do you know
something that we don't?
If you can't make your
decision after three minutes...
Then I'll make
you disappear.
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
I'll disappear?
Don't do it!
Fafner won't be able to contain
all of Fenrir's energy.
She can't do it.
She can't make a decision.
What?
The RV's are reentering
the atmosphere!
What is it you're trying to do?
I could just hit that
switch any time I want.
If that's your decision,
then do it...
And I'll disappear with you.
Until then...
We have time.
We can talk.
You want to talk?
What should we talk about?
Why are you asking me that.
Canon...
You're name.
What about that?
What does Canon mean?
Well...
It's a type of
musical composition.
Really?
What kind?
It's a melody...
that's born gradually...
...through repetition...
That's what I
was told at least...
By my mom.
What do you want from me?
What exactly do
you expect me to do here?
Make your own decision, Canon!
You can do it!
You want me to...
...make a decision?
Here they come!
Damn you!
Ten seconds left!
You have to make your decision!
Do you hear me?
I...
It's just...
I don't know...
You're there!
You exist!
Now choose it!
Canon!
Why'd I...?
I did it.
The Fenrir control systems.
I turned them off.
But why?
It's your fault!
You said you were going
to make me disappear!
You liar!
Why didn't you do it!
It was only if you
didn't make a decision.
You remember?
But you did it.
You made an own choice.
Wait.
Don't go.
You actually listened to me.
You listened to me.
You listened to my story.
Why...
did you come back?
I've wanted to come back...
for a long time now.
You know something...
I've fought against
just about everything,
not to mention Festum.
I've fought men.
Some of them were even
the exact same age as me...
And each and every time...
I've wanted to come back.
But somehow I
just couldn't do it.
You idiot!
Why couldn't you just
swallow your pride?!
You'd been gone for so long.
You should've come back sooner.
You're such an idiot!
We really ought
to be taking her into
custody now, but it's your call.
I think she needs
some time to herself.
I knew you were gonna say that.
♪ closing song ♪
Life goes back to normal.
Splashing in waves...
and friends smiling...
And the return
of my father brings
about something unexpected.
Next on "Fafner"
episode number eighteen.
"Memory."
Are you there?