♪ opening song ♪
Soshi!
Give us back Soshi!
Give him back!
Soshi!
But why...?
Why is it that I'm here...
What reason?
I see... Now that I have free
will the MIR has rejected me.
I must go then.
With the repair work we've been
doing for the past six days,
70% of the CDC's functions are
expected to be back online soon.
However, most of the
N Bloc is still in ruins...
But the restoration
that's underway of the
main facilities and
hangars is going smoothly.
I see...
What if we decide to join
the Neo U.N.'s
attack operations?
Well...
Regarding the installation of
the Fafner's remote system...
As predicted the
adjustments aren't going well.
So... you dragged
an old woman all the way
out here to tell me this.
Tamotsu.
Fumihiko...
the new system adjustments...
Let me take care of it.
I beg you!
I am going to make
those damn Festum suffer!
Just like they made
Mamoru and Chisato suffer!
Tamotsu!
Children are not tools.
You cannot use them
to seek your revenge.
It's my fault that they're gone.
Chisato...
and Ippei too...
It's because...
I wasn't there...
He promised me.
He said he wouldn't die.
He said he would keep his
promise no matter what.
Oh Yumiko...
Hey there Kenji...
How are you?
They wanted me to come
over here and get you...
If you still don't want
to fight, we all understand.
I'm going to try my
best to do whatever
your mother would have wanted.
It shoulda been me...
I was too scared...
And that's why...
Before, whenever I was
climbing this mountain,
I felt like I was climbing
on my dad's back.
But now...
I just don't feel that
way about it anymore.
I heard my dad might have died,
but it doesn't seem real to me.
I feel like... maybe I should
stop coming here to climb.
I see...
And you, Kazuki?
Why do you like to come here?
It's not so much me...
but my mom had liked it here.
Is it true there's another
enemy at North Pole?
That's what I'm
going to find out.
You don't have to go...
You could just
stay here on the island.
Actually... do you think you
could do that Maya?
If you're gonna leave, Kazuki,
then I want to go too.
Snow...?
Sorry... I just thought you
might be getting cold..
Oh right.
Thanks a lot.
It feels so warm.
Listen to me Maya,
I want you to live on, okay?
After everything, I don't know
what to say to Kazuki.
What do I do Michio?
Hey there!
Hi Kenji... Is he going
to stay with you Mrs. Kaname?
That's right.
I've already discussed it with
Kenji and he's agreed to it.
Kenji.
You go ahead and stay there.
No one else has to die...
not ever again.
Kazuki! Please... you...
You have to fight me!
What is all this?
Kenji! You can't.
He hasn't even recovered yet.
We received a message
from a Neo U.N. patrol plane.
They want to know if we're
joining their operations.
Tell them we'll join
and make sure they
give us the operation code.
Yes, sir!
Then does this mean, I can
ride a Nothung Model now?
That's right.
The alien elements you injected
in your body have stabilized.
I'm so glad.
Mom...
There's something I would
like you to check out for me.
Don't do it Fumihiko.
Don't join their operation.
The enemy is trying to take
this fight to a global scale.
It turns out
Mitsuhiro was right.
We don't have any
other choice but to fight.
Who cares!
We can still shield ourselves
and protect all of our children.
But Kazuki's already
planning to join their fight.
In order to avenge Soshi,
he'll do it alone if he has to.
He won't live very much longer.
And he can't wait for
Dr. Tohmi's research.
You can use what
little time he has
left to do many other things!
What would Akane have wanted?
What do you think she would
say to you if she were here?
I'm doing the best I can.
I don't know any other way!
We can't even provide them with
a reason to come back alive...
...with a reason to live.
It's not over yet!
Damnit!
Kazuki!
Don't worry, he's fine.
I'm sure Sakura
would be surprised
if she saw that.
You know, she once told me...
...that she could never be
interested in a weak man.
You see...
Sakura was looking for the same
type of man that her father was.
Kazuki, do you think
I'll ever be able to
become as brave as Mamoru was?
Yeah of course.
I know you can.
This time...
I'm going with you!
The target is on a
direct course for the island.
We know it's a Sphinx-type,
but there's a high
probability it's a new kind.
We're maintaining
the cloaking device
and ready to deploy
the Welle Shield.
Have the pilots be on standby!
Welle Shield at maximum power!
Once we make contact
with the enemy, separate the
eastern part of Takeru
Island and start Fenrir.
Those bastards
can have that part.
Additional enemy
combatants sighted
at a heading of two o'clock.
Then that first one
was just a decoy?
Commander!
The new target is
flying directly toward
the earlier one that appeared.
Why would it do that?
I'm receiving an image.
Projecting on the main monitor.
Uh...
what is that?
I don't believe it.
The Festum are
fighting each other.
That thing destroyed
the core with one blow.
Amazing...
The remaining Festum
has disappeared.
We're not even picking
up any trace elements.
The Welle Shield is coming down,
but I haven't done anything.
But how?
Incoming message.
It's in Japanese.
What is going on?
What does it say?!
Oh... right!
More of them
are headed your way.
I need to talk to you.
I will wait at the mountain.
Akane Makabe.
It's from Akane?
But how?
It can't be...
Welcome back.
There is nothing
biologically that
connects me to
this place anymore.
However, I believe I was led
here by my previous memories.
So you really do understand what
it's like to have
human memories.
I knew that you would.
I want you to meet
someone. He's on his way.
All right.
I'm here.
What do you want, Festum?
What are you up to?
I find it impossible
to believe that
Festum would fight each other.
Solomon has determined
that it is a master-type.
It's a Master-type.
A kind of Festum that's...
...human-shaped.
Are you saying that all Festum
are just parts of the whole?
If you consider
the situation carefully,
you will see
that it is possible.
However, you cannot predict what
they will potentially become.
I don't quite understand?
It is extremely rare for us to
develop individual personalities
as a result of
assimilating with humans.
They usually become immediately
homogenized into the collective.
But the entity that had
been Akane Makabe
managed to keep forming
its own resonant core.
The change was very slight.
And it took almost
ten years for it to be able
to have any influence
on the collective.
Actually, we only developed the
concept you humans call time
because of the many factors
that she exposed us to.
To us, time was like gravity.
It's a natural part of the
universe that we hardly notice.
But the entity that was
previously known as Akane Makabe
connected with many cores
and we have in turn,
formed a reality on which
time is the ultimate plane.
Why'd it only happen with her?
How many millions of other
people have been victimized?
We are currently
still searching for the
answer to that
question ourselves.
The most basic explanation
we've come up with
is that it is
"a phenomenon."
So in other words...
It means that Akane
Makabe herself
had hoped to be assimilated.
I dare you to say it again.
Do not misunderstand.
She did not seek for it to be
and it was of course unexpected.
But from the moment
she made contact with us...
...she whole-heartedly welcomed
us and she blessed us.
What do you mean by blessed?
That is the only word that can
most closely describe the
experience that occurs on
our level of existence.
The assimilation and
destruction of entities are a
blessing to those who
exist in our space.
However, your Akane Makabe
reversed the effect.
Reversed it?
And what does that mean?!
She is the first of the
human entities to understand us.
Our latest results show that
the Festum are entirely
composed of a silicon
type of substance.
That's the most abundant
element that exists in space.
In other words,
it's sort of like they're soil.
So, while Minashiro and the
others are out there busting
their buts analyzing the MIR,
you're trying to better
understand the Festum by getting
your hands a little dirty?
It's just that...
I really wish I could
communicate with them.
I'd like you to
do this Fumihiko.
Try putting your
hands in the soil.
Who knows, someday
you may be able
to understand the
Festums' feelings.
Why...
why did you come here?
Because
I need a favor,
but it is something that only
one of your kind can perform.
A favor?
The core which is of greatest
importance and relation to me
is the core
of Akane Makabe
and the key to our
unanswered questions.
However because of that,
the North Pole MIR has
been holding it captive.
It is facing extinction and so
I want you to go rescue it.
Are you saying you're willing to
eliminate your colleagues?
Originally, we existed
as one, as a whole.
To put it in other words,
we were not separate...
Therefore neither diversion nor
mutual extinction were possible.
But Akane Makabe
changed things for
us and gave us all one
universal wound.
One wound?
Everything began the
moment it was clear
that Akane Makabe understood us.
She blessed us,
acknowledging us when
we weren't supposed to
exist anywhere.
As a result,
it antagonized the MIR
and I was made a solitary being.
Wait a minute.
So you exist as an
individual now?
That's right.
I stand before you
now as the entity
who has inherited
Akane Makabe's will.
However, without your help.
I soon will once
again no longer exist.
Once the MIR succeeds in
extinguishing the core,
it will be as it was
in the beginning.
And Akane...?
Is she still communicating
with the other Festum?
The message she has
communicated has multiplied
and continues to resonate.
Before the human race and
the MIR annihilate each other,
I would like for you
to connect my core.
I'm sure I will be
able to give you all
the resources that
you will need.
What can a Festum
possibly give us?
Unless you're planning
on returning all the
innocent lives that
you took away?
I cannot.
That is impossible.
Even we cannot turn back time.
However, in the future
where the effects
of time have yet to occur.
We can still
share mutual desires.
Go ahead and show them the data.
I'm sure they will
then understand.
They do not share the concepts
we have of the data.
It's all right. I have faith
that you'll be able to do it.
We are receiving enormous
amounts of incoming data.
It's too much for us to save.
Send it to the main server!
It is automatically doing that!
What exactly is happening here?
This is it?
This is how to defend
ourselves against the Festum?
It's Yoji.
Instead of defeating as many
of the enemy as possible,
we should be trying to
prolong the lives of soldiers.
Yoji Hino designed
this strategy.
It's a human body combined
with that of the Festum.
The genetic and
psychological patterns...
...including the
internal organs...
Is it really you?
Are you co-existing
with the Festum Akane?
That is everything that I can
hand over to you for right now.
Most of the answers they seek
are still locked up,
guarded inside the MIR.
It's all right.
It should be enough to make
everyone understand.
Right, Fumihiko?
If we can rescue
this core for you,
does this mean our
pilots will be saved?
The assimilation of
their corporeal bodies
is merely the first step.
The resonant core of Akane
Makabe has been able to
produce many answers
that go beyond that.
But how are we going
to make it through that
battlefield to even
reach the MIR?
I have already provided you
with the optimum method.
Follow it and
proceed to the MIR.
After that, my core will lead
you the rest of the way.
If everything goes well,
you will be able to retrieve
one thing that has been
taken away from you.
And what is that?
You'll be able to retrieve the
thing you call the
Siegfried System.
What?
The MIR believed
that by taking it
we could steal all
of your power.
However we are unable to use it.
And that is the reason why
the MIR is still keeping the
one human who can
operate it alive.
Do you mean the person
who is in the system itself?
That's right.
A human being named
Soshi Minashiro.
Soshi...
That means he's alive.
They're here.
They have come this time
to destroy both you and I.
What?
We're detecting
numerous gravity shifts!
Ten...
twenty...
It's still increasing...
Send the children of Alvis to
the MIR immediately.
We will do our best
to protect this island.
We?
Here he comes.
Koyo.
Were you the one who
ordered him to help you?
He was the one who chose
to fight alongside other
beings that were
similar to himself.
Thank... you...
...all of you.
--Koyo!
Koyo.
Goodbye everybody.
Thank you Koyo.
I'll accept your offer,
but only for the sake
of those on this island.
That is reason enough.
I am sure we will both evolve
from this experience.
Tell me... Why did
you use Akane's name?
Because it would have provided
me with the optimum results.
Actually...
I wanted to make sure
I would be able to see you.
That's right...
...to tell you something
special in person.
Thank you so
much Fumihiko.
For raising Kazuki.
Status report!
The gravitational shifts
have all stabilized.
This will lessen the
effects of assimilation.
We learned
of it from Akane.
When we administered
this to Sakura,
it began to work
almost immediately.
We were able to divide the
Siegfried System prototype
into four and put
them in each Fafner.
Therefore, everyone should
be able to cross over
and communicate
directly with each other.
And thanks to the new
data that the master-type
provided us with,
we've resolved any fears
that we had of
overloading the pilots.
Every single one of us owes
Akane Makabe our
deepest gratitude.
This setup does have two
important drawbacks though.
The first being
that every pilot will
sensorially experience
each other's pain.
Soshi has been experiencing
each of our pains
for a long time.
If he can do it then we can too.
The second is that if
we lose a single Fafner,
the system will be compromised.
Which means no one can die.
Understood?
We aren't going there to die.
We're all going
to come back alive.
Then I will go ahead and verify
each unit with their pilot.
Mark Sein, Kazuki Makabe.
Roger.
Mark Acht, Kenji Kondo.
Roger!
Mark Sieben, Maya Tohmi.
Roger.
Mark Drei, Canon Memphis.
I'm piloting, Sakura's Fafner?
That's right.
You have ten hours to make
any adjustments needed.
Understood sir!
The objective of the attack
on the North Pole MIR,
is to make contact
with the specified core,
and obtain the rest of the data.
We will also be
recovering Soshi Minashiro.
These are the two
objectives of this operation.
So what are we
calling this operation?
The Neo U.N.'s been calling
their operation Heaven's Door,
since in order for it to
succeed it demands that
they break through to
the outer atmosphere.
Well that's a bad omen.
Since we'll be flying our team
there in the Devil Rey.
Why don't we just call it
something like "sky"?
On that day, the
weather conditions are
expected to be good up there.
In that case, how
about we name it "Azure"?
Why Azure?
What does "azure" mean?
It means a sky
that's big and blue.
That's a cool name!
Well then that's that.
We will commence
with Operation Azure
in exactly sixteen
hours from now.
I'll be waiting for you
at the hanger, okay?
Um...
Yes?
What is it?
If I manage to
come back alive...
...do you think that...
I could call you Mom?
Of course.
And I'll be awaiting
your return, Canon. Don't worry.
Sis, is it really true?
It is.
It's the first natural
conception in thirty years.
So then it's Michio's.
A child.
So he managed to
keep his promise to me...
...in the end.
I'd like you to show my child
that there is still hope yet.
All is not lost.
It can still have a future.
Dad, if you wouldn't
mind I'd like you to
teach me something
when I get back?
Yes... What is it?
I'd like to learn
how to work with
soil or perhaps make pottery.
Sure. I'd be happy to
teach you those things.
You know I learned
them from your mother.
Thanks a lot...
dad.
♪ closing song ♪
Okay you guys,
give me your arms.
Why?
Here.
Alright, you're next Kenji.
Is this like some kind of spell?
Hey wait...
...those are Tatsumiya
Island's coordinates.
That's right.
It symbolizes the promise
we made to come back.
Do you want it too?
Yeah, sure.
Go ahead.
Thanks a lot Maya.
Hey Maya.
If you want...
I could write
yours for you.
That'd be nice.
Let's go then! And make
sure we all come back!
The great white battlefield.
Individual justice.
The return to the island alive.
Next on Fafner episode
number twenty-five.
"Symbiosis."
Are you there?