♪ opening song ♪
How wonderful...
Now I can create a real
machine for our final showdown.
Something different than
that machine Yoji wasted.
You are being too
soft if you ask me.
Besides how will
you be able to take in
all those abandoned soldiers.
They wanted to join us.
So why should I kick them out?
Are you sure you
won't change your
mind about how
you're handling that pilot?
Yes.
Tsubaki Minashiro
prefers it that way.
Oh.
Then you really
can't refuse it, can you?
All right class,
I'd like to introduce
you all to a new friend.
I'm Tsubaki Minashiro.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Canon Memphis.
Machine I.D.
Code JO17.
I pilot Babylon Model Fafners.
You can go ahead and take
that empty seat over there.
Just to clarify, I turned that
switch off as a
strategic decision.
It was not because you
persuaded me in any way.
No need to worry,
I'm in charge and
I'll be taking very
good care of you.
First I'll need you to choose
whatever you like from these.
I'm sorry ma'am.
I can't make tofu.
I don't know how.
That's precisely what
you're going to learn.
The only thing that any of you
have ever learned about was war.
So it's time I taught
you what peace is.
Hello, anyone home?
Is that Maya's voice?
My father used
to make me help with
the yard work when I was a kid.
When we were halfway done with
cutting the grass,
we'd get to take a break.
Mom would make barely tea and
we'd sit here
and drink it like this.
You know...
I got to meet your dad.
I just wanted to tell you that.
I know.
And I heard you were there
for him during his last moments.
Yeah but...
I couldn't really
do anything for him.
All I did was watch...
I'm sorry.
But because of you he had the
opportunity to talk to someone
from the island before he left.
So, thank you.
I know that made him happy.
You can't!
I don't see anything
wrong with living together!
How do you think
people will react to it?
Will you think things
through for once?
I have thought about it!
And aren't you taking the
children to the beach tomorrow?
How can you do this
and still be their leader?
I've had enough.
I'm leaving whether
you like it or not.
I want to entrust you with a new
resident, if that's all right.
I don't understand.
Why me?
I mean...
I know how you feel.
But you're the most qualified.
So please.
I'm requesting
leave superior officer.
I'm not your superior officer.
I'm your guardian, Canon.
Understand?
I'd like permission
to leave to go
exchange information
with Triple Six.
Huh?
Oh, you mean Michio.
Just make sure you come
back before it gets dark.
Roger.
I will return before sunset.
You know, Canon.
In these situations,
you can just say "I'm leaving."
Hm?
Okay...
I'm leaving.
That's better.
I'll see you later then.
Have fun.
I'm most qualified for this?
Everywhere I went
the situation was awful.
I fought the Festum just
because they were there.
In that sense,
I was no different from
the Festum I suppose.
What took you so long, Yumiko?
What? Sis!
What's in those bags?
Starting today I'm going
to be living here.
What?
You can't!
Who's going to
cook back at home?
Silly.
You're gonna be
taking over for me.
Huh?
Whaaaat?!!
She still has this picture...
Oh Yumiko...
What is it that you've done?
Why is sis being such an idiot.
Huh?
Do you know if Triple Six
is going to live
with that woman?
Uh, yeah.
At least it looks that way.
By the way,
where are you living?
I am currently residing
with Yoko Hazama.
Hmn?
Are you using Shoko's room?
Shoko?
Who's Shoko?
Uh...
Oh, Shoko was...
Ms. Hazama's daughter.
Oh, I see.
No, I'm not staying
in her old room,
they have me
in a different room.
Canon, if you
don't mind me asking,
where did you meet Michio?
Dublin.
Five years ago.
He rescued me.
He is an excellent superior.
He taught me how to fight.
You know what?
I live really close.
Do you wanna
come over for a visit?
Are you ordering me to go?
I thought it might be nice.
That's all.
Dad...
I want to start
fighting by myself...
...going on solo missions.
I guess leaving the island
made you a bit cocky, didn't it.
It's nothing like that.
It's just...
I don't want anyone else...
to die anymore.
What about if you die?
Is that okay?
And Soshi?
What about him?
Don't you think he
feels the same way?
Look...
You are not alone in this.
And that's the reason why
you cannot fight alone.
Now hurry up and
eat before it gets cold.
I cooked all of this for us.
You know.
I cooked a few meals
myself too, back in the day.
But it was before you
got married, wasn't it?
I won't forget your pain...
None of it.
Huh? I thought
I packed it in here.
What is it you're looking for?
It's this picture...
of my family...
Hey wait...
You're really, here aren't you?
I am...
And you are too.
We're both here.
Think of it as a peace talk to
make up for our
military's stupidities.
I'll even tell you what
the Neo U.N. is planning.
I'm only allowing
you to come onboard.
And even then,
only for a maximum
stay of forty-eight hours.
All right, however
I expect to be able to
visit with my daughters
as any father would.
That guy always acts
like he's such a big shot.
What do you think
he really wants from us?
I have no idea.
He's not exactly the type of
man, to be very forthcoming.
I want to make
sure I'm there tomorrow.
But aren't you supposed
to be going to the
beach with all the other pilots?
Now is not the time for that.
Actually, you should
be treasuring every
single moment you have to spend
with your friends
at a time like this.
Yes, I understand.
Good bye.
Was it a patient?
No. I just had some
business to attend to.
What've you got there?
It's Dad's camera.
I dug it up because
I want to take
some pictures at
the beach tomorrow.
I see...
If you happen
to see your sister,
will you let her know
I need to talk to her?
Huh?
I received an order informing
all pilots to
gather at the beach.
Is that what
you're going to wear?
Hold on a minute.
I may have more comfortable
clothes that would fit you.
Do you mean Shoko's clothes?
Yeah...
She was still fairly weak and
couldn't go outside much.
That's why they're
still in good condition.
It would make me happy
if you would wear them for me.
No, thank you.
I don't think they'd fit.
I'm sure they would be fine.
Don't worry.
We're here at the
ocean not just for our
mental and physical health,
but so that we can
better communicate
among ourselves.
I want you to have a good time,
but be sure to be safe.
--We will!
Oh...
Mom says to tell you
she needs to talk to you...
Why can't she
just leave me alone?
By the way, you better work
on those cooking skills soon,
or else Kazuki's
gonna make fun of you.
How does this have
anything to do with Kazuki?
That island is part of
Takeru Island's docking bay.
It's about one kilometer
here and back.
Think you can swim it?
Sure.
Alright then,
and if you beat me,
I'll forgive you for leaving
the island without permission.
Are you still mad about that?
Are you gonna
do this thing or not?!
Let's do it.
Sounds pretty interesting.
Why don't you
let me join you two.
Sakura.
Tell you what.
How about if I win,
then you have to let the
Mark Drei
launch the next offensive.
That's fine by me.
Kazuki.
Don't forget, you're not the
only one who's a pilot?
Then here we go.
I'll teach you a thing or
two about beach volleyball.
You ready, Mamoru?
Of course!
Bring it on!
Oh, hey Maya...
I didn't know you were swimming.
Yeah, I was.
And Soshi and Sakura
were with me too.
I couldn't catch up with him.
He was too fast.
Yeah, me neither.
I can't believe
how much stamina he has.
Shoko.
Canon?
Where did you come
up with those clothes?
From Yoko Hazama.
She wanted me to wear them.
You mean Shoko's
mom gave them to you?
Uh, I think I better
go and change.
They look good on you, Canon.
You should be
in this picture too.
Okay, what's four minus one?
--Three!
You've really grown, Maya.
Just look at you.
Why would he divulge the
Neo U.N.'s strategies
to us like that?
What do you think
it is that he's up to?
Commander Makabe.
I need to talk to
you about something.
I see...
So you got to see what's
beyond the island too.
Yeah.
Did you go out in a Fafner?
Uh-uh. I'm not allowed to ride
one because I'm not qualified.
That seems rather strange.
You should have that verified.
Ask your mother.
You never know.
There's a chance
the data could be wrong.
Mom!
What is that man doing
back on this island?
What are you showing him?
What is that?
The real results of Maya's
pilot aptitude tests.
Then Maya's ability is
actually really high, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
But I...
So that's what happened...
What you did was wrong.
But I really ought to
be thanking you,
since your little secret
actually works to my advantage.
What did you come back for?
Is that any way
to talk to your father?
Get out! Can't you
see no one wants you...
Stop it!
I'd listen to her if I were you!
You haven't changed
one bit, have you?
I just discovered that
they've falsified data.
That is a very serious crime.
Expel them from the island.
You have no choice.
Turn them over to me.
I can handle them from now on.
That's what you
wanted all along, isn't it?
The commission
will conduct an inquiry.
And they'll determine
the punishment if necessary.
It'll be impossible for you
to try to stage a cover up.
I've already talked to Maya.
She'll no doubt have questions.
It's nice to have
a family, isn't it...
Fumihiko?
Suppose you knew
a certain someone who
actually had the
ability to pilot a Fafner.
But they had their records
altered in order to
protect them...
...what would you do, Soshi?
Covering up or falsifying
records is a serious crime.
But whether or not
to bring charges
depends on the situation.
I knew you were
going to say that.
All right then.
I'm going to let
you in on something.
If something should
happen to me,
I want you to take my place.
Don't talk like that.
It's imperative that
Dr. Tohmi stays on the island.
We can't allow
him to take her away.
I'd sooner leave the
island than let her go.
I've been outside the
island I can survive there.
This investigative
committee demands to
know the details about
the discrepancies between
the recently discovered data and
the current data
that we have on file.
Since this is
a military tribunal,
understand that your right
to silence is not protected.
After the inquiry,
if the data in question is
verified as the original,
you will be charged
as the prime suspect.
Is this all clear to you?
It is.
Then let the accuser step forth
and enter in his statement.
Are you going
to sit there and let
your mother take
responsibility for your crime?
How disappointing.
--What a bastard!
--Unbelieveable!
It's okay, Dad.
Did you actually
think that Maya would
be grateful to you
for doing this to her?
I'm the one who did it...
I falsified the data.
Yumiko!
If I didn't say anything,
then you'd be
held responsible...
Madam Chairman,
she's reacting emotionally.
It's not the truth.
The suspects are obvious.
You might as well
begin the deliberation.
Have the commission
members made a decision?
Both will be
considered suspects.
We will move on to deliberation.
Just a minute.
According to this petition.
There are still a few people
that we haven't summoned.
What's this?
But I had only brought the
charges against the two of them.
We will question
the next defendant.
You may leave the
podium and take a seat.
Yes ma'am.
I falsified Maya Tohmi's
pilot aptitude records.
Before we will accept
your admission,
the commission
demands an explanation.
What was your motive?
I didn't want her to be a pilot.
She's too independent
which I consider a fatal flaw.
A flaw?
The fact that
she left the island
without permission
is testament to that.
As a pilot she
would be a liability
and a danger to our objectives.
This has always
been evident from
her early childhood
interactions.
So therefore I made
the conscious decision
to falsify her data, removing
her from pilot candidacy.
Now we have three suspects.
Big deal.
The situation's the same!
We're not finished yet.
Please bring in
the next defendant.
--Mamoru?!
It's true.
What can I say, I did it too.
As with the previous defendants,
we will need an
explanation for your motives.
Well I was hanging
out in the medical room,
messing around with
all the neat machines,
and the next thing I knew
I'd accidentally
rewrote Maya's data.
And I panicked
and tried to hide it.
That's our little troublemaker.
He's only just
a child after all.
I uh...
I don't think
that's the problem.
All right then, shall we
bring in the next defendant?
Sakura!
Yeah, me too.
I also falsified Maya's data.
I wanted to pilot a Fafner
more than anything else.
But Maya was standing in my way.
I know it was
wrong and I'm sorry Mom.
Sakura.
Okay.
Next defendant.
It was really me.
I did it!
I was terrified about
having to get on a Fafner.
I thought if I could just
lower my scores I'd be safe,
but it turns out I
lowered Maya's by mistake...
I'm sorry, Mom...
All right.
Bring in the next one.
I intentionally changed
the data in Maya's records.
This is weird.
Who would order all of
them to do such a thing?
They weren't ordered.
Everyone's doing
it of their own will.
Of their own will?
Really?
Okay, and what
is your motive, Kazuki?
We'd like to hear it.
It's because...
...well, because I didn't
want Maya to have to fight.
Why?
Uh...
It's cuz I...
No reason.
Nothing really.
Aah, any excuse would've
been better than that.
All right, that's enough.
I call the next defendant.
I'm next.
I also changed the data.
I think it'll be easier if you
just replied from there.
You see I was simply
double checking what
her measurements were
when I made the mistake.
You can't always tell it!
Will you please take your seat!
Though it's unusual...
...we have multiple
instances of fraud.
And since there are so
many people involved,
each person's crime holds
even less weight.
Ridiculous!
There's no evidence to back up
any of their statements.
The last defendant
called can verify that
all of our claims
have been true.
Tsubaki...?
Minashiro...?
The island core
is the defendant?
It's like putting God on trial.
It's the truth.
Everyone here
did alter the data.
In fact, I altered the data too.
Because I thought it would've
been too early for Maya.
Oh.
Is that so.
All of us know that
because of who she is,
my sister has an
infallible memory of
everything that
happens on the island.
It follows that she would know
about each individual's actions.
Nonsense!
Even the core can falsify the
records in any way she wants.
Out of all of us, the core has
the greatest ability to be fair.
How can anyone
doubt what she says?
After your mother
had been assimilated,
Chizuru Tohmi
ripped you from her womb.
She's responsible for giving you
a life filled only with pain.
Why are you protecting her?
Because that was
the will of my mother.
I wasn't supposed
to exist like I do.
But thanks to Chizuru,
I'm here before you.
Both my mom and
I are grateful to Chizuru.
Don't you kids even know
a single thing about yourselves?
Why?
What is there to know?
The alien chromosomes
that were implanted
in your bodies increase
every time you get in a Fafner.
Eventually, it could
harm or even kill you.
Those elements are what allow
them to effectively
fight the Festum.
And the potential threats
are now minimal thanks
to Dr. Tohmi's research.
Unbelieveable!
You're actually still doing
such useless research?!
Useless, huh?
Yeah right.
Surely the
commission members aren't
going to believe these things!
What do you mean by that?
They are the products of
Japanese genetic engineering
created by a
desperate people who
lost their ability
to conceive that's all.
How dare you say that!
They are merely
batteries that fuel
your precious
Fafners aren't they?
What did you say?!
Don't think you'll leave
here in one piece!
We're just batteries to them?
Apparently so.
What a bastard.
Listen Maya...
The people on this island
have got it all wrong.
Why'd you do that?
Why did you talk about
my friends like that, Dad?
Because that
is the reality of it.
It was the truth.
But... Everyone
here loves their families.
And that's also
the truth, isn't it?
Your view is too narrow.
It isn't the same when you
look at the overall picture.
I'd been wondering
about something, Dad.
When Mr. Hino died,
did you feel sad?
He believed in
a ridiculous cause.
And so he got what he deserved.
By the way...
I've been taking pictures
with your old camera.
My camera?
That old thing?
I'll tell you what.
I'll get you a brand new camera.
One much better
than that old one I had.
I was wondering...
What is it?
What's the difference...
between the Festum and you?
All right then.
If this commission has come
to a verdict, let's hear it.
This is a joke.
What kind of
ridiculous inquiry is this?
If any member wishes to make an
official charge against the
defendants, then please rise.
With no official charges
there are no suspects.
This inquiry is closed.
You may go.
Dad...
I've decided.
I'm going to stay here.
Be sure to use your head, Maya.
The people on
this island are just a
group of fools who cling to
their delusions of peace.
Good-bye.
Be safe, Dad.
If you apologize to Maya,
I'll allow you stay
here a bit little longer.
The MIR in the North Pole
have started to become active,
which means the threat
to humanity will be great.
At that time, you'll have
no choice but to fight.
Suppose we win the battle,
have you thought about
what you'll be left with?
As long as we win, I
wouldn't require anything else.
All of the information
I gave you is accurate.
Make sure you study it.
It will show you how
ill-prepared we humans are for
a full force attack
by the Festum.
Be sure to see
it with you own eyes.
You could say,
our situation is hopeless...
Thank you Sis
for trying to protect me.
I appreciate it.
♪ closing song ♪
I am going to fight as well.
In my eyes is a reflection...
...of a place
filled with battles.
Next on "Fafner"
episode number nineteen.
"Sight."
Are you there?