You've got to help
me stop Shoko!
Get off the island!
Go away!
This is Kazuki's island!
What do you think you're doing?
I am trying to...
draw it away from the island.
You need to eject!
Now Shoko!
Initiating Fenrir.
Kazuki...
Don't worry.
I will protect your island...
No, it can't be!
♪ opening song ♪
These two are the ones who
can be made battle-ready?
Yes, just barely though...
Your response speed
is going up nicely.
You shouldn't force yourself
to unite with Fafner.
Let's take our time
and do it little by little.
After all, it's not like you
need to rush out into battle.
I think that I've
had enough training now.
I have a favor to ask of you.
I'm afraid I can't allow it.
I don't see why you can't.
I happen to be in agreement
with Koyo's suggestion.
Absolutely not.
There are limits to what
the simulations show.
That's neither here nor there...
It's meaningless if he
can't demonstrate
his power in actual combat.
He needs to have training that
will ensure his
survival in battle.
Work notice to
all hangar personnel.
Due to the elimination
of Mark Zex,
work shifts have been moved up.
Be sure to confirm your
duties at each section.
Repeat.
Due to the elimination
of Mark Zex--
Man, she caused a lot
of problems doin' what she did.
Yeah, just look at what happened
to the precious Mark Zex.
Pilots ought to put themselves
in mechanic's
shoes once in awhile.
So... Then in other words,
what you're saying is
you won't hand over
the Nothung model to us...
We've already lost one
Fafner in the process of
defending the Neo U.N. convoy.
There isn't anything left to
relinquish to you people.
However...
Are you trying
to turn this island
into a scapegoat like Japan?
We can't sacrifice anymore
than we already have.
Excuse me.
Hmph.
Somehow... I find
it really hard to believe
that Shoko isn't
around anymore...
It feels like she
just transferred
to another school
or something...
Thinking that way makes
it easier, doesn't it?
Sakura...
Well then how should
I think about it, huh?
Shoko fought, and she was
satisfied to die doing it.
That's how.
You can't really mean that...
Humph.
And when the time comes, are we
supposed to do the same thing?
You should have been
able to save her, Kazuki!
You were piloting a
Fafner, weren't you?!
Then why didn't you?!
It was impossible under
those circumstances.
But you should've been able
to do something, right?!
You could've saved her!
It was just you
who came out alive...
Does that sound
all right to you?
How can you ever expect
me to believe that
saving her was impossible?
In the end...
Shoko suffered...
She suffered and died...
But only we...
Only we survived...
The death of Shoko Hazama
was most unfortunate...
...but it's imperative
now that we move
forward with the
Arcadian Project.
Yes.
The Albelihide organization
is prepared to offer
you the next child
that needs to be raised.
Are you considering accepting?
Even if...
I didn't actually
give birth to her...
Shoko is my daughter
and always will be.
Yes... and, regarding
that subject...
She's my one and only daughter!
Yes, I understand...
Hello, Kasugai residence.
Huh?
You want Koyo?
Yes...
Yes.
One moment please.
Hello, this is Koyo.
Yes...
Yes.
Yes, I understand.
What was that?
Tomorrow, I want you
and dad to come with me.
Huh?
Temperature, 26 degrees Celsius.
Humidity, 87 percent.
Wind direction south
by southeast.
Visibility is poor.
Please be sure to confirm your
positions and avoid collisions.
Can we please start already?
Are you sure that
we can really do this?
As real as we
can with this ammo.
I won't be taking it
easy on you either, Kazuki.
All Fafner pilots, please
confirm to us once more that
your entire
complement of bullets
consists of paint pellets.
Mark Elf, confirmation complete.
Mark Vier, confirmed.
Mark Drei, confirmed.
Then we'll begin at Stage 1.
Mark Vier and Mark Drei are to
head from point
zero to point one.
Mark Elf is to attack
them after three minutes.
The time limit is 15 minutes.
--Roger!
Training begins now.
You're doing very well so far.
Thanks for noticing.
Now he's after you too.
He's behind and to the left.
Contact in 28 seconds.
Get in control of
your emotions, Koyo.
or your response
time will slow down.
I know, Soshi.
Their pulse and heart
rates are slightly elevated.
But they're within the
normal range considering
that this is their
first piloting mission.
That concludes Stage 1.
Stage 2 will begin after
a 20-minute break.
That concludes Stage 2.
Stage 3 begins now.
What a difference.
They were at
approximately the same
level when they
started the training...
Shall we continue then?
This really didn't show
what I'm capable of at all.
I know that it didn't.
However, Sakura...
If you ever feel you're in
danger, please run away.
Even if it means
disobeying orders.
Eh?
I don't want what happened
to Shoko to happen to you too.
Dying isn't what I want!
But I won't run.
I want to take down
as many as I can...
As many of those
enemies who killed Dad...
I guess my power was pretty
disappointing, wasn't it...
It's all right...
Just finding out
what your potential
is makes all this a success.
Well then...
...it looks like
everything's over now.
Huh?
Okay... let's go to
the medical room.
Couldn't you do
anything to prevent this?
If it had been a real battle,
this would've been a casket...
Someone made a good shot.
Huh?
Yeah, you're right!
I knew this was
going to happen...
But...
But still...
We put the children
into this position,
and we make them
go into battle all
for the sake of
our own survival...
I can't...
I just can't
understand it at all...
I'm sorry for the wait.
We detected a change
in his chromosomes
as we thought we would.
Aren't you two
feeling concerned at all?
Not particularly.
Isn't that right, dear?
Well, we are
Albelihide people, after all.
The job we agreed
to do is over now.
We're different from
your family, you know,
and the Kanames, too.
How can you
say things like that?
Like the Hazamas,
we weren't able to
have any children of our own.
We couldn't join
the project unless we
accepted this job
as part of the deal.
Mrs. Hazama would
never do something like that!
But don't forget that that
daughter of hers was a hit!
She actually destroyed an enemy.
Whereas our "son"
is a total miss.
A total miss...?
This is the island that we found
three hundred fifty
kilometers to the north.
It certainly looks similar.
You mean...
that it looks similar to Alvis?
Alvis isn't the only island
that was constructed
under the Arcadian
Project's supervision.
But intelligence regarding
the other islands was
unfortunately something that
was never fully disclosed to us.
In any case, no matter
what this island was
protecting someone's going
to have to take it over.
However, we don't
know whether this
island was part of
the Arcadian Project.
This calls for some
scouting of the island.
I think it'll be worth
our while to do so.
It's important for us to find
out what happened here.
Send in the research unit
along with some Fafners.
I'll leave personnel
selection to you.
I understand, Commander.
Excuse me...
But why was I assigned
to the scouting team?
I heard that our medical
unit was shorthanded.
And I believe that you
have some first aid skills.
But wait...
Please stop doing that, Dad...
Stupid little stray mutt!
Dad, please!
Chocolat!
Dad don't...
We don't have any extra food in
the house to feed a dog, Koyo!
I'll share my food with her,
so please let the dog stay!
Stop focusing on such
pointless things!
All you need to worry
about is being a pilot!
Now hurry up and
get rid of that thing!
Thanks, Chocolat...
you're a good girl.
Koyo?
Maya...
Oh, look, it's so cute!
Does it have a name?
Eh?
Oh, uh...
No, she doesn't for now, anyway.
It's so adorable...
Hey, about tomorrow...
You're gonna be going out with
us on the mission too, right?
Huh?
Yeah...
I have no idea why, though...
It seems it's already
been decided.
Hm?
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing really.
Nobody's home...
Oh, wait...
Let's go to Mamoru's house.
He has to be home.
Sorry, I can't keep
a dog around here...
I see...
I'm real sorry about that.
Must've been tough
out there in the rain.
A little bit.
Uh, actually, I have a
small favor I'd like to ask...
Oh, those little guys used to
be some specimens for research.
So what was
the favor you wanted?
N-Never mind, it's all right.
So what now, Chocolat?
How about...
we go on Fafner together?
Koyo?
About that mission tomorrow...
Have you heard
anything about it yet?
Yeah...
All right.
See you then.
Hey... do you like dogs?
Huh?
I heard that my dad had a
dog once a long time ago...
You think you could...
What?
Uh... Nevermind...
Koyo.
Um... don't catch a cold.
That goes for both of you.
Oh, Koyo?
Thanks for everything.
Huh?
Why did you choose
Kazuki and Koyo?
You think I'm incompetent
or something, Soshi?!
Actually, I don't
think that at all.
However, you
haven't forgotten what
happened to the
Mark Zex, have you?
Back then, if we had left a
Fafner and an able pilot here to
defend the island the incident
wouldn't have happened.
I've been thinking that we
should always leave a suitable
pilot behind just in case
something like that happens.
Well, I'm willing to
leave it at that for now.
Thank you, Sakura.
How's the little dog doing?
Yeah, she's doing
just fine, thanks.
Here you go.
I wanted to thank you...
...you were the one
who took the time to
clean up Shoko's
grave, weren't you?
Huh?
I wasn't the only one, actually.
Kazuki and Soshi were
there and they helped me too.
Huh?
Is something the matter?
So they even brought
you along on this, Maya?
That's gotta
be rough on you.
Uh, will you be okay,
Mr. Mizoguchi?
Yeah, I'll be okay
after a little drink or two.
This is just like goin'
fishing, after all.
Here ya go.
Oh, t-thanks...
It's when the tide's about
to change direction that
you can usually catch the big
ones, in case you didn't know.
Oh...
And you can't fish
when you're sober.
Okay...
Our ultimate goal here
is to secure materials.
But the island's defense system
isn't necessarily
completely inactive.
That's why we have the Fafners
available as a last resort.
I'm counting on both of you.
We're about to reach the
target island's airspace.
Kazuki...
...do you honestly believe
that just because you helped
clean up and
restore Shoko's grave...
...that you've finished
atoning for your sin?
Kazuki!
Your emotions are
in disarray, Koyo.
Don't think of things now.
Focus on your duties.
We've arrived at the target!
Even though we
had just won a battle...
...we didn't feel the usual joy.
Instead we felt
the loss of our friend.
And just dealing with that
was all anyone could do.
♪ closing song ♪
You abandoned Shoko?
Eyes clouded with sorrow.
Hearts that pass one another.
The island where
something will begin.
Abandoning my friends is
something that I'll never do!
Next on Fafner
episode number eight.
"Koyo."
Are you there?