It doesn't exist?
It was destroyed 29 years ago.
You mean Tokto and Osaka are...?
...are gone and have
been for a long time.
And in a way, Tatsumiya
Island disappeared to.
You won't find it on any map.
Akane...
I'm sorry.
♪ opening song ♪
No visible object on the sea.
Reporting to headquarters,
target could not be
located today either.
A Neo U.N. recon plane
just passed overhead.]
I'm on pins and needles.
I have a constant fear that
they'll discover us someday.
They might have detected
something from the
previous battle.
We're hiding from
both man and alien...
I understand why...
...but it makes me feel uneasy.
I'm outta here.
I'll see ya later , Koyo.
You are so forgetful.
Mamoru!
Come with me!
Are we picking up
on underclass girls again?
Hey, you two...
Remember what
we're doing after school?
We've been discovered.
Today is our lucky day.
I'm teaching you something new.
It's a special move.
Mom?
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
By now, I'm sure you have
already heard about the neo U.N.
recon planes conducting frequent
searches over the island.
And...
I'm thinking of
moving the island,
temporarily to an
archipelago in the northwest.
Are you really moving
the island this time?
Brunhilde System is currently
still on cold stand by.
Besides that the system has...
I know that Minashiro
had been in charge of it.
But we can't let the Neo U.N.
know about this
islands whereabouts.
I want you to take over
and move us immediately.
I understand.
Dr. Tohmi.
Wait...
We need to talk.
Of course.
But not here.
In the Alvis medical room.
Yes, I understand.
Even if we could use
Mark Elf in actual combat...
...there is no guarantee
it can withstand the
upcoming operations
if Kazuki is the only pilot.
So then...
Dr. Tohmi, I would
like you to find
me some more pilot candidates.
Some of those children will have
to depart again, won't they?
These are some pictures from the
class field trip we
had the other day.
I'm so envious.
All of you got to
be in the picture.
I want to hurry up
and get better so
I can be in the
picture with everyone.
Yeah!
You will!
Just do your best!
Yeah!
I will!
These are the children with
high synergetic code
formation values.
Koyo Kasugai, Sakura Kaname,
Mamoru Kodate, Shoko Hazama...
Are you sure...
...that you want
to include Maya?
Shoko Hazahma and
Maya Tohmi It appears
the two of them have
a physical handicap.
I will place them under
Yumiko's direction for a while.
Good idea.
I'm going to begin
orientation with the parents.
I'm coming with you.
This is...
Seiichiro ...
But I just lost Seiichiro...
I'm very sorry.
That's all the
information we have.
Why?
Why does it have to be my Kenji?
As you well know, these
children were raised for this.
I know that!
It's true, but...
It's just...
...not him.
Kenji.
Please wait!
Shoko...
Shoko's condition is...
I'm very sorry.
But her physical condition
and her synergetic code
formation values...
Well, they're not correlated.
You know that, don't you?
To think that a numerical value
can determine a child's future.
This must be really
hard for the parents too.
I could have done
this alone you know.
It's all right.
This is part of my
job as a physician.
Are you serious?
Yes!
He did it dear.
Look!
Let me see.
Look at that!
This thing is for real!
Koyo!
Come down here honey!
Mamoru, what are you doing?
I'm studying.
Is this comic interesting?
Yeah!
I see.
Dear.
The project.
Did you mention it
to Mamoru already?
You know, about sending him.
But honey...!
Keep it down!
My deadline is tomorrow!]
I had no idea that Maya
had a physical handicap.
Oh mom.
She is one of the
lucky ones, you know.
She won't die as along as
she's under my direction.
Yes, I know.
I was honestly
very happy about that.
But...
...but still...
Hmm... Let's see...
I thought it was in here.
I'm coming in.
Okay.
What are you looking for?
Oh!
Here it is.
Wow. It's Dad's camera!
I didn't know it was in there.
Can all of us go
in there too now?
Yes.
And you'll be all right
because you already
have an ID chip
implanted in your bodies.
How cool!
It's like a secret base.
It actually is a secret base
cuz it's a secret, right?
Why have you guys been hiding
a place like this from us?
I mean it's so awesome.
Well we...
Children need to
concentrate on studying.
She seems a bit
different, don't ya think?
She does.
This is where he used to work...
My dad.
My Mom.
Why's she acting that way?
It's probably
because she's working.
You know, my mom's been giving
me the cold shoulder
too these days.
Mine too.
That's probably cuz your parents
have already given up on you.
Your parents would never
do a thing like that!
Look it's Kazuki.
And Soshi too.
Hey sis, got a second.
Hm?
Okay everyone...
Gather round.
They're gonna take a
commemorative photo.
A commemorative photo?
Sakura, get over here.
I see how this place is
interesting to them,
but still...
Your break is now over!
I want you to hurry up!
What's 15,436 minus 15,433?
Three!
All right, we are going to begin
your Fafner training now.
Our training?
What's a Fafner?
It's that big robot.
Now, ' which one of
you would like to go first.
Give instructions
to each section.
See?
Use this monitor.
Take your time but
make sure you're accurate.
Understand?
I think so.
Well then how are the
new recruits doing?
They're doing
pretty well considering
that it's their first time.
Well, for their
first time, not bad.
What's Mark Elf's condition?
We have completed switching out
the cockpit block
and put in a new body.
The armor's not complete.
But in my opinion
we can still use it.
What about the rest?
Well, on Mark Zex...
...the final few adjustments
should be completed soon.
I meant to talk
to you about that.
Lindwurm?
Yeah.
It's Makabe's order.
According to him the Mark Elf
is more compatible with
Lindwurm than Mark Zex.
Is there something
wrong with it?
As pilots these others
are just hopeless.
It's unreasonable to expect
them to be like Kazuki.
Yeah.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
What's the situation over there?
We are still at phase 32.
32?
You're behind schedule.
Yeah, I know.
But the Brunhilde
system remains on
cold-standby and
it's unable to start.
What is the cause?
We don't know.
See if you can speed things up.
Right.
Look at the state
we've fallen into
without Commander Minashiro.
I hope I can be as good as him.
Great.
This is no good.
Do you think it
might be a defect?
Let's try changing
the whole engine.
That might be faster.
Kazuki?
Hey, wait, uh...
Access denied.
Your ID does not give you
clearance to the lower levels.
Dr. Kondo.
We just cleared phases
35 through 46.
We're able to fire
up the reaction hearth.
But how?
Why all of sudden?
Firing up the reaction hearth.
Attention all island residents.
As of 10 a.m. tomorrow,
Tatsumiya Island
will start moving.
Repeat...
They're going
to move the island?
What's that?
No one even told me about this!
Me either.
Those bastards always
make decisions without us!
Miss Yumiko!
Hey... Sis!
Dr. Kondo.
What is this?
I don't know.
The Brunhilde System
started up all of sudden.
A prophecy from Solomon.
Increase gravity pull to
120 at a heading of 9 o'clock.
The mass is increasing.
The two of you need
to get out of here.
What exactly's going on?
We're in a battle.
Solomon's prophecy
has determined
that it's a Sphinx type.
What on earth's going on?
Is this still training?
Something's
different 'bout this.
Commander Makabe.
Neo U.N. plane spotted
at 6 o'clock,
60 kilometers away,
approaching
the island rapidly.
It will pass over the
island in about 25 minutes.
This has got to
be the worst timing!
Should we intercept
it on the island?
If we release the
Walle Shield, then we
may be discovered
by the search plane.
You think we should
change our course.
The sailing phase
is still at 73.
Commander!
I have an idea that might work.
It looks good.
I think that it's worth giving
this strategy of yours a shot.
All right then.
Take Mark Elf off standby.
Do you know where Kazuki is?
He's heading up in an elevator
from underground block 34.
What's he doing here?
Kazuki!
You have to hurry up!
It's too dangerous.
We still haven't done
the matching test.
Nonetheless, we need him to fly.
I won't be responsible for this!
We have to.
It's the only way.
Alright then... hurry up with
the Mark Elf and Lindwurm Crest.
Yumiko, contact the
Neo U.N. plane.
Tell them Tatsumiya
Island is at Point N-0-2.
But that will put them in
contact with the Sphinx model.
That's right.
The Neo U.N.
plane will be our decoy.
Meanwhile,
we'll start moving the island.
All staff, report to stations.
LDA is unfolding.
Lock number one
and number two Gewitter.
Lock number three
and number four Gewitter.
Releasing Fafner cage.
Transfer AVC Lindwurm
to the turntable.
Move the block.
Final safety check all green.
Secure Fafner
to the contact position.
Lock Contact Arm.
Fafner has made contact.]
Contact completed.
But I'm telling you,
I've never even flown before.
There's no need to worry.
Together, I am sure
that we can do this.
Don't you agree with me?
Lindwurm System all green.
Start Lindwurm engine!
Release Catapult.
All sections
operating normally.
This is Lindwurm!
Take off!
Let's go!
I wonder when it started...
...when people began to
forget how to fly in the sky.
No.
We didn't forget.
We became scared.
It's because the
sky on this planet
doesn't belong to
people anymore.
But now we're spreading
our wings in this sky again.
♪ closing song ♪
Truth.
That time we took the
commemorative photo...
Can we ever go back there?
Next on "Fafner"
episode number four.
Departure.
Are you there?