--[IO SHIOTA singing]
--[IDOL FANS cheering]
Niwaka? What in the
hell are you watching?
[NIWAKA]
Io Shiota killing it on stage!
Who is she? Io..?
[ARISA] Moi! I can't believe
you don't know of her!
She's one of the biggest idols
on the whole Akiba
pop scene right now!
She sang lead for G-N-Z-34
and is known for her
antisocial behavior at
hand-shaking events!
She's ED song-level famous!
I don't get the appeal.
--[IO SHIOTA singing]
--[IDOL FANS cheering]
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[TAMOTSU gasps]
Oh my god. I believe
I've just seen the light!
♪
--[IO SHIOTA singing]
--[IDOL FANS cheering]
[TAMOTSU]
Hm.
[ARISA, NIWAKA gasp]
[TAMOTSU]
I'm home!
[NIWAKA gasps]
[ARISA] Wow, you've upgraded to
Full Concert Armor Combat Mode!
For your sake, I hope you've
been trapped in a well.
Uh... I was watching Io,
because I have taste.
You're supposed to be on patrol!
Remember that whole,
Saving-Akiba-from-
Bug-monsters thing?
Oh yeah, right.
I guess I forgot!
[MATOME sighs]
Lousy underling.
Well, it's getting pretty late,
but we can still patrol now.
Sorry, I'm booked.
I have to watch Io's concert
review. It's about to start!
Just watch it later,
when we're done stripping
people for the good of mankind!
No way, are you crazy?
You have to watch it live and
make comments, that's the
whole point of these things!
I swear, after that show I
could die again a happy man!
But no time to enjoy
the afterglow!
I've gotta get my comments
organized in my head
so I can totally own that forum!
Her classic "5 Seconds
'Til Security Tackles You"
was great as always,
but her new song,
"Keep Your Slimy Hands Off"
was a little shaky.
She must not have had
time to practice that one.
Would you shut up?!
Is it just me or
does she seem mad?
[CARL'S EMPLOYEE]
Hi, welcome to Carl's!
[SHOPPERS]
Huh?
[MATOME]
What's he thinking?
We've got a crisis on our hands!
Who knows what
they're plotting next!
And he's wasting the day
obsessing over idols
like a squealing tween!
It makes me sick. Does he think
I went to all that trouble
to save him just for fun?
[gasps]
[SHOPPERS gasp]
[KATI] Okay meow!
Inspired choice, master!
One order of "Teddy in the Pool
Curry Rice" for your entree!
And an "OMG So Cute
Bunny Parfait" for dessert!
I'll inform the kitchen at once!
Now please enjoy
watching me leave!
[TAMOTSU hums]
[KAGE]
'Sup, playa.
Hey, Kage.
Listening to somethin' good?
The latest from Io Shiota.
It's a web-only remix
with a louder beat and egregious
auto-tuning. It's great!
Whoa. So now you're an
Idol-head, that's a switch.
If you're gonna be
on a music kick,
you should listen with
some higher quality gear.
I mean, you don't need to
go nuts and drag around
a portable headphone amp.
But you can at least do better
than those rinky-dink earbuds.
Here, man, try mine.
These are "canal-type," so you
stick 'em in there pretty deep,
but trust me,
you're gonna love it.
[gasps]
You said "Anal-type?"
Calm down. You stick 'em in
your ears, you big weirdo.
[TAMOTSU]
Hm.
[gasps]
[TAMOTSU sighs] Wow, these are
a lot pricier than I thought,
these guys aren't
joking around.
Well, if I'm gonna drop this
kind of coin, I might as well
get some that make me
look like I'm super hardcore.
This description uses
the word "quality" twice,
that bodes well.
Hm?
[yelps]
[SHOP CLERK]
May I help you, sir?
Or were you just
screaming for fun?
No. I'm in sticker shock!
How can these headphones
cost that much?
Because those are not
headphones at all.
Those are called "ear speakers."
[TAMOTSU hums]
Hey bro, did you
get new headphones?
They look expensive.
[TAMOTSU]
Oh, they're not headphones.
These beasts are
called ear speakers!
[NIWAKA]
Uh?
[KAGE]
Oh yeah, I know the guy.
So he went with
ear speakers, huh?
Damn. He's already in deep.
And it's not gonna be easy
for him to climb his way out.
You got that right. It's just
like that old saying.
The road to hell is paved
with pure audio enthusiasts.
[TAMOTSU gulp]
Sporting the latest core parts,
like the newly developed
mechanical engine
and high-quality
digital-analog converter.
With its charming short
lifespan of the pickup,
this 192 kilohertz, 24-bit
music player has everything,
making for a truly stunning
feat of audio engineering!
Vintage but cutting edge!
It connects a 5-pin
tube as a 3-pin for
unrivaled amplification
and spectral response!
And while I have no idea what
any of that means, if a smart
person did it on purpose,
then it has to be awesome!
And let's not forget
the ultimate evolution
in speaker technology!
Perfect, distortion-free
playback of sounds
outside the range
of human hearing!
An ideal match for
this limited-edition,
one hundred and eighty gram
heavy-weight half-speed vinyl!
Painstakingly mastered by the
legendary Ted Grandman himself!
Easily worth tens of thousands
of yen at any auction!
Course once I went vinyl,
I had to get a turntable, too!
What young man could resist
this brushed aluminum platter
and real wood cabinet?
Can you buy happiness? Yes!
With pure gold audio cables
whose sonic value only
true believers can ever
hope to understand!
Some call this pseudo-science.
But those people are a-holes!
Feast your eyes on this
mysterious stone that improves
sound quality just by
resting on your player!
And this emits
special particles,
re-shaping sound waves
for shocking audio clarity!
Results may vary,
void where prohibited!
Yes, ladies, this work
hasn't been easy,
especially on my credit card.
But I have now achieved mastery
in the art of hi-fi audio.
And this has revealed to
me a most powerful truth.
[ALL gasp]
The best way to listen to idol
songs is to listen to 'em live!
[ALL groan]
--[IO SHIOTA singing]
--[IDOL FANS cheering]
[TAMOTSU] This passion in the
venue, this feeling of unity,
this huge crowd
focusing our attention
on one hyper-exalted human.
This is true idol fandom.
Home audio is lame.
[TAMOTSU]
So amazing!
I should do that at
least five times a week!
Hm? Oh hey, my credit card bill.
[TAMOTSU]
Hm?
[gasps]
No choice left. I need
that part-time work!
Welcome! To the no-charge,
no-responsibility agency!
How can I help you in a
non-accountable way?
Hey there. I hate to say this,
but I need a new job.
[MASHIRO] Oh, you've come
in before, haven't you?
What sort of work are
you looking for now?
Something that pays
well and fast.
I don't care what it is,
I can't afford to be picky.
Wait a minute.
Did I just hear you say you'll
do anything for money?
Sort of. But it sounds
worse when you say it.
[chuckles] If you're that
desperate for cash,
then I've got some
perfect jobs for you!
[MATOME]
First the idol obsession,
and now he's at work?
It's ridiculous.
Is he ever gonna take
Electric Mayonnaise seriously?
That's his way. Tamotsu has
a habit of fixating on things,
and when he does,
it's like the rest of the
world stops existing.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad making you cover
for your brother like this.
Oh. It's cool, I've done
it for most my life.
[ARISA]
Well I know it's a problem,
but I can see how he'd get
carried away with idols.
[MATOME, NIKAWA]
Huh?
Idols are so dreamy!
Everybody adores them!
In fact it's my secret fantasy
for somebody on the street
to come up and
say "Moi, excuse me,
how would you like to
be an idol yourself?"
[CHIBUSA] Excuse me, girls.
Can we talk?
Yes, like that! When they
discover me they're gonna say
something just like that. Huh?
[CHIBUSA] I've been looking
for a trio like you.
How would you like to be idols?
[ALL gasp]
[ARISA gasping]
[NIWAKA]
Chibusa Benikage?
[MATOME]
Who is she?
Moi, are you kidding?
She's a famous former idol!
She dominated the scene
with her performances
and smoking hot bod!
Then turned the
industry on its head
with her auto-bio-graphical
play, "Why Don't They Pay".
exposing the shadowy secrets of
the idol-industrial complex!
Now she's a super
hyper media producer!
I'm flattered you know so
much about me, my dear.
Hi! I'm Nice Muramura!
Totally classy photographer!
I'll get to the point.
Beneath your rough,
un-exfoliated exteriors,
I see the glimmer of jewels.
You could be the best
trio in all of idol-dom!
[ALL shout]
So what do you say, ladies,
are you ready?
Will you climb on my pop
train and ride to the top?
This is so sudden,
I don't know what to say.
It's nice you see
something in us,
but I'm in the middle of
a very important mission.
I hardly have time to
be dancing around--
Hells kylla!
Sorry, kylla is Finnish for yes.
I was saying hells yes.
Of course we want to be stars!
Perfect, then it's settled.
[MATOME, NIWAKA grunt]
Kylla!
[CHIBUSA]
"Ma" for Matome!
"Ni!" for Niwaka!
And "A" for Arisa!
From now on, you three will
be known as the next big,
pop-trio craze: Mania!
Great bodies are
essential for idols.
You may be in good shape,
but how about your
jiggling stamina?
[NIWAKA pants]
[ARISA pants]
[NIWAKA, ARISA panting]
And now for the all-important
handshake training!
[ARISA]
Moi! Thanks for coming! Moi!
Oh thank you, you're so sweet!
No! I've never been
told that before!
[ALL giggle]
Aw! You're such a unique--
[CHIBUSA] Keep smiling! If you
frown you're as good as dead!
[TAMOTSU]
Hm.
Hey. What does this have to
do with our idol training?
These days they make videos
of all the pop stars climbing.
I have no idea why.
[TAMOTSU] Delivery! Thanks for
ordering the heavy stuff.
[ALL giggle]
Huh?
--[NIWAKA, MATOME shout]
--[ARISA] Silly boys!
[NICE] Yeah, bonus points
for the chocolate!
[NICE]
Yeah, work that mouth!
[NICE] Uh... A little
less teeth next time.
Uh, sir? I'm not complaining
but what is this for, again?
[NICE] For your
image video. That's all.
Sort of like a press kit, girls.
Trust me.
[MASHIRO]
What?
You did all that work and
you're still back for more?
That's right!
It's high-interest-rate
motivation!
I do have another cleaning
job at a location you
may have seen before.
[TAMOTSU gasps] Whoa, is that
place what I think it is?
Maybe while you're
cleaning the floor,
you'll get to see a
little something extra,
we'll just call it
a "business perk."
I like the way you think.
Moi! So many swimsuits,
how's a girl to decide?
I'll have to sit out for this.
Wait, what do you mean
you're gonna sit out?
You can't come this far
just to give it all up now!
I don't really have a choice.
Oh, of course!
Mayo will die if she reveals
too much skin, remember?
Oh yeah. I guess that
is a problem, huh?
Yeah. It's heartbreaking.
Obviously I'd love to do it
otherwise, it sounds so great.
[ARISA]
Wait, I know!
You don't have to give up
on your dream just yet!
[ARISA giggles]
[NIWAKA giggles]
[MATOME grunts]
[NICE]
Now we're talking, ladies!
Let's start filming.
Who wants to go first?
I can. But, what's up
with those guys?
I'm starting to get
a bad feeling here.
Oh. Don't worry
about them, they're fine
They're what we call
the Shower Squad!
What's a... Shower Squad?
[SHOWER SQUAD] Shower time!
Not-strange-at-all shower time!
[NIWAKA]
Oh! That feels so good!
Uh?
[NICE] That's it,
cupcake, lookin' nice!
[NICE]
Give me a smile, sweetie.
You're at a pool,
not the dentist.
There we go, close enough.
Oh yeah, hot-diggity-dog!
Hey! Speaking of dogs,
let's try on all fours, okay?
[ARISA]
Like this?
[NICE howls] Nice!
Now let's try a ball shot!
[ARISA]
This good?
[NICE]
Better than good!
That's an "Oh yeah,"
with a very big "O"!
Now the bed!
[ARISA]
How's this?
[NICE]
I'm getting excited!
By the quality of this strictly
professional footage, I mean.
All right. You're doing
such a great job,
now let's take
off that top, huh?
[ARISA]
Yeah! Okay!
Let's see here
Hey! Stop it!
That is not acceptable!
Look, maybe you're
not a genius,
but you should still
know better than that!
Oh yeah, you're right.
If I show all the goods now,
I'll have nothing to
fall back on later when
my career goes south.
Aw, come on,
don't spoil the fun!
You girls wanna
be famos, don't ya?
Is there a problem here, ladies?
I told you no idol can succeed
without a great body, remember?
But you never said
we had to do this!
I see what's going on!
This whole thing is just a
typical scam to get us to film
low-budget pornography!
I've had enough of this!
Let's get out of here, now!
Hey. That's no way to treat the
people who discovered you.
If you're not going to hold
up your side of the deal,
then I'm afraid we'll have to
resort to more aggressive
means of persuasion.
What?!
[CHIBUSA]
Heh!
[NICE]
Ha!
Bugged Ones.
I should've realized!
[NICE] Heh! Our plan was to
rule Akiba through a trio of
under-dressed and
overly-glittered stars
we controlled like puppets.
Fans will do anything
for their idols!
So that's it! I knew this
felt wrong from the start!
[MATOME, NIWAKA]
Huh?
I thought you'd seem more
authentic to the fans if
you believed you'd be a real pop
group right to the very end.
But if that's not
in the picture,
we'll just go to Plan B.
Bugs, attack!
[KUROBUGS shouts]
[ARISA shouts]
[MATOME shouts]
You aren't
a fighter, Niwaka. Run.
Oh. Right!
[pants]
[NIWAKA grunts]
[NIWAKA]
Owie!
[screams]
The Shower Squad,
you're helping me?
You have nothing to fear,
idol, we'll protect you.
[SThey'll never get past us.
[SHOWER SQUAD yelps]
[NIWAKA]
Huh? They're so weak!
[KUROBUGS growl]
[shouts]
[KUROBUGS giggle]
Big bro!
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[KUROBUGS yell]
[NIWAKA gasps] Holy crap,
that actually worked?
How'd you get here?
I've been here the entire time.
[CHIBUSA]
And who the hell are you?
I'm your part-time janitor!
[CHIBUSA gasps]
And I'm here...
to take out the trash!
I'm gonna wipe the
floor with you guys!
What is this,
a bad action movie?
Stop making puns and fight!
[ARISA yelps]
Aw, come on, Mayo, you can at
least give me a pity laugh!
[NICE shouts]
[MATOME]
I think this guy's the boss!
Help me! Take him out!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
On it!
I don't think so!
[TAMOTSU, CHIBUSA grunting]
[CHIBUSA giggles]
[CHIBUSA, TAMOTSU shout]
[CHIBUSA screams]
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
[ARISA shouts]
[ARISA whimpers]
[MATOME]
Arisa!
No doubt, he's a High Class!
[NICE growls, shouts]
[MATOME, NICE grunting]
Mayo!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[MATOME grunts]
[TAMOTSU grunting]
[shouts]
[NICE gasps]
I've pushed my way through
who knows how many
pop-show mosh pits lately.
Weaving through those Kurobugs
was a piece of cake!
[NICE grunts]
Impressive.
[TAMOTSU]
We've exposed your plot!
And next I'll expose your butt!
[NICE]
That's never gonna happen.
No one wants to see that!
Male nudity is lame!
[TAMOTSU yells]
[NICE groans]
[TAMOTSU]
It's the twenty-first century.
I'm an equal-opportunity
stripper!
[NICE yelps]
[TAMOTSU] Super Ultra Mega Spin
Tornado Disrobing Hurricane!
You're donion rings!
[NICE] This isn't the
happy ending I wanted!
All right, bro!
[MATOME chuckles]
Yay!
[gasps]
[CHIBUSA] What? Where am I?
What's going on?
[CHIBUSA] I see. Bug possession.
That's a first for me.
Well I'm sorry I caused you
ladies so much trouble.
Don't apologize,
it wasn't your fault.
The creatures who
took control of you
are the ones who bear
the real blame.
I don't have a clear memory
from my time as this so-called
"Bugged One,"
just jumbled fragments.
But it is true I see potential
in you girls as idols
and think you could
make it if you wanted.
As a token of apology, I could
work for you as your producer
and try to get you into
the business for real,
if you'd like me to.
[ALL gasp]
[SHOWER SQUAD MEN, TAMOTSU]
Huh?
Yeah of course, are you serious?
♪
[ALL pant]
[clapping]
[TAMOTSU]
Hm...
[sighs]
[ARISA] Our big debut concert,
and this is the turnout?
But that's not how I
imagined it going at all!
[NIWAKA] There wasn't
much we could do.
It was all so sudden and we
didn't have time to publicize.
Well you won't hear me complain.
I think it turned out fine.
[ARISA, NIWAKA]
Huh?
Two thumbs way up! Yeah!
Can you do it again?
Or sing a B-side or something?
Encore! Encore! Encore!
♪
[TAMOTSU] And thus, we built
a tower and named it Babel.
[ARISA] Nice, Tamotsu!
You sound downright mythic!
[TAMOTSU] Next episode
is about the Akiba Tree!
[ARISA] Not the red tower,
or skytree?
[TAMOTSU]
We don't have permission.
Akiba's Trip, the Animation :
Next up, "Ham Radio Fighters!"
[ARISA] It's time to play the
Waltz in the stratosphere!