Wake up. Time to patrol... Huh?
Usually I have to
drag him out of bed.
[ARISA] Moi there, partner,
Tamotsu's on the range!
Lucky for you, this gal can
cover for him right quick!
What?
He's meetin' an old cowpoke
he ain't seen in a while.
Sorry, I can't do this accent.
hat's quite the
fashion upgrade, man.
When we used to hang out,
you only wore black.
That's funny, I was
thinking a similar thing.
You look pretty
different too, Tamotsu.
[TAMOTSU]
Hm?
[ARAMATA] Like more mature,
or something.
Well, yeah, I guess I am.
A whole lot's happened to me
since I started living in Akiba.
Still, It doesn't matter
how much we've changed,
A friendship forged in
the fires of middle school
can never be broken.
[gasps]
[TAMOTSU]
Whoa, what the hell is that?
[gasps]
[TAMOTSU] Is that some kind
of Bugged One trick?
Hey, don't freak out, but
there's something next to you.
You're hilarious. Didn't I
tell you on the phone?
This is my girlfriend, Ubume.
We met at work, and she's
six kinds of amazing!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
Sorry, I think my brain
is broken. Who is that again?
[ARAMATA]
My girlfriend!
What, like a
girlfriend-girlfriend?
[screams]
♪
[TAMOTSU] This is nuts. He was
worse with girls than I was
in middle school,
and I wrote a scifi novel,
so that's saying a lot.
Was he just a late bloomer...
[ARISA] What's wrong with him?
His eyes look fermented.
Like a can of surströmming .
[NIWAKA] He was really looking
forward to seeing his old friend
after all this time.
I wonder what happened?
Well, we may not
know the details,
but I'm sure it was
something stupid, as usual.
[TAMOTSU grunts]
It's definitely not stupid!
[MATOME, ARISA, NIKAWA]
A girlfriend?
[NIKAWA]
So you've got girlfriend envy?
Of course!
I can never forgive that guy
for finding love before me!
I trusted him!
Tamotsu's so into his hobbies,
I didn't think he cared
about romance.
Honestly, I don't think he does.
It's just more of a
competition thing.
That's a pity, Tamotsu.
It's too bad you don't want one
of us to be your girlfriend.
True.
[MATOME groans]
Man! I was hoping a girlfriend
would just fall from the sky!
And preferably she'd bring
a robot servant with her!
I am so glad you added
the bit about the robot
so that description couldn't
apply to anyone in this room.
Now stop being an idiot
so we can go on patrol!
No! I don't want to!
I can't go on patrol till
I have a girlfriend!
What in the world does dating
have to do with patrolling?
[TAMOTSU]
Everything! Everything!
My friend's found love and is
enjoying the prime of his life
'cause he actually
has time for a life!
Meanwhile, I'm stuck living in a
warehouse basement in Akiba
fighting bug monsters and
hoping I don't evaporate
the next time my
boxers fall off!
Is it so terrible that I want to
find myself a beautiful flower
to decorate the metaphorical
casket that is my life?
[TAMOTSU sighs] Just once
I want to go on a date
with a cute, honest girl.
[MATOME, ARISA, NIWAKA sigh]
I'll admit I feel sorry for him.
[chuckles]
[NIWAKA]
Hey, bro. If it helps,
I can go on a date with you and
pretend to be your girlfriend!
Thanks. But you
lost me at "Hey, bro."
[NIWAKA grunts]
Fine! Then how about with me?
Huh?
A date with you?
Yeah go for it, bro,
you're never gonna get
a better offer than that!
I mean there's also Mayo,
but there's no way she'd
go on a date with you.
I doubt she knows the
first thing about dating.
Not to mention the fact that
she doesn't like you at all.
If she did, it would
be great, but--
Ahem. That is not true!
[TAMOTSU]
Huh?
[MATOME]
Tamotsu. We're going on a date!
We are? Why?
Don't overthink it, bro!
It's just practice
so you know what to do when
you get a real girlfriend!
Yeah, that's right!
It's like a real fake date!
A fake date?
Yeah. Guess if it's just
practice that's not a bad idea.
Right, it's for practice!
You think I'd do this
if it were for real?
I have zero interest in being
your real girlfriend-- Zero!
[TAMOTSU]
Fine, I believe you.
[MATOME] What's to believe?
It's just a fact!
Whatever, let's do our
fake date! Then we'll patrol!
But, this is all happening
so fast! Hold up!
[giggles]
[MATOME whimpers]
So, Mayo.
I've never had a fake date
before, what do we actually do?
Oh. That's a good question.
Uh, let's see.
--[phone beeps]
--[TAMOTSU, MATOME] Huh?
[NIWAKA] Just do the things that
make you happy! Heart emoji!
[MATOME]
The things that make me happy?
[TAMOTSU]
Hm?
I've got it!
People on dates like to go
to restaurants, don't they?
Let's go eat something tasty!
[NIWAKA] Mm-hm, good.
Start with the basics.
[TAMOTSU]
Works for me.
I eat those burgers and kebabs
by the base way too much.
[MATOME] I know!
So to shake things up,
I'll show you my favorite
gourmet spots in Akiba!
[MATOME]
I give you Bengal!
They've been serving the best
curry in town since 1973!
[TAMOTSU] Can you believe I've
never actually eaten here?
[MATOME]
Wow.
If you haven't had their curry,
you haven't had curry at all.
But going to a place
for the first time
takes so much courage.
Seriously?
What if they treat me bad
'cause I'm not a regular?
It's scary.
Don't worry, this restaurant
wouldn't do that.
Okay, but what if I do
something culturally offensive
and don't realize it?
Just put the food
in your mouth.
Can we get two beef square
curries and two lassis?
[TAMOTSU] I see. It looks
like a smooth Indian curry.
I can get behind that.
[MATOME]
Nope, wrong.
Bengal doesn't make
an Indian curry,
it's called "Indian style".
It's not classic Indian
or European either.
It's their own original
spin on the flavors.
[TAMOTSU]
Huh...
Delicious! It has the deep,
punch-you-in-the-face fragrance
and spices of Indian curry,
but with the refinement
of the European style!
It's a true East-Meets-West!
The Gandhara of delicacies!
And the meat's boiled
to perfection!
It's indescribable!
It's a good
filling portion, too!
I know right?
And if you're extra hungry,
you can order double meat!
Wow, it's amazing!
They're enjoying the food
and having a good time!
But the next step is key!
Ah! You're right, you can't
talk about curry in Akiba
if you haven't eaten at Bengal.
And the layer of cinnamon
in the lassi's
an interesting twist, too.
[MATOME] Come on, let's go
to the next place.
Uh? Next?
[MATOME] Lucky for us,
it's right next door!
[TAMOTSU]
So we're eating here too?
[MATOME]
Of course!
Gansen is Akiba's most
famous Chinese place!
[TAMOTSU]
Whoa. Their menu's huge.
[MATOME] Plus there's the
weekly fried rice specials
and limited dishes you can
hear about if you follow
Gone, the owner online,
like I naturally do!
[TAMOTSU]
Uh-huh...
[MATOME] This is the
weekend-only beef tendon
in starchy sauce fried rice!
Wow. It looks great.
Oh, it is!
Just mix the soft boiled
egg on top, and boom!
Paradise!
[MATOME giggles]
It's so good!
I want that in my mouth.
But why a second meal?
Impressive. The fried rice in
this dish is perfectly balanced,
dry and smooth,
yet jam-packed with flavor.
And it's a perfect combo
with the beef tendon sauce!
It's like Liu Bei
and Zhuge Liang
running an empire
of flavor! Hm?
[MATOME giggles]
Oh yeah...
[TAMOTSU]
Hm?
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
[MATOME]
Alright here's our next stop!
--[ARISA gasps]
--[NIWAKA] They're eating again?
So this is Kitchen
Jiro. I've heard of this place
for years but never
tried it, either.
It's the best "set meal"
restaurant in town!
Since we've already had curry
today, I'll try the minced meat
cutlet and fried
chicken with large rice.
You really still have
room for all that?
Duh! I'm gonna make room!
We have to eat when
we can, Tamotsu.
I can't believe you're not
eating. What, are you on a diet?
No, just full.
[MATOME] The meals here are huge
but reasonably priced and great!
Oh... Wow! The miso
soup is tasty, too!
Just look how tender and
juicy this cutlet is!
The minced meat goes perfectly
with the sweetness of
the onions, and don't even
get me started on how well
it complements the rice!
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum!
Sounds good.
Uh... Gimme!
Tamotsu, that's mine!
Mm! Wow the breading's
so crispy!
Never mind being full,
I can't say no to this!
[gasps]
[MATOME] A shared bite's
kinda like an indirect kiss.
Whatcha thinking?
No, nothing, just eating
delicious food!
[TAMOTSU gasps]
When you're eating, you look
the happiest I've ever seen you.
It's great. Just watching
you makes me hungry again.
[MATOME gasps] I guess that's
sort of a compliment, so thanks?
Anyway... If you're hungry,
where to next?
[NIWAKA, ARISA groan]
[TAMOTSU groans]
This seems less like a date
and more like an extreme
eating challenge.
I can't believe they went
to four more restaurants.
I'm sorry. I made you
eat too much, didn't I?
I'm... fine.
It's amazing, though. I've never
seen anyone eat like you do.
[MATOME gasps]
The truth is, well, I've lived
here for a long time.
And this district has
been through a lot.
There were darker days, when
there was almost nothing to eat.
I was so hungry it hurt.
And you never forget
how that feels.
So now, I eat when I can.
Gee, I had no idea.
Well, eating when you have the
chance sounds like a pretty good
philosophy for staying happy.
And I guess the fact we can
is also a nice reminder
we live in peaceful times.
Exactly.
[TAMOTSU] Hm. Okay you've
shown me your favorite places,
so why don't I show
you one of mine?
Ramen Kagemusha ?
It's that heavy-hitting
type that's in style.
So I'm thinking that means
it's right up your alley.
Are you sure this won't
make you feel sick?
Yeah sure, one bowl
never hurt anyone.
Hey guys, what's cooking?
[SUIDOBASHI, TAMOTSU grunt]
Okay, that was unexpected.
Huh? Hey! A vigilante!
What's wrong?
He's like a black hole.
[TAMOTSU, MATOME gasp]
[COOK A]
Please! Enough!
[TAMOTSU, MATOME]
Huh?
[SHOPPERS gasp]
Ah! Another bowl!
That brings the bounty
to 240,000y en!
Please, you have to stop!
That promotion was to help
my business, not to bankrupt me!
And you're wiping me out
of noodles and broth, too!
Hey! You're the one
who offered that bounty,
you dope, don't blame me!
Just get back in that kitchen
and make me another bowl
with extra toppings, now!
Wait, who is that guy?
A noodle hog, that's who!
Oh, when did you show up?
I've been here for an
hour waiting for ramen,
but that guy's stopping
everyone from ordering!
It's a lunch nightmare!
Hold on. I've seen him before.
On TV, maybe?
Yeah that's it! He's the world
champion corndog eater!
The food soldier,
Black Hole Kurota!
I heard he lost to
his rival, Minimum Tashiro,
in the last contest,
and then went missing.
I don't care about
his backstory, Tamotsu,
just make him stop!
Hey! Can't you see all these
customers are waiting?
[KUROTA] Huh? You saying
I'm not a customer too?
I'm saying it's a restaurant,
not your training kitchen!
I've got the right to eat what
I want, when I want, cupcake!
If you want me to listen to you,
why don't you challenge me
to an eating contest like
that silly girl just did.
If you can actually beat me,
I'll do what you say.
[TAMOTSU grunts] So that's
what happened to her.
[MATOME]
You're on!
[TAMOTSU, KUROTA]
Hm?
[MATOME]
If that's what it takes, fine!
As one of the proud vigilantes
who protects the people
of Akiba, I challenge
you to an eating duel!
It's another shocker
in Akiba, folks!
This time it's an impromptu
ramen-eating battle!
Right here in our
very own Horin Park!
The world-famous competitive
eater, Black Hole Kurota,
has been recklessly
challenged by the leader of
Electric Mayonnaise, a novice
who we will now call
Matome "Vacuum" Mayonaka.
Can she prevail with
her petite figure?
Well she better, 'cause they've
agreed the loser will pick up
the winner's tab at all
restaurants in Akiba
from now on!
I feel like this got out
of hand really fast!
Don't worry, you guys.
Mayo can handle him.
But what if she loses?
Then who's gonna pay
all those food bills?
Dunno, but it won't be me!]
Yeah, me neither!
You really think a little
girl like you can take me,
a professional food soldier,
who's won against the
best in the world?
Of course I can.
Because you don't appreciate the
food, you just do it for sport.
You don't deserve to overeat.
[KUROTA scoffs]
Taste doesn't matter.
Once it's in your stomach,
it's all the same.
[MASUTO]
The clock is set for one hour!
Whoever eats the most
ramen before time expires
will be the winner!
Okay contestants, get your
chopsticks ready! And... Go!
[horn blares]
[MASUTO] If Kurota wins
that meal ticket, he could hog
food at all the restaurants
throughout Akiba!
So the stakes are high,
and they've both hit
the ground running!
Go on. Eat, Mayo!
Eat for Akiba's future!
You can do it!
A one-hour contest, huh?
That means pacing's
gonna be crucial.
[MATOME] This is delicious.
I could do this all day.
That girl's good,
especially for a newcomer.
Her water timing's perfect.
Yeah, the water's key.
if you drink too much of it,
the noodles bloat
up in your stomach.
Next bowl!
Next bowl, please!
[MASUTO] And they finished
their first bowls
almost simultaneously!
So fast!
Just watching them eat like
that gives me a stomach ache.
Yeah! Eat that ramen, Ma!
[KUROTA]
Next bowl!
[MATOME]
Next bowl, please!
[MASUTO] The two eaters
are still neck-and-neck!
Next bowl, please!
Next bowl!
[MASUTO] They've both
finished their tenth serving!
This competition is intense!
Man, they're so evenly matched.
She needs a tactic
to pull ahead.
[MATOME] How can I
speed this up? I know!
[MATOME grunts]
[TAMOTSU gasps]
What the--?
Vacuum Mayonaka has
thrown her ramen skyward
and I have no idea why!
Is she throwing this fight?
No! She caught it!
She tossed with her right hand
and caught with her left!
And now she's back to slurping!
Oh, now I get it.
She's throwing the noodles
to save herself time. The air
is cooling them down for her!
So she doesn't have to
waste valuable seconds
blowing on them herself!
You're so awesome, Mayo!
Look at her go,
she's really speeding up!
[MASUTO] Astounding! Vacuum
Mayonaka has created a one-woman
cooling-and-eating loop,
with factory-like
precision and speed!
Black Hole Kurota has
been left in the dust!
Can she keep this up?
Son of a bitch! All right, bring
me that pitcher of water!
Why would he want to
drink extra water?
He's just gonna
fill himself up.
I am the world-famous
Black Hole Kurota!
I am not going to lose
to an eating amateur!
[MASUTO]
What's this?
Kurota has just dumped cold
water into his ramen!
--[MATOME] How could you?
--[TAMOTSU] No way!
What's he thinking?
He's completely
defiling the ramen!
That's the unconscionable
taste-destroying technique
known as Darkness Engulfing!
That broth is
totally ruined now!
You monster!
People worked hard to make that
and you killed the flavor!
[KUROTA grunts] And why
would I care about that?
The taste is meaningless!
This contest is about who
can eat the most, period!
And I'll do whatever
it takes to win!
Besides, once it's in your gut,
it just turns into crap,
so who cares?!
[MASUTO] Kurota is now
shotgunning the ramen
with incredible speed!
So that's what it looks like
when a food soldier turns
to the dark side.
It's a ramen-flavored
drink now, which is so "ew!"
[MASUTO] That's right, fans!
This is the technique Kurota
developed in the Akiba
competitive eating circuit!
It's the Akiba Super High
Building Eating Style!
[MASUTO]
Sure it's extremely messy,
but it's also extremely fast!
He takes back the lead!
[MATOME grunts]
Damn it. She's gonna lose.
I'm still not paying for this!
[TAMOTSU gasps] Professor!
Do you have a...
What? Now why would
I randomly bring a--
Oh? Oh, that's funny,
I actually did.
II knew it! Okay, can I
borrow it? Thanks!
[TAMOTSU]
Mayo! Use this!
[MATOME gasps]
What's this for? Wait, ice?
That's right! I made it
with this instant ice maker
the Professor was
carrying for no reason!
Now drop those cubes
in your ramen!
[gasps]
But why?
Oh, right! Understood!
[MASUTO]
Vacuum Mayonaka is adding ice,
cooling her ramen even faster!
And now she's back to slurping
with superhuman speed!
[laughs] I knew it, rookie!
After all that talk about
appreciating the taste,
you're the same as me!
A food soldier who's
gone to the dark side
and only cares about winning,
doing whatever it takes no
matter how it ruins the flavor!
Is he right? Has Mayo just
turned to the dark side?
Is she consumed by rage,
her only hunger the
hunger to win contests?
Guys, relax, she hasn't
turned to the dark side,
we found a good way to win.
Hey, look at those cubes
she put in her bowl.
it's not just water like
we thought! That color!
It's frozen ramen broth!
[SPECTATOR B]
Oh, I see!
That would just cool the ramen
without ruining the flavor.
It's not Darkness Engulfing!
No way!
[MASUTO] Vacuum Mayonaka
has not been seduced
by the dark side, after all!
She remains a beacon of hope
for food soldiers everywhere!
You're an inspiration!
It's time to take
back the lead, girl!
Damn it. She may be gaining,
but I'm still up by one bowl.
I just have to keep--
[KUROTA groans]
[MASUTO]
What's wrong with Kurota?
He's suddenly stopped!
I bet it's 'cause he
guzzled all of that water!
Yeah, the noodles
must be expanding and
clogging up his stomach!
He doesn't have any more room!
[MASUTO]
One minute left!
I'd like one more, please!
[MASUTO]
She's tied it up!
[KUROTA grunts]
I have to force it!
[KUROTA groans]
[MASUTO] Kurota is down!
He's reached his limit
and can't eat any more!
But Vacuum is stopping too!
I'm so full.
But I can't quit yet!
Done!
[horn blares]
[MASUTO]
Time's up!
Black Hole Kurota: 30 bowls!
Vacuum Mayonaka:
30 bowls and one bite!
You know what that means!
Vacuum Mayonaka is
the winner of this battle!
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[NIWAKA]
All right, Mayo!
[TAMOTSU]
Yeah!
Damn it! I lost
to a little girl!
[MATOME]
That's right you did.
Now as for our wager,
I'm not gonna make you
buy my food, Kurota.
[KUROTA gasps]
Just promise to stop eating like
a disposal and enjoy the flavor.
Agree to that and we're even.
That's what you want?
You're really just gonna let
me off the hook that easy?
[MATOME]
Yup.
Well I say hell no!
[MATOME gasps]
[KUROTA grunts]
You may have won the battle.
But I won't let that stop me
from winning the war!
I'm gonna starve
the people of Akiba
by eating every bit of food!
Then when they're too weak
to resist, I will conquer!
[BOTH]
He's a Bugged One?!
I won't quit 'til all
of Akiba is in my belly!
To help me achieve that dream,
I've pledged my
allegiance to Metrotica.
And if you plan to stop me,
I'll just have to eat you too!
[ALL gasp]
[ARISA] He's sucking us
in like a real black hole!
[KUROTA]
I'll eat the world!
[MASUTO] It's an out-of-season
gust of wind!
And this concludes our
broadcast! Bye!
[ALL scream]
At least I wore some!
[screaming continues]
[KUROTA] Now that my
pyloric canal is open,
no one can stop me!
No! We have to do something!
Yeah but what?
I can barely move!
[gasps]
That's it!
Mayo! When I say "go,"
jump toward Kurota!
Are you crazy, I don't
want to go in his belly!
That won't happen!
Just trust me!
[KUROTA grunts]
No!
Now go!
[MATOME]
Got it!
[KUROTA screams]
Impossible!
[SPECTATOR B coughs] What just
happened and why am I naked?
[gasps] I don't know, but look!
Ramen wearing underwear!
Bet you've never
seen that before!
[TAMOTSU]
That was some kind of date!
[MATOME] Yeah, I'm sorry.
I doubt that so-called
"practice" will apply
to normal dates.
Well it definitely
wasn't typical,
but that doesn't mean
it was lousy. I mean,
for a couple of Buggy fighters,
it really couldn't
have gone better.
What?
You heard me right, Mayo,
who else in the world could
go on a date like that?
We got to enjoy
the best of Akiba
and save it at the same time!
Oh. Yeah, I guess so.
[stomach growls]
[ARISA gasps]
Whoa. You're hungry
again already?
Well I got relaxed so
then my stomach did too.
And you know what they say,
there's always room for dessert!
I'll swing by a convenience
store for some ice cre--
[MATOME gasps]
Actually there's a new
sweets store that I'm curious
about but I haven't gone in yet.
So, want to help with
my "first time anxiety"?
That sounds good. But are
you sure you want to?
[TAMOTSU]
Mm-hm! Come on, it looks great!
And I hear their
mamekan 's to die for!
[BOTH giggle]
[MATOME gasps]
♪
[NIWAKA] Bro, come on! I want
a limited-edition event ticket!
[TAMOTSU] They use that
term for everything now.
L.E. used to mean just
figures in sweet boxes!
[NIWAKA] Well, who wants a
figure when you can have a
live show experience!
[TAMOTSU] Next Akiba's Trip ,
the Animation :
"The Midsummer Akiba
Festival Begins!"
[NIWAKA]
Just say no to evil scalpers!