[NARRATOR] Akihabara,
the otaku city of dreams,
is now under attack from
mysterious monstrosities
known as the Bugged Ones.
Some brave citizens have
formed vigilante groups
to resist this Buggy scourge,
but the invasion intensifies
with each new day.
This is the story
of Tamotsu Denkigai,
a young man given
Bugged Ones powers,
turned from superfan
into superhero.
Can he and his merry band
save the greatest shopping
neighborhood in the world?!
♪
[STAGE MANAGER] Okay, that's a
wrap for the lighting
and mic checks!
Crew, take fifteen!
[TAMOTSU]
Mm-hm!
[SUIDOBASHI]
Hey, Tamotsu!
Can you at least act
like you're working?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Though I'd say
as their producer,
watching rehearsal's part of
my super-important job!
Oh, give me a break,
you're the errand boy!
If you want to produce
something that's helpful,
then go produce posters
on those walls!
Aw, man! Okay fine, but I
am not an errand boy!
Don't come back
till they're all up.
And make sure they're straight!
Wow! Marvelous, ladies,
you really are honing
your stage presence!
Perform like that at
the Akiba Festival,
and you'll generate major buzz.
I'm telling you, you'll shoot
straight to the top!
Well it's all thanks
to you, Miss Benikage!
We'd be nowhere if our Super
Hyper Media Producer hadn't done
some Super Hyper
Media Producing!
[CHIBUSA chuckles]
While I do appreciate
the compliment, Arisa.
You girls deserve the credit.
I'm just a guide.
It's your hard work that's
gotten you here.
I guess all those small
gigs outside the spotlight
really helped!
Hope so.
Yes. If I just close my eyes I
can see every struggle you girls
have gone through, all the
way from your debut to now,
and it's been quite
the rollercoaster.
[ALL]
Yay! We are Mania!
[CHIBUSA] There was that
whole fish head debacle.
[NIWAKA]
Free samples!
[MATOME]
They're totally free!
[NIWAKA] Greatest thing
since sliced bread!
Sliced and yummy fish head!
[CHIBUSA] Then there was
the attention-getting stunt
for that mystery sponsor...
Yay, congratulations!
[ARISA] Find out what this is
for, and you could win a prize!
Yeah I still don't understand
what that one was about.
After all that work and
hardship on the Akiba Strip,
You're finally facing
your big day.
The day you'll shoot
up like a rocket
and join the other bright,
shining stars in the sky.
Especially you, Miss Mayo.
[MATOME]
Huh?
When you're performing
under those lights,
you have the
unmistakable expression
of a girl who's in love.
Maybe there's someone special
in your life making you
sing from the heart?
[MATOME gasps]
[TAMOTSU]
Double peace!
[MATOME grunts]
There's no one special!
There's not! There's not!
[CHIBUSA] Fine, you don't
have to bite my head off.
[MATOME] I'm telling you,
there's no one!
[CHIBUSA] You realize
your face has turned
the color of your hair, right?
[MATOME] Because I'm so
angry you're mistaken!
[CHIBUSA] All right, all right.
Don't strain your voice.
[MATOME] Now when do we eat?
Getting angry makes me hungry.
♪
[TAMOTSU]
There we go.
[sighs]
Not a wrinkle in sight!
[KAGE]
Working hard, man?
[TAMOTSU]
Huh? What up, Kage?
Looks like you could use a
burger break. My treat!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE]
Hi, welcome to Carl's!
Wow, you ordered the six
dollar without hesitation.
Your great love of
spending knows no bounds.
But, anyway, what's this
Akiba Festival?
[TAMOTSU] I hear it's gonna
be a pretty flashy show.
It's part of this "Nice Japan"
initiative the government
just rolled out.
Everyone's putting in a
ton of effort... and dough.
[KAGE] Hmm. Did you say
just say "Nice Japan"?
[PRESS SECRETARY] Today we're
proud to designate
Akihabara a special
subculture zone.
We'll encourage tourists from
all around the world to visit
this unique treasure, and also
seek to boost Japan's image
as a wellspring of new
ideas and culture.
This is a key element of our
"Nice Japan" initiative
that we'll continue to build
on throughout the year,
and we've got a lot of great
events in the works to get
people feeling jazzed
and ready to go!
Like the Akiba Festival!
Coming this midsummer!
[REPORTERS chatter]
[Akiba's become a holy land for
enthusiasts of countless genres,
and we want super fans to
help us make a festival
to celebrate all that they love!
So are all you people
ready to party or what?
A summer festival created
by fans, for fans, huh?
Pretty awesome, right?
The government's actually
encouraging us to geek out!
If I don't give my all to this,
it'll be an affront
to all I stand for!
And if that's not reason enough,
volunteering as a staff member
also gives me early access to
the limited-edition
festival merch!
At last we come to the
heart of the matter.
I know what motivates you,
old buddy.
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
So what do you say, Kage?
You're a super-fan. Wanna help?
Nah, I think I'll pass.
[TAMOTSU] Ah, come on!
You were born for this!
Okay, gotta get my gameface on.
It's time to drive some trains!
[gasps]
What's that crowd?
Is everything okay, fol--?
[screams]
[AUDIO CLERK hums]
Huh?
Guess that part-timer
was slacking off again.
Where's the pride? Eh?
Huh? What's going on?
Who would do this?
[AUDIO CLERK]
Huh?
[screams]
[AUDIO CLERK] No... No!
All my beautiful capsules!
[SHOPPER A]
Hm...
[gasps]
Yes! I found it!
It's the new book by famous fan
fiction author, Type Question.
This is so hard to get!
[SHOPPER A grunts]
I'm so pumped!
I can't wait, I have to
read it right now!
[SHOPPER A hums]
[gasps]
All the pages are blank!
[DELIVERY MAN]
Gonzo Delivery!
[SHOPPER B]
Coming!
Alright! My limited-edition
Earphones figurine set
has finally arrived!
It's so crazy-popular,
the first shipment sold
out instantaneously!
Come to papa! Huh?
[SHOPPER B screams]
Producer Tamotsu,
I'm feeling kinda parched.
Here you go!
Producer Tamotsu, my shoulders
could really use a massage.
Your wish is my command!
Producer Tamotsu, I'm hungry,
I'll take the usual, please.
I thought you'd ask.
[MATOME sighs]
Hey! She was right!
You call me producer
but you're just treating
me like an errand boy!
Why are you mad? That's standard
practice in the idol biz.
Don't you know producer's just
a nice word for man-slave?
I know, but an errand
boy can still dream. Huh?
[SUIDOBASHI grunts]
[TAMOTSU]
Is this about the posters?
'Cause I hung 'em
up real straight.
Tamotsu Denkigai!
[TAMOTSU]
Uh...
[SUIDOBASHI]
Matome Mayonaka!
Arisa Ahokainen!
Get ready to gasp.
Because you're all under arrest!
[ALL gasp]
[SUIDOBASHI]
Order! Order! Let's begin!
The Akiba vigilante court,
presided by the Main Street
Vigilantes, is now in session
in this hall of the Akiba guild!
[ARISA] You have a court?
[MATOME]
Since when?
Hey! This is ridiculous!
What did we do wrong?
You've betrayed the public trust
and the solemn duty
of all vigilantes!
Instead of keeping the peace
in Akiba like you've vowed,
you've created
chaos of your own!
And it's an even greater sin
that you're doing it now,
right before the festival!
Okay slow down,
what chaos did we cause?
Yeah what are you
talking about?
These charges are false!
[SHOHEI] Don't play innocent!
We have all the proof we need!
What proof?
That's enough talk,
you scoundrels!
Just look at this
crime scene footage!
[SUIDOBASHI] This tree
near the Showa Dori exit of
the JR Akihabara station was
brutally slain in the prime of
its life, with this card jabbed
into its still-warm stump!
[ALL gasp]
[SUIDOBASHI]
Exhibit B!
All the wondrous capsule toys
were stolen from this store!
And on the pile of
empties left behind?
Another card, with a cruelly
sarcastic taunt!
And on it goes! The vile list of
atrocities is so long it would
take days to go
through all of them!
Fan fiction books on sale at
Tora no Ana swapped with blanks,
collectible figurines replaced
with suggestively-molded
devil's tongue, trading cards
from bags of potato chips
callously removed!
And on and on and on!
Anyone could have
written those cards,
so they don't prove anything!
And why would we just
tell everyone it was us?
[SUIDOBASHI] I see. So you want
to go down swinging, do ya?
Okay fine! Then feast your
eyes on the smoking gun!
This crude and talentless
graffiti was scrawled
on the side of the
Myojinzka Bridge!
And a security camera caught
you in the act, you morons!
Oh, come on!
How can you think that's me?
[ARISA] Or me?
I don't look like that!
It's like a bootleg figurine of
me you'd buy off the street!
When she puts it like that,
she does have a point.
Well I guess the eyes are a
little bit off, aren't they?
Maybe, but so what?
The outfits are the same!
The eyes are hardly the
only difference, guys!
If I looked like that,
I'd never leave the house!
[SUIDOBASHI]
Hm. I guess not, but look!
What about Matome?
She looks exactly the same!
[MATOME]
Huh?
[ARISA] Mm. I'll admit, that
does look like Ma's back side.
But without seeing her face,
we can't know for sure, right?
So you admit it's
possible that's Matome!
[TAMOTSU]
No! There's no way!
Tamotsu.
I can testify right now!
It's impossible that's her!
You expect us to simply take
your word for that, Tamotsu?
Or do you actually
have proof?
Mayo's part of our team and
we do everything together!
We would know if she'd left!
Besides, she's way
too good to do this!
[MATOME gasps]
[SUIDOBASHI grunts]
I'm sorry, but you vouching
for her does not
satisfy this court!
Unless you can present
tangible proof,
we have no choice but
to continue this trial!
[TAMOTSU] Okay, if you want to
keep wearing your little judge
robe that's fine with me,
we'll just catch these fakers
and bring 'em back to you.
How does that sound for justice?
I must say, that was a
pretty cool line, Tamotsu,
but now what do we do?
[TAMOTSU] Like I said!
We catch those fakers!
Okay. But how do we do that?
Well I haven't gotten to
that part of the plan yet.
What should we do, Professor?
[PROFESSOR gasps]
Uh, let's see.
We should start with what
we know about these posers,
which isn't very much except
they seem to enjoy performing
acts otaku consider
unspeakably evil as a way
to soil the good name of
Electric Mayonnaise, correct?
Oh! Why don't we do a
stakeout where we think they'll
strike next, then we can catch
'em in the act and grab 'em,
like they do in the movies!
Yeah. But how do
we figure that out
[NIWAKA] Uh... Good question.
They have been all over the map.
[ARISA] What do
you think, Ma? Any ideas?
For what? Who this girl is?
No I mean where do you
think they'll strike next
to make otaku mad at us?
Oh right, sorry.
I don't know, lots of
things make otaku mad.
Yeah, that's true.
[ALL sigh]
[TAMOTSU]
Wait. I got it!
[MATOME]
What?
[ARISA]
You know where they'll go?
[URAME chuckles]
[TAMOTSU]
I knew you'd come here!
[ARISA] Like moths to a
pop-idol-stage flame!
When it comes to fandom,
nothing's more sacred than
camping out over
night to line up
for limited-edition
merchandise!
I knew you'd try
to mess with that!
We see right through
your scheme to ruin our
reputation as vigilante
defenders of Akiba!
You want us to get kicked out,
so that you'll be
free to conquer!
It's a plan far too sinister
to come from human brains!
No. You're Bugged Ones--
[ALL yelp]
Guys, we practiced
that for hours!
[ARISA] It's your fault!
You changed poses too fast!
[BUGGYS grunt]
[grunting]
You're about a million
light-years away
from accurately cosplaying me.
And that's not kung fu!
[grunting continues]
--[BUGGY TAMOTSU] Hm?
--[TAMOTSU gasps]
[gasps, screams]
[TAMOTSU grunts]
Tamotsu!
Say moimoi you overgrown,
no good, thick-necked,
inconsiderately tall,
clearly-not-Finnish, lousy--
[grunts, shouts]
Not too bad for knock-offs, huh?
But they won't knock off me!
[MATOME, URAME
grunting, shouting]
[grunting, shouting continues]
[MATOME screams]
[grunts]
[grunting, shouting]
[BUGGYS scream]
And stay down!
Rip-offs may be cheap,
but they can't measure
up to the real deal!
Now that's what I
call a case closed!
Huh? Wait, where'd the
other one go?
[TAMOTSU gasps]
[MATOME grunts, gasps]
Can't be... no way.
[URAME grunts]
[MATOME gasps]
Tamotsu!
That was close. You okay?
[grunts]
[ARISA shouts] It's time to
face the music, faker,
and pay for what you've done!
[TAMOTSU] Hope you like
being interrogated!
[grunts]
[ALL shouts, cough]
[ALL gasp]
[MATOME]
She got away.
[ARISA] Huh? What is she,
like a ninja?
[TAMOTSU] Damn, a smoke
bomb's a classic move!
How'd we fall for that?
This is bad. How are we
gonna exonerate Ma
if we don't have the fake one?
[TAMOTSU grunts]
Good question.
It's all good, I'm on it!
Professor?
[ARISA]
Huh? Where did you come from?
[PROFESSOR]
Don't worry about that.
All that really matters is
I captured the whole fight
with my new invention,
the super ultra crispy
clean night vision camera!
Complete with an
irresistibly retro design!
[ALL gasp]
[TAMOTSU]
Yeah! You did it!
[PROFESSOR] Hey! Be careful!
Don't make me drop the camera!
Oh, okay, I'm getting nauseous
I'm sorry!
[VIGILANTES]
Please forgive us!
It's cool, as long as
you're convinced. Right, Mayo?
[MATOME gasps]
Oh yeah! Fine.
[TAMOTSU] You were protecting
Akiba, I know that.
What do you say we
shake hands and make up?
What? You're seriously
going to forgive me?
After all of my
terrible accusations?
Thank you, Tamotsu.
You're such a good guy.
Now let's get back to work,
and make sure this festival
kicks major butt!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Hello and welcome to
the very first Akiba Festival!
Today's opening event,
Idol Festa, will be kicked off
by a new idol trio rapidly
shooting up the charts!
Give it up for Mania!
♪
[gasps]
Oh no, what's happening now?
A technical issue?
[TAMOTSU, SUIDOBASHI]
Huh?
[MASUTO]
Listen up, fans!
We've got a breaking,
bombshell report!
[TAMOTSU, SUIDOBASHI]
Huh?
And I'm sorry to say
the news is not good!
The whole Akiba Festival
has been cancelled!
[ALL gasp]
[CROWD chatters]
To learn more, we're switching
to a live feed of the minister's
press conference,
which has just begun!
[REPORTER A] Minister Kiyoi!
What can you tell us?
Why has the festival been
abruptly cancelled?
After careful review
of the programming
set up by the
festival organizers,
We've determined this
event is wholly unfit as a
government project and
must be shut down.
But we were told the government
is actively promoting the Akiba
subculture as part of the
Nice Japan initiative.
Is that not true?
Let me set the record
straight on that.
What we support is healthy.
globally-facing subculture,
like movies with artistic worth.
We must completely eradicate
this otaku culture,
which has become a dangerous
pornographic industry!
[REPORTERS chatter]
You just used the words
"completely eradicate,"
which some of our viewers
might find slightly troubling.
Do you have specific
policies in mind?
Yes I do. Let it be known.
Starting tomorrow we'll be
enforcing a full Akiba Ban!
[ALL gasp]
[MATOME]
That can't be true.
[MASUTO sighs] Not just
cancelling the festival,
but a new law banning
all of Akiba?
No offense, But don't you think
you're going a little too far?
[KIKUCHI] This is
only the beginning.
The real battle starts now.
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[TAMOTSU exhales]
--[phone rings]
--[TAMOTSU grunts]
Yeah, what's up?
[URAME mimicking Matome]
Tamotsu! Come quick.
It's her. My imposter, she's--
Wait. What?
Mayo, did she attack?
[URAME mimicking Matome]
Come to Manseibashi. Hurry!
I don't know how long I can--
[TAMOTSU]
What? Hello?
[gasps]
[TAMOTSU]
Mayo!
I'm coming!
[TAMOTSU] No! Did she do
this to you? Talk to me!
[gasps]
[URAME gasps]
[TAMOTSU grunts]
What's he mean?
Why is he going there?
[gasps]
[MATOME gasps]
No. Don't tell me.
Tamotsu!
♪
[KIYOI]
Akihabara is a city of dreams,
and I've been dreaming
for a long, long time.
[TAMOTSU]
Who the hell are you?
[ARISA] Tamotsu! We have to
say moimoi! Don't forget me!
[TAMOTSU] Arisa, what are
you talking about?
Next time on Akiba's Trip ,
The Animation :
"Electric Mayo's Falling Apart!"
[ARISA]
I am eternally forever!