[NARRATOR] Akihabara,
the otaku city of dreams,
is now under attack from
mysterious monstrosities
known as the Bugged Ones.
Some brave citizens have
formed vigilante groups
to resist this Buggy scourge,
but the invasion intensifies
with each new day.
This is the story
of Tamotsu Denkigai,
a young man given
Bugged Ones powers,
turned from superfan
into superhero.
Can he and his merry band
save the greatest shopping
neighborhood in the world?!
There! This beam antenna should
give me clear enough VHF
reception to catch everything
from Hokkaido and Okinawa too!
Been ten years since I got
my Amateur Fourth Class.
Now that I've finally earned
my Amateur First Class License,
it would be a crime not to
spend this much on gear.
What is that?
It's a big antenna
for amateur radio.
[MATOME, ARISA]
Amateur radio?
[NIWAKA] Yeah, he's had
an antenna at home
ever since elementary school.
I thought he was over it,
but he stumbled on a
radio shop in Akiba,
and now the passion's
back with a vengeance.
[ARISA] So his idol addiction
already went moi moi?
[MATOME] Did he really
have to put an antenna
that big on our base?
Yeah, looking good, Tamotsu!
If these atmospheric
conditions hold up,
we could even have a sporadic E.
Gotcha! We're picking up
all the way from Area 6!
I'm so good--
[groans]
--[NIWAKA, ARISA shout]
--[MATOME] Oh, no!
[TAMOTSU screams]
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[TAMOTSU]
Hey, watch it, Professor!
You trying to break me in half?
[PROFESSOR]
Sorry, my bad!
[ALL sigh]
[PROFESSOR]
It's the perfect day for radio!
I'm sure nothing's
gonna go wrong!
♪
[TAMOTSU]
Tamotsu here, hailing Arisa.
Where are you, over?
[ARISA] Copy, this is Arisa.
Target in sight.
Standing by for orders. Over.
[NIWAKA]
Niwaka, chiming in!
You've got a visual on
the target? That's great! Over.
Cut the chatter, sis,
and Arisa, hold your position,
alpha team will confirm, over.
[ARISA] Arisa here, negative,
we have to to hurry
or it'll all be over, over!
What? Tamotsu to Arisa,
stay put! It's too risky, over!
[ARISA]
There's no time, I'm going in!
[gasps]
Arisa. Over and out!
[ARISA]
Firsties! Moi moi!
We are number one!
Super-rare item grabbed
at bargain price! Victory!
[TAMOTSU] You're a loose cannon,
Arisa, I told you to wait!
This shop had it for a
hundred-twenty less!
You're gonna bankrupt us, over!
This is Niwaka, hailing her bro.
If you're gonna be cheap,
can't you do it quietly, over?
That's a negatory, over.
You really have to
use those things
when you're this
close to each other?
If I want to use them
at all, then yes!
They only reach 30
meters in the city.
Which brings me to
our next mission.
[TAMOTSU]
Ha! It's time to upgrade...
[TAMOTSU] ...our communications
infrastructure!
I love you, Fuji store.
I'd have your radio babies.
[TAMOTSU] Oh wow,
the legendary Truo TO830!
Whoa! The Yagesu GT101Z!
And look, that's the FGDX9000!
And the DS990!
What, the Kenrod M2400,
but that's crazy rare!
It even has the UT1200
and UT430S add-ons for
triple-band support, and we all
know how important that is!
Oh, the Yagesu SL2100 tube amp,
that's a sight for sore eyes!
This one uses the 572B at
the final step. Ingenious!
You can talk to me all day
about automatic tuning
and crystal-clear digital
signals, but the warmth
you get from this little bad
boy just can't be beat!
Can I kiss it?
Tell me I can kiss it!
[NIWAKA sighs]
[MALE RADIO VOICE A]
Cleared for landing.
Radar guidance has
been activated.
[gasps] I don't know
who's sending that,
but it sounds kind
of top-secret.
Are you sure we're
allowed to listen?
Oh yeah, the airwaves
belong to everybody,
so hobbyists can
listen all they want!
[TAMOTSU]
Sweet! This one just came out!
It can actually send and
receive pictures digitally!
And connect via VoIP networks!
[MATOME] Sorry, but aren't those
transceiver things outdated?
By smartphones?
[TAMOTSU]
Handies!
They're called handies
or hand-helds okay?
Oh!
Radio waves travel
differently every day.
Capturing them accurately
is an artform!
It takes skill, creativity,
and well-built tech!
Amateur radio is about
harnessing the spirit
of adventure and curiosity
modern sheeple have forgotten!
When done right, it lets humans
around the world communicate,
anywhere and anytime!
Radio waves are out there,
waiting to be caught!
It's like hunting for
invisible treasure!
And here I thought
you were a nerd.
[TAMOTSU] Smartphones
are useful, sure.
But ultimately they're just a
way to connect to artificial
environments built and
controlled by corporations!
Use their networks alone and
we're nothing but mindless
androids relying on
global overlords!
We must forge our own networks
to preserve our very humanity!
[MATOME sighs]
I believe in the great
radio resistance,
which is why I have a hand-held
shell covering my smartphone!
I see.
[TAMOTSU]
Yes, it's a noble--
--[electronic noise]
--[BOTH yelp]
--[ARISA whimpers]
--What's that noise?
It's shattering my ear drums!
[MATOME grunts]
[TAMOTSU gasps]
[SHOPPERS shout]
Up there!
[MATOME, TAMOTSU, ARISA gasp]
Where in the world
did that come from?
It looks like Tokyo Tower.
This doesn't make any sense!
[ARISA]
A tower in Akihabara?
Weren't they talking about
doing that years ago?
[DENKO] Exactly! This is
the Akihabara Tower!
A.K.A. Akiba Tree!
A.K.A. Tokyo Tower Two!
We're reclaiming the
dream robbed from us
by that obscenely huge Skytree!
[ALL gasp]
It's a Bugged One!
[DENKO] This tower's
equipment emits my special
Bugged One Waves,
which destroy all communication
devices within range!
And that range is vast,
far greater than any normal
broadcasting tower!
We'll conquer the airwaves!
We'll be the greatest and
only broadcaster in Japan!
What?!
That goes against everything
I was just blabbering about!
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[DENKO]
Prepare the microwave attack!
[KUROBUG A shouts]
[ARISA, TAMOTSU, MATOME grunt]
[ALL gasp]
Aw, come on!
Not again!
[ALL shout]
[TAMOTSU]
Ow! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot...!
[DENKO laughs] How do you like
my special microwave attack?
Neat, right?
It is pretty neat.
It's like being inside
a microwave oven!
[ALL gasp]
[DENKO laughs]
Bugged One Radio!
Where the hits
just keep on coming!
[DENKO laughs]
[TAMOTSU groans]
That stings!
This is some troubling news.
A Buggy fighting with EM waves
could be quite a threat.
The neighborhood's
in total chaos!
Computers and smartphones
are blowing up!
It seems like the only
way we can stop those
wave attacks is to
destroy that tower.
But if we get close, we'll be
cooked like baked potatoes.
I think her Tokyo Tower Two
dream is more like a nightmare!
Wait, Tokyo Tower Two?
Yeah. That's what the
lady up top called it.
Then she said something about
"reclaiming the tower dream."
[sighs] I see. I'm afraid
that means this
Bugged One woman is
someone I used to know.
[ALL gasp]
What makes you say that?
[PROFESSOR] We're going to need
help from the professor who
mentored me, back in
my Tsukuba days.
Anyone else lost?
Before she moved here,
Professor Latu used to be a
researcher at the Cutting Edge
Science Center in Tsukuba.
Cutting Edge Science, huh?
[ARISA]
You must be a real smarty-pants!
If you weren't in Akiba,
how'd you learn about
the Bugged Ones here?
Well, it was a blatantly
ambiguous number of years ago.
Back then, the Tsukaba
Express train to Tokyo
wasn't running yet, so it felt
way more like the boonies.
But the Science Center
drew researchers
from around the world.
Even though the Bugged Ones
weren't as active then,
we knew they worked behind
the scenes in Akihabara.
I was teamed with a woman
named Denko Busujima,
the one who must be
behind that tower,
to study these mysterious bugs.
We were guided the whole
way by Professor Yagyuda,
our instructor who ran the lab.
He was a researching heavyweight
in countless scientific fields,
including paranormal phenomena.
He was the one who encouraged
me to study Bugged Ones
in their natural habitat.
That's how I first
came to Akihabara.
[ARISA] Oh, Professor!
I had no idea!
How was that sad?
So? There's gotta be
more to the story.
Where does that Tokyo
Tower Two come in?
Yes. This is where
it gets interesting.
Through our research,
we discovered the
Bugged Ones emit a weak
but very distinct radio wave,
so we set our sights on a bold
new construction project.
Did you ever hear about the old
plans to build a replacement
for the Tokyo Tower?
Tokyo Tower Two in Akihabara?
That sounds vaguely familiar.
I remember, but wasn't
that over ten years ago?
[PROFESSOR]
With that huge antenna here,
we could have easily detected
their faint radio waves,
and probably have made some
kind of major breakthrough.
Denko and Professor Yagyuda
spent everything they had
to try and lure the next
broadcasting tower to Akihabara.
They tried, and tried,
and tried, and tried,
and tried--
[bell dings]
[laughs]
Wow, that's hilarious!
So that's why she's
tower-obsessed.
You've got a brilliant scientist
who's evidently gone Buggy.
Good news is Professor
Yagyuda is an EM wave expert
who could help us out.
Of course, that presents
another problem.
[MATOME] What?
[PROFESSOR] After losing all
his money in that tower bid,
Yagyuda moved to Brazil.
To fund his next research,
he's been working
there as a garimpeiro.
As Gollum's pillow?
A God of play-dough?
Guys, she means a prospector!
Our problem is, the man
best-suited to help
is lost in the
Brazilian wilderness.
And thanks to the waves from
that tower, we don't have
working phones for calls or
computers to send emails.
Though he likely doesn't
have those either.
What we need is an alternative
form of communication.
An alternative form.
[gasps]
I've got it!
We can contact this Professor
Garimpeiro guy over the radio!
'Cause they're not
like computers!
Radios can't be
hacked by signals,
which makes them
practically invincible!
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yes. Right! That's why I asked
him to set up that beam antenna
on the roof, because I'm
smart and was thinking ahead!
[NIWAKA]
Really?
Hold on.
Can you really reach him on
the other side of the planet?
I thought radio couldn't even
handle a parking garage.
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
Yeah. You have no idea!
Grab your ballgowns, ladies,
it's time for a waltz
in the stratosphere!
[PROFESSOR] Tamotsu's right.
Communicating with Brazil
by radio is possible, though
it's not going to be easy.
Thanks to our resident fanatic,
we have the gear we need.
But the weather and ionospheric
conditions are beyond our sway.
If we could control the sun
through worship I'd pray,
but unfortunately I believe
in that gobbledygook
they call "science."
Okie doke!
Then I'll pray instead!
Oh, Amaterasu. Oh, Tsukuyomi,
please do some sun stuff!
You think Japanese gods are
gonna listen to someone
who says "moi moi" all day long?
[gasps]
How 'bout Finnish gods?
Oh, Ukko! Oh, Ilmarinen! Help!
I'm afraid that all we
can do now is be patient.
And wait for the "wind."
[ALL]
Right!
[TAMOTSU]
Hm...
[PROFESSOR] Good.
We're set to start trying.
Now let's discuss
Matome's question
about delivering radio
all the way to Brazil.
Since radio waves normally
travel in a straight line,
reaching the other side of the
planet would seem impossible.
However, nature gives us a
workaround in the form of
the Earth's ionosphere, an
atmospheric layer that has been
ionized, or charged, primarily
by the sun's ultraviolet rays.
This layer reflects radio waves,
similar to how a
mirror reflects light.
And variables, such as time
of year, time of day,
weather conditions,
and solar flares,
can expand the ionosphere and
intensify the reflections,
allowing us to bounce the waves
all the way to the
other side of the globe.
But even if we can do it,
the long distance
will make voice
communication unrealistic.
That's why Tamotsu
is using Morse code,
which can still be distinguished
through a weakened signal.
The professor knows
Morse code and scans the
frequencies for fun, but we
don't know when he's listening.
Or if our waves are
reaching that far.
So Tamotsu's testing
with a call sign.
Hm... Why don't we try switching
to the other antenna.
Niwaka, will you please
unplug that coaxial cable
and patch in number
three instead?
[NIWAKA]
Okay!
Before we're done, we may
need to replace that rig.
Matome! Grab that box
from under the stairs!
[MATOME]
Got it!
[PROFESSOR]
The rotator might be acting up.
Arisa, check it out!
[ARISA]
Yes ma'am!
[ARISA grunts]
[ARISA gasps]
Mr. Ionosphere.
Please get big and strong,
and help us save Akiba!
[radio beeps]
[TAMOTSU gasps]
[ALL sigh]
Knock knock!
It's your order from Pizza Pop,
pizza maid delivery!
Two extra ham pizzas and a
free side of garlic chicken!
Piping hot and ready
for your mouth party!
[TAMOTSU gorans]
[TAMOTSU] Whoa! "Ham" pizza
for a radio operator!
Points for the pun!
Niwaka placed the order
in person this morning
on the way to school!
She is such a great
sister-slash-hero!
You're working at the
pizza place now?
Yeah! Our maid draft
was this month
and the pizza parlor
had a first round pick!
What are you guys doing anyway?
It looks serious.
It's way too much
exposition to explain,
but it's a big
communication mission!
Communication? But I thought
that new tower was causing
total chaos and no
one could use their
connected devices anymore.
Aren't those crazy radio waves
screwing up your
equipment down here?
Well we're mostly using radio,
which is safe,
plus we're underground
and I installed some extra
shielding in the walls too.
We hope that's good enough
'til we figure this out.
Okay, guys, you have
fun with that!
[PROFESSOR]
Hey, listen!
This is cool, it looks like
something from a sci-fi movie!
What does it do?
[TAMOTSU] Careful with
the paddles, please.
[radio beeps]
[YAGYUDA]
Hm?
[MOMO gasps]
--[TAMOTSU] Ye-hah!
--[ALL gasp]
[radio beeps]
--[MOMO grunts]
--[ARISA, MATOME gasp]
[TAMOTSU] Professor!
It's an "A"!
[inaudible]
[TAMOTSU
"K"!
End of message.
Uh, "T-N-X, D-O-C".
Did you write that
stuff down, Professor?
Sure did!
[TAMOTSU]
A-L-M-H-K?
[MOMO]
Is it some kind of code?
[ALL]
Hm...
Do you know what it means?
[TAMOTSU] Hm... It could be
an acronym for something.
Agressive.
Lovemaking.
Makes.
Hens... Kluk?
Of all the possibilities,
you went with that?
Or maybe instead of an acronym,
the ordering of the letters
is some kind of key?
For a logic puzzle
that takes mathematic
reasoning to figure out?
I have no idea what
you just said.
Should I throw this out,
or do you recycle?
Arisa, that's it!
I can't believe I didn't
see it sooner! Thanks!
I hope you don't
mean the chicken,
because I kinda just ate it all.
[PROFESSOR] No silly,
don't play dumb with me!
A-L-M-H-K! Of course
that's what he meant!
[ALL]
Uh...
But we'll have to
stock up! Hurry, Momo!
We need the garlic chicken
early-bird special,
One hundred orders, now!
[ALL]
What?
[DENKO laughs] I'm dominating
the Akiba airwaves at last!
I've waited so
long for this day.
Through years of heartbreak,
watching them build
that Skytree!
And feeling my will to live
vanish under its shadow.
But now, thanks to
Metrotica's help,
Akiba finally has
its own tower,
and its waves will
rule the whole city!
[KUROBUG A squeaks]
[DENKO]
What's that?
People in weird alien costumes,
like, from cheesy old movies?
Where?
[DENKO gasps]
Is this some kind of joke?
[TAMOTSU] The joke's on you,
Denko Busujima!
Your waves can't hurt us now!
Your tower is
about to fall down!
[DENKO] You think I'm scared
of those homemade costumes?
Microwave guns, fire!
[TAMOTSU] Ha, Ha, Ha!
You've been foiled!
[DENKO]
But how?
[TAMOTSU] We may not win
any costume contests,
but our Aluminum Foil Armor will
beat your waves every time!
[DENKO]
No!
[TAMOTSU] Aluminum Blue!
Aluminum Pink! Let's roll!
[MATOME] Is that us?
[ARISA]
Copy that, Aluminum Red!
I, Aluminum Blue,
am at your side!
[MATOME]
Do I have to be pink?
[TAMOTSU, ARISA yell]
[PROFESSOR chuckles]
Thanks a lot, Professor.
I knew you'd have the answer.
[PROFESSOR]
Alumi Haku!
--[MATOME, TAMOTSU] Alumi...?
--[ARISA] ...haku?
That's right. That's the
old Japanese term for it,
though you kiddos probably
call it aluminum foil.
If you use enough of it,
aluminum can completely shut out
EM waves in the radio and
microwave frequencies!
Those attacks won't
be able to hurt you!
But that tower is so powerful,
I doubt a single sheet
of foil is can stop
waves that intense!
[chuckles] Who said anything
about a single sheet?
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[ARISA shouts]
[PROFESSOR]
Tamotsu was right, of course.
One sheet wouldn't do the trick.
But each of those suits is like
a giant foil ball,
300 millimeters thick!
Though an average
person wouldn't be able
to move in that, they're all
strong enough to fight!
Sure, we had to eat a
mountain of chicken
to get that much foil,
but that's just the kind of
selfless heroes we are.
Now go and save the day,
you'll be more or less
invincible in there. And sorry
in advance for the chafing!
[ARISA] She wasn't kidding
about the chafing, guys!
[MATOME]
Yeah, this is not comfortable!
[TAMOTSU] You're lucky
you don't have boy parts!
[DENKO]
This is bad news!
What do I do?
[DENKO gasps]
That's it! Their eyes!
Focus all the waves
on their eye-holes!
They don't have any
protection there!
[KUROBUGS]
Ha, ha!
[DENKO]
They can run backwards?
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[DENKO yelps]
[DENKO screams]
[MASUTO] The mysterious
tower has just exploded
in a fabulous flurry
of fireworks!
I'm now being told from credible
inside sources this was an
overzealous ad campaign
from a local antenna shop!
I hope all your devices gets
repaired quickly, viewers,
so you can see this broadcast!
[DENKO groans]
[gasps]
What? Latu!
Hey Den-Den, long time no see.
I guess the last time was
Professor Yagyuda's
"Brazillian Send Off" Party.
Mind telling me
how you went Buggy?
[gasps] I, uh... I'm pretty
sure it was three days ago.
After the tower fiasco,
things got pretty bad for me.
I wandered the
country for years,
then finally ended up here.
I was going to end my life
where my dream
had been shattered.
But then a woman
with a weird hat
appeared out of nowhere
and stopped me.
She told me not to die, that my
dreams could still come true.
Then weird-hat-lady reached out
to me, and when I took her hand,
something happened.
It was indescribable.
Next thing I knew, I was
standing on the tower,
attacking the city
with those waves.
Oh god, what's wrong with me?
I did terrible things!
Don't cry. It wasn't your fault.
I'll make some phone
calls to clear your name.
So hang in there. You're okay.
Just keep off those ledges.
You never know, Akihabara could
still get its tower one day.
[sobbing] Oh, Latu.
Do... you... think... so?
[cries]
[PROFESSOR] Come on, let's have
drinks with tiny umbrellas
and talk about old times. Oh!
I talked to Professor Yagyuda!
It was all dots and dashes,
but he seems well!
[DENKO]
Really?
[TAMOTSU] Hello, radio lovers!
This is 89.3, the Mini-FM
broadcast by Electric
Mayo Studios! As usual,
we're broadcasting live from
the pulsing heart of Akiba!
I'm your DJ, Tamotsu Denkigai,
and we've got some
great guests today!
It's the pop idol trio tearing
up the local scene: Mania!
[ALL]
Moi, listeners!
So. I hear you're
on fire, ladies!
Is it true your
digital downloads
have reached triple digits?
[NIWAKA] Yup! Our new
song's called "Match for 3,000!"
And we're just
enjoying the ride!
Wow, that's so fun!
Who said you could make
our base a radio station?
You should be thanking
me for the free publicity!
Do you even know if
anyone's listening to us?
Nope! But our static
reaches Brazil!
And speaking of Brazil,
boy do I like coffee!
Isn't that so interesting?
I think it smells like natto.
Hey speaking of natto,
what do you girls put in yours?
Me, I just go with sugar.
I'm old-school.
[NIWAKA] That's not old-school.
That's not any school.
That's just you!
[TAMOTSU] Great chat,
now let's get to the tunes!
Here's Mania, with
"Match for 3,000!"
♪
[TAMOTSU] Street Fighter
Five is coming to our show!
[NIWAKA] Don't you have to say
Sneak Fighter, or Street Farter
or something you know,
a fake title?
[TAMOTSU] No I don't!
We actually got clearance!
[NIWAKA] Awesome!
How'd you pull that off?
[TAMOTSU] Next on,
Akiba's Trip, the Animation :
"No Reason I'd Lose!"
[NIWAKA]
I'll get some tokens!