[NARRATOR] Cards. They have
existed since the
Big Bang first banged
out the Universe.
It is said that from the
dawn of civilization,
humankind has
assembled forty cards,
and faced their enemies
in extreme combat,
with empires
rising and falling
on the strengths of
those ancient decks.
As warring humans have
advanced through the ages,
so too have the cards,
finally reaching their pinnacle
with the ultimate card game:
Battle Creatures.
American presidential elections.
The disbanding of
pop idol groups.
The shipment dates
of new anime discs.
All these crucial moments
that shape our lives
are determined by
this fateful game.
Whoever masters "Battle
Creatures", masters the world!
So unwrap those foil packages,
ye players of earth!
Assemble your decks mightily!
Join the tumultuous fray!
Climb your way to the
top and rule over all!
[ARISA hums]
[ARISA]
Okay, I think I'm streaming!
[ARISA giggles]
[ARISA sighs]
Ahem.
Let my great
unwrapping video begin
as I see what new cards
fate has in store for me!
They're from the latest and
greatest Battle Creatures
expansion set: "Evolution
of Nerd!." Okay, here goes.
I've unwrapped my
glorious first pack!
Huh? Aw, no rare
cards yet, viewers.
Looks like nothing
but vanilla creatures.
Oh well. Just testing
the waters, right?
I've got a lot more
unwrapping to go!
Let's see. Will I get
a rare card this time?
[sighs]
And survey says "no."
That's fine! If it were easy,
they wouldn't be rare!
I'll just keep on looking and
I'm sure I'll find one soon!
[ARISA]
No! No! No, no, no...!
Aw, come on.
[ARISA grunts]
Okay...
This is the last
new pack I've got!
[gulps]
[ARISA gasps]
[groans]
[TAMOTSU]
I'm home!
That was one anime episode
I never thought I'd see
since it was banned
the first time,
but it definitely lived
up to the hype!
And that's the power of
the revival run! Huh?
No! Don't die on my couch!
Oh. Yeah that is
crappy luck...
[ARISA] It's a tragedy! I never
thought I would bomb so hard!
The Goddess of Good Card Fortune
must have completely
forsaken me!
Hey, it's not that bad.
Huh? Oh, look.
You forgot to open
this pack up.
[ARISA]
Huh?
[gasps]
It... it's a miracle!
That's the magic card,
Thirty-Year Hermit!
And just like its
shut-in namesake,
it's almost never
seen by anyone!
It's a legendary class,
ultra-rare card!
[TAMOTSU]
Wait, for real?!
[ARISA gasps]
This isn't just dumb luck!
This means you have the
Destiny Power over the cards,
and can become a
Battle Creatures master!
[TAMOTSU] Really?
I have a special power?
[TAMOTSU]
Hm!
[ARISA gasps]
Tamotsu!
[NARRATOR]
A new age begins!
♪
[TAMOTSU] Hm... I do want one
more of these in the deck,
but then I'd have to take
out this sweet trap card.
Tough call. Is that gonna throw
my balance all out of whack?
[KAGE]
New passion?
[TAMOTSU]
Oh, hey, Kage.
You're playing Battle
Creatures now, Tamotsu?
I didn't think you
iked this game.
[TAMOTSU] Yeah, I had a serious
phase when I was younger,
but I quit a few years back
when there was that huge
change to the meta.
[KAGE]
Right? That was terrible.
Wait, does that mean you were
into Battle Creatures too?
Big time! I used to
challenge myself
by building decks purely
out of banned cards!
Why would you do that?
You couldn't play in official
tournaments with them.
Yeah I know. But I could still
destroy all the grade-school
kids in my neighborhood!
You are a one of a kind, dude.
[SUIDOBASHI]
I can't believe you!
You think I'm just gonna
sit here and take that?
What are you getting worked up
about, captain, it's no biggie.
Thanks, Shohei!
I don't know why the small
one keeps picking on me.
Yeah, I don't see
the problem here.
Some change can be good, sir.
Come on! You're actually siding
with this fluffy, pink piglet?
[MIUMIU gasps]
What an awful thing to say!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Why are you being mean to me?
Isn't anyone going to defend me?
[gasps] Yeah, that's not nice!
You crossed a line, Captain!
Apologize to Miumiu!
You men are so damn
predictable sometimes.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Yeah that's offensive!
Don't act like I'm as bad as him
just because we both
have dangly bits!
[SHOHEI] What?!
Sounds like the Main
Street Vigilantes
are coming apart at the
seams over there.
Unfortunately, we've seen
these kind of fights before.
The trials of youth.
Koni! But you said
you'd go with me to the
Heavy Low End anime
film fest tomorrow!
No, Koni, you can't go with him!
You said you'd go with me!
Oh...! I just
can't decide now!
Sorry I'm so torn,
what's a girl to do?
[OTAKU]
She's so cute!
[OTAKU A]
Miss Tetsuko, look!
This photo. I took it for you!
What a beautiful train,
thank you!
I want to take pictures
of trains like that, too!
Then you can have my camera!
You deserve it way
more than I do!
Oh! Are you sure?
If we can go alone together
on the "Abandoned Railroads
of Hokkaido" trip--
Uh, hey! Why would you
want to do that when I've got
two tickets for the
"Sleeping Express"
that's about to go out of
business! Go with me instead!
[GAMER A] You creep! Is it true
you tricked Miss Sacred Angel
to stand still at the idol
event last weekend
so you could jerk off to her?
[GAMER B] So what if I did?
Isn't it true you asked her to
have chat-sex with you in
exchange for a super-rare item?
[GAMERS grunting]
[GAMER C] Hey, save the
violence for the game!
Guys., please! Don't fight
over little old me!
[GAMERS] But Sacred Angel,
I'd do anything for you!
[grunting]
If that's how it is, I don't
want to be a team anymore!
[ALL]
We're over!
[TAMOTSU] Hm... And the group
disbanded, just like that.
But that's so stupid. If they're
letting something like that
tear them up, they must
not care about Akiba at all.
Wait you guys, I know
what this is!
It sounds like a "circrusher"!
A circa-what-now?
A "circrusher," and that's
"circ" as in circle, you get it?
It's slang for new girls who
join an existing circle
of friends then break them up
through crushes and rivalries.
Come on, we've all
been there, right?
Wow, Niwaka. Where'd you pick up
that fascinating bit of trivia?
Hey, check out Clamas TV!
It looks like we're not the
only ones talking about this!
Breaking news! Another
strange anomaly in Akiba!
Various vigilante groups who've
been keeping the peace in our
beloved neighborhood
have been breaking up
one after another, and it seems
that in every case a girl
who recently
joined the group
was at the center
of the friction!
That's right! Circle crushing!
And it seems to be hitting our
streets like pink petals
in cherry blossom season!
We here at Clamas TV
will continue to
investigate these
troubling incidents!
So stayed tuned for
updates from your
hollerer-with-the-followers!
I don't know if it's fair
to blame the girls,
since boys who don't
have experience can get
crazy-excited by even the
smallest amount of attention.
Maybe the girls are just being
nice and they can't handle it.
[MATOME] But why is it
happening so much at once?
[ALL]
Huh?
[PROFESSOR] This could have
something to do with it.
[ALL]
Hm...
[TAMOTSU]
"Princess Company".
Let's see, "introducing
'Princesses' to your circles."
Ah, this flyer is definitely
laying it on thick.
"Akiba vigilantes, how about
adding a pretty flower
to your activities?"
"For a girl to idolize, contact
the following address." Sheesh.
Okay that is bad.
I feel like I've peered
into the otaku dark side.
That's troubling.
[TAMOTSU] Of course it is.
It's a total creep-fest.
Yeah, but it's more than that.
I'm sure if they tried,
that kind of business
could attract all sorts of
customers from around Tokyo.
Why limit themselves to the
Akiba vigilante groups?
That is, unless they have
something else in mind?
My thought exactly.
Which means--
[TAMOTSU] Which means
we're taking a field trip!
[TAMOTSU] Hey, isn't this where
that butler bar used to be?
I would say that makes it
even more suspicious.
[TAMOTSU]
Let's go!
[gasps]
[ALL] Welcome to the
Princess Company!
Thank you for your business.
Now what kind of princess
are you looking for?
The only business we're here for
is putting you out of yours!
[ARISA]
Yeah that's right,
we've already set up our
own harem with Tamotsu,
so we don't need any help
from you girls, but thanks!
That is not what
we're talking about!
[gasps]
A harem of your own, huh?
Now you have my attention.
[ALL gasp]
[IKETERU'S WOMAN sighs, giggles]
Good to meet you.
I am the founder and CEO
of the Princess Company.
The Iketeru Masada!
CEO?
That is some seriously
weird hair!
Moi, good-looking!
A young, handsome,
successful CEO.
Does it get any better
than that, Ma?
I know it's hard, but I'm
gonna need you to focus.
But he must make at least 30
million a year, probably more.
How does that not
make him great?
The hair's
definitely weird, though!
Don't judge a man's
worth by his income!
Judge him by how much of that
income he's willing to spend
on super-cool hobbies!
[ARISA swoons]
If you're done being stupid,
I'd like to move on!
This guy is obviously
a Bugged One!
[ARISA, TAMOTSU grunt]
Ha! Guess that means
you've figured out
my wickedly brilliant plan.
By using these ladies
to cause mad drama,
I was going to destroy all the
vigilante groups in Akiba,
leaving us free to
do as we please.
But, alas. I wasn't
expecting you to unravel
my scheme so quickly.
If the hottie guy seems
too good to be true,
then he probably is!
That's what grandma used
to say, but in Finnish!
Since you came all this way,
I feel I owe you something.
I want you to enjoy the full
Princess Company experience.
That's your cue, my lovelies!
[PRINCESSES giggle]
Here we come!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[PRINCESSES scream]
That was easy!
[MATOME] You're the only
Buggy left to squash, Masada!
[IKETERU laughs] I suppose it
shouldn't surprise me that they
weren't enough for the
famous Electric Mayonnaise.
You've slain quite a few
of my comrades.
It appears that I'll have
to show you my true power.
[MATOME]
Ready when you are!
You fool!
[MATOME gasps]
[gasps]
[TAMOTSU, ARISA gasp]
[MATOME]
No!
[IKETERU] That's just a taste.
If I show you what I'm capable
of in simple hand-to-hand
fighting, you'll be obliterated.
Of course, where's the beauty
in that sort of brutish melee?
I choose combat by cards!
You really thought
we'd go for that?
[TAMOTSU]
I accept!
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
Come now, it's time to duel.
[NARRATOR] In Akihabara,
holy land of the Otaku,
the brave vigilante groups who
maintain peace in the realm
have been attacked from
within by ruthless,
circle-crushing hot girls.
Weakened by jealousies
and hormones, many groups
have disbanded,
raising the suspicions of
Electric Mayonnaise
and Friends.
So the gang traced the
growing crisis to its source,
the sinister Princess Company.
They infiltrated the
rent-a-babe lair
and confronted the company's
CEO, the questionably-quaffed
Iketeru Masada, whose
exposure as a Bugged One
surprised no one but Arisa.
Though to be fair, he's rich,
and who doesn't like that?
Now Iketeru has challenged
Tamotsu to combat by cards.
Can our hero defeat the CEO and
stop the evil Buggie conspiracy?
[FANS cheering]
What's say we play
under the Animated Rules,
and go with 2,000
points of starting life.
Works for me.
4,000 could take weeks.
And I don't really have the
attention span for that.
The starting turn is mine!
Time to draw!
Wait, the rules changed!
Starting players don't
draw first turn!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Well then, from my hand I summon
my first creature, Happy Nerd!
[HAPPY NERD gasps]
And I'm not done yet!
I also play Long Blade Glow
Stick, equipped to Happy Nerd!
That's right. And by
equipping the Glow Stick,
his attack raises by 300!
I see you've built
an Otaku deck,
based on Pure Boy
type creatures.
You clearly don't stand a chance
against my Promenade deck.
Ridiculous! We haven't
even started playing,
you can't tell that
from two cards!
You don't have to believe me.
I'll just show you.
And now... I will draw!
Here comes my first creature.
I summon forth
Bright Eyes Hot Guy!
[HOT GUY chuckles]
When Bright Eyes Hot Guy's put
in play, he gives me the power
to summon as many Groupie Girls
from my deck as I like!
[GROUPIE GIRLS giggle]
[TAMOTSU]
Three copies of the same card?
He's as hardcore as I thought!
[MATOME]
Huh? Um...
Sometime today, maybe?
Sorry, I'm just having trouble
deciding what to play next.
It's always hard at the start,
there's so many choices!
What in the world
are we doing here?
What do you mean,
it's obvious, Ma!
Now that he's realized
his destiny
and dedicated his life
to Battle Creatures,
Tamotsu's bound by honor to
accept any player's challenge!
Okay. But it's
three against one,
why can't we just
gang up on him.
And kick the guy's
butt in real life?
How can you say that?
Real life violence should only
be used as a last resort!
Alright I play the magic card,
Otaku Dance Squad!
This lets me Special Summon
up to three Happy Nerds
from my deck for a dance party
and inflict damage to the enemy
player of 300 points
times the number of nerds!
Activating my trap card!
You must now face the
Drinking Party Game!
This forces two target creatures
to do battle with each other,
and get used to it because
the effect lasts five turns!
[TAMOTSU] I activate my
Convention Staff effect
to play Sample
Booklet Inspection!
Reveal all face-down cards in
the opponent's playing field!
I activate "Busts" ability
on Hidden Breasts Girl!
You can do it!
Discover your self esteem!
[HIDDEN BREASTS GIRL gasps]
Oh, no!
[IKETERU] During this turn,
Pure Boy type creatures
can only attack
Hidden Breasts Girl!
I activate the Exploitative
Gatcha card from my hand!
While in play, this allows
me to take three cards
every time I draw!
Moi, that's amazing!
What a super-strong card!
Really? It doesn't sound
that super to me.
Trust me, by the
next tournament,
it'll be officially Forbidden!
[IKETERU] Then I play
my Flash Magic card!
"But Only If You're Hot!"
Any Promenade type creature
or attack party
gains 500 attack!
[HIDDEN BREASTS GIRL gasps]
[HAPPY NERDS grunt]
[TAMOTSU] I disable the effect
that disables the effect,
that disables the effect!
[IKETERU] And I disable that
effect that disables the effect,
that disables the effect
that disables the effect!
[ARISA gasps] Wowie, this fight
is incredibly intense!
[MATOME] Are we watching
the same thing?
It seems pretty low-key to me.
Open your eyes, Ma! Can't you
see the blood, sweat, and visual
effects between those clashing
souls locked in epic battle?
All you have to do is set
your imagination free!
Just open your mind
and join in the fun!
[MATOME]
Eh, I'd rather complain.
Not so fast!
I activate the second effect on
my "Take Home From Party" Card!
[TAMOTSU]
Oh, no!
[MATOME]
Uh... Wait.
The "second effect" is printed
on the card, right?
And since it's on the table,
Tamotsu could read it any time.
[ARISA groans]
So why was he acting shocked?
I mean obviously the guy's gonna
use the effect but Tamotsu
freaked like it was the biggest
surprise in the world.
[ARISA]
Don't question the tropes!
[MATOME] And why did you just
blast off like a rocket?
Hey, can you guys keep it down,
I'm trying to battle over here.
Now it's time for the
real fun to start.
I equip the
Virgin-Killing Clothes!
All Pure Boy type creatures
experience sensory overload
and are instantly sent
to the graveyard!
[HAPPY NERD C] Yes! Yes!
Bow-chicka wow-wow!
This can't be!
Without your nerds, your
playing field is wide open!
So I can launch a direct and
undefended attack against the
enemy player using my
Bright Eyes Hot Guy!
[chuckles]
[TAMOTSU screams]
[groans]
[gasps] No Tamotsu!
Please, don't die!
As long as the enemy
utters that cliché phrase
before the smoke clears,
you'll be all right!
You're finished.
What? But how?
That would have destroyed me,
but when you attacked I
played my "Self-Published Manga
Express Option Printing" card.
Which negates all
attacks during the turn
and sets my life to
one hundred points.
So that cost you four
hundred life points.
Big price to pay for some
extra time, Tamotsu-Boy.
Now what? You only
have a hundred life
and no creatures on the field.
You can't possibly think there's
a way out of this predicament.
Surrender and save yourself
more embarrassment!
Hate to disappoint you,
but there's nothing in my
deck's flavor text that mentions
anything about surrendering!
[IKETERU grunts] It's pointless!
Look at the table!
How can you keep fighting in
the face of absolute despair!
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
That's easy.
Because I... am a
Battle Creatures player!
[IKETERU, ARISA gasp]
[TAMOTSU] True, I don't
have a card in my hand
that can save me. And the
odds would say I'm toast...
...but I believe in my deck!
Because this deck and I have
been through it all together!
We've survived battles against
countless worthy foes!
It saved me then,
and it'll save me now!
I'll bet my life on this draw!
Here I go!
[TAMOTSU]
That's it. I can feel it.
This is the card I need!
From my hand I summon
Silent Unemployed Guy!
You're summoning a creature with
zero attack and zero income?
And how is that
supposed to save you?
Because I'm not finished yet!
I also play the magic card
Thirty-Year Hermit from my hand!
When this card is activated,
all Pure Boy type creatures
on the playing field
are immediately set
to defense mode! And Pure
Boy creatures affected
by this magic
cannot be attacked!
Ha! So you're going to
barricade yourself and defend?
How fitting for a
reclusive otaku!
But there's something
else about Pure Boys.
If they're still virgins at 30,
Then they transform
into wizards!
Wait, really?
When Thirty-Year
Hermit's in play,
it triggers another effect!
Silent Unemployed Guy
is able to evolve!
End the flow of wasted
milky fluids...
...and reach your
true potential!
[TAMOTSU] I Special Summon
the Mighty Mage of Virginity!
Pureness Wizard!
An attack strength of 3,000?
[IKETERU grunts]
Those are impressive moves,
but it's still not enough!
My Bright Eyes is at
twenty-five hundred!
Even if you beat him,
I'll only lose 500!
I'll survive your attack and win
the game on my next turn!
There won't be a next turn!
What now?
[TAMOTSU] When summoned,
Pureness Wizard disables all
effects of all cards
in the field,
and can attack the
enemy player directly!
And no, I'm still not done!
Because while this is in play,
the enemy can't counter!
That means you can't
activate any magic cards,
any traps, or any
creature effects.
You see? It's over for you!
I'm no expert, but that
doesn't sound fair.
[TAMOTSU]
By the rules of the cards.
I attack the enemy
player directly!
Descend your virginal
hammer of righteousness!
Justice! Judge! Kill!
[IKETERU yells]
[NIWAKA]
Yeah! You get him, bro!
[IKETERU grunts]
[MATOME]
Huh...? Ah!
This is insane! How did losing a
card game rip off his clothes?
Don't you see?
It's because I'm a
Battle Creatures player.
[groans]
[FANS cheer]
Um, no. I don't see.
[SHOHEI] You guys, I'm so sorry
I was tricked by that vixen!
Forgive me!
Forget it. I'm the one
who needs to apologize
for being so impatient.
Hey, it's water
under the bridge.
All that matters is the
Main Street Vigilantes
are back together,
and we'll keep Akiba safe!
Yeah, you said it!
The gang is back!
[VIGILANTES chatter happily]
Well that's nice.
It looks like everybody
kissed and made up.
Silly vigilantes. They were
all fighting over nothing.
But that's youth for ya.
♪
[TAMOTSU] Next Akiba's Trip ,
the Animation :
"Did You Open Your
Pyloric Canal?"
[ARISA] Do I even want
to know what that is?
[TAMOTSU] The pyloric canal
connects the stomach
and intestines. Open it,
and you can surpass
the normal limits of eating!
[ARISA] Moi! This could
be a giant killing!
The upset of the century!
[TAMOTSU "I'm done eating,"
is only the start!