[MATOME]
Hey! I said no phone!
[TAMOTSU gasps]
Sorry, I'm listening, I swear!
[MATOME grunts]
As I was trying to say,
those freaks you fought
are the Bugged Ones.
The cruel monsters who've been
disturbing the peace in Akiba.
[gasps]
No way. It's true?
[MATOME] The ones we fought
tonight used to be normal humans
who had been cosplaying
here in the neighborhood
when they were ambushed.
They only turned
violent when beings
called Kurobugs took
over their bodies.
These are the Low
Class Bugged Ones.
There are also more powerful
beings called the Hazoku,
who can create stronger,
High Class Bugged--
Are you even listening to me?!
[gasps] Sorry. I'm hungry
after that fight.
Can I go grab a katsu sandwich?
I'm talking!
I know, I know, I heard you!
You said somethin' about,
uh, hackie sacks, right?
[MATOME] The Hazoku
are non-human beings
who have the power to
create Bugged Ones.
I am a Hazoku myself.
[gasps]
Some of my kind seek
to peacefully coexist
with the human race.
I'm one of them,
so I'm here fighting to keep
this land safe for all of us.
[TAMOTSU gasps]
And recently our enemies,
the ones who don't want peace,
have been growing more bold.
I'm not sure why that is,
but I have to defeat them.
My clan's been defending
Akihabra for over 300 years.
I refuse to be the
one who lets it fall.
Now there's you. And since
you've been transformed,
you can no longer
leave this district.
You have to join me and--
[TAMOTSU]
See ya!
[MATOME gasps] Hold on!
I said you have to help!
And I say I don't want to.
It sounds like a drag!
First I was curious but
now that you've told me,
it's lost the appeal. Get the
cops or vigilantes to help. Bye!
Hey! Come back!
[TAMOTSU]
I'm coming, katsu sandwich!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
Ow... What the--?
[MATOME]
Like I was saying.
From now on, you can't
leave Akihabra.
The entire neighborhood has
been enclosed in a powerful
force field, to trap the
Bugged Ones inside.
I saved your life by performing
"Transcend Providence,"
But that turned you
into my underling.
In other words, a Bugged One.
That hair color is the proof.
During combat, it glows with
energy, unlocking your powers.
[TAMOTSU]
It can't be true.
[NIWAKA]
Hey, bro!
We finally found you!
Thank goodness you're okay!
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
[NIWAKA giggles]
♪
[TAMOTSU]
Whoa! Awesome!
It's a bunch of old video
games I've heard about,
but never actually played!
I know you're in nerd heaven,
but you should come sit down.
This stuff she wants to tell
you is probably important.
Probably?
Ha,ha! This used to be a
warehouse for a hobby shop.
I can see why Tamotsu's excited!
You should sit
down too, Miss Arisa.
It's not really
a sit-down dress.
And please, you don't
have to say "Miss".
Just call me Arisa,
we're friends here, right?
[gasps]
Moi!
[TAMOTSU]
Holy crap!
Am I really holding the
world's very first home
video game console, the Ottosei?
Not worthy!
What am I gonna find next?
Maybe I can take some notes?
You were saying my
brother is no longer human?
[MATOME] Yes. That's right.
I know it's a shock.
[PROFESSOR clears throat]
It might be best if I explain.
Professor!
Wait, what? This little
girl has a degree?
A pleasure to meet you,
I'm Professor Tejasvi Latu.
Actually my full legal name
is Tejasvi Najawarden Bangal
Bengal Rajah-Rajah-Maha-Raja
Veerendra-Varendrah
[TAMOTSU] Why don't we
just call you Professor.
That works!
So. What happened is
Tamotsu almost died,
or rather, he did die,
technically speaking.
Then Matome performed
"Transcend Providence"
to save him by altering
his biology, turning him into
a Hazoku underling,
a High Class Bugged One.
This gave him the power to
defeat the other Bugged Ones
with a single blow.
The Hazoku are far superior,
so naturally the Bugged Ones
they create are more powerful
than the ones made by Kurobugs,
thus the High and Low
Class distinction.
Oh, by the way, Matome,
was it hard to convince
yourself to perform it on him?
I'm sure you didn't
have any fun doing it.
Alright. I don't think
I got most of that,
but I got that my brother
isn't really a human anymore.
Dad always says you're a
failure as a human being.
Now it's literally true.
Now, now, this doesn't have
to be a negative thing.
You should feel lucky that
you've been transformed
into a more powerful being.
You're like an
Instant Super Hero!
I guess so. But it feels
kinda cheap and unearned
to get this power without work
or even a training montage.
Hey, hold on.
If I'm a Bugged One like
those cosplayers I battled,
What if my clothes
get ripped off?
The others turned back
into normal humans
when they were disrobed, so is
that what would happen to me?
Uh. We can get to that later!
Huh? What's with you?
[MATOME whistles]
And if I can't take
off my clothes,
how am I supposed to bathe?
I just have to stink?
Fear not, Tamotsu!
This secret base is equipped
with a special shower,
designed by yours truly!
[TAMOTSU] I've always
been more a bath guy.
[ARISA]
Tamotsu, you naughty boy!
What are you doing in there?
[MATOME]
Don't look!
We don't have time to
talk about your hygiene.
Now that you've fought
as my underling,
The rest of the Bugged Ones
are going to come after you
any chance they get.
And like the saying goes, the
best defense is a good offense.
We're going to be
a vigilante squad.
[gasps]
You mean like those people
who patrol the streets,
calling themselves
Akiba Vigilantes?
That's right. The vigilantes
are volunteers who stand up
to defend this place.
Most of them are just regular
people cleaning the streets.
But some of them are dedicated
Bugged One hunters like me,
and we'll do anything
to stop this chaos.
That sounds cool,
can I join too?
It'd be like we're shadow
warrior hitmen or something!
Put on clothes!
[TAMOTSU]
Okay, fine.
[MATOME]
Huh?
No choice but to
accept my fate, right?
So if I'm stuck in Akiba,
I guess that means I have
to live in this base?
Live here?
[NIWAKA] Huh? This isn't
exactly "homey," bro.
Well I can't go home,
it's outside of the force field.
You live here, don't you, Mayo?
Huh? Well yes,
it is my base.
[TAMOTSU] Then your
underling can live here, too.
Uh. But it's so small.
So what do I tell mom and dad,
they'll be worried sick!
Tell 'em I got a sweet job,
and a company apartment
is one of the benefits.
Huh... Mom might believe
someone would hire you,
but dad definitely won't.
I demand to have a say in this!
[ARISA] Moi! I love that idea,
it's like summer camp!
I can't wait, yay!
[MATOME]
Hey!
Don't worry, Matome,
we'll make this work.
Look. If we clear out that
space under the stairs,
we can fit one more person.
Well yeah, but--
I know he seems like an idiot,
but he's a harmless idiot.
Besides, he's your underling,
which is kind of like a pet
and thus your responsibility!
[MATOME]
Hm...
[MATOME grunts]
Make sense?
[MATOME]
Tamotsu!
[TAMOTSU]
Huh?
You can live here,
but your work starts today!
What? Seriously?
[gasps]
As a member of my
elite vigilante squad,
you will obey my instructions
at all times! Got that?
If you ever dare disobey
me or I find you useless,
I will kick you out immediately.
Out of the squad
and out of my base!
Can I make a counter-offer?
[MATOME]
Just say yes.
Fine, yes.
Good, now your first assignment
is to clear out these boxes.
[TAMOTSU sighs]
Yes, ma'am.
[MATOME] Patrol starts tomorrow
morning at seven sharp!
[TAMOTSU] That's insane!
Who wakes up before ten?
I'm not sure my brother
can survive this.
[ARISA hums]
And why are you here again?
'Cause I'm part of your
vigilante squad, Ma, you silly!
What's Ma?
Me... Ma!
Ma's me? Ah god, I'm starting
to sound like you.
Look, I didn't say
you could join us.
You don't have to say it!
Your actions speak
louder than words!
I saw all those toys
on your shelf!
[MATOME gasps]
[ARISA]
The Rangers you broke yesterday.
You went back to the store,
bought 'em, and then fixed 'em!
That tells me all
I need to know, Ma!
Anyone who cares that much
won't to say moimoi to me,
who just wants to help!
Uh... well. I just felt bad.
For the store owner and
the toys. Um... And uh...
...for you, too.
For me?
[MATOME] I thought you were
a Bugged One. I'm sorry.
Moi!
You're so cute, Ma, I love it!
You like to act icy but you
really care about everyone
and everything! From now on
we should be team mates,
soul mates, and whatever
other kind of mate--
[TAMOTSU]
Okay, I've got it!
[MATOME, ARISA]
Hm?
You've got
what exactly, Tamotsu?
A name for our squad.
It's the best team name
in team name history!
What? So is that
what you've been
concentrating so
hard on this morning?
[laughs] Actually, it was
this morning and yesterday.
You ready to be amazed?
[MATOME]
What?!
No, that sucks!
It's totally terrible!
It's inspired by your name
and my sweet glowy hair!
We should make some T-shirts!
Bonehead!
[SUIDOBASHI]
Excuse me, citizens.
[TAMOTSU]
Huh? The vigilantes?
Got some questions for ya.
Concerning the string of violent
incidents in Akihabra yesterday.
[KOZAKURA] We have intel
suggesting you were involved
in all of 'em.
[MATOME grunts]
And you hoodlums seem
to be organized.
Are you a vigilante group, too?
If so?
[TAMOTSU]
Yeah that's right! We are!
And you should learn
our team name
'cause we're gonna
be famous soon.
Presenting... The defenders
of Akiba: Electric Mayonnaise!
But,wait. You only used you and
her for the name, what about me?
[TAMOTSU gasps] Oh yeah, that is
kind of a jerk move, huh?
Okay, how about "Electric
Mayonnaise and Friends,"
is that better?
Oh, definitely.
It's perfect, thanks!
I told you I hated that,
didn't I?
No one's gonna fear us if we're
called "Electric Mayonnaise"!
Look. We don't care if you call
yourselves Electric Mayonnaise
or Peppy Ponzu Sauce,
we just want to know if you
caused that trouble yesterday!
That's right.
we don't like people
making messes on our turf!
[MATOME] What does
that mean? Your turf?
[HIJIRI] What do you
mean what do we mean?
Turf is one of the great
unspokes rules of vigilantism!
You're ridiculous. Let's go!
We're leaving 'cause
we're bored, not scared!
You better respect Electric
Mayonnaise and Friends!
We're not done talking!
[gasps]
[ARISA]
It's been swell meeting you!
I respect any group who wears
matching outfits! Moimoi!
Don't be mad, okay.
Moimoi, moimoi! Moimoi!
Hey, get back here! Uh. Captain?
Oh my god. She's so cute!
[KOZAKURA]
Eh?
[SUIDOBASHI]
Electric Mayonnaise.
We'll definitely
keep an eye on them.
Welcome home, master,
we're pleased to serve you!
Paradise is right this way!
These Bugged Ones.
What exactly are they trying
to achieve here, anyway?
'Cause all they've seemed to do
so far is light up the internet.
The online news is calling
our fight yesterday
"Cosplayers Gone Wild!"
The Kurobugs are used
to create armies.
So I'm sure the end game
is taking over Akiba.
My question is who's
running the show.
[METROTICA BOSS]
Humankind will kneel
at our adorably stockinged feet!
[MATOME] It could be
that Metrotica group,
or they may just be one faction.
Look. No offense, but how are
we supposed to fight a war
when we aren't even sure
who their real leaders are?
I don't know. I'm doing what I
can to save this place, alright?
And why wouldn't you?
Akiba's full of
"splendid somethings,"
like they say in that
old radio jingle!
I would do anything
to defend it, too!
Hell yeah there's
"splendid somethings".
That's why I love this place!
I'm here in the Mecca of Otaku
but you make me patrol all day!
When am I supposed to shop?
Oh, boo-hoo!
[TAMOTSU]
Wait, I just realized.
Fighting off evil is
an unpaid job, right?
How do I support myself and
my shopping addiction?
Well, the research institute
where the Professor works
does give us a stipend to
help fund our operation.
But, to be honest,
it's barely enough money to
cover the rent for my base.
[TAMOTSU gasps] Then what
am I supposed to live on?
I can make room in your
schedule for a part-time job.
[sighs]
But if I'm stuck in Akiba,
that kinda' limits my options.
How am I gonna find work?
--[MOMO] Pardon me, Master.
--[TAMOTSU] Huh?
[TAMOTSU gasps]
But did you say you're
looking for a job in Akiba?
[TAMOTSU shouts]
Please don't scream,
you'll scare our guests!
Oh, great to see you, Momo!
So you're working here today?
[MOMO]
Yes meow!
You're Momo? As in Tsukumo Momo?
The famous free-agent maid?
But you're a living legend!
No one in the world can
do maid service like you!
Moi! It's such a great
honor to meet you, ma'am!
I'm a huge fan of yours!
Oh, thank you very meow-ch!
Make sure to buy a handshake
ticket at my next concert!
Whoa, so you're a big deal, huh?
[MOMO] Anyway, Master. If you're
looking for a job in Akiba,
I know of a great place
you can go for help!
Huh?
[MASHIRO]
Hi!
Welcome to the no charge,
no responsibility agency!
Momo just texted me.
You're the cute, desperate guy
looking for a job, right?
That's me. I'd like something
with no experience required
that's easy and
pays a butt-load!
Gig like that would be too
good to be true. Like this!
Whoa! Eighteen hundred?!
Look again,
that's the "max" pay.
Yeah, you probably wouldn't
make anywhere near that.
Well, that's why it's my
policy not to protect you
from getting screwed. But on
the plus side, I am free!
[MATOME] Wait... I remember
getting a strange reading
around that business address.
What is that?
It's a Bugged One sensor
the Professor built for me.
It's mostly useless, though,
'cause it only works when
they reveal their true nature.
Let's check it out!
Sounds like a win-win!
[MATOME] Are we positive
this is the right place?
[TAMOTSU]
Sure is crowded in here.
Who knew that weapon
collecting was so popular?
Maybe the pay is real after all!
Yeah, after shows like Admiral
Connection and Tank Babes,
there's a whole community
of military-themed otaku!
And who doesn't love
a good gas mask!
[MATOME gasps]
Yeah, it's just a bunch
of casual noobs
chasing the latest
trend-of-the-month.
[ARISA gasps] Does that
mean you're a bona fide
hard-core military otaku,
Tamotsu?
No, actually. I'm kind
of a noob myself.
That's surprising! Does that
mean you're one of those people
who thinks the Type Zero
was the only fighter plane
that Japan ever made?
So it's not?
[HARDMAN]
Die, casual fans, die!
Listen up you
butt-brained maggots!
You make me sick! I got nothin'
for you soft-core sissies
but a magazine
of whoop-ass!
[CROWD shouts]
Whoa. What gives?
[CROWD gasps]
[KUROBUGS grunting]
[grunts, laughs]
They bugged the crowd!
Guys look! He's off the charts!
[TAMOTSU] Does that mean he's
the boss?
Where only serious
maggots-in-the-know are welcome!
[ARISA]
He's the owner of this store!
Must be a High Class.
Tamotsu! Come on.
What? What do you
want me to do?
Just do what you
did yesterday, all right?
[TAMOTSU gasps]
Wait for me,
I want to fight too!
[TAMOSTCU]
Damn it!
[MALE SHOPPER A whimpers]
[MATOME shouts]
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[HARDMAN]
Hm?
And who are you turd-wads?
Vigilantes?
Fine! If you want
a war, you got it!
[SHOPPERS screams]
[BUGGY SOLDIERS grunting]
[TAMOTSU, ARISA shout]
Owie!
If it hurts,
then dodge 'em, dummy!
Shut up! Like it's that easy!
Oh right, dodge! Why didn't
I think of that? Moi!
[ARISA giggles]
[ARISA]
Moi!
[BUGGY SOLDIERS grunting]
Excellent plan, Ma.
Your brain's smart!
Where'd she learn
to fight like that?
Yeah I don't know,
but lookie what I found!
Just try not to shoot me!
[TAMOTSU shouts]
Only our kind has
those sort of moves,
but we can deal with that!
Sir, sir! The enemy is
charging our line!
I know, nitwit!
Switch to special ammunition
and light 'em up!
[BUGGY SOLDIERS]
Yes Manager sir!
[TAMOTSU, MATOME gasp]
[ARISA gasps]
You okay?
With my shoulder exposed,
it feels like I'm on fire!
Those weapons are crazy!
[BOTH grunt]
[HARDMAN laughs] Say hello
to Disrobing Rounds!
I'm burning up!
We can't afford to lose any
more clothes! Let's go!
[grunts]
Tactical retreat!
The enemy retreated
through the window, sir!
Yeah, I see that!
[MATOME, TAMOTSU groan]
I nearly went back to human!
[MATOME gasps, whistles]
[SUIDOBASHI]
What do we have here?
Are you punks causing
trouble again already?
We don't have time
for a lecture!
Why? You too busy getting
half-naked in public?
Trust me, it's none
of your business, okay.
Sure it is! If we let you get
in the way of law and order
around here, you'll hurt the rep
of the Main Street Vigilantes!
[MATOME grunts] You're the
ones getting in the way.
[SUIDOBASHI]
Huh? You wanna fight, C-Cups?
[MATOME gasps]
What's that?
[ALL]
Huh? Hm?
[ALL scream]
[BUGGY SOLDIERS chuckle]
[SUIDOBASHI gasps]
Who the hell's attacking us?
The Bugged Ones.
Surely you've heard
of 'em, right?
[SUIDOBASHI gasps]
You've gotta be kidding.
I thought that was just an
urban legend around here.
I'm not gonna waste my time
telling you people
what to believe.
But the one thing you need to
accept is Akihabra's in danger.
And protecting this place
is the whole point
of your little posse, right?
[ARISA] We're the same!
The three of us are out
risking our lives to save
Akiba so it doesn't go moimoi!
Because we love it more than
anywhere else in the world and
want it to be safe, and that's
what you want too, right?
Well... yeah, but--
[ARISA] Perfect! Then hug
it out and feel the love!
Let's say moi to our new
friendship as fellow vigilantes!
We should ditch these guys
and work on a strategy.
We need a real plan of attack.
I agree.
Come on, Arisa.
[SUIDOBASHI]
Wait!
She's right. we should take
on this threat together!
[ALL gasp]
Why, Captain?
But we've been chasing them!
Call it a temporary truce.
I don't believe in this
"Bugged One" crap,
but if there's any chance it's
real we need to stop it fast!
And it's not 'cause anyone
has a crush on anyone.
Oh! So you're like a yandere!
That isn't it!
[MATOME gasps]
Thanks, but--
Let's not turn down help.
We need all the manpower
we can get, right?
And besides, this is
giving me an idea.
I'm not saying it's a good idea,
but if I die you can just
bring me back again!
[gasps]
About that.
[ARISA]
It's decided!
Let's get in there and
squash some Bugs for Akiba!
[TAMOTSU, SUIDOBASHI]
Woo-hoo!
[KUROBUGS growl]
[KUROBUGS gasp]
[ARISA shouts]
Okay, I'll keep
the outside clear!
All right, let's go!
[MATOME] Up to now,
I always fought alone.
I never thought I
needed anyone else.
The enemy is here!
I know! Attack!
[ALL shouting]
I'll take care of
these Kurobugs,
you focus on the manager!
Got it!
[KUROBUGS grunting]
[TAMOTSU]
So what's the deal, Hardman?
Why are you doing this?
[HARDMAN] I have no need for
faithless, gutless, cockroaches
chasing the next trend, feel me?
My shop is only for
the trivia-knowing
ephemera-collecting,
limited-edition,
hard-cores who deserve
to have hobbies, son!
The most these casual
scum-eaters deserve
is to be pawns in my
army to conquer Akiba
and rid it of the rest
of the damn fakers!
Ha! We all know that
newbies are annoying,
but you still have
to welcome them.
It's the only way any
content can survive.
Even you started as a casual
fan! I bet you used to think
all Japanese warplanes
were Type Zero!
[gasps] What? No I didn't,
I swear I didn't!
I've known about Hayate
and Kikka planes
since the day I was born, punk!
[TAMOTSU, SUIDOBASHI grunt]
That oughta do it! With those
Disrobing Rounds, he's cooked!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[HARDMAN gasps]
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[HARDMAN]
Maggot!
[TAMOTSU grunts] Royal Ultra
Super Miracle God Hand!
[HARDMAN yelps]
Sir, sir! You're nude, sir!
[HARDMAN] I know that,
dirt-for-brains!
Mission accomplished!
[HIJIRI] Woo-hoo!
Nice stripping, kid!
Yeah, you really did it!
[chuckles] Thanks for
the assist, Captain!
[SUIDOBASHI groans]
You're gonna owe me big time
for this one, buddy!
Now let's see if that guy will
hire me once he's human again.
[gasps]
I wanted to tell you.
Low-Class Bugged Ones.
They're just possessed.
They go back to normal
humans when the Kurobug's
been driven out.
But High-Class Bugged Ones and
Hazoku like me are different.
Our condition's permanent and
there's nothing to go back to.
We just evaporate.
Tamotsu. That's your fate, too.
I'm so sorry.
Things have moved so fast,
and I didn't know how to say it.
[TAMOTSU]
So, that means...
[MATOME]
Yes.
That means I've gotta
live it up while I can!
[MATOME]
Huh?
If I don't know how many weeks,
days, or hours I have,
then I need to experience,
and mostly buy,
everything I can so I
don't have any regrets!
Wait, what?
[TAMOTSU]
Excellent! I'm glad you agree!
And to buy stuff, I need to
make two butt-loads of cash!
Okay! Back to that shady agency!
Wait a minute!
My god. Is he
really that stupid?
[BUGGY SOLDIERS groan]
[ARISA sighs] Piling up naked
people is a real workout!
[MASUTO] A brawl today in
the back streets of Akiba!
Sources say it was in-fighting
among military otaku!
Probably some kind of argument
about military aircraft!
And that's it for our afternoon
addition of online news,
brought to you by your GonTube
"hollerer with the followers,"
Masuto Niikura!
[MASUTO sighs] You know,
It's getting really hard
to spin this stuff. Not even
people on the internet
believe everything you tell 'em.
[KICKUCHI] I wouldn't keep
you around if it were easy.
[MASUTO sighs]
Right.
[KICKUCHI]
Troubling...
I didn't expect that a High
Class member of Metrotica
would be eliminated so easily.
Their deck is stronger
than I thought.
Might be time to play
a stronger card.
♪
[TAMOTSU]
You ever heard of the Earphones?
[NIWAKA] Wh-- Yeah, it's not
like I was born yesterday!
[TAMOTSU] I just wanna be
sure you to hear good stuff!
[NIWAKA] Well, you sound like
one of those artlian people!
[TAMOTSU] Next time on
Akiba's Trip, The Animation :
"What Happens When You
Mindlessly Follow Someone
Who Offers You an Idol Debut!"
[NIWAKA]
What happens? Tell me!