[TAMOTSU]
Hmm...
It's a bit off.
Her pose still needs
to have more oomph.
Maybe skewing the camera angle
would give it some energy.
Huh...
Better.
Now let's really
push that diagonal.
Classic Kanada perspective.
And to be fair, maybe it's
a little Obari style too.
[crash]
No!
Oh, man, that's not good!
[NIWAKA]
Tamotsu.
That's my figurine.
What did you do?
Um.
I'm sorry. My bad.
♪
[NIWAKA] This figurine
was important to me!
And it was a special
limited-release, too!
I'm sorry, Niwaka, really!
[NIWAKA] It's impossible
to get another one!
Nonsense, where there's
a web there's a way!
We'll search the
auction sites. It's fine!
Well even if I can replace it,
you're missing the point, dummy.
How do you think you'd feel
if somebody broke something
you really cared about?
"Take care of it."
Do you not remember
who said that to me?
This shot is on a
whole other level!
[NIWAKA]
Are you even listening to me?!
Focus on the positive, sis!
I mean look at this!
That angle's called the
Kanada Perspective,
after the anime titan
Kanada Yoshinori,
who was super influential-- Uh?
[NIWAKA]
Whatever!
[TAMOTSU]
Why is she so pissed off?
[MATOME] It's a reasonable
reaction, you jerk.
You broke her collectible
and then brushed off her
feelings like nothing.
That's super bad!
I'm not sure I've seen
her this angry before.
I know, me neither.
You really picked the wrong
figurine to break, Tamotsu.
Don't act like I'm a heartless
monster, you guys.
I'm working on it. See?
I'm already searching the
auctions for a replacement.
I'm gonna buy her
the exact same one!
You sure that's gonna be
enough to make it better?
Maybe not, but the
"You Break You Buy" rule's
a pretty good start!
[TAMOTSU]
Let's see,
my part-time work
funds are already low,
so I'm hoping I can
snag a cheap one.
Let the bidding begin.
Hai ! Arigato gozaimasu !
Fujiyama ! Ninja! Hikikomori !
What?! Where'd that
bid come from?!
[ARISA]
Whoa! That price is crazy!
Damn it! Sorry, sis.
Your brother lost without
even putting up a fight!
So keep searching.
[TAMOTSU]
But that was the cheap one!
The other auctions
are all jacked up, too!
Aw, man!
This is starting to look
way harder than I thought.
To replace that thing,
I'm gonna need a lot more dough.
[TAMOTSU groans]
[MASHIRO]
Hey, what's up, champ?
Any good short-term gigs?
[MASHIRO]
Already back for more?
Wow, you must really
love to work, huh?
Let's see what's come in.
Short-term, short-term,
what do we got?
Ah, here's something.
What do you think?
It's a great hourly rate
with bonuses depending
on performance!
[TAMOTSU]
Hell yeah! That's perfect!
"Interview in the CEO's
office, third floor."
[KUROI] So what makes you
wanna work here, young man?
I have a love for labor, sir.
In particular, I've always been
fascinated by bar management,
especially with maid
and-or butler themes.
It's kinda my passion.
[KUROI]
I see.
And do you live
close to Akihabara?
[TAMOTSU]
Oh, yeah, you could say that.
[TAMOTSU chuckles]
[KUROI] I trust you saw
our generous hourly rate?
[gasps] Yes! It's
very lucrative, sir!
That's an energetic response.
Sounds like the money's what
you're really passionate about.
[chuckles]
Well sir, I didn't think
"wanting to rake it in"
would have been a good answer.
[KUROI]
Don't worry!
We basically hire anyone
who's willing to work,
as long as they're not
an absolute train wreck.
[TAMOTSU]
Really?
That's reassuring.
[KUROI chuckles]
You're not the first worker
to come for the money.
[chuckles] I thought so!
[KUROI]
However!
That was only at the start,
then they saw the light.
They came to learn
there are some things
more valuable than money.
It's my sincere hope that
working with us here
will teach you what really
matters most in life, too.
Welcome to our family, Tamotsu!
Uh. Thank you, sir.
Glad to be here.
This place is impressive.
But what's with the get-up?
Honestly. I feel kinda
ridiculous in this thing.
[NISHI]
Don't worry.
It looks great on you, Tamotsu.
[TAMOTSU]
And you are?
I'm Jiro Nishi,
good to meet you.
And I work as the
Lead Butler here.
Oh. Okay, good to meet you too.
Thanks for the encouragement.
I'm curious, though.
What's the deal with this
heart on my nametag?
[IWAKADO] The hearts
are like achievements.
They mark your training level.
My what?
[IWAKADO] Everyone gets
one heart for free.
That's to show our appreciation
for you joining the team!
And then you can
earn the other two!
[NISHI] The two of us
are at three hearts.
That means we've truly learned
to serve not just ourselves,
but our colleagues
and our customers.
I see.
Thanks for clearing that up
in a not-at-all confusing way.
[IWAKADO]
So work hard!
And hopefully you can catch up
to our heart level
soon, Tamotsu!
Uh, yeah. Okay.
Staff! Line formation!
[TAMOTSU]
Uhh...
[NISHI] Let us speak
the Five Sacred Phrases
of Customer Service.
[TAMOTSU]
Uh. Uh...
Welcome home, Master!
How may I serve you?
[MAIDS, BUTLERS] Welcome home,
Master! How may I serve you?
My apologies, Master!
Please forgive me!
[MAIDS, BUTLERS] My apologies,
Master! Please forgive me!
One moment please, Master.
I'll be right with you.
[MAIDS, BUTLERS]
One moment please, Master.
I'll be right with you.
Thank you for waiting, Master.
I am here to serve you!
[MAIDS, BUTLERS]
Thank you for waiting, Master.
I am here to serve you!
Fare thee well, Master!
Have a safe trip!
[MAIDS, BUTLERS]
Fare thee well, Master!
Have a safe trip!
[TAMOTSU yelps]
[NISHI]
Tamotsu!
Let your voice ring loudly,
or your master won't
be able to hear you!
[TAMOTSU]
Sorry, it's my first time.
I got performance anxiety.
[KUROI]
Go easy on him, Nishi.
We have to crawl
before we learn to fly.
[MAIDS, BUTLERS whimpering]
[KUROI] Now let's get
on with it, shall we?
[chuckles]
So who wants to tell me
our Great Goal of the Day?
[MAIDS, BUTLERS shouting]
Please! Let it be me, sir!
No! I want it more, sir!
[IWAKADO]
No, sir! Let me do it, please!
I want it with every
fiber of my being!
[KUROI] Very well.
You may have the honor.
[IWAKADO]
Oh, thank you, sir, thank you!
You won't regret this...
[TAMOTSU] What the hell
kind of workplace is this?
[TAMOTSU sighs]
[MATOME]
You were out late.
[TAMOTSU]
Huh?
Does that mean you
found a new job?
Yeah.
Now I'm working at a
maid-and-butler bar.
And I may have made a bad
choice, or at least a weird one.
Well just don't let your job
affect our patrols, okay?
[TAMOTSU] I think we need to
pause those for a while.
'Least till I settle in.
You're always making excuses to
get out of it. It's important!
I have to get up early,
will you let me sleep?
I need money.
The Buggies can wait.
What kind of attitude is that?!
Fine, I'll protect Akiba myself!
But you better patch
things up with Niwaka!
At least then you'll
do one thing right!
[NIWAKA]
He's so stupid.
One moment please, Master.
I'll be right with you.
Hi, thank you for
waiting, Master.
I am here to serve you!
[TAMOTSU yelps]
Uh, thank you for waiting,
Master. I'm here to serve you!
Whoa, that looks great!
Thanks, man!
Oh. Yeah, of course!
You're welcome!
I got a load of dishes here!
[COOK A]
Okay!
[sighs]
[IWAKADO]
I heard that.
Huh? Heard what? What'd I do?
Relax it's not bad.
I mean I heard you got your
first "thank you" from a master!
Great job!
Oh, but that's normal, right?
You get thanked all the time.
I do now, but when I started,
it took me a long time
to get my first "thanks."
Looks like you might have a real
knack for this job, Tamotsu.
[chuckles]
Wow, you think so?
[NISHI] Could I get some
assistance out here, please?
Yeah! I'm coming!
Tamotsu.
This young lady is celebrating
her birthday with us today.
Oh, that's great to hear.
Happy birthday, master!
[NISHI] She would like to have
a photo to mark the occasion.
Yeah, sure.
Uh. Actually. Why don't we
kick it up another notch?
Say "cheese"!
Wow.
I haven't seen one of those
in a while. How retro!
Well I figure since
it's a special occasion,
we might as well do
something special, right?
[NISHI]
I think it's brilliant, Tamotsu.
From now on, you're the bar's
special event photographer!
[TAMOTSU]
Uh.
Photographer? I do like
the sound of that.
[GIRL A]
Wow!
I love it! It's perfect! Thank
you, Mr. Butler-photographer!
Using your talents
to delight a master,
now that is some
next level servitude!
You are a great new butler!
[TAMOTSU yelps]
It wasn't that impressive.
It was mostly point-and-click.
Let us both labor hard together!
Right. Yes sir!
[MAIDS, BUTLERS] Fare thee well,
Masters! Have a safe trip!
[KUROI]
Tamotsu.
[TAMOTSU]
Manager, sir!
Seems you found
the elbow grease.
Guess so.
But it's nothing I would
complain about, sir.
I just realized that when
masters have a good time,
I do, too.
Wow, that's great!
You've already reached the next
stage of service enlightenment
by seeing things from the
master's point of view!
[NISHI] Your call, sir.
[KUROI]
Mh-hm.
[KUROI chuckles]
[KUROI]
Here. You've earned it.
Whoa, you're giving
me a second heart?!
[KUROI] That's right, Tamotsu.
You're more than ready.
Keep working hard, and the
rewards will be vast, indeed.
Congratulations, Tamotsu!
This calls for a Cheer Circle!
[BUTLERS]
Congratulations, Tamotsu!
[MAIDS]
[MAID 7A] And up!
[MAIDS, BUTLERS]
Huzzah! Huzzah!
Huzzah! Huzzah! Huzzah! Huzzah!
[TAMOTSU]
Thanks, guys!
[MAIDS, BUTLERS]
Huzzah! Huzzah!
Huzzah! Huzzah! Huzzah! Huzzah!
[TAMOTSU laughing]
[sighs]
[TAMOTSU snoring]
[MATOME]
We barely see you anymore.
[MAID B]
I wonder how I'll do this week.
[IWAKADO]
You'll be fine. You worked hard!
Yeah, we all did.
There's no reason to worry!
[TAMOTSU]
Huh?
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, yeah, that's right,
this is your first one!
We're about to have our
weekly Thank You Pay Day.
What's a Thank You Pay Day?
We get extra "Thank You Pay"
for all the times
masters thank us.
Best day of the week!
So what, like he
hands out checks?
[IWAKADO]
You'll see!
Trust me, it's great!
[KUROI]
Excellent maid work!
[TAMOTSU] That flyer did mention
a unique payment scheme,
and getting more based
on performance.
I wonder how much I'll get.
[NISHI]
Wow, 40? Thank you, sir!
[TAMOTSU] Forty what?
Forty G's? Like forty thousand?
[KUROI]
Tamotsu.
Yes, sir!
You've done quite
well for yourself.
That's rare for a butler
in his first week.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you very much, manager!
[TAMOTSU]
This feels like a major wad!
[VOICE]
Thank you!
What the hell is this?
No way!
I've never seen anyone
get so many "thank you"s
in their first week!
[NISHI]
I knew you had great potential.
Am I missing something?
Do these have actual value?
The greatest value of all.
The value of knowing you've
made so many masters happy!
And shattering the
opening week record
is an incredible accomplishment,
which calls for
another Cheer Circle!
Thanks for making
us proud, Tamotsu!
[BUTLERS]
Thank you, Tamotsu!
[MAIDS]
[MAIDS, BUTLERS]
Huzzah!
Okay. You're welcome, I guess.
Niwaka. It's good to see you.
So my brother's not here?
[MATOME]
Mm-mm.
[MATOME] You come to talk to
him about that broken figure?
[NIWAKA] Yeah. I think
I may have been a bit
too harsh on him.
And even if he deserved it, I
don't want it to drive us apart.
[MATOME sighs]
That big idiot.
He doesn't deserve a sister as
sweet and understanding as you.
And now he's left
you alone to worry.
[NIWAKA sighs]
Big brother! Whatcha readin'?
I'm learning how to set myself
up with a work-free life!
Wow, really?
[TAMOTSU]
Done!
[NIWAKA gasps]
Looks great! You're so good!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[NIWAKA]
Hey, bro!
[NIWAKA chuckles]
[gasps]
[NIWAKA gasps]
Tamotsu. If you care
why don't you show it?!
Did I... miss something?
[TAMOTSU gasps]
I'm sorry, Masters!
[IWAKADO] What's going
on with you today?
You're not acting like yourself.
Please forgive me.
You'll never get "thank you's"
with this kind of performance.
Look, You're way
better than this.
Are you giving your all?
I think so.
[IWAKADO] Lies! You're working
scared 'cause of one mistake!
Sorry, Head Maid.
I don't want to
hear more apologies.
What I want is for you
to rise to the potential
you've already
shown us you have.
When you got your first
"thank you," you were glowing.
That's the lover-of-work
I want to see.
But I'm not like you,
I don't love working.
I just wanted the cash!
I'm living a lie!
[IWAKADO] Nobody starts with
the pure passion for labor.
I was just like you once.
But I found the true path,
and so will you.
[TAMOTSU gasps]
[IWAKADO] Collecting smiles
and "thank you's" from masters,
that's the real essence of life.
Don't be scared, you'll learn.
We'll show you.
Let's stay on the "thank
you" path together, okay?
Okay!
[NISHI] You're not alone
and never will be again.
We're your new family, Tamotsu.
Don't give up
the fight, Tamotsu!
Stand up and make us all proud!
[TAMOTSU]
Yes. I'm sorry for doubting.
I'll never give up! I'll work
hard and always give my best!
[ALL] Do your best, Tamotsu!
Do your best, Tamotsu!
Huzzah! Huzzah! Huzzah...!
[TAMOTSU giggles, laughs]
[MASHIRO grunts]
[TAMOTSU] The Butler and Maid
Bar GON-chan is awaiting our
master's return! We hope that
we may serve you soon, master!
[MASHIRO] Hey! Street soliciting
is banned!
[TAMOTSU] Miss Mashiro!
Thank you for pointing me
to a great new job
and way of life!
Here you go! Fare thee well!
[MASHIRO] That doesn't look
healthy. Hmm, whatever!
[KUROI] Who wants to say
the Great Goal of the Day?
I do! I do! Please pick me, sir!
I want it! I crave it!
I need it so bad!
Another round, please?
Thank you for waiting, master!
I'm here to serve you!
I need 50 orders of
sliced cabbage, quick!
Our masters are hungry!
Wait, 50?!
Don't worry guys,
I'm on it!
I'm writing up the schedule
for next week. What's your--
Please put me down
for every shift, sir!
You're really in
top form, aren't you?
Thank you sir! I finally
realized fate brought me
to Akiba so I could
work as a butler here!
This is my life's true calling!
It's strange. He's not even
coming home at night now.
We haven't seen
him in a week.
[ARISA] Guys, guys!
It's worse than we thought!
What's is it?
Tamotsu's in major trouble!
[NIWAKA]
What have they done to him?
[NIWAKA] Where is he?
[MAID B,C]
Hm?
[TAMOTSU] Welcome home, Master.
How may I serve you?
[ALL gasp]
[NIWAKA] Bro! Why do
you look like that?
Tamotsu! You have
to quit, right now!
You're way too close to
the point of no return!
What are you saying?
Why would I quit?
It's the best
workplace of all time.
Collecting "thank you's"
is everything.
It's my dream come true!
Your dream?
How does someone collect
"thank you's"?
You're making no sense!
This is bad, they've really
got into his head!
[MATOME, ARISA gasp]
Yes! You understand,
don't you, Niwaka?
Oh, I knew you would.
Now let us join as a team and
collect "thank you's" together!
[NIWAKA]
I'm doing this for you.
Huh? Doing what?
[TAMOTSU groans]
Wake up, Big Bro!
Oh, snap!
Man, that girl can hit.
Niwaka--
[NIWAKA]
I said wake up now!
[TAMOTSU groans]
[NIWAKA gasps]
Tamotsu! Bro, are you okay? Hey!
I wasn't trying to hurt you.
I was just trying to help you
snap out of this, so you
could be yourself again.
I know your real dream,
and it's not to work here.
You want to write your
own novel, which becomes a
best-seller and gets made
into a live-action movie.
The movie's a total flop, but
then it's rebooted as an anime,
and that's a gigantic hit! Then
you spend the rest of your life
lounging off the royalties! It's
your dream of unearned income!
Don't tell me you've
forgotten that!
[gasps] Unearned income!
That's right!
How could I become a sweaty cog
in the conformity machine?
That's not like me at all!
There's the Tamotsu
we know and love!
You've got a lot of
making up to do.
You made your poor
sister cry again.
Yeah, that's right
you big dummy!
[TAMOTSU] Sorry. Those were
some nice hits, though!
What's going on in here?
Those aren't the
sounds of hard labor!
[KUROI sighs] That's a shame.
And he showed so much promise.
Seventeen days.
The record ends there.
To make us slave away in
these inhumane conditions,
you must be inhuman
yourself, aren't you?
[chuckles] I never would've
guessed that this would be
the day I was exposed.
--[GIRLS] A Bugged One!
--[TAMOTSU] I called it!
My beautifully sinister plan
is to cut labor costs,
provide cheap food and drink,
and rule Akiba from its stomach,
and now that you've outed me,
I clearly can't let you live.
Technically-part-
time-warriors, attack!
[BUTLERS, MAIDS] Welcome home,
Master! How may I serve you?
I've got this.
[shouts]
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL giggle]
[MATOME gasps]
They're not Bugged Ones,
they're just people brainwashed
into thinking work is cool!
Stripping them won't help!
What? Then what should we do?
[MAID B]
Huh?
[ARISA]
Moi!
That's easy, Ma!
Just kick some butt!
[ALL shouting]
It works every time!
Feels wrong when
they aren't Buggies.
[NISHI, IWAKADO groan]
[TAMOTSU] Looks like we're gonna
wrap this case up pretty easily.
[KUROI]
Spoke too soon!
Aw, crap.
Don't move another muscle, boy!
Big brother!
Don't hurt her!
--[MATOME] Niwaka!
--[ARISA] Niwaka, no!
[KUROI] What's the best way
to manipulate a worker?
His family! Attaching her
clothes to mine
will make you powerless!
[KUROI laughs] Now stripping
me would strip her as well,
and what kind of brother
would do that?
Cowardly bastard!
You're the worst boss ever!
Charge!
Damn it!
[ARISA grunts, screams]
[MATOME grunts]
How do we get out of this?
If we attack him,
then Niwaka will be--
[screams]
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[TAMOTSU]
Niwaka.
Tamotsu! Help me!
[TAMOTSU]
I'm coming!
Tamotsu!
What're you doing?
Niwaka. You have
to trust me, okay?
You don't care what
happens to your sister,
is that what you're saying?
Okay, Fine!
Here's my resignation!
[TAMOTSU shouts]
[NIWAKA screams]
[KUROI]
But I'm a job creator!
[TAMOTSU sighs] Wow, it's so
great getting to go home
when the sun is still out!
[NIWAKA]
Hey, bro?
[TAMOTSU]
Huh?
[NIWAKA] I'm sorry I got so
mad at you the other day.
[TAMOTSU] No, you had
a right to be mad.
It was important to you.
Which is why I want to make
it up to you with this.
[NIWAKA gasps]
You got one?
[TAMOTSU] I may have lost
sight of who I was
in that sake' sweatshop,
but I never lost sight of you.
[Gasps]
You're the best, Tamotsu!
Really! This'll be my
most prized possession!
Thank you! Oh, thank you!
[TAMOTSU gasps]
What's the matter?
Something wrong?
What did you say to me?
I just said, "thank you."
[sceams]
No! I can't take it!
What are you freaking out about?
Just say, "you're welcome,"
you weirdo!
[TAMOTSU] No more "thank you's"!
Anything but that!
♪
[TAMOTSU]
Arisa mastered a new "art"?
[NIWAKA]
Yes! " Atozuke ,"
the ancient art of casually
explaining key plot points.
[TAMOTSU]
Where'd she learn that?
[NIWAKA] A book by Minmin
Bookstore: Become a Writer !
Secret Chinese Techniques From
Fifty Thousand Years Ago !
[TAMOTSU] Next Akiba's Trip ,
The Animation :
Akihabara Grand Tournament!
[NIWAKA]
I am Niwaka Denkigai!