[NARRATOR] Akihabara,
the otaku city of dreams,
is now under attack from
mysterious monstrosities
known as the Bugged Ones.
Some brave citizens have
formed vigilante groups
to resist this Buggy scourge,
but the invasion intensifies
with each new day.
This is the story
of Tamotsu Denkigai,
a young man given
Bugged Ones powers,
turned from superfan
into superhero.
Can he and his merry band
save the greatest shopping
neighborhood in the world?!
Come on. It's cool my
parents sent me food,
but can't they get
with the decade?
[NIWAKA]
Look, bro! Mom sent you rice!
Wow! That looks like
some high-quality stuff!
When do we eat?
But then I guess if
the base actually had
a rice cooker,
it wouldn't be a problem.
Yes, as great as our Ma is,
she doesn't seem to
be much of a cook.
Loves to eat, though!
Yeah!
Oh shut up, you guys.
We all have things
we're good at and
eating's one of mine.
Tamotsu doesn't cook either!
Whoa, hey! Just 'cause I don't
cook, doesn't mean I can't!
Oh god, don't get
him started on that.
That seems like the
kind of thing Tamotsu
would spend too much money on!
You're not wrong. That reminds
me of the time he got obsessed
with making his own curry.
He spent hours hand-picking
and mixing spices.
Then nursed the soup for
three days without sleep!
He chose his rice
one grain at a time!
It took him a whole week just
to finish cooking one meal!
You didn't even mention
my craft pickling!
[ARISA]
Oh, don't worry.
Next time you want
some curry, you can ask me!
Wait, really?
You can do that too?
You bet, I'm a curry master!
Wow.
Uh...
Huh?
[TAMOTSU] What's going on?
Some kind of street show?
Look! What are those things?
[ALL]
Huh?
I think they're boxes.
Wow. How is that even possible?
Yeah, they look heavy.
Why is his neck not snapping?
[ARISA]
I know him!
[TAMOTSU, NIWAKA, MATOME]
Huh?
He... He's my old master!
♪
[TAMOTSU]
You sure about this, Arisa?
Yeah. When he passed us
he didn't react at all.
There's no way I could
forget that face,
he was definitely my
old kung-fu master,
from my training days in China!
You trained in China?!
Interesting. Well that explains
how you're so strong.
That's right. The training he
put me through was super tough.
But it was such a
rewarding experience,
because up until then,
my life had been
nothing but school.
Ten years ago, I graduated from
Ultimate University in the U.S.
I'd been obsessed
with academics,
so after I got my diploma,
I started traveling to figure
out what to do next.
[TAMOTSU] Hold on, you have
a college degree?!
[MATOME]
So you're actually smart?
[ARISA]
I wanted to find my passion,
something to commit my life to.
I thought travelling around
the world would open my eyes
to all the possibilities,
so I could see what
spoke to me most.
I perfected
curry-making in India,
explored the finer points of
British humor in England.
And harnessed my wild side
in the African jungle!
That's amazing, Arisa!
You've been everywhere!
Must've been exhausting.
This escalator's not long enough
for the full list, but let's
just say I've tried lots of
things in lots of countries.
And one of them was learning
kung-fu with my master in China.
[ARISA]
I only trained for a year,
but I can't describe
how much it meant to me.
He didn't just train my body,
he trained my heart.
Whether I was facing my fears,
overcoming giant obstacles,
or simply learning to relax,
he was with me all the way.
Then finally after I
mastered the martial arts,
it was time to move on,
so I came here to master
the equally-sacred
art of the otaku.
So that's the story of
how you came to Japan, huh?
I just thought you
were a foreigner
who got on the wrong plane.
You silly!
But that doesn't explain why
your old master's in Akiba.
I know, that's a
mystery to me, too.
He did want to take his
family to see Japan one day,
so maybe that's it.
[giggles] Anyway, back to
the rice cooker!
[NIWAKA] Never heard of
a rice cooker shortage.
How can every brand be sold out?
And the display models too?
[CLERK A] Sorry. As you
see we're completely out,
you'll have to wait for
our next shipment.
Sir! But we have
a rice emergency!
Is it normal for rice
cookers to sell out?
Must've been a real
shopping spree.
[gasps]
Look Tamotsu, over there!
Huh?
Walking boxes again?
Could it be?
Actually, he's the
one who bought
all the rice cookers today.
He's my new favorite customer.
Wait up!
Listen, I need a--
[TAMOTSU grunts]
Hey, I'm talking to you, dude!
[ARISA] It's been a
long time, Master!
Moi, you should have told
me you were coming here,
I'd be happy to show you around!
What do we have here? Did you
run into somebody you know?
How bizarre.
I could stare at her
attack powers all day!
[groans]
Who in the world are you, lady?
You know my master?
[RISA] I think "knowing him"
is an understatement,
considering how
important I am to him.
The name's Diva Risa McWhite.
I'm his manager.
Diva Risa McWhite, really?
The Diva Risa McWhite?
You know her?
She's a mysterious promoter who
came out of nowhere in the world
of competitive martial arts.
She's been causing gigantic
waves in the industry
and is famous not only
for how well she works
behind the scenes,
but in the spotlight too!
She's ultra-aggressive
with promoting
and sometimes even jumps in
the ring and wins herself!
A promoter, huh? So what's
she doing with your master?
The answer to that
is obvious, you amateur.
I'm using this talented fighter
as my tool to conquer Akiba!
[TAMOTSU]
How's that obvious?
[MATOME] And what's
martial arts promoting
have to do with rice cookers?
[RISA] Nothing, so they
won't see it coming!
I'll use his foreign status to
buy goods at duty-free discounts
then resell to Japanese at
full price to warp demand
and confuse the market.
And in that economic chaos,
we will swoop in and conquer!
That's the craziest
plan I've heard yet.
And I thought internet
resellers were bad.
Only a Bugged One
could be that evil!
Guilty as charged. I admit
you've guessed well.
Now you can die!
[BOTH gasp]
Cue the usual song and dance!
Not my Master!
Oh, no!
[RISA] Yes, I've turned him into
my slave, buying my rice cookers
and carrying them on his big
strong kung-fu master head.
That's unforgivable!
For the neck strain alone!
It can't be true.
My master wouldn't be
controlled that easily!
Look at his hair, Arisa.
It's not up for debate.
[RISA chuckles] I'm afraid we
can't carry out our plans
with all you flies
buzzing around,
so it's time to bring
out the swatter.
[gasps, groans]
Master!
[RISA chuckles] Unless you're
the masochistic type,
I suggest you leave
while you still can.
Look at him, Tamotsu.
He's strong.
Guys. Stand back.
[ARISA gasps] Master, you can
fight through this!
Your mind's far too
strong to be taken over!
[MASTER shouts]
[ARISA groans]
[TAMOTSU]
Arisa!
I did warn you not
to stick around.
Take care of them, slave!
Here he comes!
[MATOME grunts, shouts]
[TAMOTSU grunts, shouts]
[BOTH grunt]
[NIWAKA]
You okay?
[TAMOTSU, NIWAKA gasp]
[ARISA shouts]
[gasps]
This is my battle.
[CLERK A] My dear shoppers.
While the customer is usually
always right, we do draw
the line at grappling.
And as you see you're
stopping others from doing
their shopping,
which is a cardinal sin.
If you'd like to keep fighting,
I will take appropriate action,
which may include calling
security and the dreaded
nuclear option of revoking
your frequent shopper points.
[ALL]
No! We're sorry!
That sales clerk was
really something.
If saving Akiba meant ruining
people's shopping trips,
then would we really be
saving Akiba at all?
That's a tragic dilemma for you,
but we can't just let
our fight fizzle out.
So why don't you let
me provide the arena?
Say what?
I mean a truly epic
venue that befits a battle
between kung-fu masters.
Yes. Let the Akiba Grand
Tournament begin!
[ALL gasp]
If that's how it has to be.
[FANS cheering]
[MASUTO]
No doubt about it, Kage,
the feeling in this
arena is electric!
[KAGE]
Yeah, this turnout's incredible!
I bet anyone who thought you
couldn't set up a ring in the
middle of a shopping district
feels dumb right now!
Well I know I do!
[BOTH gasp]
--[FAN A] Yeah! Bring it on!
--[FAN B] Woo, here we go!
♪
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen!
Introducing the first fighter!
From Hunan China,
weighing in at 154 pounds!
He's the kung-fu champion
of the world, Master!
And here comes the
fearsome Master,
stalking down the walkway
in his devil panda style!
[KAGE] He knows how to make
an entrance, that's for sure!
Wow! As quickly as this
fight was organized,
it's shocking he
has so many fans!
One might even say
it defies credibility,
but I'm just here for the ride!
[KAGE] I'm not surprised.
He's clearly got the right mix
of scowling and
flamboyant weirdness
to be a charismatic heel!
[MASUTO] Let's see if
he can work the crowd.
[FANS cheering]
[MASUTO] And work it he does!
With his Extreme Akiba Pose!
The fans are warmed
up and ready to go!
[MASUTO]
Ooh, and what's this?
Diva Risa is entering
the ring with a mic!
Listen up, all you weak
little boys of Akiba!
I went all the way to China
to find me a real man,
and now he's gonna
help me conquer you!
This is bad, fans! Diva Risa
wants to rule over us all!
[RISA]
And who's gonna stop me?
You so-called vigilantes who
pretend to defend this town?
Well I'm sure it's fun
to act like sheriffs,
but I don't remember
anyone giving you badges,
so excuse me if I don't shiver!
[KUROBUGS cheer]
[MASUTO]
She's right,
the vigilantes have
no legal authority!
Just the unwritten
code of the street!
[KAGE] Maybe so, but at least
their intentions are good!
[VIGILANTES]
Risa sucks!
[RISA] Scream all you want,
babies, I won't stop!
If I have to knock you out
one by one to get my way,
that's fine with me!
--♪
--[FANS cheering]
[MASUTO]
Wait! That entrance music!
Could it be?
[ARISA giggles]
Moi!
[ANNOUNCER] And his opponent.
From Helsinki, Finland,
weighing in at a fierce
112 pounds, Arisa Ahokainen!
[FANS cheer]
[MASUTO] You heard that right!
It's Arisa Ahokainen,
from the rising stars
of the vigilante world,
Electric Mayonnaise and Friends!
Tonight she'll defend the
name of unlicensed
crime-fighters everywhere,
and try to put Diva
Risa's plans on ice!
[KAGE]
These are both accomplished
kung-fu martial artists!
So get ready, fans,
this should be an incredible
fight worthy of the hype!
Moi, Master, you have to
wake up, it's not too late!
You can't let this promoter-
slash-appliance-reseller
ruin you!
[MASUTO]
Ooh!
It sounds like these two
have some history, Kage!
[KAGE]
Indeed they do.
Arisa was actually
Master's apprentice.
Least that's what it
says in the press kit.
[MASUTO]
I know it hasn't started yet,
but I'm calling it anyway.
This is the fight
of the century!
[MASUTO] And we're off!
Akiba's fate is on the line,
and the rules of this match
are extremely hardcore!
This won't be easy for Arisa.
[KAGE] That's right!
Because other than
three-counts-and-your-out,
there are no rules!
Not only is Master
a kung-fu champion,
but who knows what
Risa has up her gloves!
[MASUTO] Yes, Arisa will have to
keep an eye on her opponent
and her back!
In terms of raw power,
it seems Arisa has the edge.
[MASUTO] But he uses it against
her and throws her to the ropes!
Astounding technique!
[grunts]
[MASUTO] And there it is!
Our first chair attack!
[KAGE] That hurts even more
when you don't see it coming!
Hey! No fair!
Didn't you hear?
This is a no-rules fight!
[REF grunts]
[MASUTO] The ref is down!
Earlier than usual!
[RISA]
Now! Use the chair!
[ARISA gasps]
Yes, I knew it!
[RISA]
What? Disobeying?
Don't you care what
happens to them?
[MASUTO] Oh no! Looks like
Master's family is being
held hostage in some sort
of lettuce labor camp!
[KAGE] Yes, looks like
a mountain village
lettuce labor camp.
Those are the worst.
Do it!
[MASTER grunts, shouts]
[ARISA]
No, Master. Fight it!
[ARISA shouts]
[BROADCASTERS gasp]
Dios Mio!
Arisa no!
[MASUTO]
This is looking dangerous!
[MASUTO] Is he really
going to jump from there?
[grunts]
[MASUTO] That's Master's
Tombstone Bomb!
[MASUTO] Oh no! Our
Spanish-language broadcasters!
[FANS cheering]
[KAGE] That was awesome!
I mean, I hope they're okay.
[MASUTO]
What do we have here?
Master is pulling out...
a kendo stick!
[ARISA grunts]
[MASTER shouts]
[ARISA gasps]
[MASUTO]
His weapon attack fails!
[grunting]
[MASUTO] Now Arisa unloads
with rapid-fire chops!
She's unstoppable!
[ARISA yells]
[MASUTO] What is that
on the mega-screen?
[KAGE] I think those are
the locker rooms. But why?
I'm sorry. I let my
guard down, Arisa.
It's my fault.
Please rescue us, big bro!
[MASUTO] They're from Electric
Mayonnaise and Friends!
This is a full-blown disaster!
They've been taken hostage, too!
[ARISA, TAMOTSU]
Oh, no!
[FANS cheering]
[KAGE]
Very dirty move!
Time to end this nonsense
and bow down to me!
Lest you don't care what
happens to your friends!
Aw damn it, I was wondering
where they were!
[growls]
Ma! Niwaka!
[grunts]
[MASUTO] Master launches
his counter-attack,
with Arisa afraid to fight back!
No, Master! Stop!
[RISA] Ha! Your only
choice is surrender!
[MASUTO] Even for a
no-holds-barred fight,
this is brutal!
[ARISA grunts]
[MASUTO] There it is, folks!
The infamous move!
Master's Shaming Spread!
[KAGE] Punishing both physically
and psychologically!
Great camera work, though.
I can't fight or my
teammates will suffer.
What do I do?
I can't just stand
here and watch!
[TAMOTSU grunts]
[ARISA grunts]
[MASUTO] Master releases her!
What is he up to now?
I think I see a table!
Oh! Make that
tables with an "s"!
[KAGE]
No doubt about what this means.
He's setting up his
trademark high-altitude move,
the Last Emperor Press!
[MASUTO] He's climbing
the extra-tall ladder!
[KAGE]
Nice and slow.
[MASUTO] If he pulls this off,
the match will be over!
Right, Kage?
[KAGE]
Oh yeah!
This was his finisher in the
Chinese tournament, too.
--[ARISA grunts]
--[engine revs]
What the--?
Tamotsu!
[FANS]
TM2, TM2, TM2...!
[KUROBUGS growl]
[KUROBUGS grunt]
You guys okay?
Yeah, now!
I knew you'd come save us!
[KAGE]
His daring rescue worked.
This frees up Arisa for
her own counterattack!
Damn you!
[ARISA grunts]
[ARISA shouts]
[MASUTO] Could it get any more
intense?! A triple-table slam!
And both fighters are down!
Now's your chance, Master!
While she's still reeling!
Use this to finish her
once and for all!
You do want to save
your family, don't you?
What, don't you care?
[RISA gasps, grunts]
Hey! What the hell was that?
You're attacking
the wrong woman!
My wushu is sacred.
I did not master these
arts for dastardly deeds.
[MASUTO] A shocking
betrayal by Master!
What could've caused
this sudden turn?
[KAGE]
Maybe head trauma?
He crashed through
those tables pretty hard!
Or maybe it was Risa's
slap that did it.
Wouldn't that be ironic?
[MASTER, RISA grunt]
[MASUTO]
Oh! And Diva Risa is down!
Master.
This fight is not over.
I trust you understand.
[ARISA grunts]
[MASTER, ARISA
grunting, shouting]
[MASUTO] Here comes his killer
Clothesline from Mapo Tofu!
Oh! A crushing counter!
She smashes his
groin like a gong!
Now brace yourself, Master!
[MASUTO]
This is it, folks!
Arisa's signature
finishing move!
[KAGE] She calls it her
"Lovely Final: The End
of Attack!" Very catchy!
[MASTER groans]
[FANS cheer]
[gasps]
[FANS]
One, two... three!
[bell rings]
[MASUTO] The Master-Apprentice
Fight of the Century is over,
and the apprentice has won!
--[RISA shouts]
--[ARIS grunts]
[MASUTO]
Uh, oh! Bad news for Arisa!
[KAGE] She spent all
her energy on Master.
Is there anything
left in the tank?
Because of you,
my sinister scheme
to buy and resell rice
cookers is ruined!
I can't forgive you for that!
♪
[MASUTO]
What does this music mean?
[KAGE]
Looks like Tamotsu is back!
Akiba belongs
to everybody, lady!
There's no way I'll allow
a monster like you
to ruin our town!
[FANS cheer]
[RISA grunts]
Now get ready for a
face-full of Tamotsu!
Even if you strike me down,
you won't be free!
Another reseller
will take my place!
Then I'll crush them too!
Your only choice is surrender!
[KAGE] It's the legendary Two
Platoons World of Gonzo!
[MASUTO]
They did it!
Sorry, Arisa. I hate that I
caused such chaos in your town.
Don't worry, it's no big deal!
I'm a resilient girl, you know!
[MASTER chuckles]
Yes I do.
I'm just happy it's over now.
And you're safe.
It's looks like your
family's safe, too.
Obviously I need
to get stronger
if I can be manipulated
by somebody like her.
I'm restarting my
training from scratch.
Remember everyone! We vigilantes
will keep you safe in Akiba,
you can take that to the bank!
[FANS cheer]
Yeah! We'll defend the
peace no matter what,
so moi moi for now and
have fun shopping, guys!
We're Electric Mayonnaise,
so help us to help you!
Now let's have one last cheer!
[ALL]
Electric Mayonnaise!
[FANS] Electric Mayonnaise!
Electric Mayonnaise...!
♪
[MATOME]
Stop, Tamotsu!
Your life points
dropped to zero!
If you continue this
card battle, you'll die!
[TAMOTSU] Sorry, Mayo.
It's out of my hands.
[MATOME] No! Next episode:
"Tamotsu Falls!"
[TAMOTSU] No! I'm playing
a title-change card!
Now it's. "Whoa, I Battled
with Game Cards!"
[MATOME] From now on,
it's my turn forever!