I am Dark Grasper,
the chief's right hand.
[TAILRED] Is that some
kind of Tail Gear?
Not even close.
This is the ultimate armor
forged by the power
of glasses attribute.
Behold the robust
beauty of Glass Gear.
I've come a long way for you,
my friend. Let's talk.
[TWOEARLE gasps]
[TAILRED]
Who is this?
And why does she
want to talk to me?
That disguise won't fool me.
As long as you're wearing
your Tail Gear, I know
exactly who you are.
So how about you stop
playing dumb, Twoearle?
[TAILRED] I get it.
My Tail Gear has Twoearle's
attribute strength in it,
so she thinks I'm Twoearle!
[TWOEARLE] Mr. Soji.
Do you read me?
I'll use the Tail Gear's
voice changing function
to speak for you.
So you'll have to match
your body to
what I'm saying.
[TAILRED]
Roger that!
[TWOEARLE] And I think we
should try to keep things
as simple as possible,
so I need the two of you
to pretend to be passed out.
I think we can handle that.
[TAILBLUE groans]
[TWOEARLE]
Here we go.
Acena?
Oh my goodness, I can't
believe it's really you!
Yeah! That's right,
it's me, Acena!
And I want you
to know, I'm still
your number-one superfan
even after all this time!
You've changed quite
a bit, haven't you?
[DARK GRASPER]
I sure have!
I devoted my entire life to
becoming a top-notch warrior,
so I wouldn't
embarrass myself
standing next to someone
as amazing as you.
[TAILRED] She really
means business.
Wait, something's different...
Your boobies?
What happened to those
mighty mammaries?
[TAILRED] They disappeared
into a distant dimension.
No way!
[TAILRED] Yes way, so now
I don't have much left.
I lost my attribute strength
fighting Ultimaguil.
Twoearle, no!
What have you done?
[DARK GRASPER sobs]
You mean those giant,
supple love-globes
that you pressed
our young faces into
all those years ago are gone?
Are you saying that they're
never going to come back?
Like, ever?
[TWOEARLE] Unfortunately,
yes. The blue-haired girl
lying down behind me is wearing
some of my hand-me-downs.
[DARK GRASPER]
I thought that was a boy!
No boobs at all!
It looks like you dressed
a freakin' two-by-four
in some Tail Gear!
[TWOEARLE &amp; TAILRED]
By passing my Tail Gear down
to some poor flat-chested
excuse for a girl,
I've released myself
from the past.
[DARK GRASPER] You're still just
as noble and resolved as ever!
How inspiring!
I'm gonna find those
legendary cuddle cushions!
Why don't we exchange emails?
That way when I find them,
I can get in touch with you!
[TAILRED]
What are we gonna do?
I would, but... I don't
have a phone right now.
[TAILRED] She's not going to
buy a lame excuse like that!
[DARK GRASPER]
Yeah, right.
The selfie-queen I remember
always had her phone on her.
Wait! Fine!
I didn't wanna hafta say this,
but you've left me no choice.
I like breasts that haven't
developed yet and yours have,
so I don't want you anymore!
[wind whistles]
[DARK GRASPER
chuckles weakly]
I see. I didn't know
you felt that way.
Maybe now is a
good time to tell you
that I didn't join Ultimaguil
in order to destroy humanity.
I have become
Dark Grasper...
because I wanted to
get you back, Twoearle!
And I won't stop until I do.
If you need to get in touch,
I still have the same e-mail.
Well. Looks like
things are about
to get a lot
more complicated.
Owowow! Ow!
Let's see, what should
I do to you first?
I don't believe in torture!
Hey Red? Do you mind
if I stop by my house
for a while before
we all meet up again?
I don't want my family
to worry about me.
Sure thing! Just meet us at
the secret base in an hour.
[TAILYELLOW giggles]
Roger!
[TWOEARLE screams]
[DARK GRASPER]
Now, my Beautiful Hearts.
Which one of you will go first?
[indistinct groans and mutters]
[SPARROW GUILDY] It has become
clear that losing Dragguildy
was only the beginning.
Now, Leviaguildy and Krakeguildy
have also been taken down!
Dark Grasper has been acting
on her own this whole time.
She hasn't let us in
on any of her plans.
Which leads me to believe that
she's trying to edge us out.
[ALLIGAGUILDY]
Listen up, everybody!
It's already taken two hours for
a basic analysis of Tailred!
Okay, next up is the
footage of Tailblue.
Any objections to
fast forwarding this part?
[WALLA: ELEMELIANS] No
objections!
[ALLIGAGUILDY]
Good!
[ELEMELIAN 2A] That one has some
really nice twin-tails, too.
[ELEMELIAN 2B]
Oh yes, indeed.
[ALLIGAGUILDY] And now
we come to the new warrior
who defeated Krakeguildy--
Tailyellow.
She'll be a serious
problem for us.
By bringing humiliation
upon herself,
she can increase
her latent abilities.
We must not underestimate
this new warrior!
[HAROLD THE HERALD]
Make way, everyone!
[indistinct mumbling]
[SPARROW GUILDY]
Dark Grasper?
[indistinct mumbling]
As you all know,
I am Dark Grasper.
I will be taking
charge of this unit.
So from now on,
you report to me.
[HEDGEHOG GUILDY]
How can we be certain
this order came from the chief?
[DARK GRASPER]
Hm?
[HEDGEHOG GUILDY] Your
twin-tails may be incredible.
But to allow a lowly human
to hold Ultimaguil's reins
is unorthodox
to say the least.
[DARK GRASPER] Well,
in that case... Come at me.
[HEDGEHOG GUILDY]
Eh? Foolish girl.
You dare to challenge me?
I accept! Graaahh!
[ALLIGAGUILDY] Ahh--!
What did she do to him?
[SPARROW GUILDY]
You didn't see it?
[ALLIGAGUILDY]
Huh?
[SPARROW GUILDY] She struck him
down with her deadly sickle...
The Darkness Glaive.
[ELEMELIAN 2B] Whoa! She truly
is a dark executioner!
I sincerely hope
that our relationship
can continue amicably.
[indistinct mumbling]
Take down my address.
[DARK GRASPER]
You there. Alligator!
Are you some kind
of mind reader?
Come on, where is
your smartphone?
I'm just a simple-minded
barbarian warrior,
so I don't have a cell phone.
Technology is hard!
[CELLPHONE GIRL]
You have mail, Big Brother.
You have mail, Big Br--
[ALLIGAGUILDY laughs weakly]
This is my friend's phone,
I was just holding it for--
Although it's difficult not
to take this personally...
I will go easy on you today.
All I ask is that when
your head stops spinning,
stop by and get
my email address.
[SPARROW GUILDY] She truly is
a force to be reckoned with.
Each and every one of
those perverted monsters
makes my skin crawl.
I don't want anyone
to look at me right now.
I just can't take it anymore.
[MEGA NE] Poor Acena,
you have such a hard time
making friends, don't you?
If you want them to be
comfortable with you,
you're going to have
to meet them halfway.
Here.
Hold on. What's that?
[MEGA NE] These are QR codes
for your email address, Acena.
I think they'll make
this whole process
go a little more smoothly.
See, this group gets skittish
being around girls.
So if you hand these out
instead of talking to them,
which clearly freaks
them out, you might have
an easier time getting
their contact info.
Wow! That's great,
Mega Ne. Thank you!
[MEGA NE] I wish you'd stop
abbreviating my name like that.
Mega Neptune Mark Two
has a little more panache,
don't you think?
Too long.
[MEGA NE] And who's the
one who gave it to me?
Sorry for snapping, Acena.
No matter what you call me,
I'll always be there
for you and your glasses.
I just want all of your
wishes to come true.
I'm sorry to
keep you waiting!
Oh look, Miss Erina is here;
we should probably get started!
Just a moment, Madam President.
I just need to finish this!
[SOJI]
Cut it out, guys!
[TWOEARLE] Here's what
I've gathered so far.
My twin-tail attribute
powers Mr. Soji's Tail Gear.
I assume she followed its
signature to this planet.
And that's why she
thinks Tailred is me.
What other information
do we have about her?
Well, we know that
Dark Grasper is a human.
So why did those
freaks accept her?
Good point. They've
made it perfectly clear
that they have no intention of
coexisting with human beings.
[ERINA] Clearly there's
some deep dark secret
that we haven't been
able to uncover yet!
[TWOEARLE]
Huh?
[ERINA] All the telltale
signs are there.
A girl who used to idolize
Twoearle shows up
as an enemy commander?
Seems like a reckoning
is about to happen!
You could cut the tension
between them with a knife
and that only
happens when people
have secrets no one
could imagine.
Madame President. This isn't
some cheesy superhero show.
We're talking about
having to do battle
with a fellow human being!
[ERINA] Don't you
think I know that?
No one said claiming
your destiny was easy!
But whatever her end game is,
we're not gonna sit back
and watch her plan unfurl!
If Dark Grasper shows up again,
she'll have to
take on all of us!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ERINA] And I was
so excited too.
But after that last encounter,
she just disappeared.
And it's been sixteen days
since all of that happened.
[SOJI makes muffled noises]
Hey! What do the three
of you think you're doing?
Don't worry, this'll all
be over in just a second!
'Cause as soon as I can get her
off of Soji, I'm gonna kill her.
[TWOEARLE gasps]
I don't know why
it's such a big deal
for me to help a friend out
when I notice his
zipper is down.
It's only a big deal if you try
to help him with your mouth!
Would you guys stop
fighting already?
I'll bet you used one
of your weirdo devices
to pull down his zipper
in the first place.
[TWOEARLE] Yeah, well the
only way you would know that
is if you've been staring
at Mr. Soji's crotch!
So now who's the
filthy heifer, huh?
[AIKA &amp; TWOEARLE grunt]
Look at the TV, everybody!
[SOJI]
What the...?
Yeah!
One, two, three, go!
[SOJI]
Ah! Oh, man...
This might be the
best thing ever!
A twin-tail idol!
I've never seen her before.
She calls herself Anko.
Can't forget that name!
[siren blares]
[TWOEARLE] Oh, no!
Elemelian readings
from an island in the south!
Okay! Let's go!
[OTHERS]
Right!
[MIKOTO sighs]
Tail On!
[PAPILLON GUILDY]
Why, hello there.
I am one of Dark Grasper's men.
My name is Papillon Guildy.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
Hey, is it just me? Or is this
one being really polite?
[PAPILLON GUILDY] I hope you'll
forgive me for being so forward,
but I have a particular
affection for lips
as lovely as yours. Did you
know that in many cultures
it is customary to give a
kiss when you greet someone?
Yeah? I wonder how you'll
feel about being punched?
[TAILYELLOW] I've got
this, guys! Stand back!
You can't just lead
off with the boobs!
Really? But Miss Twoearle
told me that I have
special photon absorbers. She
said I should let them breathe
since I don't have to rely
on my armor for protection.
You put those things away,
right now. If you want
to be a hero, you can't go
around exposing yourself!
I'm sorry, Blue.
Still, your twin-tail bobbing
was awesome. Good work!
[TAILYELLOW gasps]
Thank you so much!
Your compliments
mean the world to me!
[PAPILLON GUILDY] Oh my,
I can see that I must
not underestimate you,
Miss Topless Twin Tails.
Don't make it sound like
she's some sort of stripper!
[TAILYELLOW] What am I supposed
to do? I feel... I feel so...
[PAPILLON GUILDY]
Now then. I think I will begin
with her lovely lips first.
Scan. Please!
I can't take it anymore!
That's it!
Butterfly!
Suck on this!
What the heck are you
doing back there, Yellow?
[PAPILLON GUILDY yells]
[TAILYELLOW] It all started
with one little compliment.
Now these feelings
are so intense
I couldn't contain
them if I wanted to!
Elemeletion!
School Swim!
[TAILYELLOW laughs]
I feel amazing! This is the
greatest day of my life!
Aura Pillar!
Voltic Judgment Time!
[TAILYELLOW yells]
[PAPILLON GUILDY] That's
not a kiss, that's a kick!
[TAILYELLOW snores]
[TAILRED] That's weird. Based
on her personality, I thought
she'd be more of a G-rated hero,
but I guess I was wrong.
Aw crap, I forgot!
I was going to ask that guy
if he knew what Dark Grasper's
ultimate objective was.
We didn't really have a lot
of time for conversation.
[TWOEARLE] If I had to guess,
I'd say her primary objective
was analyzing Miss
Erina's power.
Now that she's analyzed
each of you, we can be sure
that the coming battles
will be even more difficult.
Oh, she's good. What exactly is
your next move, Dark Grasper?
And how can I get in the way?
Yeah!
[ASST. DIRECTOR]
And cut!
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
Good work, everyone!
Anko, your performance today
was absolutely amazing!
You're getting
better every day!
Thank you so much,
that's very sweet!
I'm glad you liked it.
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
I started out pretending
I couldn't sing very well.
So it appears I'm improving
a little every day.
[DARK GRASPER] I've been
stepping it up, gradually,
just as I planned.
There was a time
when you truly were
a great producer,
Kerberos Guildy.
[DARK GRASPER] You want
me to braid my hair?
[KERBEROS GUILDY]
Yes! It's very important.
I'm afraid I must insist.
The question is whether
or not braided hair
will have a positive
effect for Iisuna Anko.
[KERBEROS GUILDY] Of course
it will! How could it not?
[DARK GRASPER] I have become the
top idol on over 20 worlds now
thanks in part to your
expert production skills.
However, having
braids in my hair
will interfere with my
ability to wear twin-tails.
[KERBEROS GUILDY]
O-Oh...
That's not gonna
work for me.
Asking me to wear braids would
go against the chief's wishes.
[KERBEROS GUILDY] He doesn't
have to know, right? Besides,
it's not like twin-tails really
need to spread any farther?
If they do, there wouldn't be
any room left for braids.
Then I wouldn't have
anything to snuggle with
and I couldn't take that!
Do you understand?
My purpose has
always been the same.
My ultimate goal is
to spread the gospel
of the twin-tails and glasses
look that I love so much.
I want everyone in the
universe to understand
that glasses look the
best with twin-tails.
And of course I want to be
known as the best partner
Twoearle ever had. I won't stray
from either of these goals.
So no matter how badly
you want me in braids,
it will never happen.
[KERBEROS GUILDY] I would love
to keep being your producer,
but this was the last straw.
I've had enough.
I can't take it anymore!
[DARK GRASPER]
Then what should we do?
[KERBEROS GUILDY]
Fight it out.
[DARK GRASPER] I have
no desire to hurt you.
[KERBEROS GUILDY] My apologies.
But the time has come
for me to give my
life for braids.
[DARK GRASPER] All right.
In that case, I won't hold back!
[KERBEROS GUILDY yells]
Chaosic Infinite!
[KERBEROS GUILDY] Take proper
care of your beautiful hair!
[AIKA] I'm telling you,
that super-sexy attack
of the president's is going to
be a problem sooner or later.
[SOJI] Eh... Well, if the
president is okay with it,
then I don't think it's so bad.
Remember, you've got to be
careful when she gets like that.
She seems innocent enough but
once that switch is flipped,
there's no telling how
mixed up things could get.
What're you talking about?
I don't understand.
Aika's just jealous because
Tailyellow is so much sexier
than she is. The one
thing Aika can do better
is fight, and lets be
honest, that's not hot.
[AIKA] I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm not violent. I just
enjoy the sounds you make
when I'm choking
the life out of you.
Oh. Hey, you're awake.
[AIKA] I could listen
to it all day.
What do you think
about that? Huh?
[ERINA]
Aika!
I need you to come over
here and hit me too!
[AIKA &amp; TWOEARLE]
Huh?
You two seem to be best friends
and you're hitting
her all the time.
If I'm truly going to be
a member of this group,
then I need to be part
of that stuff as well.
Go ahead and slap me across
the face, Aika! Please!
No. Sorry. I couldn't
possibly do that.
Well, I guess I can't
force you. All right, Soji.
Looks like you're gonna
have to hit me instead!
No way! I can't do that!
[ERINA] I need you to hit me so
I can feel closer to you guys.
Go on. Do it!
Well, if it really means
that much to you...
Wha-- Hold on, Soji!
This is what I've been waiting
for. Your hands on my face.
Now do it harder.
I want that sweet sting
to linger for a while!
[SOJI] Time out,
Madame President!
I think you might be
missing the point!
[TWOEARLE] Miss Erina, can we
talk over here for a moment?
I think I can help you out.
[AIKA] Wait, what
are you guys doing?
So look, here's the deal.
Soji is still at a stage
in his development
where he has a difficult time
acting naturally whenever
he's around you.
Oh, I see. What do you think
we should do about it?
I'm not quite sure. But there's
got to be a way we can
help him get more comfortable
with these situations.
Okay.
You're totally right.
Why don't we just
expose him to more women?
What? That's terrible!
It's a pleasure to meet you,
young lady. I'm Soji's mother.
Ah. Hello, my name is Erina
Shindo. The pleasure's all mine.
It's okay, you
shouldn't worry, Aika.
If you think about it, this
could be your big chance.
Once he's comfortable with
women, I bet he'll notice you.
So, how are we
going to fix this?
Well, for Soji's sake,
we'd better introduce him
to one of these
as soon as possible.
[ERINA] Uh...
a porno magazine?
Oh yeah! The right kind of
magazine should help him become
much more comfortable when
he's dealing with normal girls.
Do you really think so?
It's a heck of plan.
I say you do it!
Great! Then I'll get right on
it. I'm going to go out there
and find Soji the best
porno magazine there is!
[MIHARU] All right!
That's the spirit!
Listen up, everybody!
Does anyone know what
a porno magazine is?
[STUDENTS gasp and chatter]
I'm looking for the
ultimate porno mag.
Any advice you have would
be greatly appreciated.
[BOY STUDENT 7A]
Well, if you ask me,
I'd say bondage is
definitely where it's at.
Bondage is where it's at.
[BOY STUDENT 7A groans]
[BOY STUDENT 7B] All right,
if you want the best porn
money can buy, you
gotta go with "yuri."
Do you mean "Yuri" like
the old Russian cosmonaut?
[BOY STUDENT 7B]
Nah, it's spelled the same,
but this stuff is pretty much
all girl-on-girl action.
[ERINA] Girl-on-g-- Oh my.
Wait, you don't mean...
Don't loose your cool, Erina.
Try to remember you're
helping a friend!
I don't look at anything
if it's not S&amp;M.
So you're into magnetic poles?
What're you talking about?
I said S&amp;M, not S&amp;N.
Are you sure
about this, Twoearle?
Learning about all these
fetishes might warp her mind.
She'll be just fine.
I can't really go into
the details right now,
but I guarantee that
what she's doing
is going to bring
all three of you
so much closer
to one another.
Wait. This is all for us?
[TWOEARLE] She's trying as
hard as she can to rid herself
of any shame so she can be
the best Twin-Tail she can be.
She's doing all of this
to help the Twin-Tails?
Well, Madame President,
I'm with you!
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
♪ One, two, three, go! ♪
♪ Surely, surely, one day, what
you wish for will come true ♪
♪ You've gotta increase
the scope of your dreams ♪
♪ Start today and frame
the outline of your world ♪
♪ Follow the beating
of your heart ♪
♪ Eyeglasses! Eyeglasses!
Eyeglasses! Eyeglasses! ♪
Yeah!
[EMU] Be honest with me.
Erina has been
severely neglecting her
lessons lately, hasn't she?
No ma'am.
She studies hard.
I know you're covering for her.
I have already
made my decision.
I will be arranging
a marriage for Erina.
[MIHARU]
The time has come!
There's so much drama in
store for the Twin-Tails!
Imagine Erina taking
Soji's virginity.
[AIKA] Hold on!
You shouldn't go around
spreading rumors like that!
[MIHARU] Don't you know the
title of the next episode?
[AIKA]
No! What is it?
[MIHARU] Next time:
"Erina--A Tearful Smile
on her First Night. Soji's
Excitement--Everything Builds
to a Climax in Full Blast
Mode!" Tail On!
[AIKA]
Huh?
[SOJI] Stop lying, Mom! There's
no way the title is that long!
[MIHARU] A hero makes
a lie come true!
I'm sure that means you, so you
better hang in there, too!