[school bell chimes]
[sighs]
C'mon, it's not that bad.
It's not like you
started doing all of this
just so you could
become more popular.
That's easy for
you to say since
everyone and
their mother adores you.
Getting the cold shoulder
from everybody even though
I'm trying to do
my best is awful.
Uh. What's the matter?
Is it my birthday?
Look at all the twin-tails.
They're everywhere!
Huh?
[FEMALE STUDENTS
giggle, chatter]
Oh wow.
You weren't kidding!
This is like a dream.
Pinch me.
Can this be happening?
[ERINA]
Hello there, friends!
Isn't it such a beautiful day?
[SOJI, AIKA] Good morning,
Madam President!
What's going on? You seem
to be in a good mood.
Indeed! Ever since I saw that
Tailred has a new sidekick,
I've been on cloud nine!
Madame President,
I am so happy
to hear you say that.
I worry about
Tailred so much.
I can't bear the
thought of her fighting
to keep us safe
with no one to help her.
Huh?
We all know
how strong she is.
And I know she'll
always be there for us.
But sooner or later, she's
going to need a helping hand.
And I'm not talking
about super fans like us.
In the end, we won't
be there to help her fight.
But now, Tailblue is
there to do what we can't.
She'll look out for Tailred!
Wow, you really are
a big fan of the Twin Tails
aren't you, Madam President?
You probably think it's
strange for a girl my age
to feel this way.
But the thing is,
I've always been
obsessed with heroes.
It's weird.
But I still watch those
superhero shows made for kids.
Sometimes, I even
buy the toys. Hang on.
Uh. Are you okay?
[sighs]
Yeah. It's nothing at all.
Sorry about that. See ya!
[BOTH]
Hmm?
[ERINA] Oh! The application
that you submitted
has been approved.
Application?
Uh! The Twin-Tail club!
It was actually approved.
All right!
[SOJI] Every day from then
on the Ultimaguil creeps
came to steal
twin-tail attribute.
[AIKA] But each one
of them had their own
pervy private agendas,
so they basically ignored
their overall mission.
[SOJI] Yeah well, whatever
the reason behind it,
we're on an unstoppable
winning streak.
[AIKA] It must be nice
getting to be so popular.
Then again, who wouldn't
like being a superstar.
[SOJI] Would you please
cut that out, already?
[ELEMELIAN 2A] The damage
report is as follows.
In total, 27 of our comrades
along with 458 Ultiroids
have been obliterated.
[DRAGGUILDY] At this point
it's clear that sending
more mediocre warriors to their
deaths will accomplish nothing.
Henceforth, this is
a holy war to be won
by our greatest combatants.
Will anyone here dare
to be the hero we need?
[SWAN GUILDY] Yes! I'll
claim victory for us all!
[ELEMELIAN 2C] Ah, Swan Guildy,
known throughout our ranks
as a champion
of nurse attribute.
Surely no one would have
any objection to you.
[ELEMELIANS gasp, chuckle]
[DRAGGUILDY] Very well.
But before you go: a test.
One to see if you are truly
fit to fight these Twin Tails.
Bring it in!
[ULTIROID]
Moge!
Moge.
[SWAN GUILDY gasps]
My computer!
Why have you
brought this here?
[DRAGGUILDY laughs intensely]
[SWAN GUILDY gasps]
[SWAN GUILDY]
Aaah...
[DRAGGUILDY]
Are you ready for this?
[GAME NURSES]
Naughty Nurse Angels
will make you all better!
[SWAN GUILDY groans softly]
[GUILDIES]
Mmm.
[DRAGGUILDY] It only
went on sale yesterday
and yet you have
already unlocked
the much sought
after bonus harem.
I commend your
deviant dedication
in achieving this so quickly.
[SWAN GUILDY]
Uuh...
[DRAGGUILDY] Out of all these
deliciously titillating pics,
I can see you only
have one rosy-cheeked
young girl in your stock.
Most irregular!
[SWAN GUILDY] Forgive me!
Please, I'm begging you!
[AIRI] Okay. If you're sure
that's all you want to do.
Yakiniku. For two.
[AIRI]
Ah!
[DRAGGUILDY] Things were
heating up with an old friend
and you went back to her room.
But the mood changed,
and you didn't bother
to save the game, did you?
You figured you'd start
with a little pillow talk,
and take if from there,
but then it suddenly
jumped to the next day.
Bumming you out!
[SWAN GUILDY yells]
[ELEMELIANS gasp]
[DRAGGUILDY]
I shall go myself!
[cheering]
[ELEMELIAN 2A] Quite the
formidable erotic game,
is it not?
[car horns honking]
[AIKA humming]
Hey. It feels like they've
gotten a little bigger.
Uh. False alarm.
It's muscle.
[chime]
[AIKA gasps]
[SOJI] Aika!
They've shown up again!
And it's a really
strong reading this time!
Well I can't
leave right now!
I'll be there as
soon as I can though!
[SOJI]
All right, but hurry!
[alarm sounds]
Now, Tail On!
[distant bird squaks]
Hey, uh, Twoearle,
I don't see anyone.
Are you sure those
readings were accurate?
[TWOEARLE] You're not alone.
I guarantee it.
So stay alert and
keep your wits about you.
[TAILRED]
Mmm.
Okay. But I really
don't think anybody's here.
[gasps]
[DRAGGUILDY yells]
[DRAGGUILDY]
Excellent block, Tailred.
You're just as
strong as I'd hoped.
What kind of coward
uses sneak attacks?
[DRAGGUILDY]
My name is Dragguildy.
[TWOEARLE gasps]
No, not Dragguildy!
[DRAGGUILDY] In all the world,
and throughout the universe,
there is no one who rivals me
in my love for twin-tails!
This untouched
back of mine
is a testament to that.
[TAILRED]
Your back?
[DRAGGUILDY] I have lived
my entire life in such a way
that no one has
ever laid a hand on it.
All so that one day,
when I have the supreme
twin-tailed girl wash me
in a hot bubble bath,
I may experience, in full, the
gentle sensation of her touch.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're mistaken if you think
you love twin-tails
more than me!
[DRAGGUILDY yells]
[TAILRED grunts]
[TWOEARLE] Mr. Soji,
the enemy's attack force
is greater than your photon
absorber's threshold rating!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Now let's try it faster!
[TAILRED gasps]
Now that's
swordsmanship!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Ah! I see that volley
wasn't nearly fast enough!
[TAILBLUE]
Are you okay, Red?
Hey. What kind of
sword is that?
[DRAGGUILDY] This? It's a
twin-tail sword!
Huh?
[DRAGGUILDY] And you are
the first of my opponents
to ever elude the
ungodly speed of my slashes.
Well yeah,
I can totally see them!
Most likely because of
the deep love for twin-tails
that I carry in
my heart at all times.
Oh-kay?
[DRAGGUILDY] Although
you're my mortal enemy,
I admire your passion.
So I'll try to cut you in half
as painlessly as possible!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Magnificent twin-tails!
It pains me to
call you my enemy!
So weird.
You know what?
If you weren't such
a creep I bet we'd have
a great time hanging out
and telling stories
about all of the
twin-tails we've admired!
[TAILBLUE grunts]
[DRAGGUILDY]
I just realized.
True twin-tail
attribute is something
that possesses
mutual resonance!
Mutual resonance?
You mean you and me?
He's saying you're
the same kind of perv!
Honestly, I think he's right!
[DRAGGUILDY] A blue warrior?
How long has she been here?
[TAILBLUE] Long enough
to feel deeply disturbed.
[DRAGGUILDY] Now that
I see you up close,
I can tell it was
the warrior from
that other world
who put you up to this.
Huh?
From another world?
[DRAGGUILDY]
You don't know?
There was once a girl
who challenged us
to battle by herself.
She was clad in the same armor
that you are wearing now.
What did you say?
Are you telling us that
you've already battled with
another version of Tailblue
on a different planet?
[DRAGGUILDY]
That's right!
She had an obscenely
large bust that looked
out of place
with her twin-tails.
And when you looked
her in the eyes,
there was no connection.
She had big boobs?
Wait, you mean?
[DRAGGUILDY] It's quite
ironic that the brilliance
you two display
wearing that armor
will end up completely
destroying this planet
the exact same way
it did back then.
[TWOEARLE exhales quaverly]
What are you
talking about?
What does that even mean?
[DRAGGUILDY]
She was once considered
a goddess on her world.
Eventually everyone
wanted to wear twin-tails
so they could
be just like her.
And that's when
the real fun began.
Are you saying...?
[DRAGGUILDY] Correct.
The twin-tail attribute
that we crave spread
around the planet.
Before long,
the entire world became
the most ideal hunting
ground we could imagine.
[grunts]
[DRAGGUILDY] The people
of this world have begun
to idolize you as their savior.
In reality, you will be the
cause of its destruction.
Eeh!
[TAILBLUE] This is
all part of their plan.
We fell for it hook,
line, and sinker.
[TAILRED]
No!
[TAILBLUE]
Can't you see?
Look, maybe Twoearle
gave in to despair
and now she's trying
to make sure that
all the twin-tails
on our world end up
the same as they did on hers.
Twoearle wouldn't do
something like that!
Just think about it, Red!
We're fighting
the same way she did
and she's letting
twin-tail mania spread.
She may not work for them,
but they couldn't
do this without her!
If what she's doing
helps you guys out,
why risk everything
by telling us about it?
[DRAGGUILDY] Because Tailred's
twin-tail attribute
is the real deal.
[gasps]
[DRAGGUILDY] Having engaged
her in battle, I know,
without a doubt, that she
truly loves twin-tails
more than anything else.
[DRAGGUILDY] I would rather
fight without any deception.
Consider it a
gesture of goodwill,
so that she doesn't
learn the truth
after her world is destroyed,
and then become
consumed by guilt.
[TAILRED] Thanks but
no thanks, Dragguildy.
You can keep your goodwill.
Now more than ever,
I know what I have to do!
What are you
getting at, Red?
It doesn't make any sense
to keep fighting!
I think it makes
perfect sense!
These jerks want to harvest
twin-tail attribute.
Thing is, it's just now starting
to develop on our planet.
But they can tell
it's here to stay!
Huh?
If it were a passing fad,
people would get tired of it.
Don't you get it?
There's no reason to worry.
Huh?
I'd say we're
lucky you creeps
set your sights on us.
You got the ball rolling
on a twin-tail revolution.
And that means all the girls
who are just starting
to wear twin-tails also
have high attribute levels.
What're you saying?
All I gotta do is get this
weirdo outta the picture.
And the glorious gospel
of twin-tails will spread
to the furthest
reaches of the world.
And that would be
like a dream come true.
[DRAGGUILDY]
Wait. What?
[laughing]
Uh. Did I miss something?
You are
completely hopeless!
You're crazy for twin-tails.
And you're just plain crazy.
Your passion never
ceases to amaze me.
It's what I love about you.
Thank you, Tailblue!
I can't imagine
a better compliment!
[DRAGGUILDY] Tailred. The girl
with the ultimate twin-tails.
My admiration for you
soars even higher now.
Your indomitable spirit
is unshaken even while
facing the cataclysmic
end of the world.
[TAILRED]
End of the world or not,
I'm sick of listening to
all your evil dragon crap!
Now you listen up!
I'm ready to fight to
the death for what I love!
[TWOEARLE]
That's enough. Dragguildy!
[TAILRED whimpers]
Who was that?!
[DRAGGUILDY] Who are you?
Identify yourself!
[TWOEARLE] I am
the planetary avenger!
The Masked Twin-Tail!
[DRAGGUILDY] The Masked
Twin-Tail, huh?
I'm not reading any discernable
attribute strength from you.
[TWOEARLE] I'm not here
to fight with you.
[TAILRED] If you're
not here to fight,
then what exactly
are you doing here?
[TWOEARLE] I think it's
important that you listen
to what I have to say.
[TAILRED, TAILBLUE]
Huh?
[TWOEARLE] Red, that first
day when you fought,
the reason they were looking
for the ultimate twin-tail
was not so they could simply
take your attribute strength.
Their plan was
much more insidious.
It was to develop whoever
had the strongest
twin-tail attribute
into a hero of sorts.
A hero that the world
could rally behind.
And eventually try to emulate.
[gasps]
[DRAGGUILDY] Just as
we have done with
countless worlds
before yours.
So this has
happened a lot?
[TWOEARLE] Yes. I developed
Tail Gear from technology
that they
intentionally leaked
and I did my best
to fight them with it.
Little did I know that
they were just using me
as a means to an end.
I was merely
a pawn in their game.
[DRAGGUILDY] So, you're the
woman who so valiantly
fought against us
on that distant world.
But I'm curious--
Why is it I no longer detect
the incredible twin-tail
attribute you used to emanate?
[TWOEARLE] Because
I relinquished it.
[DRAGGUILDY]
What?
[TWOEARLE] I got the feeling
that something wasn't right
when I was fighting.
It was almost as though
the enemy's weaknesses
were a little too
easy to spot.
That's when I started
to put the pieces together.
[TAILBLUE] After you figured
out what those freaks
were really up to,
you knew what you had to do
in order to ruin their plans!
[TWOEARLE] That's right.
All I needed to do was
act in a way that would
make people lose interest
in twin-tails.
But I couldn't do it!
[TAILRED gasps]
[TWOEARLE] You see, I
refused to let the newfound
twin-tail attribute
fade away into nothingness.
There was no way
I was going to stand by
and watch all those girls
who were trying to
awaken something beautiful
in themselves go back
to their horribly dated,
uninspired hairstyles!
Huh?
[TWOEARLE] But I wasn't
strong enough, and I lost.
While I was struggling
with all of that,
the invasion continued until
they bled my world dry
of all twin-tail attribute.
It was my own foolish pride
that destroyed my world.
Oh no!
That sounds like hell!
[TWOEARLE] It was. After I
realized what I had done,
I got rid of my twin-tails
and I never looked back.
With those distractions
out of the way,
I devoted myself to constructing
another set of Tail Gear.
And eventually,
I completed the Tail Gear
that you're wearing now.
Oh Twoearle. How
incredibly brave of you.
[TWOEARLE gasps]
[DRAGGUILDY]
She's no martyr.
That was nothing
but vengefulness,
plain and simple.
Ex-Tailblue, I underestimated
your deep love of twin-tails.
However, it won't
make any difference
now that there are two
of you instead of just one.
In fact, having the
two of you will help the
twin-tail phenomenon spread
across the globe even faster.
Two of us?
That's where you're
mistaken, Dragguildy!
Let me break this down.
Having Twin-tails requires
more than just the hair.
You have to have
a head. And that's her!
Which means
that all three of us
are the Twin Tails!
[TWOEARLE]
Red!
Ugh. Come on.
Does everything
in the world have to
be about twin-tails
for you guys?
Twoearle, I realize now that
you never meant any harm.
I'm so sorry for doubting you.
All right, then.
You ready to go?
Yeah!
[DRAGGUILDY] I hope you
realize that you are
outnumbered 300 to 1.
Do you honestly think
you stand a chance?
Blue. I'm gonna
do my best to take out
Dragguildy by myself. Can you
handle the rest of those
Ultiroid guys
on your own?
Piece o' cake.
Sounds to me
like I got the easy job.
Are you sure?
Yeah! Let's go!
[DRAGGUILDY] You're
fighting me alone, eh?
[ULTIROIDS yell]
For the love of
twin-tails everywhere,
I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to defeat you!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Hm!
I was told that
you have to consume
attribute strength to
survive. Is that right?
'Cause this is your last
chance to go on a diet.
[DRAGGUILDY] The thing
I enjoy most about being
an apex predator is that I
eat what I want, when I want.
Do you honestly expect me to
start bargaining with my meals?
So that's it, huh?
Then I guess there's
nothing left to say!
[yells]
[DRAGGUILDY yells, grunts]
--[TAILRED yells]
--[DRAGGUILDY groans]
[DRAGGUILDY] You've become even
stronger and more beautiful
than you were before.
It's like you're
a different person.
I am a different
person, now!
That's because you've
got me fired up!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Huh?
[TAILRED yells]
[DRAGGUILDY yells]
You've wounded
my pristine back!
You're more powerful
than I ever imagined!
In that case!
[TAILRED]
Uh! What the--?!
[DRAGGUILDY bellows]
You've actually been a
twin-tail this entire time?
[DRAGGUILDY] Yes! And I'll
risk blowing my cover
to make my true power known!
This is the solemn
duty of all those
who possess
twin-tail attribute!
Too bad you're my enemy.
If you weren't, I'd give you
crazy props for coming out.
It's a hard step
to take after being
in the twin-tail
closet for so long.
I really respect that.
[DRAGGUILDY]
Here I come, Tailred!
[TAILRED gasps]
[DRAGGUILDY grunts]
I should thank you!
Because of you
I've left my position
as the leader of Ultimaguil.
I've gone back
to being the old
devil-may-care twin-tail-lover
I was back in the day!
If you love twin-tails
as much as you say you do,
then you know
how much it would hurt
to have them taken away!
[DRAGGUILDY]
I'm used to the resentment!
As someone who
devours minds regularly,
it kind of comes with
the territory.
I will now strike
a blow of vengeance.
For the people
of all the worlds
that you've
plunged into darkness.
[yells]
[TWOEARLE] You never cease
to amaze me, Mr. Soji.
There was a reason
I fell so hard for you.
I could never truly stand up
to them all by myself.
But you're strong enough
to save this world.
[ULTIROIDS]
Moge!
[TAILBLUE]
What's going on up there?
Is their battle
conjuring up some kind of
twin-tail magic spell?
Watch where you're grabbing
or you're gonna be
pulling back a stump.
Ah. Oh. So that's
what you're after.
Let go of my hair!
[ULTIROIDS yell]
[TAILBLUE] I've been keeping
these for a long time
and they're only
for one person.
And you'd better appreciate
it, you oblivious idiot!
You're so trusting.
And careless. And brave.
When you jumped into battle
without hesitating,
I was so proud of you!
I'll stick
with you forever!
[ULTIROIDS yell]
How many are left?
[TWOEARLE]
Exactly 831.
What? Come on!
Break Release!
[ULTIROIDS yell]
Execute Wave!
[groans lightly]
[AIKA] I hope one day
you understand...
..,that I--
[TAILRED grunts]
[DRAGGUILDY] In all my days
I've never seen someone
fight so well.
You are not only
the greatest foe
of my lifetime,
but also the greatest
love I have ever known!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Farewell!
[TAILRED grunts]
[DRAGGUILDY]
What? A second sword?
Well, they don't call us
Twin Tails for nothing,
you know!
[DRAGGUILDY groans]
Brake Release!
[yells]
[DRAGGUILDY]
Tailred!
[TAILRED]
Grand Blazer!
[DRAGGUILDY bellows]
Beautiful.
Truly divine tresses.
A heavenly hairstyle.
Was the first sword
just a decoy?
[TAILRED]
No. Not at all.
I didn't think about it
until I realized
that I was defending
two other people.
So it seemed only natural
that I would need two swords.
[DRAGGUILDY]
Well played, Tailred.
I am honored
to have been defeated
by such a beautiful
twin-tailed girl.
I can say
without a doubt,
this is how my life
was always meant to end.
Just how positive
can one guy be?
[DRAGGUILDY]
May we meet again, someday!
[groans]
As long as you have
love in your heart
for twin-tails, there's
a chance that will happen.
[gasps]
It's over now, huh?
That's great.
Maybe... I'll just...
[BOTH gasp]
Heck of a day.
Huh, Twin Tails?
[AIKA]
Soji. I can't believe it.
We finally had our first
real joint operation!
[SOJI] "Joint operation"?
More like "fight."
[TWOEARLE] Well, well,
well, Miss Aika,
aren't you desperate?
[AIKA] Shut up! At least
when we're out there
fighting you won't be
able to get in my way.
Then I'll have
plenty of chances to--
Wait, who is that?
A third member
of the Twin Tails?
[TWOEARLE] Yep!
And unlike someone I know,
she's got some hefty hooters!
[AIKA] Oh, don't be immature!
Just say she's busty!
[SOJI] Next time:
"The Third Twin Tail"!
[AIKA]
Tail On!