[OWL GUILDY] They're so buoyant
and bouncy and silky and soft
that I dream about twin-tails
and think of them oft.
They tickle and titillate
down to my core.
I want them so badly,
so badly I'm sore.
Glorious bunches of
girly-girl hair--
just like breasts,
they come in a pair.
While we're at it,
I also like spectacles--
their shape and form
remind me of breasticles.
I feel like these words have
somehow set my soul on fire!
It's almost like I've
gone back in time.
The forgotten days of my youth
are all coming back to me.
Now this is literature!
I can't believe it's
already this warm outside.
Don't you get hot wearing
that white coat year-round?
[TWOEARLE] Actually, it's
equipped with a fully automatic
temperature control system,
so it keeps me nice and cool.
[AIKA]
Hmm...
If I didn't know
better, I'd say
you've got something
on your mind.
Hey! Would it cheer you up if
you wore my boobs like a hat?
[AIKA] Keep your oversized
udders to yourself!
Oh please, I can
read you like a book.
So there's no point in
trying to act tough now.
That lame punch along
with your lame attitude
tells me you're insecure
in your summer uniform.
You're worried that without
the comforting cover
of your blazer everyone
will finally notice
your flat-as-a-flounder
chest and see you
for the little "Miss Six
o'clock" that you really are.
Hey! I don't need any of your
pity for my itty-bitty...
Ugh! Just shut your mouth
before I pound your face in!
Hi. I hope everybody is
having a great morning.
Morning, Madame
Presi-- Whoa!
It looks like you
were up all night.
[ERINA] Pretty much.
I stayed up until morning
sitting at my computer,
searching the internet
for something that could help
us out and now I'm exhausted.
Thing is, no matter how many
different ways I searched,
I never found a single shred
of pornography on the web.
Isn't that weird? I guess
there's no porn online.
[AIKA] Madam President.
I would have been happy
to do that for you,
if you had asked me!
Thank you for your
kind offer, Miss Tsube.
It's just... This is something
that I'd rather do on my own.
[MIKOTO] After school today,
Young Miss is going out
to purchase an adult magazine.
[SOJI]
Uh...
[MIKOTO] I would like
to ask you to escort her.
You called me down
here to go buy porn
with the student
council president?
She asked around.
And during the course
of her investigation,
she learned of a store
that carries a wide variety
of "adult" literature.
She then made it clear
that she didn't want me
to accompany her.
'Kay...
Now then. Watch her from a
distance so she doesn't see you.
But you've also got
to be close enough
that you can keep her safe.
[SOJI] How come you can't go
stalk her at the porn store?
Because I've got to
come up with a way
to sabotage all of this
arranged marriage nonsense.
[SOJI] Are you sure
you want to do that?
I mean, if you get caught aren't
you afraid you'll lose your job?
You shouldn't be
worrying about me.
Soji. Do you think
you can keep her safe?
Of course.
Very good. There's one more
minor detail left to attend,
which is to sign and stamp this
guardian service agreement.
Oh boy...
[school bell rings]
This must be the place.
[OWL GUILDY]
Poetry anthologies!
Get your poetry
anthologies right here!
Sacred text for modern lovers!
Hot off the presses!
Poetry anthologies!
An owl selling poetry?
[OWL GUILDY]
Get your poetry anthologies!
Crap! It's an Elemelian!
[OWL GUILDY]
Hm? What's this?
[OWL GUILDY] Oh! What a
wonderful sight to behold!
A bright young twin-tail
earnestly perusing
some literature
right before my--
[TAILRED yells]
[OWL GUILDY] Whoa! Tailred!
What are you doing here?
[TAILRED] If you want Erina,
you'll have to go through me!
[OWL GUILDY pants]
[TAILRED] Stay away from her,
you feathered freak!
[ERINA]
Uh?
[OWL GUILDY] This can't be
happening! My masterful disguise
was supposed to be a foolproof
way to blend in perfectly!
And yet you still detected
me as quick as a flash!
Very impressive, Tailred!
Yeah. Well, I guess
I'm just that good.
[OWL GUILDY]
My name is Owl Guildy!
I'm a veteran soldier sent
once again to the battlefield
to defend the thing
that I hold most dear!
I'll do anything it takes to
protect literacy attribute,
even if it means
fighting you to the death!
You're defending the thing
that you hold most dear, huh?
Well, I'm trying to protect
something special, too!
Time for you to meet
my Blazer Blade!
[OWL GUILDY]
Here we go!
What kind of bird
uses birdlime?
[OWL GUILDY] Unfortunately,
this is a world where some
of our most cherished attributes
are languishing in obscurity,
biding their time
until they're forgotten.
All I want to do is preserve
them so that they can be enjoyed
for generations to come.
Dark Grasper has a plan
to help these time-honored
attributes survive.
Wait, you work
with Dark Grasper?
[OWL GUILDY] Don't waste
your energy. I can assure you
that it's quite impossible
to break through my birdlime.
Listen! The great tragedy
is that literacy attribute,
and minds that
adore literature,
are slowly vanishing
from this planet.
Since time immemorial,
literature has been
the gateway to a
fantastical world
of unlimited imagination.
Then everything changed!
Nowadays your bookstores
are filled with nothing
but salacious images of young
women dressed as harlots!
How dare you call
that trash literature?!
Yeah? Well maybe
people just find
picture books
easier to read!
[OWL GUILDY] I will not deny
that this garbage can be
a gateway to true literature
for children like you.
However, it takes something
more substantial than these
trite picture books to truly
nurture a rich imagination.
Which is why I'll
soon be flooding
the world's bookshelves
with literature
about the beauty, wonder,
and majesty of twin-tails!
I gotta admit,
you're a lot different
than all of the other
enemies I've fought.
[OWL GUILDY]
I told you, it's no use.
[TAILRED grunts]
[TAILRED] Don't give me
that "real literature" crap!
You're not the one
who gets to decide that!
It's up to the people
who live on this planet!
And we don't care
what you think!
As long our literature is
entertaining and enriching,
it doesn't matter
what form it takes!
Aura Pillar!
[OWL GUILDY screams]
[TAILRED] Haaaaa! Get ready
for my Brake Release!
[TAILRED]
Grand Blazer!
[OWL GUILDY screams]
[ERINA] I'll take
this one, please.
I can understand
you being obsessed
with something as
awesome as literature.
But here's a little
fun fact about me.
It was the glory of
twin-tails that unlocked
my imagination and
showed me who I really am.
What I'm trying to say is:
Twin-tails are my literature!
[OWL GUILDY coughs]
That's the Tailred I know.
There's no way I could
refute such passion.
Therefore, I must
concede defeat.
That's a smart move.
I'm glad I was able
to protect her while she
bought her porno mag.
[OWL GUILDY] Wait!
What did you just say?
[TAILRED] I said, "porno mag."
The girl you were creeping on
earlier was actually
here to buy porn.
[OWL GUILDY] Aahh! She was
buying a pornographic magazine?
That's outrageous! Why would a
girl with twin-tails that classy
debase herself by buying that
kind of filth in broad daylight?
Ah, the humanity!
Like I said earlier, don't go
pushing your snobby ideals on--
[OWL GUILDY] You listen to me,
Tailred, and you listen good.
Remember these words.
It is not me that is dying.
It is literature!
[ERINA]
Eh?
Soji!
Uh, hey, Erina.
What a strange coincidence
running into you here.
It's perfect timing,
actually. You see...
I've failed us all and I feel
like I need to apologize.
What? So you ended up not being
able to buy the porno magazine?
That's right. I didn't
know this, but apparently
you have to be 18 to
buy magazines like that.
I'm so sick of being treated
like I'm some delicate child.
I can't do anything by myself,
because people are always
trying to protect me.
At this rate, I'll
never be able to feel
like I'm pulling
my own weight.
I'm so worthless.
Erina. Don't talk
like that, okay?
We're grateful
to have you here.
When you feel like
you don't belong,
just try to think
about your twin-tails.
Remember, these will
always bind us together.
And It's not like you only
have Soji to rely on either.
I mean, I'm here for you too!
[ERINA] Thank you, Aika,
that means a lot to me!
[ERINA]
What's this?
A Twoearle phone.
It's a communications terminal
that I've been meaning to
give you all for a while.
Consider it a token
of friendship
and solidarity
from me to you.
Miss Twoearle! Thank you
so much, everyone!
And thank you, Soji.
For everything.
[SOJI] The bond between
us Twin Tails is stronger
than ever before and I
gotta say, it feels great!
[MIKOTO] Young Miss.
The mistress is calling you.
[ERINA] Well, then.
I'll take my leave.
Good night, Mother.
Sleep well.
[ERINA sighs]
[SOJI yawns]
[ERINA]
Good morning.
[SOJI gasps]
What has she done?
Why would she forsake
her beautiful twin-tails?
Damn it all! This is so unfair!
I tried with all my might,
but I couldn't protect
what was dearest to me!
Don't read too
much into this.
[SOJI] Huh? So she's just
rebelling against her mother?
[MIKOTO] Correct.
She's lashing out.
Poor girl. It hasn't
been easy for her.
But she's finally
standing up to her mother,
Emu Shindo, the chairman
of the school's trustees.
[SOJI] But why now? Is it
because of the marriage talks?
[MIKOTO] Those have
been resolved.
But regrettably,
the mistress learned
of Young Miss' search for
a pornographic magazine.
Aw man, so she's in trouble?
[MIKOTO] No. Quite the
opposite, in fact.
The mistress was rather
delighted that she was
finally taking an
interest in such things.
But, as you know, Young
Miss has been busy lately
what with her
student council work
and her "extracurricular"
activities with the Twin Tails.
The mistress took this to mean
that her life was out of order,
so she began talks for an
entirely new arranged marriage.
In response to this, Young
Miss became very hard-headed.
That's when she took
down her twin-tails,
which are essentially
a family rule.
[EMU] You are my daughter,
Erina! You will do as I say!
My decision on this
wedding is final!
It makes no difference
what you do with your hair.
I can only assume you
took down your twin-tails
with the childish hope that
it would change my mind. Yes?
[SOJI gasps]
What a beautiful
set of twin-tails!
It's like she's some
kind of twin-tail goddess!
I think I just hit
the twin-tail jackpot.
Now that I think of it.
I'm actually relieved
you've taken down those
soulless twin-tails of yours.
After all,
you never earned them.
[door opens loudly]
I won't let you talk that
way about my friend!
How dare you? What's
your name, young man?
My name is Soji Mitsuka! You and
I need to have a little talk!
It's about your daughter's hair!
[EMU]
Huh?
You said she didn't
earn her twin-tails.
And that's where you're wrong!
[EMU] What is this?
As her mother, I can say
without a doubt that
I know her twin-tails
better than anyone else.
If I say she didn't earn them,
then she didn't earn them
and that's the way it is.
No way! I guarantee you
I know Erina's twin-tails
better than you ever will!
[EMU]
What do you mean?
Did Soji really storm
into the chairman's office
to try and get Erina back
to being a Twin Tail?
Keep your voice down.
[SOJI] Erina!
I can't imagine
how frustrated you are.
But it's just not like you
to take it out on
your own twin-tails!
[ERINA] Soji. Do you remember
what I told you before?
Shindo women wearing their hair
in twin-tails is a family rule.
So taking them down
is the greatest
expression of free
will that I have.
[EMU] Erina. Do you really
trust this young man enough
to let him in on
personal family matters?
[ERINA] Yes.
I trust him completely.
[EMU] Huh. You just
told me that you know
my daughters' twin-tails
better than I ever will.
Tell me, young man, do you still
stand by this rather bold claim?
I do! I know that you,
as her mother,
usually see her twin-tails
more than anyone else.
But if that's
the case, how is it
that you haven't noticed
how strong and beautiful
her twin-tails have become
over the last month?
You're more interested
in pointing out her faults
than you are in
taking the time to see
how much your
daughter has truly grown.
Just try to look beneath
the surface. Please.
You've got to understand that
what she's doing is important.
That being said, I know
her grades have slipped
and that she's not doing as
much on the student council.
But those things were
sacrificed so she could
accomplish something much
more meaningful with her life.
Oh, Soji.
[SOJI]
So, I'm begging you.
Try to look past it for
a little while longer.
Ow! Ow! Ow! I think you're
fracturing my cranium!
It hurts!
[SOJI] Then, I'm sure
that she'll go right back
to being the hard-working
student council president
that she's always been.
[EMU] And I didn't think
there were any real men
left in the world. But I
can tell that a deep love
for twin-tails courses
through his veins.
And just think, he was right
under our noses this whole time.
[EMU]
Ah-- Erina?
Yes, ma'am?
[EMU] I think you'll enjoy
being married to him.
[AIKA gasps]
[ERINA screams]
[EMU] Young man, I expect
you to take good care
of my daughter and my
daughter's twin-tails.
Wait, what?
Can't we at least
discuss this?
[EMU] There's no need.
I already know that I like him.
He is the one for you.
If you disagree, I can always
arrange another marriage.
But... We're friends.
[EMU] A few moments ago he
told me what you're trying
to accomplish is both important
and meaningful to you.
If your future husband says
that is the case,
I must believe him.
Ah... Well, okay.
Since you've decided Soji's the
one for me, I suppose I could--
[EMU] Very well. Then the
matter of whom you shall marry
has been brought to a close.
[SOJI]
Please excuse us.
What are you doing?
You're back.
I'm thrilled to hear
that everything appears
to have been settled.
There's nothing new
to report out here.
I've been doing my best to
keep things nice and quiet.
But I'm the one who's supposed
to claim Soji's sweet virginity!
So unfair!
[AIKA]
That's far enough!
What are you dragging
me out here for anyway?
What is it you
want to talk about?
I thought we should
chat about Erina.
[AIKA] You want to talk
about the President?
Why are you pretending
it doesn't upset you?
You and I both know that Erina's
been scheming on Soji's V-card
from the moment she laid
those dopey eyes on him.
And now he even has
her mother's approval!
Let me break it down
for you, Miss Aika.
The advantage you worked so hard
for spending all those years
cozying up to Soji's mom doesn't
mean diddly-squat anymore!
Yeah, well,
who cares about that?
What?
Everybody knows that
Erina's a great person.
I mean, she was the first one
to give Tailblue a compliment.
Don't worry about the small
stuff! That's my new motto!
It's slow.
[MEGA NE] What do
you mean, "it's slow"?
The plan, obviously.
I should have millions of
adoring fangirls at this point.
I don't. So it's slow.
[MEGA NE] No way!
The gospel of the glasses
has been spreading
like wildfire!
It may take a little longer
because they're already
in love with twin-tails,
but it's certainly not slow.
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Mega Ne.
I want you to bring me that
thing I told you to keep.
[MEGA NE] Are you
sure about this?
You specifically told me
you wouldn't look at
Twoearle's pictures until your
dream had finally come true.
It's all right. I mean,
It doesn't really matter
because I've already
seen her in person.
Maybe we'll just consider it a
reward for all of my hard work.
[MEGA NE]
If you insist.
All her pics.
They're so exciting!
It... can't be. But why?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA) gasps]
Why don't these pictures
show Miss Twoearle
wearing her
beautiful twin-tails?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)] The only
explanation I can think of
is that Twoearle somehow
lost her twin-tail attribute,
and the effects from that
are reaching backwards
into the past, so that
even in old photos
she no longer looks like her
normal twin-tailed self.
[MEGA NE]
Oh my goodness!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)] I thought
Tailred was Twoearle.
Because their
attribute strengths
are nearly identical
to one another.
Deep down I knew something
wasn't right about her.
In fact, I can remember
what gave her away.
She didn't notice my
newfound beauty. And I'm hot.
[DARK GRASPER]
Very clever, Tailred!
But you can't fool me.
You are not Twoearle!
♪ I'm so overwhelmed
My feelings spilling out ♪
♪ Got zettabytes
worth of thoughts ♪
♪ It's getting
serious in my world ♪
♪ You can try to hide the
cheesiness in your mind... ♪
Oh, come on.
I really hate it when Aika and
Twoearle wander off like this.
I hope that they're okay.
Those are great specs.
--Thank you!
--They're really cute!
[GIRL 2]
They're just like Anko's!
[SOJI] Well, this is odd.
I guess glasses are in now.
There's Anko again.
Wait... glasses...
It's weird.
It's almost like she's...
trying to make them stand out.
What kind of person makes their
glasses the star of the show?
[SOJI gasps]
[DARK GRASPER]
Wait, that woman...
Standing behind Tailred...
The one with the weird mask!
And the great rack!
How could it have taken me
so long to notice her?
Twoearle has been hiding
from me in plain sight!
Anko is actually Dark Grasper!
Why did it take me
so long to notice?
It must be Imagine Chaff.
Just like the Tail Bracelets.
She must be using it
to throw us off.
That's why we haven't
been able to track her!
She's been secretly
pushing her own agenda
from the very beginning.
By turning herself
into an idol and spreading
glasses attribute,
she's been laying
the groundwork
for those Ultimaguil jerks
to take over the world!
[MEGA NE]
Hi there! It's Mega Ne!
[DARK GRASPER] I am Dark
Grasper! And together, we are:
[BOTH]
The Chaosic Girls!
[MEGA NE]
And I just wanna say--
[TWOEARLE] Stop it! This isn't
some stupid standup routine!
[MEGA NE] So why don't you
come over here and tell us
what we're supposed to say?
[TWOEARLE] Oh, no!
I know a trap when I see one!
[MEGA NE] Come on, let's
get crazy and do things
we'd never get away
with in the real story!
[TWOEARLE] No! Stop!
Enough, you two! Cut it out!
[MEGA NE] Next time.
"Smash! Chaosic Infinite."
Glasses On!
[DARK GRASPER] C'mon Mega Ne,
"Glasses On" is my thing.
[TWO EARLE squeals]