[TAILRED giggles]
Uh. What are you doing?
[TAILRED]
Huh? Oh. Nothing.
It's not what you
think it is, I swear! See?
[TAILRED] Now that the
Twin-Tail Club is official,
I'm trying to come up with
some activities that will
help spread the message of the
true majesty of twin-tails.
It's the only way we'll
ever attract new members.
Right. Or maybe
you wanted to transform
into Tailred so you could
sit there like a creeper
fingering your twin-tails?
[TAILRED]
That's not it!
[TWOEARLE] Mhmm-hm!
Someone's upset!
It's because you
have small boobies.
And your twin-tails are
the only thing you've got
going for you and now
you're super jealous
because Mr. Soji doesn't
need yours anymore!
It must be hard to be
flat chested and useless.
Waaah!
[TAILBLUE]
Wave Lance!
[TIGER GUILDY groans]
[TAILBLUE]
Execute Wave!
[TIGER GUILDY groans]
[TIGER GUILDY] Aah...
All I ever wanted
was to see Tailred...
in a swimsuit.
And maybe have her
sit on my lap.
[groans]
[TIGER GUILDY]
I love swimsuits!
She's so strong.
[AIKA] Come on.
We're late for school.
Right.
[bird chirping]
[STUDENTS murmur]
I'm Mikoto Sakuragawa.
From this moment forward,
I will be your new
assistant teacher.
Uh! Uh...
[MIKOTO]
One more thing.
If any of you have single
fathers or older brothers,
please give them this form.
[MIKOTO]
Remember...
Don't you think
this is weird?
Why is the president's
maid teaching?
It doesn't make any sense.
Yeah. I know.
And, we have a new
transfer student
joining us today.
[MALE STUDENTS gasping in awe]
[gasps, yells]
Pleasure to
meet you, everyone!
You can call me Twoearle!
I'm one of Soji Mitsuka's
distant relatives!
Aw, come on!
Does she have to go to the
same freakin' school too?
[distant whirling]
[electronic chimes, buzzing]
[BOTH gasp]
I'm currently giving the
clubroom an extreme makeover.
Don't you dare
go peeking, okay?
Who does she think she is?
[footsteps]
Madame President.
Congratulations on
the Twin-Tail Club.
It's a big achievement.
[SOJI wails]
Hey! Take your
hands off her!
[SOJI] I'm really sorry
about that, but the thing is--
We'd love to have you
come in, but unfortunately,
we're still
sorting things out.
I'd be more than happy
to lend you a hand.
After all, cleaning up
is my specialty, you know?
Thanks, but that's okay.
I'm sure you're busy.
What with your new teaching job
and being the president's maid,
you must have your
hands completely full.
Head maid, thank you.
The truth is, things are
a little out of control.
Strange monsters
are on the loose
and now this mysterious
Tailblue shows up.
And so...
as a protective measure,
I've taken a position here.
That way I can keep my eyes
on her "twenty-four-seven."
Oh yeah, I'll be advising
the Twin-Tail Club as well.
[BOTH]
Eeh?
It's Erina Shindo,
Student Council President.
Would you mind if I come in?
[TWOEARLE]
Oh, please do!
[SOJI]
Hey!
Whoa.
Come in and make
yourselves at home!
Hey, you're the new
transfer student.
You just got here
today, right?
You can call me Twoearle!
She's actually
a relative of mine.
She moved here
from somewhere far away.
That's the story
we're going with, anyway.
Wow, that's wonderful.
I hope you
enjoy your time here.
If you need anything,
just ask.
[SOJI] So, Madam President,
what brings you here today?
I looked over
your application.
And I have a question about
one thing in particular.
Of course. Whatever it is,
we're glad to help.
Super. So, it says
your club is focused
on studying twin-tails.
And yet you've also
vowed to protect them.
That's absolutely right!
Well, my question
is this. Tell me,
why all the fuss
over twin-tails?
Because they're awesome!
Liking something
is one thing,
however, loving it enough
to form a club is another.
Not to be rude,
but does a person really
need a reason
to love twin-tails?
[ERINA]
Mm.
[SOJI] She's got some of
the most amazing twin-tails
I've ever seen.
I thought she would
approve for sure.
Wait, I get it!
She's trying to determine
the depths of my affection.
She wants to see
who loves them more.
Well, I won't be outdone!
[AIKA]
Hmm?
Well thank you
for your time.
I have no issues with
your club or its activities.
As Student Council
President it's not my place
to pass judgment on the virtue
of any specific organization.
But there is one thing.
[SOJI]
Uh.
[gasps]
[AIKA gasps]
As you probably
already know,
gaudy accessories are
against school rules.
It's designed to look like
Tailred's isn't it?
I've seen quite a few
of them around lately.
[SOJI]
Uh...
Pardon my interruption, but
we're just about out of time.
[ERINA] I look forward
to the Twin-Tail Club
making great strides as our
newest campus organization.
So what in the heck
was that all about, Twoearle?
I thought regular people
couldn't see the Tail Bracelet
until after we transformed?
That's supposed
to be the case.
The Imagine Chaff technology
should make it invisible.
[SOJI]
That's it, then!
The President has an incredibly
powerful twin-tail attribute,
which explains why Ultimaguil
keeps on attacking her.
She's like us!
Yes, I suppose that
hypothesis could be true.
[AIKA]
Uh, Twoearle?
You said you were giving
this place a makeover,
but it's exactly the same.
[TWOEARLE] Oh, it's
made over, all right.
I even installed a secret
dimensional transporter.
Where did you find room for
a dimensional transporter?
A place where
flat-chested psychopaths
can't see it. Sorry.
[AIKA]
What did you say?!
[SOJI] What if
she was playing dumb?
What if she's already onto us
and has been the entire time?
[TAILBLUE yells]
[SPARROW GUILDY] Tiger Guildy,
head of the reserve troops,
has been defeated
by the Twin Tails.
[ELEMELIAN 2A] Tailred
was bad enough but now
we also have to deal with
her counterpart, Tailblue.
[SPARROW GUILDY]
These "Twin Tails" are just
too strong for us, I'm afraid.
We have all but lost our
greatest fighting force now.
There's no time to waste!
[ELEMELIAN 2B]
An urgent message!
Krakeguildy's regiment
has just arrived, sir.
[SPARROW GUILDY]
What? Already?
[ELEMELIAN 2C] Leviaguildy's
men are here as well, sir!
[SPARROW GUILDY] Both
Krakeguildy and Leviaguildy
have come to our aid.
With these two unstoppable
forces combined,
the Twin Tails are finished.
They don't stand a chance
against us now!
[KRAKEGUILDY'S MEN] Flat chests!
Flat chests! Flat chests!
[LEVIAGUILDY'S MEN]
Giant breasts!
[KRAKEGUILDY]
Hmph. Leviaguildy.
I have long since
abandoned trying to
talk you out of your vulgar
obsession with gigantic breasts,
and so I shall leave it
at this: agree to disagree.
[LEVIAGUILDY] How I pity you
and your antiquated views.
To believe in the primitive
notion that twin-tails
actually look better
with flat chests
is nothing short of folly.
I fear you are lost
forever, Krakeguildy!
[SPARROW GUILDY]
Come now.
We're here for
a common purpose.
[LEVIAGUILDY] Sparrow
Guildy, there's no need
for you to play mediator.
I've already sent some of
my men down to the surface.
We'll see soon enough which
of us is more competent.
[KRAKEGUILDY]
You got the jump on me?
[ULTIROID whispering]
Moge, moge.
Moge, moge, moge.
[SPARROW GUILDY] What?
Dark Grasper is coming here?
The chief's most
trusted officer.
This is unbelievable.
[CROWD screaming]
--[ERINA panting]
--[CROWD screaming]
[ULTIROIDS cheering]
[BUFFALO GUILDY] You possess
magnificent twin-tails!
Certainly worthy
of capturing! Hm?
Uh?
[BUFFALO GUILDY]
Uuh...
What a delightfully
large bust you have.
[TAILRED, TAILBLUE]
Hold it right there!
[ERINA]
The Twin Tails are here!
It's the President!
Careful, she's already
suspicious because of
that incident with
your Tail Bracelet.
We'll be in trouble if
she finds out who we are.
Yeah. Good call.
[BUFFALO GUILDY] I won't let
you interfere, Twin Tails.
My name is Buffalo Guildy!
I would gladly give
my life for my master,
whose goal is to spread
the giant-breast attribute
across the land!
What? The
giant-breast attribute?
Jerk. Wave Lance go!
I'll handle this
sleeze-bag, Red.
Just make sure you
get these people to safety.
Now get moving!
Uh, okay.
Come on, miss.
Right this way!
[TAILBLUE] What's so great
about giant breasts, huh?
You think a girl
can't be pretty without
big ole' blouse busters?
[BUFFALO GUILDY] No. Wait.
Now I never said that.
I've had enough
of you! Aura Pillar!
[BUFFALO GUILDY]
Uuh?
[BUFFALO GUILDY,
ULTIROIDS yell]
[BUFFALO GUILDY groans]
Execute Wave! Haaa!
[BUFFALO GUILDY grunts]
[BUFFALO GUILDY]
To be defeated this way.
By an A cup!
[TAILBLUE grunts]
[TWOEARLE] Yes, it's possible.
Using this elemela orb,
I could make
giant-breasted Tail Gear.
You seriously think
you could make that happen?
What the heck are you
waiting for, do it?
[SOJI]
Uh...
[TWOEARLE chuckles]
Actually, I have some
really terrific news.
[SOJI]
Whoa!
Using the elemela
orb you obtained
by defeating Dragguildy,
I have developed a new
and improved Tail Gear.
Granted, at this stage
it's just a prototype.
But I'm very close
to being done with it.
And get this.
This Gear also incorporates
the giant-breast attribute
we got from Buffalo
Guildy's elemela orb,
making it a hybrid gear
with a never before
achieved functionality.
So, you're saying...
this Gear can transform me
into a person with big boobs?
[AIKA gulps]
[TAILBLUE giggles]
[AIKA]
Aaah...
Please, Twoearle!
Make that Tail Gear
and give it to me right now,
and you have my word:
I'll be your
best friend forever!
So, that's what you want?
In that case...
Hm-hmmm.
First, you have to
bow down and apologize
for all the heartache
and pain you've caused me--
[AIKA]
Please, forgive me!
I'm sorry for everything
I ever did to you!
[screams] Why is
Madame Mosquito Bites
bowing down to me?
I won't be swayed
by emotion, Miss Aika!
This is a ruse so you can
try to get back at me later!
[sobbing]
I'm begging you!
Please, Twoearle!
Listen, Aika, I think you're
being a little dramatic.
Haven't you heard that
size isn't everything?
[AIKA]
That's a cruel lie!
Really?
[TWOEARLE]
Mr. Soji.
Under normal circumstances,
I tend to stand in opposition
to everything
Miss Aika says or does.
But, in this particular case,
I am afraid I have to
agree with her.
There isn't a girl alive
who doesn't care about
the size of her breasts.
I'll grant your wish.
It would be an honor
and a privilege.
[giggling]
This is the
third Tail Gear.
So go ahead. Try it!
Tail On!
[AIKA]
Hm?
I said,
"Tail On," bracelet!
What's wrong? Why isn't
it reacting to me?
Perhaps it's a matter of
compatibility, Miss Aika.
This Tail Gear is
specifically designed for
a person whose chest
doesn't look suspiciously
like an ironing board.
Yep. Apparently, there
are some limitations
that even the marvels of future
technology can't correct.
[AIKA] Figures. I was
a complete fool to actually
believe Tail Gear
could transform me
into a
giant-breasted superhero.
Look, Aika. Twoearle
may say it's your body,
but I don't really think so.
[BOTH]
Huh?
It has nothing to do with
the size of your breasts.
Just think about
what you've done.
You've been fighting
with all you've got
in the blue Tail Gear.
And you've become an
indispensable partner.
Don't you see?
It's not the bracelet,
Aika, it's you.
Your heart's rejecting it,
and that's keeping you
from transforming.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, I suppose
you're right.
It's not meant to be.
But, when you
put it that way,
it doesn't seem like
such a bad thing after all.
[ELEMELIANS murmuring]
[KRAKEGUILDY] Why is
everyone whispering?
[ELEMELIAN 4A] They are
probably spreading rumors
about Dark Grasper's
imminent arrival.
[KRAKEGUILDY]
Dark Grasper, huh?
The big chief's right hand?
But I don't understand.
Why would he come here
so soon after our arrival?
[ELEMELIAN 4B] At this point,
we cannot afford to fall
any farther
behind Leviaguildy.
[KRAKEGUILDY] Not to worry.
I have already sent
the mightiest warrior under
my command to the surface.
The days of the Twin Tails
getting the best of us
will soon be over.
[CROWD screaming]
--[ERINA panting]
--[CROWD screaming]
[CRAB GUILDY]
Well! We've got some
rather high potential
here, don't we?
This is exactly
what I was talking about!
We've already run
into monsters here!
It just happened yesterday!
I needed toys!
[CRAB GUILDY]
My name is Crab Guildy!
I strive night and day
to seek out that attribute
which beautifully
showcases twin-tails,
the back-of-the-neck attribute,
so that ages to come
may know of their majesty!
Attack!
[ULTIROIDS yelling]
[CRAB GUILDY] Wow. Talk about
a back of the neck.
Uh. That one has
seen better days.
What was that?
[CRAB GUILDY] Steal their
twin-tail attribute, too.
The chief'll be--
[groans]
[ERINA]
Look, it's Tailred!
Huh? Whoa, this is
like déjà vu.
Elemeletion!
Let's send these creepers
back where they belong!
Are you sure
you're okay, Blue?
Don't worry. I'll be fine!
And I owe it all to you, Soji.
Come on. We need to
hide you somewhere.
[ERINA]
Mm-mm.
[CRAB GUILDY] Hmm. What
wonderfully miniscule mounds.
Hey wait a second,
weren't you just going on
about the back of their necks?
[CRAB GUILDY] Mmm.
More than anything, I'm for
the back-of-the-neck
attribute.
However, Krakeguildy,
whose service I'm in,
goes for the
flat-chested attribute.
And of course, Ultimaguil
as a whole goes for
the twin-tail attribute
above and beyond them all!
Aah! Everything you say
is total nonsense!
[yells]
[CRAB GUILDY] There is not
a single Elemelian in all of
Ultimaguil who can
sneak behind an enemy
better than yours truly!
Do you know how hard
I had to train
so I could go around looking
at the backs of necks
without people
knowing about it?
[ULTIROID chattering]
Don't worry,
you'll be safe here.
Make sure you
keep your head down.
[ERINA]
I'm glad to see you again.
I knew you would come.
Thanks a lot, Tailred.
Or should I say... Soji.
Thank you for everything.
Oh, it's no big deal,
I'm glad to--
Hold on.
Did you just say Soji?
I have no idea who that is!
It's okay. I promise,
your secret's safe with me.
When I saw your bracelet
in the clubroom, I knew.
And now all of my
suspicions are confirmed.
Wait! I can explain!
The bracelet you saw
was clearly a knock-off.
People just can't
get enough of Tailred!
[ERINA] No.
It wasn't a knock-off.
It's the exact same one that's
on your wrist right now!
[TAILRED]
Mmm.
What's the use?
Twoearle, could you
come here please?
[TWOEARLE]
I'm here!
[shrieks]
[gasps]
[TWOEARLE]
Mr. Soji, I swear,
you sure give up easily
in the strangest situations.
I'd already made up my mind.
When Aika couldn't transform
with that other bracelet
back at headquarters,
I decided we should
let the President
use it instead.
She's being attacked
by Ultimaguil
as much as anyone is.
And if she had the bracelet,
maybe she could
look after herself.
Well, give it here.
My whole life I've always
wanted to be a hero.
But now,
I'm terrified I'll fail.
[SOJI]
You can do this!
You can do anything
you set your mind to!
As long as you have
the love for twin-tails
in your heart!
[TAILBLUE grunting]
Oh no!
It looks like Miss Sakuragawa
is in a tight spot!
[ULTIROID]
Moge!
We could use a
little help, Tailred!
[gasps]
He transformed back right
in front of the President?
[TAILBLUE yells]
Now yell out "Tail On!"
Do it!
[ERINA]
Hm!
Tail On!
Wow! So this
is Tailyellow!
Uh.
[ULTIROID]
Moge!
Hey, behind you!
[ULTIROIDS yell]
You transformed
that easily?
Your love for twin-tails
must be stronger
than you thought it was, huh?
And that yellow gear
is totally awesome.
It's really different
from the suits we have.
It's more heavily
armored and durable.
And bigger. Much bigger.
Please trade bracelets
with me, Madam President!
That bracelet was
supposed to be mine!
If you give it to me,
I'll be your best friend!
This means I'm
part of the team, right?
[TAILBLUE]
Huh?
I've wanted to be
one of you for so long,
you have no idea!
A brave hero,
like Tailred and Tailblue.
A hero who risks her life,
everyday, no matter the cost!
You think I'm
a hero. Seriously?
[TAILYELLOW]
Ah...
[chuckles]
You know, when you
put it like that,
this doesn't seem so bad.
[ELEMELIAN 2A] Dark Grasper
has officially arrived!
[SPARROW GUILDY]
Dark Grasper.
Even I only know him
by name and reputation.
[SPARROW GUILDY] But what kind
of warrior is he really?
[ELEMELIANS murmur]
[footsteps]
[LEVIAGUILDY]
Hmm?
[KRAKEGUILDY]
It can't be.
[SPARROW GUILDY]
This is Dark Grasper?
Our chief's right hand.
The keeper of discipline among
all of the Ultimaguil
organization...
...is a little human girl?
[ERINA] As though in sync
with my own grand entrance,
the enemy's new
lineup appears, too.
[MIKOTO] More importantly,
next time Soji and I
register together, and our
life as newlyweds begins!
[AIKA, ERINA, TWOEARLE]
Huh?!
[SOJI]
Wait just a darn minute!
I don't know
anything about this!
[MIKOTO]
Of course you don't.
This is the first time
I'm saying it.
But the way things
have been going,
that seems like a
logical next step to me.
[AIKA] That is completely
off-base and crazy!
Ah, our preview time
is almost up!
[SOJI] Yeah,
I better say it then!
Next time: "Brake Release!
Tailyellow!"
[ERINA]
Tail On!