[SPIDER GUILDY]
After a long warrior's journey,
your faithful servant,
Spider Guildy, has returned.
I must apologize for not coming
to pay my respects sooner.
Apology accepted.
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Thank you, Ma'am.
If it suits you,
I'll get right to it.
I've been away honing
my skills in battle,
and I'd like to do something
to make up for my absence.
I have learned much.
And now I wish
to test my skills.
Against Tailred?
[SPIDER GUILDY]
No. Not against Tailred alone.
I want to go up against all
three Twin Tails at once.
Well.
Very ambitious.
I wish you luck
in this endeavor.
[SPIDER GUILDY]
By your will.
Before I leave I have
a question for you.
Hm. Tell me have you ever had
any experience with kissing?
[ELEMELIANS gasping]
[SPIDER GUILDY]
You mean Tongue Fu?
No, I'm afraid I haven't.
--What a shame.
--[SPIDER GUILDY] Hm?!
Well, try not to be too jealous,
but I just kissed Tailred.
[ELEMELIANS murmur]
Whew! It sure is hot today.
[ERINA]
Uh?
[SOJI]
Hey, what's goin' on with you?
You want to know what's
going on with me?
All right, fine.
Then I guess I'll just come
right out and say it.
I can tell you're still thinking
about kissing Dark Grasper.
Well, actually, I'm not
thinking about anything.
No surprise there.
How could you be?
You would need
a brain for that.
[SOJI]
C'mon, it's no big deal.
Keep in mind I wasn't
exactly my regular self.
I was transformed into Tailred
when all that stuff went down.
So it was two girls kissing.
To me that isn't
such a big deal.
Girls kiss each other
all the time, right?
She was basically just saying
hello. That's all it was.
[AIKA]
Well, okay.
When you put it like that,
it doesn't sound so bad.
[SOJI]
Forget about that.
I saw the most awesome
set of twin tails earlier.
[AIKA]
What kind of twin tails?
They were so powerful, but it's
like she didn't even notice it--
--[phones ring]
--[ALL] Uh?
[TWOEARLE] An Elemelian has
appeared!
Come on Twin Tails.
Get moving!
[ERINA panting]
Hurry up, let's go!
[GIRLS screaming]
All right, where
is this Elemelian?
This is actually a famous
all girls' school.
I'd guess Ultimaguil is here
because there are so many
different attribute strengths
all in one place!
Hey! Creeper at
three o'clock!
[STUDENTS gasping]
I'm a boy!
I'm sorry I've kept that
from you for so long.
Thank you for
finally telling me.
But I was only
pretending not to know.
Then you're not mad
at me? Are you sure?
What about all
the sleep overs?
We've even taken
bubble baths together.
It's fine. Really, it is.
However, I'm going
to make you pay.
[TAILRED, TAILBLUE, TAILYELLOW]
Uh...
[TWOEARLE]
I've got it!
It Looks like this freak's
favorite flavor of creepy
is girlyboy attribute.
So this one's after
girlyboy attribute?
Just when I thought these guys
couldn't get any stranger.
Whatever he's after,
he can't have it.
All right. Kissy-face
time is over you guys.
You two better get out of here
before he steals your
attribute strength.
[STUDENTS gasp]
--Whoa! Tailblue is here!
--Run!
[TAILBLUE sighs]
--[TAILRED] Hey!
--[SPIDER GUILDY] Hm.
There's no way we're gonna
let you get away with this!
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Ha! I am Spider Guildy,
the greatest swordsman
in all of Ultimaguil.
Do you dare challenge me?
[SPIDER GUILDY growls]
For a warrior,
girlyboys are worth dying for.
[TWOEARLE ]
Be careful with this one.
He's honed all of his senses to
find boys who look like girls.
His obsession with that fetish
could mean big trouble for you.
It's possible that the Imagine
Chaff won't work on him,
and he'll be able to see you
for what you really are.
[TAILRED whimpers]
Hey, no spacing out.
Be careful.
You're exactly what this
creep is looking for.
After all, you are a boy who
is transformed into a girl.
What?
Wait a second.
So I'm a girlyboy?
That's weird.
You better let me
take care of him.
I'll end this as
quickly as I can.
[TAILBLUE]
Besides, if we draw this out,
Dark Grasper might
show up again.
[SPIDER GUILDY]
How fortunate,
the attribute I crave is hidden
among my archenemies.
Looks like I'll be killing two
birds with one stone today.
I know a girlyboy when
I see one, Tailblue.
[TAILBLUE]
U-Uh...?
[SPIDER GUILDY chuckles]
[TAILBLUE growls]
Die, you moron!
[TAILBLUE grunting]
That girl's terrible temper
makes her act like a wild beast.
[TAILBLUE grunting]
But even with that
short fuse of hers,
there's still something about
her that Mr. Soji is drawn to.
Then again,
she has quite a pair.
Of twin-tails at least.
They're pretty much perfect.
[SPIDER GUILDY, TAILBLUE
grunting]
[TAILYELLOW yells]
Come to think of it,
Erina has an epic set too.
They are totally freakin' cute!
[DARK GRASPER humming]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[humming continues]
[DARK GRASPER laughs]
[MEGA NE] I like the color
red as much as the next robot,
but I gotta say,
everything being red
actually hurts my eyes.
[DARK GRASPER] Don't be silly,
it matches my collection
of Tailred merchandise,
and it matches how I feel.
I've fallen in love.
[MEGA NE] To be frank,
I don't think it's love.
That shrine of yours is straight
out of the stalkers' handbook.
Isn't it great?
I think it might be nice to get
some red Glasses Gear.
Let's get to work on that.
[SPIDER GUILDY grunting]
[SPIDER GUILDY] Already I can
see that the twin tail warriors
who defeated Draguildy
and the others
are not to be trifled with.
In that case, I shall have
to unleash my full power!
[TWOEARLE]
Be careful!
He's no run-of-the-mill perv!
He looks like an
officer-class Elemelian!
Yeah, I can kinda see that!
[SPIDER GUILDY grunts]
They're so close I can't
give covering fire.
It's just too dangerous.
I don't have a choice.
[TAILYELLOW yells]
[TAILBLUE, SPIDER GUILDY
grunting]
I'm ending this. Right now.
[yells]
[TAILRED grunts]
--[TAILRED gasps]
--[SPIDER GUILDY grunts]
Aura Pillar!
[TAILRED yells]
Get ready for my Brake Release!
[TAILRED grunts]
[TAILRED]
Grand.
Blazer!
[SPIDER GUILDY grunts]
[TAILRED]
Uh?!
[SPIDER GUILDY grunts]
[TAILRED gasps, screams]
Tailred!
[TAILRED groaning]
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Serpent Slayer!
[TAILRED groaning]
--[SPIDER GUILDY grunts]
--[TAILRED screams]
How dare you hurt Tailred!
[TAILYELLOW]
Blue! Come quick!
[TAILRED groaning]
[SPIDER GUILDY]
That will be all for today.
[TAILBLUE]
Talk to me!
[TAILRED groans]
Please tell me you're okay.
Yeah... Fine
It's just that his last attack
really caught me off guard.
I'm all right, guys.
It's nothing, I swear.
[AIKA] Come on Soji!
We're gonna be late!
[gasps]
[TAILRED]
Uh?!
Uh!
Soji.
Why the heck would you transform
while you're still in bed?
I wouldn't do something
like that. [gasping]
But it looks like
I did. So weird.
What's even weirder is that
I don't remember doing it.
Uh. How do you not
remember that?
This could be serious.
Well, get yourself together.
It's time to go to school.
--[door closes]
--[TAILRED] Mm...
[AIKA]
I'm off!
[MIHARU]
'Kay, have a good one!
[SOJI]
Wait up!
[TWOEARLE]
Hey! Slow down, would you?
I'm sure the beast will be
just fine walking by herself.
[SOJI]
Yeah, I guess so.
--[SPUDS barks, panting]
--[SOJI] Uh!
[SOJI]
Uh...
[car door slams]
[ERINA] Good morning,
Soji. How are you?
Huh. After a brief examination,
I see no major injuries.
I was worried after
yesterday's fight.
Is there anything
we can do for you?
[TWOEARLE]
Oh, relax! He's not hurt.
You see, I've been watching
Soji very closely.
His strong but supple
body still moves
like that of a panther
on the prowl.
Trust me, he's just fine.
[SOJI] You can't keep worrying
like this, Erina. I mean,
his attack was pretty impressive
and it did throw me for a loop.
But I can take it.
I promise.
The Tail Gear wasn't
damaged either, right?
Good, I'm so relieved to
hear it. You're okay.
That puts my mind at ease. Uh?
[SOJI]
Huh?
Sorry, guys. I don't
know what's going on.
I was just thinking about it,
and now I'm wearing it.
[SOJI]
Huh?!
Hey. It might be nice
to give it a try.
Would you like to take me
for a little stroll, Soji?
[TWOEARLE]
Hm...
Um. Sit puppy!
[ERINA barks]
[ERINA squeaks]
This is so humiliating!
I can't believe I'd
ever let someone
who isn't Master Soji
order me around.
What gives you the right
to do this to Young Miss?
It's not like she
belongs to you! Give it!
You know, technically, she
doesn't belong to you, either!
So I'm keeping this!
[MIKOTO growls]
[TWOEARLE]
Sit!
--[ERINA] Uh!
--[MIKOTO growls]
I said sit down, Patches!
--Patches! Patches!
--[ERINA whines]
You have one last chance
to put a stop to this
madness right now!
[TWOEARLE] Oh, yeah?
Whuduya gonna do?
[MIKOTO]
Give me that leash!
[TWOEARLE]
You can't have it!
--Patches! Patches!
--[ERINA barks]
If I'd stayed to deal with that,
I'd be later than I already am.
Yeah. Probably.
[SOJI yawns]
I can already feel it, Aika.
Today's just gonna be
one of those days.
[AIKA laughs]
At least I have you
here to keep me calm.
[AIKA] But it's not me
who keeps you calm.
You and I both know it's my
twin tails that do it for ya'.
That's true.
But your twin tails are
only a part of it, you know?
Hey. What're you looking at?
Oh. I was just looking
at your lips.
Maybe it's the light, but they
look unusually shiny today.
[AIKA gasps]
[AIKA]
I got Soji's attention,
and it wasn't by acting coy and
tossing my twin tails around!
Today he was all
about my lips!
[CHERUBS laugh]
[AIKA] That idiot sure
keeps me on my toes.
But wait. What does it mean?
Maybe that's what did it.
She kissed him.
I bet that's what triggered
his interest in girls.
Then again,
he noticed me.
And that means I might still
have a chance with him!
[SOJI sighs]
I don't know what's going
on with me this morning.
All I could think about
were Aika's lips.
Why wasn't I focused on her
twin-tails like I usually am?
This is not okay. I can't
imagine anything worse than
forgetting about twin tails.
How could this be
happening to me?
[SOJI] Maybe I got hit a little
harder than I thought yesterday.
[SPIDER GUILDY]
What do you mean
Flea Guildy "popped
out" on his own"?
Are you saying
he's gone rogue?
Start talking.
[ELEMELIAN 2C]
Well, I...
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Out with it!
[ELEMELIAN 2C]
Yes, sir.
Yesterday, after you graciously
allowed the Twin Tails to escape
with their lives, an unpleasant
rumor was started.
Apparently there are some
who say you were frightened
of the Twin Tails and your
exit was actually a retreat.
[SPIDER GUILDY] Flea Guildy went
down there to clear my name?
And is that the only reason my
apprentice took it upon himself
to face the mighty
Twin Tails alone?
[ELEMELIAN 2C]
Yes, sir!
Well, he also said that
he wanted to see
Tailred's legs
with his own eyes.
At any cost.
[SPIDER GUILDY]
I see. The truth at last.
[MIHARU chuckles]
Wh-What're you staring at?
Something on my face?
Did I get it?
[MIHARU]
I saw what happened.
On the way to school
this morning.
Soji was looking at your lips
and he got all turned on.
At first you felt insecure
and confused.
But then you realized
how great it is. Close?
[AIKA] Uh... How did you
know about all of that?
It didn't even happen
until we were right
in front of the school.
[MIHARU] The limitless
information systems
of my unconscious mind had
a spontaneous entanglement.
[AIKA]
Huh?
Or, in other words,
I had a hunch.
I thought something might
be up, so I followed you two.
[MIHARU]
It's crunch time, honey,
which means you've got to close
the deal in one fell swoop.
Okay, here's the plan.
You're going to propose a
harmless little wager to Soji
the next time all of you go out
and do battle as the Twin Tails.
Oh! And if you win the bet, he's
gotta take you out on a date.
What kinda bet?
Let's see...
--[FLEA GUILDY groans]
--[TAILBLUE grunting]
[FLEA GUILDY] Oh, yes!
What shapely legs!
And without any
bothersome breasts,
you're one perfectly straight
line from top to bottom!
You like that, huh?
Have some more!
Since I don't have any
'bothersome breasts',
I could go all day long!
I guess that Tailblue gave up
on trying to win that bet.
[TAILYELLOW]
Hm?
What do you mean, 'a wager'?
It's like a bet.
I want you to let me have a go
at the next Elemelian we see.
I'll make a bet with you
that I can settle
everything peacefully.
So if I can get this freak
to retreat or surrender
without using violence,
then I win the bet.
And if I do,
it means you have to do
something extra special for me.
I thought she said she was
gonna try to do this peacefully.
Then she went berserk the second
he started talking about
how flat chested she is.
I know his thing is legs,
and in a weird sort of way,
the punishment fits the crime.
But she doesn't have
to kick him that much.
--[TAILBLUE grunting]
--[FLEA GUILDY] Thank you!
Thank you, so much for this gift
you've given me!
I always wanted to get stomped
by a girlyboy with shapely legs!
--Die!
--[FLEA GUILDY screams] More!
[GLEA GUILDY moans]
I'm almost there!
[TAILRED]
Uh...
She didn't even use
a finishing move.
She beat him just
by kicking him.
[TAILBLUE pants]
[SPIDER GUILDY] The Twin Tails
have defeated Flea Guildy!
It's all my fault! I confess,
the rumor that I became
frightened during our
battle and retreated is true!
[ELEMELIANS murmur]
[SPIDER GUILDY]
I can't deny it.
The Twin Tails were far more
powerful than I anticipated.
[SPIDER GUILDY] I won't say that
I couldn't prevail against them.
However, it will require a
great deal of preparation.
When I realized that,
I returned here.
Once Flea Guildy had
made up his mind to fight,
there was nothing I
could do to stop him.
It would have brought shame
upon him to hold him back.
I was only thinking of honor.
That was my mistake, and it
cost a great warrior his life.
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Obviously, we must change
our way of thinking
to destroy them.
Do you like that? Huh?
[FLEA GUILDY]
Oh, oh, yeah.
[SOJI, MIKOTO, ERINA sigh]
[AIKA growls]
[TWOEARLE laugs]
Hey, everybody!
Check out the insane barbarian
beating up a helpless bug!
[TWOEARLE laughing]
[AIKA growls]
Oh, man! This is the best!
--[TWOEARLE laughs]
--[AIKA growls]
Goodness. Now nobody
will ever want to marry her.
Well that was something. I sure
am glad she's on our side
I think we should
probably head on home.
Spend too much time with her,
and there's a chance her violent
tendencies will rub off on you.
Wait! But I... Aw.
[SOJI]
Uh... So Aika, listen,
about that bet you
made with me...
[AIKA]
Uh!
It seemed like you were
confident that you could
get that creep to
surrender peacefully.
But what you did to him could
hardly be described as peaceful.
I mean, death by stomping wasn't
really on your list of options.
'Kay. That's enough.
I know I lost the bet.
Can we please just
forget about it already?
There's no reason for you
to leave here in a huff.
You know, it's possible to take
the kinda passion you used
to stomp that flea and
channel it in to love.
That kind of energy
can be very useful.
[AIKA exhales]
[SOJI]
Mm...
Shiny lips.
But I can't forget twin tails.
Uh! Uh...
[SOJI grunts]
No, please, I can't.
You don't wanna kiss me?
Is it because you don't
like me anymore?
[SOJI]
Uh...
Uh! No, wait!
It's not what it looks like!
[SOJI]
Uh!
[SOJI panting]
Please! Don't go!
You can't just leave
me here like this!
You're me!
Please come back to me!
Please come back
to me, Tailred!
[AIKA]
Good morning!
Good morning, Aika.
You're just in time.
Soji still hasn't
gotten out of bed.
Would you mind trying
to wake him up, please?
[AIKA] What an idiot!
He's gonna make us late!
C'mon Soji, get up.
I'm not messing around,
we gotta go.
If you don't get out
of bed right now,
we're gonna be late.
What's going on here?
Did you transform into Tailred
while you were sleeping, again?
[gasps]
Who're you?
[GIRL]
What're you talking about?
You know me.
[AIKA gasps]
My name is Soji Mitsuka.
We're best friends,
you weirdo!
[GIRL]
Uh?!
[SOJI] Things have taken
a turn for the worse!
I've turned into Tailred
when I was sleeping before,
but this time I'm
just a regular girl!
What am I supposed to
do if I can't turn back?
What if I stay this way?!
[MIHARU]
What's the problem?
Three girls would be
a nice change of pace.
It would definitely make
the show more cheerful.
[SOJI] Mom! I don't want to
know about your crazy fantasies!
[MIHARU] We could
even change the title to,
"Triple Twin Tails Tales".
You gotta admit
that's pretty catchy!
[SOJI] Next time:
"Red on the Ropes"
Tail On!
[MIHARU]
Oh, but then
my little boy wouldn't
get to be in the show.