[birds chirping]
What the--?
Am I--?
I'm glad to see you're
finally awake, Mr. Soji.
Hey, this is my room.
I hope this is all right.
I took the liberty
of transporting us here.
Where's Aika?
She took the hint
and was kind enough
to leave us alone for a while.
--[SOJI] Huh?
--[AIKA] Tell me where they are
--[TWOEARLE] Hm?
--[AIKA] right now!
How dare you leave me
stranded there like that!
Don't make me out
to be the villain.
I was trying to do you a favor.
Since you are absolutely
and unequivocally
not involved in this,
I was nice enough
to leave you behind and
not trouble you anymore.
Is that what you
call nice, you jerk?
Stop! Calm down, Aika!
Look, I need you to
explain some things to me.
First off who were those guys?
And, why the heck
did I turn into a girl?
Are you sure
you wanna know?
Yeah, of course I am.
Then I will answer you.
But, you must touch my heart
to know the truth!
No you don't!
[DRAGGUILDY] Have you arrived
at a conclusion yet?
[FOX GUILDY] Yes. We believe
that this is optimal
for that beautiful goddess.
[SWAN GUILDY] No. Here,
take a look at my prototype!
[GUILDIES chatter]
[DRAGGUILDY] You must take your
cases to Tailred directly.
More importantly, what is
the council's determination?
[BOTH gasp]
[DRAGGUILDY]
Unless I'm mistaken,
I believe I told you
to decide which one of you
would attack her next.
[TWOEARLE] After they--
After Ultimaguil had already
invaded and destroyed
many other civilizations,
they came to this planet
in an effort to steal
all of the attribute
strength called "elemela."
They're invading
civilizations.
Just so I'm clear, what is
attribute strength again?
It's quite simple,
Miss Aika.
It's the love that
you feel in your heart.
Oh, okay.
For example.
You have a great affection
for twin-tails.
This affection has been
condensed down into
mental energy. And it's
called "twin-tail attribute."
To put it another way,
attribute strength is
what a person
deeply believes.
And these monsters, they feed
off those deep desires.
It's the greatest
need they possess.
So, in other words,
it's like food or water.
They can't survive without it?
Hm.
In basic terms,
yes, that's correct.
But it's not that simple.
They desire the "twin-tail
attribute" the most.
It is widely considered to be
the strongest attribute
of them all.
So twin-tails are...
the strongest?
What? That can't be right.
I know it sounds ridiculous,
but it's a fact.
It's what the
Elemelians live for.
But Soji, trust me.
You can stand up to them!
[SOJI gasps]
Don't be afraid.
Tail Gear is a mighty,
counter-Elemelian armor.
It's based on incredible
attribute strength.
And as a result,
it takes a lot of
attribute strength
to control it.
That's where you come in, Soji!
Wait a second, are you
saying there's something
that actually appreciates my
deep love for twin-tails?
All right, slow down.
Aren't there better examples
of the power of love?
I get that some people
are really into twin-tails.
But what about friendship,
or the love of your family?
Those types of desires
are instinctive
to most creatures of a certain
level of common intelligence.
They're universally
held attributes.
This needs to be the
kind of love for something
that leaves you spellbound.
A deep obsession
for which you would be
willing to risk your life.
That's it!
That's the cornerstone
of attribute strength.
What kind of idiot
would risk their life
over something
like twin-tails?
This kind of idiot! So why
don't you just back off?
So lame.
I was not wrong to fall
for you at first sight,
and I am so happy I did.
I see now that giving you
the Tail Gear was
the best decision
that I've ever made.
Your love of twin-tails is
the greatest love there is.
You are the chosen one,
after all.
Wait. Seriously?
I'm really the "chosen one"?
[AIKA]
Uh-huh-uhhh...
[FOX GUILDY] Look at her
petite little body.
So small, and yet she was able
to defeat Lizard Guildy.
We are studying this video
carefully to make certain
we do not make the
same mistakes next time.
[DRAGGUILDY] You have
all fallen in love
with this twin-tail
haven't you?
Indeed, she is
a deeply mystical girl,
with an oddly
intimidating presence.
It will not be easy
to steal from her.
[ELEMELIAN 2A] True,
but remember, that's just
the kind of challenge that gets
a warrior's blood pumping!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Do you have a plan?
[ELEMELIAN 2A] Yes. In order
to restrict her movement,
I'll dress her up like a maid.
I want to see her
apron strings flopping
through the air
in perfect harmony
with those big,
beautiful twin-tails!
It will be a sight to behold!
[ELEMELIAN 2B]
No! Even better!
Dress her in a summer outfit
and splash her with water,
making her clothes cling
tight against her body.
Once her outfit is wet,
we'll be able to see
everything there is to see!
Not good enough! Hear me!
Tie her up with ropes so
the only part of her body
that's free to move about
is her twin-tails!
[DRAGGUILDY]
Silence!
[ELEMELIAN 2A gulps]
[DRAGGUILDY] It is hard
to say which of your ideas
is the most effective.
Therefore we will decide
who will attack her next.
In the throws of battle!
Not to interrupt,
but why're you guys still
staring at each other?
Yeah, it is
a bit strange.
In that case mister Soji--
[SOJI]
What are you--?
[AIKA] Oh no
you don't, Coconuts!
[SOJI] Will you two
stop fighting
so I can get some
straight answers?
I still don't understand
why I turned into a girl!
Are you sure
you want to know?
I am.
Typically, becoming
a woman means
your bud has blossomed.
That you've achieved
the age of sexual maturity
and have taken a man to--
[AIKA] If you don't
give us a real answer
I'm gonna make your elbow
bend the other way.
The truth is, the answer
is incredibly personal.
And if I'm being
completely honest,
it's not easy
to talk about at all.
[SOJI, AIKA]
Hm?
You see, the real
reason Mister Soji
becomes a girl when
he transforms is because
I have a taste for cute
girls! Is that a crime?
Hey, no judgment
over here!
Don't you dare
try to tell me that
you didn't
enjoy it, Mister.
Besides,
in the Tailred form,
you can draw the enemy
out into the open
with the allure
of your twin-tails.
It's the best strategy
to defeat them.
[AIKA]
Uh...
And Lizard Guildy learned
the hard way that
when it comes to doing battle,
you're not just a cute,
little play-thing,
you're a powerful combatant,
who is not to be
taken lightly.
Oh. Speaking of that
creepy lizard monster,
after I beat him
I picked up this thing.
Wow, that's so
pretty! What is it?
That, Miss Aika,
is a crystallization of
the ability strength that the
Lizard Guildy creep was using.
That stone is commonly
called an "elemela orb."
[SOJI] This might sound weird,
but the moment I picked it up,
I had the image
of a doll in my head.
A doll? Hold on,
does that mean Lizard Guildy
was obsessed with dolls?
That's right.
Or to be more specific,
he's really into little
girls holding dolls.
It's weird.
I see. So that's why
he wanted me to do that.
[LIZARD GUILDY] Would you do me
a small favor and hug this?
But isn't that
a little unusual?
Isn't what unusual?
[SOJI] Well, if he's into
little girls holding dolls,
he should be stealing
the attribute strength
of doll-lovers, right?
But, by doing so,
the girls wouldn't
love dolls anymore.
Which means that, in reality,
his actions would lead to
a perpetual cycle of
self-inflicted disappointment.
Hm. Yes, that is correct.
You might very well
say these Elemelians
are paradoxical beings.
Or paradoxical pervs.
Paradoxical, huh?
--[SOJI] Hm.
--[AIKA] Hmm...
[FOX GUILDY panting]
[TURTLE GUILDY panting]
I figured it'd come down to
the two of us, Fox Guildy.
[FOX GUILDY]
I'll be the one standing
when this is all over,
Turtle Guildy.
[TURTLE GUILDY]
I wouldn't be so sure.
[FOX GUILDY]
Let's go!
[FOX GUILDY, TURTLE GUILDY]
One, two, three!
Rock, paper, scissors!
[FOX GUILDY]
Total domination!
[TURTLE GUILDY grunts]
Wow.
By the way, Twoearle,
you haven't really told us
very much about yourself.
Oh, you wanna know me?
Okay then. Fine.
Here goes.
[AIKA]
Hm?
Come to bed,
and you'll know me.
Over my dead body!
[TWOEARLE squeals]
He didn't mean
"know you" like that,
boobs for brains!
Truth is, it's not
a very happy story.
I felt the least I could do
was turn it into pillow talk.
[AIKA]
You're weird!
[SOJI]
We're fine just like this.
Please, I'd like to hear it.
As you wish, Mr. Soji.
Many years ago,
my home planet was invaded
by the Ultimaguil organization.
They invaded your planet?
Did they destroy it too?
[TWOEARLE] No. They only stole
our attribute strength.
There was no looting or carnage,
but all that remains is a
lonely world devoid of hope.
Even though
they spared our lives,
there's nothing as cruel or
quiet as an invasion like that.
The pain of a world
without love
is a devastating
sight to behold.
Uh-uh. No. That's insane.
I'd never wear my hair like
that, not in a million years.
But when I took out
Lizard Guildy,
even the student council
president went back to normal.
If I can defeat Ultimaguil,
then your people might go
back to normal too, right?
I'm afraid not.
The reason the damage
was reversed is because of
how fast you were able
to beat them yesterday.
[SOJI gasps]
Once the Elemelians
have taken your
attribute strength,
unless the enemy is defeated
within a twenty-four
hour time-frame,
you can never go back
to the way you were.
Twenty-four hours,
that's it?
Yes, that's it.
Which means, when they attack,
we have to strike fast.
All right, then.
In order to avenge your world
and to protect mine,
I will use this awesome power!
I will do whatever is required!
[gasps cheerfully]
Thank you very much.
In that case, there is
one important thing
we have to discuss first.
[AIKA gulps]
[TWOEARLE]
When you go into battle,
you're going to
need some backup.
Which is why I am
going to construct
a super secret lair
underneath your house.
[SOJI, AIKA]
Huh?!
It's finally time.
At last, the moment I've
been waiting for is here.
But that's impossible,
in more ways than one!
Yeah! Any way
you look at it,
it's completely absurd!
Don't worry,
I've got it covered.
With my scientific capabilities,
I can finish the base
before morning without
anybody knowing.
[BOTH]
Uh-uh...
But there's
one small issue.
Before I do anything else,
Mr. Soji, I'll need you
to get your mother's permission
for me to live here with you.
[BOTH]
Huh?
There is no way
she'll ever agree to!
It's okay by me!
[SOJI, AIKA]
Are you for real?
[MIHARU] Absolutely. I heard
everything you said.
[SOJI] Hold on a second,
you heard everything?
When I saw that
story on the news,
I knew that was you out there
doing good deeds.
I'm so proud!
[SOJI] I don't understand, how
are you so calm about all this?
I've kept the truth
from you for too long.
It's time that
I told you everything.
Wait, did you
know about this?
That I would be the one
chosen to wear the tail gear?
Oh, no,
don't be ridiculous!
Then what are you
talking about?
I'm talking about my dream.
[SOJI, AIKA]
Your dream?
When I was a young girl,
I dreamed of becoming
a super heroine
who'd save the world.
But instead, all I became
was your mother.
So I passed along my
hopes and aspirations to you
so that you could
achieve them on my behalf.
Aww, that is so sweet!
What are you saying?
Did you do something
to me before I was born?
I'm pretty sure
your father wanted to be
a super heroine
when he was young too.
[SOJI] I'm seriously
losing my patience.
In that case,
I have a quick question.
Ask me anything, Twoearle.
"I don't know what to do.
We don't have a
spare futon for you.
Oh wait. I know, you can
just sleep in the same room
as Soji while
you're here." Well.
It wasn't a question really,
but that's the kinda thing
I'm trying to get you to say.
Are you insane?!
Hey, did you forget
that I'm sitting right here?
Twoearle, you're lovely.
I'm so glad someone
like you is here.
You're the answer to my prayers,
and I would be honored
to have you as a guest.
My house is yours for anything
that you might need.
But, I don't
know what to do.
We don't have a spare
futon for you. Oh wait.
Hey, how about you just
sleep in Soji's room instead?
[SOJI, AIKA]
Are you serious?
You're sweet!
Thank you very much, Mom!
I have one condition.
You have to promise you'll
make a man out of Soji.
Consider it done!
Come with me. Right now.
[TWOEARLE hums]
[AIKA]
She is not to be trusted.
If you let
that woman stay here,
you'll be putting your son's
virtue in jeopardy!
Oh believe me, I know.
A sexy space girl from
another planet moving in
and suddenly making things
all hot and heavy!
This is exactly what
I fantasized about!
It won't bother me one bit if
she forces herself on Soji.
And actually, I'll be
upset if she doesn't.
And you have the nerve
to call yourself his mother?
Yes, I do.
And I'm proud of it.
I'm his mother. And the only
thing that I have ever wanted
for my baby boy is for him
to have a girlfriend!
[gasps]
I hoped that
it might be you.
But I guess the sweet, little
girl he's known since childhood
never found the courage
to make her move.
[AIKA] Wait, what?
What are you talking about?
But this Twoearle--
I can tell she's the one
when I look
into those eyes.
The eyes of an unprincipled
girl who's out for
my son's virginity,
no matter what.
Uh. You would
take that kind of risk
with a complete stranger?
No. Twoearle is now a
proper member of the family.
My dearest Mother!
[AIKA]
Whoa. Ow!
Forgive me for
saying this to you, but--
I'm not unprincipled,
Mother, not even a little.
But you were absolutely
right about my interest
in attempting to
steal his virginity.
I think you've just
made my life!
[TWOEARLE]
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
With your permission,
I'll go and build
the secret underground
base right away.
[chuckles]
While you do that,
I'll go and make us
all some dinner!
If I catch you peeking,
you're gonna be in big trouble.
[AIKA] Soji! Be sure
to lock your door
when you go to
sleep tonight, okay?
Okay. But why?
You know why! Please!
Just do as I say
and lock that door
or I'll weld the
stupid thing shut!
[SOJI]
It's made of wood.
[AIKA] Be careful. There's
a lot she's still hiding.
Huh? A lot of what?
She said that
Ultimaguil invaded her world
and stole all of
the attribute strength.
But how did she get her hands
on the twin-tail attribute
that makes up the main core
of the Tail Gear?
[gasps]
Whatever you do, just
don't let your guard down
with her, okay?
Hm.
[FOX GUILDY grunts]
[TURTLE GUILDY] I'll admit.
I never imagined you were
this good. But I
will not be beaten!
[TURTLE GUILDY groans]
[ELEMELIANS gasp]
[FOX GUILDY chuckles]
[TURTLE GUILDY grunts]
[ELEMELIANS]
Aaah...!
[TURTLE GUILDY chuckles]
[SOJI] That evening,
even though I should've
been worn out
from everything that was
going on, I couldn't
sleep at all.
The sounds of
the super secret base
being built downstairs
were just too weird.
What were
those sounds anyway?
If her "scientific capabilities"
were really advanced,
then why was it so loud?
[footsteps]
[TWOEARLE moans]
[TWOEARLE sighs]
[SOJI gasping]
I'm officially done building
our super secret lair,
so why don't you give me
a super secret smooch?
No, Twoearle, hold on.
I think this is moving too fast!
Hey you!
[TWOEARLE]
Huh?
Put those things away!
--[AIKA grunts]
--[TWOEARLE groans]
[snoring]
[SOJI]
I'm leaving!
[MIHARU] Be careful
out there! My heroine!
[SOJI sighs]
Good morning, Soji.
Did you check out the news?
Why? Whatchya'
got there?
[AIKA]
It's nothing really.
The Tailred angle
didn't get much coverage.
Yeah, well,
it's breaking news
in my mom's mind,
that's for sure.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do about her.
[STUDENTS chatter]
Oh boy.
[BOY STUDENT 2A] Whoa! That
looks exactly like her!
[BOY STUDENT 2B]
You're a manga guru!
Sweet. Dude,
check out this Tailred!
Yeah, you're totally
nailing that, man!
[SOJI] Hey! How do you guys
know about Tailred?
From this
incredible picture!
People are posting it
everywhere, dude!
Whoa. She's so freaking cute.
I can't take it!
If I keep looking at this,
my head's gonna explode!
Ugh. This is bad.
I feel dizzy.
[BOY STUDENT 2B] She's the
cutest chick I've ever seen!
[BOY STUDENT 2B] I used to
be more of a boob man,
but I'm coming around!
Look at those lips,
I just wanna kiss 'em!
[SOJI]
Cut it out, you sickos!
What do you think
you're doing, man?
You should all be
ashamed of yourselves.
She's just a little girl!
Aww. Poor little Soji
wants to have Tailred
all to himself and now
he's upset because
he'll have to share her
with the rest of us,
isn't that right?
That's not it at all!
[ERINA]
Attention students!
We will now be holding
a special school assembly!
Please report to
the gymnasium at once.
[SOJI] What is going on?
I feel so objectified.
[ERINA] Fellow students.
As many of you know,
we faced an unprecedented
crisis yesterday,
as mysterious monsters wreaked
havoc on our community.
I know first hand
because I was one of
the first people on the scene.
One of the first to be attacked.
[STUDENTS gasp]
But here I stand
in front of you all,
safe and sound. Because I
was saved by a hero
of justice that
swept onto the scene
like a gust of wind and
blew those monsters away!
[BOTH gasp]
[SOJI] Don't tell me
she knows it was me.
Oh. Not "hero."
I meant to say "heroine."
[BOTH sigh]
I've had my heart
completely stolen away
by this incredible girl.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[ERINA] Of the many videos
that have been uploaded
on the internet, I have selected
this one for you to see.
Uh. Does somebody wanna
tell me what's happening?
The Shindo Family will
support this brave girl
with everything we have.
And so, students and teachers.
Join with me in supporting her!
Well! Here's to our new savior!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SOJI] This is crazy.
I'm a savior?
And a super cute,
twin-tailed heroine
that everyone's
in love with, at that?
[SOJI]
But I'm a boy.
[SOJI] I'm exhausted.
I think I need a nap.
[AIKA] Are you going
to continue on as Tailred?
[SOJI]
Huh?
[AIKA] When we get home,
that secret base
should be finished, right?
You'll need to make a decision.
[SOJI groans]
I've got time.
It's not like they're appearing
in the sky every five minutes.
I wouldn't be so sure.
[DRAGGUILDY] Attention
all peon earthlings
who occupy this planet!
We are the chosen
disciples of the Universe.
We are Ultimaguil!
We have no intention
of bringing you any harm.
All we want is
the powerful light of love
that shines in
each of your hearts.
Resistance is futile!
As long as you do not resist,
your lives will be secure.
Allow us to take
the deep yearnings
of your hearts freely.
Obey! And your days of peace
and tranquility will continue!
[SOJI grunts]
If I let them do this, our
lives won't be secure at all!
If these monsters
take away our desires,
this won't be a world
of peace and tranquility,
it'll be a world full of
apathy and boring hairstyles!
And there's no way in hell
I'm letting that happen!
Does that mean...?
[TWOEARLE] Mr. Soji,
did you see that just now?
Yeah, I sure did.
[TWOEARLE] I'm picking up
Elemelian readings
on the newly finished
base's radar.
I have to stop them.
Tell me where?
[TWOEARLE] At Kyuaru High
School, in the next town over.
Okay, I know
exactly where that is.
Here.
[TWOEARLE] I almost forgot, I
thought up an activation code
for Tail Gear, so call it out
when you're ready!
Wait. You mean like
a transformation cry?
[TWOEARLE] Yes. The activation
code is "Tail On"!
[SOJI]
Mm! Mm...
[AIKA]
Mm?
Tail On then!
[TAILRED] I don't understand.
Why Kyuaru High School?
[TWOEARLE]
I can't be certain.
According to the internet,
it's a school that uses
old-style gym uniforms.
Pretty rare these days.
[KYUARU GIRLS screaming]
[TURTLE GUILDY chuckles]
[TURTLE GUILDY] My name
is Turtle Guildy!
Before I start looking for
twin-tail attribute strength,
I'll take a moment to admire
your cute gym shorts.
[TAILRED yells]
[TURTLE GUILDY yells]
That's one less
creepy monster!
[KYUARU GIRLS squeal, giggle]
No! Please! Stop!
[SOJI] By that second day
I had become a celebrity.
Sorry, I mean, Tailred
had become a celebrity.
She was generating a lot of
a buzz all around the world.
Apparently,
even NASA responded to
the Ultimaguil organization's
declaration of war.
I just hope this thing doesn't
become some kind of a big deal.
[SOJI]
This Tail Gear is awesome!
[TWOEARLE] Yes! The
full-body-enveloping,
lightweight and flexible
metal photon mail
is eighty times
harder than diamond
and still as supple as silk.
[TWOEARLE] Its punching
power is a hundred tons,
and its kicking power
is one fifty!
[AIKA] What about
these Excelion Shorts?
[TWOEARLE] Oh right,
they're shorts that
wick away moisture quickly.
[SOJI]
But why shorts?
[TWOEARLE] To make
a long story short:
sometimes when a battle
gets drawn out,
you may have to tinkle
and nobody wants to
feel like they're wallowing--
[SOJI]
Okay, that's enough!
Next time: "The Azure
Surge! Tailblue"!
[AIKA]
Tail On!