[GIRL]
To you new students,
congratulations
on your admittance.
My name is Erina, and I'm the
Student Council President.
I am so pleased to have
each and every one of you
as a classmate and
I can't wait to meet you all
and get to know you better.
It's a special day. A day
I hope you will remember
for many years to come.
[SOJI] There's so many
twin-tails here,
I don't even know what to do!
First, there's that older girl.
Simple, but very cute.
I'll call her
"Strawberry Twin"!
And her!
Well, no, not her.
Nnnh!
[SOJI] That girl is sporting
the short but sweet look.
I haven't seen that in years!
But I definitely think
she's pulling it off!
And then there's the President.
She's got the greatest
tails of them all!
Wow! Such long, glorious and
perfectly crafted twin-tails!
Look at the graceful,
gently-wound curls
down at the tips of the tails.
She must have spent hours
crafting them to perfection!
The way they bounce
in concert with her
hand and body motions!
It's like watching a princess
waltzing on the dance floor!
[gasps]
I never thought a place
this awesome existed.
I've died and gone
to twin-tail heaven!
Ah! These are gonna be
the best three years
of my entire life!
Yep. Nothing beats
twin-tails, all right. Eh!
[AIKA] Why are you
spacing out, loser?
Have you filled out
your questionnaire yet?
[SOJI] Mind you own business,
I'm finishing it now!
'Kay. Time's up, so please
pass them forward right away.
[SOJI]
Uh...
Uh-oh. Someone forgot to
fill their name in
at the top of the form.
Yeah, that's probably mine.
Sorry about that.
Ah. Soji Mitsuka, right?
Well, uh. You'd like to
establish a new club?
Interesting. What does one do
in a "twin-tail" club?
[STUDENTS whispering]
This sucks.
[STUDENTS continue whispering]
Idiot.
You know there's no way
that's gonna happen.
How embarrassing for you.
I told you
it was an accident.
I wasn't thinking clearly!
That makes it even worse.
Dirty twin-tail hound!
Hey, Soji, look, the
twin-tails you love so much!
[SOJI]
Stop that!
[SOJI grunting]
[AIKA giggles]
[yells]
Impressive.
Oh, shut up!
I've been better than you
ever since we were
little kids and you know it!
Heh! I kicked your butt then
and I can still kick it now!
Yeah, right!
You could never take me--
[MIHARU] Soji, shouldn't you
be home making some lunch?
Cook up a serving for two.
Aw Mom. Come on.
How are you today?
I'm fine. I was just
doing some shopping.
Like I said, Soji, make sure
to cook up enough for two.
If you're hungry, you can
have him for dessert.
--[AIKA] Ah!
--[MIHARU giggles]
[MIHARU] Oh, what I wouldn't
give to be young again!
[SOJI]
Oh jeez.
Hm? You okay?
What? Yeah.
I'm perfectly fine!
But your face is bright red.
Idiot.
Come on, what's the deal?
[AIKA] If my face is red it's
'cause you say stupid things.
[SOJI] What stupid
things did I say?
[WOMAN]
Hm.
[running footsteps]
[STRAWBERRY TWIN panting]
[gasps, panting]
[AIKA]
You know, Soji,
you could actually start
a twin-tails club for real.
And... hey, I might
even be willing to join
in exchange for a whole year's
worth of free dessert!
That's a crappy deal.
Come on, isn't it enough that
you and I are old friends?
Doesn't that count?
[AIKA] We're not friends, we're
just stuck with each other.
[SOJI]
Mm? What?
--Uh...
--Is she a customer?
Uh. Sorry, Miss.
But we're closed
for the rest of the day
so you'll have to leave.
[beeping]
--Hey uh, Soji.
--Hm?
Oh, sorry. My bad.
No. It's okay.
[gasps]
[WOMAN] Do you mind
if I sit next to you?
Uh...
[WOMAN] Please forgive me
for my intrusion.
[AIKA]
Oh, jeez.
Just hold it right there!
Pardon?
Hey! Who are you?
Oh, don't worry.
I will worry! What exactly
do you think you're doing?
[AIKA yelps]
There's no use
trying to attack me,
so don't waste your time.
Mister female impersonator.
[shrieks]
Who are you calling
an impersonator?!
Hey, calm down!
I'm sure she didn't mean that!
[WOMAN]
It was just a joke.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Twoearle.
I've never
heard that name. Cool.
Thank you.
Tell me something.
Do you like twin-tails?
Yeah! I love 'em!
[gasps]
[TWOEARLE]
Then take this.
It's okay, there's
no reason to be afraid.
Just take it. Please!
[AIKA] All right,
that's enough, weirdo!
What exactly is that thing?
Some kinda weird perversion?
I promise you, there's nothing
shady about me at all!
At this point,
there's nothing you can say
that will convince me you
aren't the definition of shady!
I'm sorry, but I don't have
time to explain right now.
Please, you have to put it on!
Don't do it, Soji.
It's probably just some
cheap, dime-store jewelry.
If you put that thing on she'll
try to charge you for it.
Look, I don't
want your money!
But I'm begging you,
do as I say!
Just stick it in,
I'll be all right.
It'll probably hurt a bit,
but in the end,
I know I'll be able
to make it through!
Please, put it around that
big, thick, thing of yours.
And make sure you strap it
on good and tight!
Don't make it
sound so dirty!
Well, I guess we know
whose mind is in the gutter.
Uh! All right, let's just
take it easy, Aika!
You too, Miss Twoearle.
Whoa!
[SOJI] Actually, now that I've
gotten a good look at her,
she would look amazing
in twin-tails!
Please, you have to trust me.
Put it on right now,
and I promise I'll do
anything you ask of me!
[gasps]
Wait, anything?
Yes! And I don't care
what it is, either!
Just tell me what you want.
If it is within my power,
I will make it so!
Wow. Really?
Well, Soji what
are you waiting for?
She said anything,
and I'm betting that
you ask for a lovely
pair of you know what!
[gasps]
Uh. Don't be mad!
So that's
what you want, huh?
In that case, go on and
grab a couple hands-full!
Don't be shy,
it's perfectly fine.
And I think you'll find
they're surprisingly soft.
Go ahead. You can even
squeeze them if you'd like.
Uh. Wait,
what are you...?!
Should I take 'em out
so you can see 'em?
Listen up, Airbags.
Back away
or I'll rip those things off!
This's none of
your business!
None of my business?!
There's no time to argue!
Don't you understand?
If we don't do
something right now,
all of the
twin-tails will vanish!
[gasps]
What did you say?
What do you mean "all of
the twin-tails will vanish"?
Tell me this is some kind
of sick joke! Please!
[TWOEARLE]
Gotcha!
[BOTH gasp]
[TWOEARLE] I'll explain
everything later.
For now it's important
that you come with me.
[AIKA screams]
Uh. Whoa! Soji!
What happened?
Wait, where are we?
I'm sorry for
all the confusion.
But I thought this would
be faster than explaining.
Soji! You see
where we are?
That's the exhibition hall!
[SOJI]
You're kidding me.
But that's, like,
a twenty-minute drive
from where we live.
[AIKA] All right, spill it!
What did you do to us?
[TWOEARLE]
My apologies, Miss Aika,
I didn't intend
to bring you along.
But you happened to be inside
the effective radius.
Hold on!
[TWOEARLE]
Are you all right?
Hey, doesn't that girl
go to our school?
Yeah.
She's an upperclassman.
[gasps]
Wait, that's
Strawberry Twin!
Huh?
[SOJI] I'm positive.
She's a senior.
She loves her
twin-tails a lot.
She always kept 'em
neat and tidy!
You're weird.
Her twin-tails are to blame.
That's why she
ended up like this.
[SOJI, AIKA gasp]
Where am I?
What happened to me?
[SOJI]
What happened to your hair?
The last time I saw you,
you had magnificent twin-tails!
Really?
That's your question?
[STRAWBERRY TWIN]
What are you talking about?
Your hairstyle! Uh!
It was in twin-tails, right?
Uh-uh. No. That's insane.
I'd never wear my hair like
that, not in a million years.
[gasps]
She forgot.
[TWOEARLE] That's because
the Elemelians attacked her.
Which means she's had her
twin-tail attribute
stolen from her!
[SOJI]
What do you mean?
In other words, her passionate
love for twin-tails
has been removed from
her personality altogether.
[WOMAN 1A screams]
[distant screaming]
Who are they?
They're the bad guys.
[CROWD screaming]
[ULTIROID]
Moge!
[MAN yells]
[screaming continues]
[WOMAN 1B yelps]
[WOMAN 1B gasps lightly]
[TWOEARLE]
Elemelians!
[SOJI]
Whoa.
[LIZARD GUILDY laughs intensely]
Yes. At this rate, we'll have
them all in our clutches.
Every last twin-tail in the
whole world will be ours!
[gasps]
[AIKA]
Hey, Soji.
I think that guy might be
your doppelgänger?
[SOJI]
Don't be ridiculous!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
She must be here.
The question is where?
[ASUKA'S MOTHER]
Asuka, no!
Mama! Mama! Help me!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Oh.
[whimpers]
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Ah.
[ASUKA groans, whimpers]
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Uh. The mighty power
of the twin-tails
is formidable!
But I have a mission
to accomplish.
And I must not succumb!
[whimpers]
[LIZARD GUILDY] It's too much!
All of you, listen!
Bring them here right away!
[ULTIROIDS]
Moge!
[ULTIROID grunts]
[ASUKA gasps lightly]
[LIZARD GUILDY] Go on! Your
furry friends want to play.
Huh...?
[ULTIROID]
Moge! Moge-moge-moge!
[LIZARD GUILDY] Silence! We're
at an important juncture.
[ULTIROID]
Moge. Moge... Moge!
[LIZARD GUILDY] What?
The "ultimate" twin-tail?
[SOJI] I'd know
those twin-tails anywhere.
It's the Student
Council President!
[grunts]
[distant screaming]
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Hm...
[gasps]
[ERINA] I don't know who
you are. Or what you want.
But you'd better
let her go right now!
[LIZARD GUILDY] I'm afraid
I can't do that.
[ERINA] She's nothing
but a little girl,
why does she matter to you?
[LIZARD GUILDY] I have orders
and I follow them.
Personally, I hate having
to do this sort of thing.
But for the greater good,
it must be done.
Which is why I'm going to take
away your attribute strength.
[ERINA] Wait.
My attribute strength?
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Yes, your twin-tail power.
Let it abide forever
within the sacred ring!
[ERINA gasps]
Uh!
[SOJI]
No, Madam President!
I'll make them pay!
How can they do this
to our President?
Her twin-tails are so sublime.
A picture of true perfection!
Tell me what I
should do, Twoearle!
This's gone too far.
The reason you
brought me here is because
I have the power
to stop them, right?
That's just the
attitude I was hoping for.
Well, Mr. Soji,
use the bracelet
to transform yourself!
Transform?
[TWOEARLE] That bracelet is
a device that produces
a combat suit which increases
your physical abilities.
Once you transform,
you should be able to
easily hold your own in
a fight with those monsters!
Whoa. Awesome.
Hey. Hold on a second!
What does "transform" mean?
Is it safe? Because if there's
a chance of him getting hurt,
there's no way
I'm letting him do it!
No! I have to!
Those evil monsters
are going after twin-tails!
I can't just stand by
and do nothing!
Glad to hear it.
All you need to do is wish
hard with all your being.
That'll activate
the bracelet's power.
All right then!
[grunts]
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Hm?
[gasps]
Wow. Talk about an
amazing set of twin-tails!
Ah! Wait, that voice?
Is that really me?
Hey. What the heck
is going on?
Soji is wearing
an all-powerful armor.
The only chance we have
of defeating these monsters.
Tail Gear!
I meant why the heck did
Soji just turn into a girl!
[TWOEARLE groans]
Listen, Miss Aika!
In order to obtain a
tremendous power like this--
The fact is, it requires an
equally tremendous sacrifice!
Why does this sacrifice
have to take the form
of transforming into
a girl? I don't know.
Let's just say
that it's a mystery.
What?
More importantly,
aren't you a little concerned
about whether or not
Mr. Soji can win?
Oh, yeah!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
What incredible elemela!
She is, without a doubt,
the strongest twin-tail bearer
I have ever encountered!
Everyone! Take her down!
[ULTIROIDS]
Moge!
Whoa. This many of 'em
right off the bat?
[ULTIROIDS holler, chuckle]
Twoearle, what am I
supposed to do?!
How can I beat them?!
[ULTIROID groans]
[ULTIROIDS]
Moge...!
--[ULTIROID] Moge!
[ULTIROID]
Moge.
[groans]
[gasps]
[LIZARD GUILDY sighs]
She took out those
Ultiroids in an instant.
What unbelievable power is this!
Who are you, twin-tail?
[TAILRED]
Huh?
[TWOEARLE]
Go on, say something.
This is your chance
to make a big introduction!
[TAILRED]
Good call. All right.
I'll tell you
who I am, monster man!
Yes. My name is...
What's my name?
--[ULTIROIDS] Moge!
--[LIZARD GUILDY groans]
What is this?
Comedy hour?
[chuckles]
Just pick a name.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay then.
Well... Yeah!
My name is Tailred!
[screams]
[grunts]
--Ah!
--Uh!
[TAILRED] I think
I jumped a little too far.
Listen, you have to focus.
You created that jumping gear
with your own will, Soji.
There's no reason
you can't control it!
Okay, I can do this.
Right!
[LIZARD GUILDY
breathing heavily]
Ahh! Whoa!
You're really close!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
Oh, powerful, beautiful one.
Would you do me a
small favor and hug this?
[TAILRED screams]
He's a creeper!
[CROWD gasps]
Don't I at least
have some kind of
weapons or something?
[TWOEARLE]
Listen, Soji!
If you just touch your ribbons
and wish really hard.
Weapons will materialize!
Ribbons?
[gasps]
All right then!
Blazer Blade! Go!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
What!
[yells]
[LIZARD GUILDY groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[moans softly]
[LIZARD GUILDY] Not bad.
But I will not be beaten.
Not until...
Not until I hand
over all of these!
[shrieks]
That monster.
How did he survive
such an amazing attack?
He's tenacious,
that's for sure!
Here comes
my ultimate technique.
Super secret attack,
like when a doll
is held in the arms
of a little girl
and enjoys the
companionship of it's owner.
Lightning Spark!
Eh!
Aura Pillar!
[LIZARD GUILDY] Nice aim
you have there. Take this!
[yells]
It can't be! No way!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
I can't move!
Brake Release Attack!
[grunts]
[TAILRED]
Grand Blazer!
[yells]
[LIZARD GUILDY]
I-I thank you for this.
Because of your
tremendous strength,
I have finally learned
the true power
and beauty of twin-tails!
[TAILRED]
Huh?
[LIZARD GUILDY]
I beg of you!
Now that I am at the end,
please allow me
to touch your twin-tails.
Eww. Yuck. No way!
[LIZARD GUILDY]
She's so adorable!
[ULTIROIDS]
Moge? Moge?
Moge!
What in the world is this?
[yells]
Huh? Oh my. Where am I?
Mommy, I'm okay!
Everything's all right now.
[CROWD chatter]
[ERINA]
Excuse me.
Thank you so much
for saving us.
You are one powerful girl.
I'm not a girl--
I mean, I am, obviously,
but what I mean is that
looks can be deceiving.
You can't judge
a book by its cover!
Gosh.
You fought so beautifully
and with such incredible grace.
For someone so tiny,
you showed a tremendous
amount of strength
and bravery.
I'm so impressed
I don't know what to say!
[TAILRED] Uh, yeah. I guess I
don't know what to say either.
[ERINA] Well, will you please
tell me who you are?
[TAILRED]
Uh. Sure, why not?
I'm a champion of justice. Yeah.
[ERINA]
Mh!
So, will I ever see you again?
Of course. I'll be here.
As long as people like you
love twin-tails.
[MIKOTO]
We're on our way!
[ERINA]
Huh?
[MIKOTO]
Don't you worry!
[panting]
Are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
No. I'm fine, actually.
[gasps]
Wait! Don't go.
What's your name?
The name's Tailred and
I'll see you soon! Bye!
I'll be looking
forward to it.
[DRAGGUILDY]
Listen up, everyone.
Our search for the ultimate
twin-tail has finally
come to an end!
Victory will be ours!
[ELEMELIANS cheering]
[DRAGGUILDY laughing intensely]
[AIKA] So who are
these Elemelians?
They seem like a bunch
of perverts to me!
[TWOEARLE] You must not
underestimate them!
They are fearsome foes
who have already conquered
a countless number of worlds!
To that end, the name
of the organization
they've assembled is...
"Ultimaguil."
[SOJI]
I get it.
So the generic term for
the monsters in Ultimaguil
is "Elemelians?"
[TWOEARLE] Yes! Mister Soji,
please make sure
you put that long, thick,
big, strong what's-it-called
of yours to
good use next time!
[SOJI, AIKA]
It's called a wrist!
[TWOEARLE] Next time:
"A Twin-Tail Mystery?"
[SOJI]
Tail on!