C'mon, Soji, get up. I'm not
messing around, we gotta go.
If you don't get out of bed
right now, we're gonna be late.
Uh. What's going on here?
Did you transform into Tailred
while you were sleeping, again?
[gasps]
Who're you?
[GIRL] Mhm? What're you
talking about? You know me.
[AIKA gasps]
My name is Soji Mitsuka.
We're best friends, you weirdo.
[GIRL]
Uh?
Uh.
Who's that?
[AIKA] "Who's that?"
That's all you can say?
A girl? But how come
it's not Tailred?
Oh, wow. Squishy.
Shut up, you big perv!
[ALL gasp]
You know, I've always
wanted a little girl.
[ERINA]
I've got a plan!
If Soji doesn't
show up to school,
people are gonna get suspicious,
so we'll tell everyone
he's home sick with a bad
case of twin-tail-enza!
And for now, you
can just pretend
to be new transfer student:
Miss Solar Metca!
Wait, before we get to that,
am I gonna be a girl forever?
Hey, Twoearle,
do you have any idea what
caused this to happen?
Not at the moment, no.
But think of it this way,
at least you have experience
turning into a girl.
This is a completely
different type of transformation
and you know it!
Tailred has special powers. All
this girl has is massive boobs!
[MIKOTO] Yes, if those
sweater stretchers carry over
to your Tailred form,
they'll weigh you down,
affecting your agility.
Not to mention you could
throw your back out!
Mikoto, will you please get
one of my uniforms ready?
[MIKOTO]
As you wish.
So weird.
I guess if Soji was a girl, this
is what he would look like, huh?
I wish his late
father were here.
He would've been so proud.
This is not exactly
a proud moment! Uh!
[whimpering]
[AIKA growls]
What's wrong, Miss Aika.
Don't tell me you're jealous
just because Soji's female alter
ego has bigger boobs than you!
[TWOEARLE yelps]
[gasps]
[AIKA]
What're you so upset about?
There are worse things
than being a girl, you know?
It's not that. I have to pee
and I can't hold it anymore!
[gasps] Well, why are you
holding it at all, Weirdo,
girls can go to the bathroom
the same as boys?
I know!
[AIKA]
So, go then.
I would, but the problem is, I'm
not exactly sure how to do it.
[AIKA]
Boys stand up and girls sit.
Come on, it's not
rocket science!
[SOLAR]
No. I can't.
I'm sorry, but I can't
go to the bathroom.
Mr. Soji can't pee
because he doesn't understand
the female anatomy! What a
delightful comedy of errors
this has turned out to be! Oh!
I have just the thing. I've
invented this top-notch diuretic
guaranteed to make
you flow like the Nile.
Just Leak!
Take a drink. And you'll
tinkle freely once again!
But, personally, I rather
enjoy the pee-pee dance!
--[AIKA grunts]
--[TWOEARLE yelps]
Seriously, what the heck
is wrong with you?!
All right, then, I'll
accompany you to the bathroom.
I am a professional
maid, after all.
[ERINA]
Wait a second.
[BOTH gasp]
Soji, please.
If you have to walk through
the flames of uncertainty,
then I'm going too!
No, you don't have to do that!
[ERINA]
Don't worry! I'm not afraid!
[SOLAR gasps]
Reminds me of college!
[heartbeat]
Uh! Oh my gosh. It's fast.
Not to mention... intense!
[ERINA yelping]
[groaning]
But still, at least you and
I are in the same boat now.
I'm with you, Soji!
[AIKA] Yeah, whatever.
Let me show you how it's done.
[ERINA groaning]
It's cool. I'll be okay.
[whining]
Don't worry, Miss, help is
on the way. I'm going to call
the Shindo family emergency
potty-wagon right now!
Just hold it for 20
more seconds, okay?
[ERINA]
Can we make it ten?
[toilet flushing]
[AIKA]
Did you do exactly what I said?
Oh, hey! Did you see
that special on Tailred?
Yeah, I did!
[gasps]
Uh, I'm sorry about that!
Does that girl
go to our school?
We don't have anybody
that cute here.
[AIKA]
Hey, Twoearle!
Do you have any idea what it was
that could've turned
Soji into a girl yet?
[screams]
What the heck is
going on in here?
You know me, when
I'm doing research,
I take a hands-on approach!
[TWOEARLE laughs]
Truth is, I have no
idea what caused it.
As of now, not a single
one of my analytical tests
have rendered a
meaningful result.
I'm afraid it might
be a lost cause.
[AIKA]
Maybe you should try taking this
--a little more seriously!
--Oh! Please, stop that,
Miss Aika, I'm sorry
for being so handsy,
but I'm concerned that if
you don't let go of my head.
My brains will start oozing out
of my ears and that'll probably
--make everyone puke!
--[ERINA] Excuse me,
I'm very sorry for interrupting.
But I think you should
all take a look at this.
[ANKO]
♪ ...wish for come true ♪
♪ You've gotta increase
the scope of your dreams ♪
Oh, no! I was doing such a
good job of keeping an eye
on that tyrannical
lunatic until yesterday,
but when Mr. Soji suddenly
transformed into a girl,
I completely forgot!
What the heck is she
after this time?
[AIKA]
Hold on,
what if it's Red's--
I mean, Soji's lips
that she's after again.
I don't know what
her end game is,
but remember she's
an Ultimaguil officer.
She's probably coming up
with her next plan as we speak.
[SPIDER GUILDY] In order to
obtain indomitable strength,
I will now commence the rite
that will grant me new life.
Until it's complete,
I shall not allow myself any
word from the outside world.
I'm leaving you in charge.
[WORM GUILDY]
I'm goin' in!
[SCORPION GUILDY grunts]
[SCORPION GUILDY]
What?
[SNAIL GUILDY]
Worm Guildy, wait!
[WORM GUILDY]
My mind's made up!
[singing]
--[siren]
--[ALL gasp]
Oh, no, an Elemelian!
[SOJI]
Please! Don't go!
You can't just
leave me like this!
Tail On!
[sighs]
Let's go!
[TWOEARLE, AIKA, ERINA grunt]
[SCHOOLGIRLS screaming]
There it is!
Yuck. A worm!
An earthworm at that!
[WORM GUILDY]
Slimy-slimy?
[yelps] Ew, gross! This one
is all snaky and slimy!
I think I'm gonna throw up!
Is it wearing a tutu?
[WORM GUILDY] I am Worm Guildy,
in the service of Spider Guildy,
master of the girlyboy attribute
and the most fearsome
member of Ultimaguil!
So, even though it's pretty
awkward and embarrassing,
and I have a long way
to go before I achieve
Spider Guildy's level, I will
pursue girlyboy attribute
with all of my being.
Not only does
it look disgusting,
everything it says
is disgusting too!
You're one of Spider
Guildy's henchmen?
[WORM GUILDY]
That's right.
I'm here to challenge
you as his apprentice,
so I can show you just how
great Spider Guildy's power is,
and try to earn the
respect of my master!
An-And, while I'm at it,
I'll snatch up your twin-tail
attribute as well,
so all of Ultimaguil
will know how awesome I am!
Then, maybe everyone
will acknowledge me.
[bell rings]
Let me handle this one.
Go right ahead.
--[WORM GUILDY] Slimy-slimy!
--Let me help you, Red.
There's no sense in you
doing this yourself!
[TAILRED]
No.
Huh?
There are still tons of innocent
people here. Stand by, Yellow.
Just "stand by"? Okay.
But couldn't you ask
me to stay instead?
Uhhh, please, stay here.
[TAILYELLOW] Oh, more like I'm
your pet, and you're my master!
[whines]
You stay put!
Okay.
All right.
[TAILRED yelling]
[WORM GUILDY]
Shing! Squirmy-squirmy!
Huh? That didn't work?
Something's really
wrong here, isn't it?
That's my line, you jerk!
--[WORM GUILDY yelps]
--[TAILRED grunting]
[yelling]
[TAILRED]
Damn!
This is bad.
Is it possible that slimy freak
is just stronger than he looks?
[ACENA] Strange. Red doesn't
seem like herself today at all.
[yelling]
[WORM GUILDY yelping]
Something's not right.
That's not even half as
fast as her usual speed!
[TAILRED] I'm so slow!
What's the matter with me?
It's like it's not
even my own body.
Something is wrong.
[WORM GUILDY]
Does this mean I have a chance
of beating the Twin Tails
and gaining the love
and respect of my master?
[screaming]
[WORM GUILDY]
Slippery-slippery!
Oh, no, Red's in trouble!
Time for my Voltic Blaster!
Careful, she's way too close.
If you're aim is off,
you'll hit Red, too.
Yeah, you're right.
I can handle this one!
Wave Lance! Ha!
[WORM GUILDY]
Slimy-slimy! Shiny-shiny!
[yelps]
This freak's a full-body
tentacle sicko.
But I have to help her,
Red's in trouble! Hey, Worm!
Execute Wave! Ha!
[WORM GUILDY cries]
[WORM GUILDY] I'm sorry,
Spider Guildy. I have failed.
Just know that I
did it all for you!
[sighs] We beat him.
Wait, where'd Red go?
[TAILRED]
I'm down here.
Uh?
[yelps] Sorry about that!
[TAILYELLOW]
Good job, Blue, way to go!
[TAILRED]
I'm all right.
You guys head on
back without me.
[BOTH gasp]
Uh?
[DARK GRASPER] What in the
hell are you doing, Tailred?
Do you really call that crap
you just pulled fighting?
I've seen you in action
and that wasn't you!
[grunts]
--[DARK GRASPER] Worthless.
--[gasps]
The whole reason I came here
was to see my future
bride in action.
For a moment I thought
maybe my glasses were dirty.
I know. I was.
You disappoint me.
[TAILRED yells]
[AIKA]
Hey! How's the water in there?
[gasps]
Aika! Go away!
[AIKA]
Nope! I'm coming in!
[gasps]
[AIKA]
What are you doing?
Soji, look at me.
Did you really think I'd
come in wearing nothing?
You're such a mess.
Are you mad at me
or something?
[AIKA]
Hair is extremely delicate.
If you dangle it in
the water like that,
you're gonna get split ends!
What am I gonna do with you?
Okay, come on. Out of the water.
What? No way!
I'm naked. I can't do that.
Yeah, I know you're naked,
but you're in girl form,
so it's not embarrassing
if I see it.
[SOLAR]
Oh, right.
[AIKA]
Come on, turn around.
[TWOEARLE]
I see what's going on here.
Miss Chibi chest is planning
to get me out of the picture
so she can show the naked Mr.
Soji all the joys of womanhood.
I wanted to do that, but
since she beat me to it,
I guess I'll just watch.
Watch me, Soji, I'm gonna
undo my twin-tails.
[gasps] Wait, why
would you do that?
[AIKA] Don't stare at me like
I'm some sort of alien.
It's perfectly normal to take
down my twin-tails. I'm bathing.
Yeah, right. But, if
I wash 'em like this,
I wouldn't have
to take 'em down.
If you keep them
tied up all the time,
you'll damage the
roots and ruin them!
Do you want your twin-tails
to pop right off of your head?
[SOLAR yelping]
[AIKA] Exactly, so do what
I say and take them down.
[sighs]
[screams]
[SOLAR]
What an awful sensation.
It's as if I've lost
something... a piece of myself.
Oh, please, don't act
like you're about to die
from grief just because
you let your hair down!
Twoearle's the one
who has it bad.
She can never wear
twin-tails again.
I finally understand
what it feels like to have
my twin-tails taken away.
Remember, before bringing
a hairdryer into the mix,
you should dry your hair
thoroughly with a clean towel.
Always use low heat.
Are you sure? Because normally
I dry my hair on "turbo".
[AIKA] Using hot air for too
long can damage your scalp
and permanently
dry out your hair.
Proper upkeep and
care is very important.
Your hair isn't always
guarded by Tail Gear,
so you're gonna have to be
more careful from now on.
Yeah, I'm sorry. You're right.
[grunts]
[AIKA] Don't be sorry,
there's no crime in not knowing.
Up until now, you've gotten
a perfect set of twin-tails
just by transforming
and saying "tail on".
[SOLAR] I guess I never
realized how much work
went into maintaining
twin-tails. Wow.
I suppose, in the end, I didn't
know as much about them
as I thought I did, huh?
I'm gonna tie up your hair now.
I'm gonna use the same
rubber bands that I use.
[gasps]
[AIKA]
What are those?
Oh, these are the barrettes
that I used to wear,
back when I was still
wearing twin-tails.
[gasps]
And, since I have no
use for them anymore,
I thought that Mr. Soji
could use them.
Then I'll tie them up,
in your honor.
Thank you. That's
very nice, Twoearle.
[gasps]
[SOLAR gasping]
[SOLAR chuckles]
They look cute. Really cute.
[crying]
[SNAIL GUILDY]
Brothers!
Worm Guildy, who everyone
loved, has fallen!
[ELEMELIANS gasping]
[SNAIL GUILDY]
For the rest of our years,
we will never get to
see his slimy smile,
nor that adorable, wriggly
way he moved, ever again.
[crying]
[ELEMELIANS crying]
[WORM GUILDY laughing]
[SNAIL GUILDY crying]
--[phone ringing]
--[grunts]
[TWOEARLE]
We've got an Elemelian
at the same arena where Worm
Guildy appeared yesterday!
It's the middle of the night.
There isn't even
anyone there right now.
What could they be thinking?
[TWOEARLE]
Mr. Soji, are you okay?
Uhh. It's nothing, I'm just a
little off my game today is all.
I'm on my way! Let Aika
and Erina know, too!
[SNAIL GUILDY]
I am the great Snail Guildy!
Spider Guildy's number
one apprentice. Also...
You should know that my love for
Worm Guildy was second to none!
You'll pay for
killing my friend!
[yelps]
So you want revenge! Is that it?
[TAILRED yelps]
[TAILRED grunts]
--[TAILRED groaning]
--[footsteps]
[SNAIL GUILDY growling]
[BOTH]
Tailred!
[TAILBLUE yells]
[TAILBLUE]
Hey, are you okay?
[sighs]
Yes, I'm fine.
[SNAIL GUILDY groaning]
[TAILYELLOW]
How dare you hurt Red.
You'll pay for this!
Aura Pillar!
[SNAIL GUILDY gasps]
[SNAIL GUILDY grunts]
[TAILYELLOW]
Brake Release!
Voltic Judgement time!
[TAILYELLOW yelling]
Is he dead?
Yes.
[TAILBLUE] Then, let's hurry
and get Red the heck outta here.
[TAILBLUE gasps]
[SNAIL GUILDY]
You're going to have to do
a lot better than that.
My massive armor-plated
shell completely protected me
from your finishing move.
[growls]
[SNAIL GUILDY]
If I were you,
I wouldn't underestimate
me or my crew!
[SNAIL GUILDY] Even as we
do battle here tonight,
Spider Guildy is
gaining new powers!
[SNAIL GUILDY] He is making
preparations to challenge you!
[SNAIL GUILDY]
And when you finally face him
on the field of battle,
it'll be the end of the
Twin Tails once and for all!
[BOTH grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[TAILRED groaning]
[TAILRED]
It's no use.
I had less power tonight
than when I took on Worm Guildy.
What's happening to me?
I don't understand.
Why isn't my Tail Gear
giving me any strength?
[TAILRED]
Dark Grasper's kiss.
That has to be it! Ever since
her lips touched mine,
twin-tails are
taking a back seat
to my newfound
obsession with girls!
[TAILRED] I've turned
my back on Twin-tails!
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Everything is now in readiness.
[SPIDER GUILDY growling]
[SPIDER GUILDY yells]
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Spider Guildy is no more.
Now there is only
Arachne Guildy.
This time, I will
settle things for good.
[ARACHNE GUILDY]
You're mine, Twin Tails!
[SOJI] The thing I feared
most has come true.
What am I gonna do?
I no longer have a role!
[WORM GUILDY] You don't
have to worry, Mr. Soji!
[SOJI]
Worm Guildy?!
You've already been defeated,
so what are you doing here?
It doesn't make any sense!
[WORM GUILDY]
Heh. Trust me, you'll be fine.
Next time, you're going
to run into a surprise guest!
At least you have that
to look forward to, right?
[SOJI] A surprise guest?
Your chief officer?
[WORM GUILDY] Next time.
The final episode:
"Twin-Tails Forever!"
Tail On!
[SOJI] Oh, no, now
Ultimaguil is saying it!