[SOJI]
When did this start?
Since when have this many
people worn eyeglasses?
[SOJI gasps]
Wait a second. That woman.
The one standing behind Tailred.
With the weird mask
and the great rack!
How in the world did I
not realize it until now?
That was her.
That was Twoearle!
[SOJI] So, Anko is...
Dark Grasper!
It's her. But still,
it doesn't make sense.
The only logical
explanation is that Tailred
stole the twin-tail
attribute from Twoearle.
That must be it!
[MEGA NE] And what
makes you so sure?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
She likes her.
She probably took her captive
because she plans on keeping
Twoearle all to herself.
[MEGA NE] Yeah, that
makes perfect sense.
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
You'll pay for this, Tailred.
That goes for your blue
and yellow friends, too!
I will defeat you all.
I swear it!
[AIKA] How the heck did
we not notice this before?
You guys,
take a look at this!
"A Meganez Devil, I?
My heart is full. But you?
You will get stabbed
with a love shiv.
Right in your stupid heart!
Because you?
Your heart is molten lava.
Though once you
were quite fair.
Now you are nothing
but a paranoid jezebel."
What kind of
lyrics are these?
Take the last letter of each
line and read them in order.
You can see a secret message
hidden in the verses.
[TWOEARLE]
I-L-U-V-T-U-A-R-L.
But that says,
"I love Twoearle!"
[TWOEARLE and SOJI scream]
How dare you take
advantage of this situation?
Come on, this is no time
for messing around.
He's right. This poem
could only be...
a public declaration of love!
[TWOEARLE]
Huh?
She's putting on a show.
The Meganez Devil Paranoia Tour.
And It's clear to me that she's
trying to get us to attend.
I think you're right. She's
sending us a coded message
so that all of us
will go to the concert.
Oh, no! That means
if I don't go to the venue
and accept her kiss,
then not only will she steal
all the fans' attribute
strength, she'll also
turn them all into super
embarrassing eyeglass-Ultiroids!
Do you really think she
would take things that far?
[TWOEARLE] Who knows
what she's capable of?
After all, she did poke
holes in a newspaper
as a makeshift screen
so she could spy on me
while following me. Then
she took my hand and tried
to make me fondle
her absent breasts,
and chased after me
so she could sneak
into my room in the
middle of the night.
Any way you look at it,
she's one of those people.
And I have no tolerance
for such behavior!
But that's exactly the
kind of person you are!
We can't forget she went over to
the enemy's side to get to you.
So there's no telling
how far she'll take this.
Anyone who would go
to such extremes
is a dangerous foe,
to say the least.
Soji, I cut eyeholes
in a newspaper,
but I never made you
fondle my breasts, did I?
Well. What now?
I don't think we really
have much of a choice.
Let's get to that concert
before it starts.
And stop Dark Grasper!
[panting]
[ELEMELIAN 9A] Welcome
back, Spider Guildy!
we're so glad you're home!
[ELEMELIAN 4A] Indeed.
We have all been eagerly
awaiting your arrival!
[ELEMELIAN 2C] Since Dragguildy
met his unfortunate end,
our unit has been all but
obliterated by the Twin Tails!
[ELEMELIAN 2C] You are
the only hope for us now!
Please lead us, Spider Guildy.
Your wish is our command!
[SPIDER GUILDY]
Patience, friends.
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
♪ One, two, three, go! ♪
Guess what, everybody? The
party is about to get started!
And if you can't make it to
the concert, don't worry!
You can watch me on the
worldwide live stream instead!
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
Yeah!
[TAILBLUE] Whoa.
Don't you think this is weird?
[TAILRED] There isn't
a single fan around.
[TWOEARLE] Trust me,
they're here.
Apparently, she let
them all in early.
She did what? You're saying
they're already inside?
[TAILYELLOW] But our
plan was to charge in
and save the day
before they got here.
--[TAILRED] Twoearle!
--[TWOEARLE] Acknowledged!
[indistinct crowd chatter]
Get your Anko concert
programs here!!
[TAILRED]
That's a lot of fans.
Or is it more accurate
to call them hostages?
[crowd cheers]
Huh?
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
If you love glasses..
then make some noise!
[crowd cheering intensifies]
This girl loves
glasses, and I bet
this young lady
loves glasses too!
But not as much as me!
[crowd cheers]
Huh?
I'm so happy
you're all here!
How about I kick things off with
a little song and dance routine?
[crowd cheers]
What now?
We have to
draw her offstage
and away from all
these innocent people.
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)] I'm
afraid that's not gonna happen.
[TAILRED] Anko! Or should
I say.... Dark Grasper!
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)]
Heh! Nice Detective work.
You're pretty clever, Tailred!
If you're here, who's that?
[DARK GRASPER (ANKO)] A hologram
from an earlier concert.
I know what's going on:
that 3-D hologram
has some kind of hypnotic
effect on the fans, doesn't it?
Oh, please. I would never do
something horrible like that!
I have the most incredible
fans in the world--
fans who love and worship
glasses almost as much as I do.
They're my people.
They paid to see me perform,
and I would rather die
than cancel a concert.
Wait. Now I'm really confused.
Are you a good guy or a bad guy?
There's only one
"bad guy" at this concert
and you know exactly
who it is, Tailred!
[TAILRED] Hold on,
why am I a bad guy?
We can't discuss this here--
let's take our chat outside!
[DARK GRASPER] Tailred. You
are my sworn enemy and a villain
because you stole everything
from my beloved Twoearle!
And on top of that,
you are fawned over
as the number-one twin-tail
around by the Elemelians,
who are supposed to be
serving at my command!
Check your facts before you
start making accusations,
'cause I didn't steal anything!
Don't play dumb with me.
I can see right through you.
You wanted to steal
Twoearle's identity.
Didn't you?
Urgh... No, my
photon absorbers!
[TAILRED yells]
Tailred!
Dark Grasper.
You should at least listen
to what Red has to say.
If either one of you tries
to stand in my way,
I will show you no mercy!
[TAILYELLOW] Oh, yeah?
Well we've got experience
and teamwork on our side!
[TAILBLUE]
Yeah!
[TAILRED]
We do?
Remember, Dark
Grasper's a human,
so concentrate your
attacks on her armor.
Let's just hurt her a little
and make her surrender.
Yeah! I'm okay with that.
[TAILBLUE &amp; TAILYELLOW yell]
[DARK GRASPER] Not good enough!
Darkness Whip!
[TAILBLUE screams]
[TAILYELLOW screams]
I'm coming, guys!
Winding Moebius!
[ALL THREE scream]
And now the moment
I've been waiting for:
Tailred, I'm gonna
undo your twin-tails.
Wait! You're what?
And then I have a special pair
of glasses I want you to try on.
I hope you like 'em,
cause once they go on,
they can never come off!
What do you mean
they never come off?
Yes, that's right.
These glasses will be fixed
to your face forever and you'll
never be able to remove them.
Also, they're my personal
prescription, so from now on,
you'll see the world
the same way I do.
Which means your
precious twin-tails
will look blurry to you!
[TAILRED gasps] No!
That would be a living hell!
[DARK GRASPER] Put them on,
put them on, put them on!
[TWOEARLE]
Stop right there!
[DARK GRASPER]
Twoearle!
Oh, Twoearle...
[TWOEARLE] Acena.
I'm sorry about earlier.
[TWOEARLE] I will tell
you the honest truth now.
What do you mean?
No more lies. My decision
to turn over my power
to these people
was of my own will.
And I did it
with full knowledge
that I would no longer
be a twin-tail!
[DARK GRASPER gasps]
This is heartbreaking. To think
that they've brainwashed you
into believing
this nonsense.
It's no use.
She's completely delusional.
You have to remember
that the only version
of Twoearle she knows is
one that treated her kindly.
But she's really just a sicko
with a thing for little girls!
Please try to understand me,
Acena. I only care
about one thing now. And
that's destroying Ultimaguil!
I've made my decision, and
there's absolutely nothing
you can say that
will change my mind.
[DARK GRASPER] This isn't you,
Twoearle. After I defeat
these monsters, you'll go back
to the way you were before.
You leave me no choice.
No. Wait.
[TWOEARLE] I don't want us
to hurt each other.
I swear to you, I don't.
Just do me a favor and take
off that armor, Acena.
For you... Yes.
[TAILRED] Guys, look, it's Dark
Grasper's true identity. Acena!
What do you think
Twoearle's planning to do?
Soften her hard
heart with love?
At least that's what I would do.
Please, trust me.
I beg you.
Remember the way
things used to be.
Come on.
Let's touch boobs.
What's wrong with you?!
Would you stop joking around?
This is a serious situation!
Yeah, I know, and I
seriously wanted
to touch some boobies. Geez.
Come on.
Stop it! Don't hurt her. I can
see now that Miss Twoearle's
not being controlled by
the Twin Tails. I get it!
You finally understand?
[TAILRED] This is
wonderful, Twoearle!
Are you sure you're
okay with this?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)] It saves
me the trouble of having
to win back Twoearle. I can
move forward with my plan
to eyeglassify all of humanity
at once. Glasses on!
If you care about Twoearle
like you say you do, then how
could you betray her by joining
up with those Ultimaguil pervs?
It's all out of love
for glasses!
I mean, sure, I would like
to see Twoearle's twin-tails
brought out by a pair
of sweet specs,
but more than anything,
I want to protect glasses.
Because the Glasses Attribute
has all but vanished
from your world!
You're upset because
modern science
has brought about technologies
like Lasik and contacts?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
That's only part of the story.
It makes me sick to my stomach
that girls are constantly told
they look more beautiful,
or look more grown-up,
or they look less like a nerd
if they take off their glasses!
Right? You know
what I'm saying!
Yes. Unfortunately, people
say the same horrible things
to young girls about
their twin-tails
and I don't like it
any more than you do!
I told Ultimaguil I would
join them in an effort
to achieve their conquest
on one condition.
I made them promise to never
steal Glasses Attribute.
What? No way!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)] Even if
they take every other attribute
in the whole Universe,
they won't touch glasses
and that's all that
matters to me!
So far, they've held up
their end of the bargain.
And on the countless
worlds they've conquered,
the love of glasses is
the only one that remains.
So that's why you
became a pop star--
so you can spread the Glasses
Attribute all over the world!
Not to steal it, like
the Elemelians do,
but to foster it and
protect it from harm!
But above everything else,
I have one ultimate objective.
To fill the entire
world with glasses.
And make Twoearle love them .
'Cause then she'll
want to wear these.
I made this pair especially
for you, Twoearle.
And once you put them on,
you will clearly see
that I am your one and only
love in this universe.
It's not love if you
have to force her!
Acena, what you're
doing is plain wrong!
If you think we're gonna
let you get away with this,
then you've got
another thing coming!
Ha. Like you're one to talk.
What are you saying?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but aren't you the
biggest idol in the world?
Isn't everyone looking
to you to be their leader?
Yet you're assisting
Ultimiguil by creating
more attribute strength
for them to steal.
No, that's completely different!
I'm protecting Twin Tail
Attribute! To preserve it.
I'm not stealing from anyone!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Tell me this: are you prepared
to become a god?
Okay, now you're
just overexaggerating
this whole situation. I love
twin-tails and that's the end
of the freakin' story!
So why don't you back off?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)] It
appears talking is pointless.
And since that's the case...
Chaosic infinite!
What have you done with them?
Don't worry your pretty little
head. I've bid your friends
to a dream world where they
will want to stay forever!
At long last, it's just
the two of us here,
unburdened by those
annoying, twin-tailed twits!
Bring them back!
I'm warning you, Acena,
if you don't bring my friends
back right this instant,
I'm really going
to start hating you.
I'm not worried. No matter
how much you resist,
in the end, I'm going
to make you love me.
[TWOEARLE shudders]
Plus, I can't
bring them back.
Unfortunately, I only have the
power to send them there.
They have to decide
to return on their own.
But odds are,
they won't want to.
[SOJI screams]
[SOJI gasps, pants]
Huh? Did I really
just dream all that?
You have to promise
that you'll be gentle.
You are so cute.
[AIKA]
Thank you.
Hey! No fair, you guys!
Erina?
I want you to
treat me like a dog
and tie me up by
my twin-tails! Arf!
I couldn't do that
to your twin-tails.
I would never forgive myself!
[ERINA whimpers]
[MIKOTO] Speaking
of tying knots...
How about we get married?
[SOJI]
Uh...
This doesn't make sense.
Why is Mikoto here? So weird!
[STRAWBERRY TWIN] Don't
forget about me, Soji!
Our twin-tails belong
to you, Mr. Soji!
They're yours until
the end of time!
Is this a dream or have I
died and gone to heaven?
Hold on. Seems like
we're missing someone.
Twoearle, it's you.
Oh. Hi. Would you like to
watch, Mister Soji? I'm gonna
make myself a twin-tail,
like you've always wanted.
[TWOEARLE giggles]
[TWOEARLE] And so, after I
realized what I had done,
I got rid of my twin-tails
and I never looked back.
[SOJI] Wait, that's right.
Even if Twoearle wanted
to go twin-tail again,
she wouldn't be able to!
What kind of messed-up
place is this?
This is wrong!
It's all a lie!
How could I have
believed this crap?
Damn it, Soji!
You're such a dumbass!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA) gasps]
[TWOEARLE gasps]
How can this be happening?
There's no way
she could burn through
subspace like that and live!
Tailred!
No way. That's not
even possible!
No one escapes the
dream dimension
without being swallowed up
by my Chaosic Infinite!
In that strange illusion,
Twoearle was about
to tie up her twin-tails, which
she could never do in real life!
Wait. I was?
Twoearle, who gave up twin-tails
for our sake, and for the sake
of atoning for sins she
committed on her world. She was
about to tie up her twin-tails
like it meant nothing.
As if it was just some
kind of stupid joke!
Can I ever forgive myself
for being so weak
that I actually allowed
my mind to entertain
such a ridiculous
fantasy? No!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA) laughs]
So you're saying that
the anger you felt towards
yourself ignited your heart?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA) laughs]
I have no patience
for a world comprised
of foolish fantasies
of false twin-tails.
And I will do everything
in my power to destroy them!
You wanna see some real
twin-tails, Dark Grasper?
Take a look!
Well. Apparently you really
do have a great love
for twin-tails! However, simple
passion won't be enough!
All right, Tailred,
It's time to find out
whose love is stronger,
once and for all!
Now, Brake Release!
[TAILRED]
An Aura Pillar? No!
Ha! I have no need
for an Aura Pillar!
I hope you're prepared
for what comes next,
because just as I've
done to countless enemies
on numerous
worlds before yours...
I'm going to pulverize
everything with darkness!
Uh oh. Not good.
[TAILBLUE] Soji.
Just leave the lights on!
Then you'll be able
to see my boobs!
Huh?
[TAILYELLOW] No, I can't!
I don't care if it's night-time;
I can't go for a walk
looking like this.
What kind of hallucination
are you having?
[TAILRED]
Oh, wow.
This is the
Braid Attribute Orb.
[TAILYELLOW squeals]
What? I was right
in the middle
of my super naughty
puppy-walk fantasy!
[TAILBLUE squeals]
What the hell?
I was almost there!
I hope you enjoyed your
trip to dreamland, ladies.
I'm sorry to wake you.
Sounds like your hallucinations
were just getting good.
[TAILRED] All right!
Time to unite, Twin Tails!
[TAILYELLOW &amp; TAILBLUE]
Let's go!
[ALL THREE] All done!
Fusionic Buster!
They just
joined together.
Which means they're using
Kerberos Guildy's power.
This should be interesting!
Blue, take that side.
Red, take the trigger.
And when everybody's ready.
Yell, "Fire!" Kay? Let's go!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Darkness Bani!
That was too soon!
We did it. Her armor
has disengaged!
So we wanted to
get her naked?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA) laughs]
Bravo, Tailred, well done!
What is that?!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Allow me to introduce you
to Mega Neptune Mark Two.
My closest confidant
and partner!
[MEGA NE]
Nice to meet you.
Thank you so much for
taking care of Miss Acena.
I'm really sorry. She
doesn't have any friends,
so she gets a little clingy with
anyone who plays with her,
which is how she loses her
friends in the first place.
It's a vicious cycle.
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)] Hey!
Why are you telling them that?
Just drop it already!
[MEGA NE] Oh, my,
how very unladylike!
A girl your age
should know better!
Traipsing around naked.
Here. Put these on
where it matters most.
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Huh?
Uh, why do these bandages
have my QR code on them?
This is awkward.
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Well, Tailred!
I'll admit that you defeated
me this time around!
But we'll need to set up
a time to do this again.
Here, take my e-mail address!
Oh! There's really
no need for that.
I can just get it from Twoearle!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Well. In that case...
[ALL THREE scream]
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Scan me anytime you want.
Hey, guys?
What just happened?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
I'm sorry, Twoearle.
I know you might think
this makes me a floozy.
But I don't care.
I've had my heart
stolen away by Tailred!
And you'll just have to deal
with it. Let's go, Mega Ne!
[MEGA NE]
Alright, you got it!
Hold on.
Wait just a second.
Does somebody want to explain
to me why I totally feel
like I just got dumped?
Come back!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Hey everyone!
How did you like today's story?
The Twin Tails are going to
go all-out next time, too!
[STRAWBERRY TWIN] So let me get
this straight: we're just gonna
pretend that wasn't a
bombshell moment earlier?
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
Wait! You're that
Strawberry Twin girl,
aren't you?
What's a bit player like you
doing in the preview?
[STRAWBERRY TWIN] Let's
just say I know how to work
my way up the ladder!
[DARK GRASPER (ACENA)]
But you're not even in
the next episode.
[MEGA NE] Hey, is that
any way to talk
to someone who's your senior?
[STRAWBERRY TWIN] Next time.
"How Come? I'm In Bad Shape."
Tail On!
[MEGA NE &amp; DARK GRASPER]
That's a senior for you!