[NARRATOR] It has been 27 years
since humankind's "Great Leap."
Interstellar travel
has opened a doorway
to the reaches beyond
our Solar System...
to deep space...
Thus far we have explored
over 18 unique star systems
and traveled over ninety
light-years from home.
Back on Earth, the global
wounds from the Austral Wars
are slow to heal, as humanity
faces the bleak reality
of existence in a Solar System,
whose resources are
rapidly depleting.
Now, in the
twenty-second century,
humankind has a
newfound purpose:
the exploration of
new worlds to inhabit
and the establishment
of trade routes
to resupply the dying Earth.
[SNAUT] Arbiter Lange...
[LANGE] Ahh...
This "hyperspace travel"
certainly does
make me feel my age.
Such an unpleasant sensation...
How you young space faring types
tolerate it the way you do,
I'll never understand.
Well... it's a small
price to pay,
for traveling twenty-four
light years in five hours.
[SNAUT] There she is:
Beta Hydri...
Beta star of the
Hydrus constellation...
Spectral type: G2-IV.
Magnitude: two-point-eight...
Fifteen planets in orbit...
Our destination
lies on the fifth.
[Great Birnams vocalize]
[ALINA] Ion.
[ION] Alina.
[ALINA] Looks like you
managed to train a Piccard.
[ION] I figured out that they
use thermal air currents
to help them find
new grazing areas.
[ALINA] Ah, so they
show intelligence.
[ION] Mm-hmm.
And look at this.
Do you see that
mold-like substance
growing all over its body?
Well, it turns out that it's
actually a type of fungus...
It feeds on the Piccard's waste
excretions, and in the process,
it breaks down moisture from the
air into hydrogen and oxygen.
[ALINA] Interesting...
Which is why the Piccard
doesn't need lungs to breathe.
[ION] Exactly, plus the
hydrogen makes it light enough
to sail anywhere it wants.
It's remarkable...
[ION] It's called symbiosis--
two organisms that need
each other to survive.
It's quite common...
This planet is full of examples.
[Great Birnams vocalize]
[ION] There. Just take
these Great Birnams,
slogging through a hyperbaric
sea of carbon dioxide...
They couldn't survive without
the trees on their backs
feeding them oxygen.
Uh--
I wish you'd...
hold me without
this suit sometime.
I promise you I will...
Our survey here
is nearly complete.
[ION] Alright, so...
same place tomorrow?
Yes.
[BELTIN] So Romeo,
how was your date?
You get some?
[footsteps]
[ION] That's none
of your business.
[ION] You got a problem,
Major Beltin?
I've got enough diplomatic
headaches on this rock
without any extra help from you.
Word is the tension
back on Earth
is getting worse every day.
One little screw up here could
start another godamn war.
We done here?
No... I'm watching you...
Try sneaking off with
that Eurasion again
and you're dead, alright?
That a threat?
You know where the
problems come from?
Military guys like you who
try to control everything.
If you want to have
yourself another war...
you can do it without me.
Little asshole.
Forcing me to have a curfew?
I can't believe you're serious.
Are we going to
have a problem?
Because you can
always just leave.
I suppose you could make
this a lot simpler...
Of course that would mean
telling me where you're
going every night.
[ALINA] It's nothing...
I'm just studying
the eco-systems
of the plankton creatures.
[TATIANA] And when did you
become such an avid biologist?
You could jeopardize
this whole mission.
Do you know what
that would mean?!
This project
could be dropped!
We had a hard enough time
placating the radicals
just so we could
start this dialogue.
Ahlina...
Please stop seeing
the American...
People eventually will
start saying things.
[clock chimes]
[TATIANA] That was
an order by the way.
[FEMALE COMPUTER] Reducing
interstellar drive to zero.
Engaging plasma thrusters.
[LANGE] Have you been
able to make contact
with the colonies yet?
Yes and as expected they're
quite eager for supplies.
I'm sure...
However I do look forward
to the time when they can
finally start bringing
materials back to us.
Most likely, that time
isn't very near.
Are you serious?
A temporary curfew
for all of us?
It's what they said...
and the order's been issued
for the entire colony.
[ION] What the hell for?
It's too bad for
you and your girl...
but it's a military order.
No... It was Beltin.
[MICHAEL] Come on, it's
probably only gonna last
until next week after the talks
with Eurasia are finished.
They're just jumpy with those
U.N. Arbiters coming in.
Next week?
[MICHAEL] Listen to me!
Don't go actin' stupid...
You just need to figure out if
we can settle on this rock...
That's why you're here you know.
[footsteps]
[ION] That bastard
probably wants a war.
Alina...
[beeping]
[ION gasps]
[MICHAEL] Ion, talk to me.
What's going on?
[ION] There's
been an accident.
An unknown fungus
sample is out...
The whole lab's
been compromised.
[MICHAEL] Hold on.
I'm on my way!
[ION] No, stay out, Michael.
We can't be sure how these
spores will react with us.
Lock it down.
[ION whimpers]
[MICHAEL] Ion! What's wrong?
Ion!
[ION screams]
[SNAUT] It's been determined
that this plateau,
commonly known as
the Europa Plateau
is the ideal place for
the new settlement...
There's only one issue...
that's how to deal
with the white fungus
that's grown across
the entire continent.
[LANGE] How interesting.
A fungus that turns everything
it touches white as snow.
[SNAUT] If you look
just beyond that ridge...
...you can see the Eurasian
Union's colony...
On this side is the joint
Euro-American colony.
They've both been occupied now,
for almost four months.
[LANGE] What do you know
about that thing down there
that looks like a balloon?
[SNAUT] I've been told
it's something akin
to an evolved jellyfish.
[LANGE] Ahh... Heh, heh.
[SNAUT] Though normally
they're only found
in the hyperbaric sea.
Commander,
the United Nations reps
are now on station with us.
Be right with them...
Is there anything new to report
with the sealed off laboratory?
[BELTIN] No sir.
We still can't
get a look inside.
[MEYER] At least the spores
have been contained.
[BELTIN] We should be careful
that this doesn't slip out
in front of the UN delegation.
I know.
It's of the utmost importance
that we keep this
matter classified...
We don't need to give the
Eurasians any leverage.
[MEYER] Welcome, Arbiter Lange.
I'm the base CO, Kurt Meyer.
You must be tired
from your journey.
[LANGE] Not at all.
Our voyage was most pleasant.
May I introduce
Arbiter Snaut?
How do you do?
[BELTIN] This starfish looking
creature has coral growing on it
that actually serves
as a protective armor.
Tests show that it's
as hard as ceramic.
Clearing all these little
guys out of the area
was not an easy job.
[BELTIN laughs]
[LANGE gasps]
[BELTIN] Here's where we
store the mineral samples.
If you're looking to
establish a resource colony,
you won't find a planet
better suited than this.
This settlement is one of the
first with the potential to
prove the benefit of
deep space colo--
Mr. Snaut, get away
from that door!
Excuse me...
The fungus we're culturing
in there is highly sensitive.
Colonel Medvedeva, our CO,
and our XO, Major Guerin,
are both here...
but object to negotiating
in English at this time.
So I will be speaking
instead on their behalf.
Developing any colony
takes time and consistency.
With that in mind we present
our five year plan to you.
Our first priority will
be to eliminate the fungi
and other harmful organisms
currently infesting
the Europa Plateau. After that,
we can reclaim the land
for expanded settlement
and food production.
Water supply will
not be a concern.
It is abundant beneath
the bedrock there,
so there will be
plenty for irrigation.
As you know, the water will
have to be purged anyway,
so as not to hinder any
future mining operations.
Our proposal is to drill
seven pumps at various depths
to move the water into the
north sector's marsh area,
creating a suitable reservoir.
This becomes the cornerstone
of our irrigation plan.
We will create several
artificial rivers
leading out from the reservoir.
They will become the
new Volgas and Rheins
on this developing world.
New rivers, huh...?
That's fine...
...if you want borders.
We don't have to put up
with this crap!
For what... This is
obviously just a ploy!
An attempt to skew the division
of land in your favor!
There's still much we have
to learn about this world.
If we carelessly start
making drastic changes,
it could have profound effects
on the local ecosystem.
[whispering]
Ko... koa nova sem.
Water at our colony
is insufficient.
The reserves
cannot sustain us.
The reservoir is
critical for us.
Your concerns are not ours.
Ee baja goja dis
butdojuvus rojuvus seeboo!
If you will not
support our plan...
...then we've no choice.
We will begin terraforming
independently...
...by force if we have to.
Oh is that so...?
How dare you threaten us!
[GUERIN sighs]
[beeping]
Ah. 'Scuse me...
It seems it's time for me
to take my heart medicine.
[LANGE chuckles]
[TATIANA] Hmm...
In any case,
we're here because neither of
your groups has the resources
to develop the entire
planet on your own.
So perhaps we can
take a break...
then we'll hear what
the other colony's ideas are
on the matter, okay?
[SNAUT sighs]
Piccard...
I can not think of
anywhere Ion could be.
[SNAUT] Is it good,
Arbiter Lange?
You enjoy your heart medicine
more than most people.
It's a twenty-one
hundred Bordeaux...
Of course it's good.
[LANGE chuckles]
[SNAUT] They're
fighting over water.
Is this why we started
traveling the stars?
I hate to admit it,
but humans could
start a war anywhere.
It's always the same.
You try to have a
reasonable discussion
but nobody wants to listen.
Things have a way
of working out...
they always do.
[SNAUT] I feel like
people will never change.
It's like we're some
kind of pathogen...
We sickened our host, the earth,
until it could
barely sustain life.
Then we journeyed out into
the galaxy in search of
a new host to whom we
could attach ourselves.
Heh...
Not so different from
spores on the wind...
Wouldn't you agree, sir?
[LANGE] I'm not so sure...
You seem to be
suggesting that we humans
leave some permanent
mark wherever we go.
Pride and youth have you
thinking we matter either way.
Ion was the one who
told you to find me?
I'm sorry I had to wake
you so late for this.
[beep]
Here he is...
Why's he in
there all alone?
[ION] Alina!
I'm so glad you're here.
Ion! You are okay...
I didn't know if I'd ever
get to see you again.
Open the door.
[ION ] I can't.
Why not?
[ION] Alina, listen carefully
and try to stay calm...
In this planet's atmosphere...
there's some sort
of parasitic fungus.
The spores became airborne
and contaminated me.
If you open the door
they'll be able to spread
throughout the whole colony...
including you.
Just hold on...
Is it hurting you?
[ION] It did at first, but the
pain went away pretty quickly.
I've done some
preliminary tests...
and my body appears to
be perfectly healthy.
Then let me in...
The spores aren't having
any effect on you.
[ION] Not yet...
It's too early to be certain.
[ALINA] You can't just
stay locked in there...
...like you're some
kind of lab animal...
[ION] Don't worry
about me, Alina...
[ALINA sobs]
As soon as I can prove
the spores are harmless,
I am getting out of here.
I promise...
Listen to me.
I'm going to be alright.
[MICHAEL] That's long enough...
If the military catches us here,
we'll all be in trouble.
We gotta go.
Let me walk you back, okay?
Come on.
[ION] Try and get
some sleep, okay.
Good night.
Ion...
[MEYER] This is pointless.
We're getting nowhere.
[BELTIN] You know
those Eurasians...
They aren't going change
their position on this.
Then the first move
is left up to us.
Before it's too late
to do anything.
[alarm sounds]
Report. What happened?
[MICHAEL] Someone
compromised the lab door.
The airtight seal
has been breached.
I've raised the colony
quarantine to Level C.
I think you should put on your
environment suit, just in case.
Damn.
[panicked screams]
Now what could
be the problem?
[BELTIN] No,
it's not hostiles...
this was the work
of our "guests."
Gone.
What is that alarm for?
It seems they've been doing work
with alien spores out here.
And now they've broken
free from containment.
[TATIANA] So what
is the outcome...?
Do the spores have
harmful effects on humans?
[GUERIN] I understand they've
already lost one man in the lab.
Ion...
Alina!
Code inbound GKQJ...
Initiate the strike...
Target is the Euro-American
joint colony...
Colony is compromised...
There are fatal
spores throughout.
What are you doing?!
[GUERIN] Don't you understand?
This is our only chance.
We can be rid of them
and do what we need to do.
No, I won't allow it.
I am ordering you to
rescind the strike.
Damn you.
We've wasted enough
time with your diplomacy.
You should go run and
find your daughter.
[TATIANA yells]
Ion!
[BELTIN] Good god in heaven...
[approaching footsteps]
[GUERIN] Strike order
authorized. Confirm.
Target is Euro-American Colony.
[VALE and GUERIN chuckle]
[SERGEI grunts]
What i-- Sergei!
I want a controlled burn
on everything over there.
[BELTIN] Did you
hear me, Michael?
[MICHAEL] But, sir...
[BELTIN] That's an order.
Spores could get out.
Burn the whole section away.
[ALINA] Nobody move!
Alina!
Ion.
[ALINA yells]
[ION stammers]
[BELTIN choking]
[SOLDIERS choke]
[ALINA chokes]
Alina! Alina!
Michael...! Raise the door!
You can see the shield
doesn't work...
Open it, dammit!
[ION] Michael...!
Open the shield!
Do you read me?!
Come in! Michael?
Michael, open the doors!
[ALINA sobs]
[ALINA] It hurts...
It's okay, it'll pass soon...
and when it does...
you're gonna feel better
than you ever have.
[TATIANA] Alina!
[TATIANA groans]
Mother...
The bombers are en route
to this station...
They're going to destroy...
the whole colony!
[BELTIN] Ion...
Launch the interceptor missiles.
Are you serious?
If you don't, everyone in
this colony will be killed.
You're the only one
who can move...
You have to do it.
I'm the only one...
[LANGE groans]
That's no good...
Outta wine... damn.
Ion...
[PILOT A] Approach time to
target, fifteen minutes. Mark.
[FEMALE COMPUTER] Three
Eurasian bombers detected
on heading two, seven, zero.
Ten minutes and closing.
Threat imminent. Be advised.
[FEMALE COMPUTER] Counter
measure window in one minute.
Stand by.
[FEMALE COMPUTER] Window
for counter measure launch
is now open.
[beeping]
Ion...
Forgive me, Alina...
I just couldn't do it...
I couldn't bring
myself to start a war.
[PILOT A] One minute
to target...
Weapons payload at the ready.
[PILOT A] Target
acquired and locked.
Fire!
Piccard!
[ALINA gasps]
Don't! No!
[PILOT A] What the hell?
[PILOT A screams]
Piccard!
[MICHAEL] What we've discovered
is that this fungus feeds on
excretory waste from the skin,
while facilitating the
exchange of CO2 and oxygen
directly through
the bloodstream.
[MEYER] That's fine by me.
I never cared much
for showering.
[MICHAEL] Heh. The increased
O2 in our systems
could definitely account
for how good we all feel.
What's more...
the inhalation of the spores
seems to trigger the pleasure
centers in the cerebrum.
[MEYER] Hmm.
Let's let the past be the past,
shall we Major Beltin?
[BELTIN chuckles]
We've shown the
worst we can do...
I say we take the time to
show the good progress
we're capable of.
I completely agree
with you, Colonel.
I think it's the only
logical thing we can do.
It is just Tanya for you.
It's like snow.
They're spores adrift...
...floating from here to
wherever the wind takes them.
Beautiful.
You're right, they are.
Such a pity...
All those lovely
spores simply die
the moment they leave the
atmosphere of their home world.
Good riddance
to those things.
They were pests...
I couldn't go back like that.
[LANGE] Mr. Snaut...
Yes.
I was wondering...
would you say we left
our mark on that planet?
Or was it reversed...
did that planet leave
its mark on us?