[DAN] The comet
Crommelin, 27P...
First observed by astronomers in
the early nineteenth century...
It cuts a wide elliptical orbit,
around the sun and deep
into our solar system...
A twenty-eight year revolution
through the cosmos.
Its infinite journey last
brought it past Earth
in Two Thousand Sixty-Eight...
And it won't pass again for
another twenty eight years.
An insignificant blink of time
in the span of its existence...
But I doubt my aging eyes
will open wide enough
to see it again.
[COMPUTER] Loading
the firing charge...
Firing.
Transport container...
B-Three-Seven-One...
on standby...
Loading of firing
charge complete.
[RICK] Midnight Bazooka calling
Moon Base Seven Five Five...
Come in, Moon Base.
[MOON BASE] Go ahead,
Midnight Bazooka.
[RICK] Container
B-Three-Seven-One comin' at ya'.
[MOON BASE] Roger that.
[COMPUTER] Seven...
Loading, of firing
charge, complete.
Three... Two... One...
Fire.
[COMPUTER]
Launch successful...
Ventilate firing chamber...
Container B-Three-Seven-One
in flight
and headed for moon orbit.
Course is normal.
[RICK sighs]
An' there she goes,
off to the moon.
[DAN] Rick.
Make sure you send
them confirmation
that the launch was successful.
[RICK] I'm on it...
Come in, Moon Base...
This is Midnight Bazooka.
Well that's
the last of 'em.
[MARK] Chief...?
Didn't they call in a
rush job this morning?
Oh, yeah.
[MARK] Should be
showin' up anytime now.
Right. Go ahead and
prep the catapult
and we'll fire it off
as soon as it gets here.
[RICK] You got it, boss.
Oh, man... I am ready
for some R&amp;R tomorrow!
[MARK chuckles]
[DAN chuckles]
[CREWMAN 2] Hey, chief.
We've got an urgent docking
request from Earth base.
That's kinda' weird.
What ship is it?
[CREWMAN 2] Ship code Zero
Seven Eight Nine Six Two E-K...
The Flying Dutchman.
They need to stop for repairs
before atmospheric reentry.
[RICK] The Flying Dutchman?
Never heard of it.
[MARK] It's practically
a ghost ship...
Resurfaces once
every fifteen years.
[RICK] Oh...
Man, so they were all the way
out in Alpha Centauri, huh?
You think the proton mining
worked out this time?
Man, if it did,
that would be like
the biggest news to
hit Earth in a century!
[RICK] They'd deserve one
hell of a homecoming...
That's for sure.
Chief?
Yeah...
You should go ahead and
start preping a dock.
A ship like that's
gotta be ancient...
You sure we got all
the parts on hand?
We should be fine, but
maybe we shoulda stocked up
on older parts after working
on that French shuttle, huh?
Heh. Yeah, no kiddin'.
[DAN sighs]
Go ahead and get
started on replacing
that main nozzle for me, Willie.
You got it, boss.
[HAYES] I can't believe we're
stuck this close to Earth.
Aw, quit bitchin'.
It's a direct order from HQ.
[MARIA] And they're right about
the condition of the ship.
You in such a big hurry
you'd risk burning up
in the atmosphere?
I'll get started on
the fuel injector.
[MARIA gasps]
So their cargo bay is loaded
with liquid proton, right?
That's level five
classification, so...
how the hell would I know?
[RICK] Hm.
Although, considering that
they were ordered to stop
for these repairs
before reentry...
it's a pretty safe bet.
Man, that crew's gonna be
famous once they get back.
Too bad their captain's the only
one who's got the looks for it.
[RICK laughs]
[MARIA] This is Horn,
the second planet of
the Alpha Centauri system.
It may look like a barren
wasteland, but it's far from it.
We dropped a subterranean
droid in 2020
and realized it's
a treasure trove.
Anyway, we put the
drilling robots to work
on our first voyage...
and we actually didn't finish
building the mining plant
until the second trip.
So this last trip was the
first time we were able to
finally reap the
rewards of our labor.
I thought so...
Nine tons...
That much proton would
provide the earth
with enough power to
last ten years at least.
And it's only
the beginning.
Cheers...
To our reunion.
To your success...
You gave up your life
to pursue this expedition.
It's good to see
that it's paying off.
[MARIA sighs]
Fifteen years...
I'm actually surprised
to see you here.
I didn't think this kind
of life appealed to you.
I feel more at home in space
than I do on Earth these days...
So that's the mining
plant on Horn, is it?
[MARIA] That's right.
How's Tokio doing?
I bet he turned out
even taller than you.
Tokio passed away.
[MARIA gasps]
[DAN] He chose to
become a soldier.
He was killed five years
ago in the African War.
[DAN] Don't even start.
It's too late for you
to act like you care.
You made a decision
a long time ago...
and you chose space over
a life with me and my son.
My wife also died last year.
So once again the
only person I've got...
...is myself.
And now you're officially
caught up on my life.
[MARIA] Dan.
Do you still hate me
for leaving you?
I guess I'm a cruel
woman... Aren't I?
[beeping]
[MARK] Chief...
The shuttle delivering that
last-minute job is on approach.
We need you in the control room.
[DAN] Roger that.
I'm heading up.
[DAN] It's life that's
cruel, not you.
But if you want to feel
responsible for my troubles,
then go ahead... I guess
you still have that right.
[COMPUTER]
Shuttle is approaching.
[RICK] Loading dock open...
Prepare to receive
container B-Four-Oh-Four.
[COMPUTER] Systems, normal.
Loading, normal.
[RICK] Auto-control's set
on the cargo loading arms.
[COMPUTER] Retrieving,
container, B-Four-Oh-Four.
Stand by.
Quit wasting
your breath.
My mind is already made up.
You're sure about this?
[TOKIO] Mm.
[MARK] Chief.
[MARK] Chief?
[DAN] Hm?
Looks like We got that cargo
successfully secured
in the dock.
Good...
Call in the load report to
ground control, got that?
[RICK] Yes, sir.
[DAN] Mark, take watch
over the bridge.
I'll be in my cabin.
Sure thing, chief.
[MARIA sighs]
[MARIA] What the hell
are you doing in here?
[WILLIE laughs]
It's my turn tonight, y'know...
Don't tell me that you forgot.
[WILLIE laughs]
[WILLIE] Ooh!
Hey!
Hey now...
--[MARIA] Go!
--Put that down.
[MARIA]
Get out of here!
Didn't I tell you to
replace the main nozzle?
[WILLIE scoffs and laughs]
[WILLIE] Why do you
think I'm here?
Just shut up...
I don't feel like it tonight!
Aww, why not? Usually--
I'm just not in
the mood tonight!
Not here, okay?
[door opens]
[WILLIE grunts]
[thud]
[WILLIE groans]
[MARIA gasps]
[WILLIE sighs]
Geez... What the hell's
gotten into her?
Hey! Wait a second.
[WILLIE laughs]
Didn't the captain stop by your
quarters a little while ago?
I think I figured out what's
gotten into her after all...
Well?
It's nothing to
be ashamed of...
We all get a little lonesome
in space sometimes...
So it only makes sense that us
little cowboys and cowgirls...
...trade mounts.
[WILLIE groans]
[approaching footsteps]
[WILLIE grunts]
[WILLIE] Come on,
Hayes, get a move on.
I don't want any more shit
from the captain today.
Don't just stand there, moron.
[COMPUTER] Loading
of firing charge...
One hundred percent...
Almost done, and then
we get that sweet day off.
Yeah...
I was startin' to get kinda
worried we were gonna lose it.
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER]
Don't move!
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER] Stay
calm and do exactly as I say.
Now...
...tell me where
your captain is.
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER]
Two through Five,
search the private quarters.
Kill anyone who tries
to get in your way.
[MARK] None of
our men are armed.
What could you hope to get
out of taking over a cargo
station, huh? What do you want?
[laughs]
[rapid knocking at door]
[MARIA] Jesus Christ!
For the last time, no!
[MARIA gasps]
[typing]
What's wrong?
What's going on?
[MARK] What...?!
Are you completely nuts?!
[MARK] You want to load a ton
of proton into a container
and fire it at the moon base?
[MARK] This is insane!
Do you even realize what'll
happen if you do that?
So much for savin'
the world, huh?
Listen to me.
There's more than three hundred
thousand people on that base...
Are you trying to kill them all?
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER] That's
not even close to the lives
we lose from hunger
everyday on my continent.
And despite how many
are starving on Earth,
you send an endless barrage
of supplies to the moon.
We lost the African War
five years ago...
But the real fight
has just begun.
We plan on winning this time.
So you can consider this
our declaration of war.
The remaining proton will
return with us, of course...
It has infinite potential
for military use.
[MARIA] No way in hell...!
Those bastards aren't gonna
use my life's work for this!
We can try to
alert the moon base
to arm their
missile system.
But even if they
can intercept it
from six thousand miles away...
It's likely the blast
from the proton
will completely
decimate the base.
[rapid knocking at door]
[SPACE TERRORIST 8]
Open up! Open the door!
[knocking continues]
[SPACE TERRORIST 8]
Open it! Now, dammit!
[MARIA] Dan...
Grab the emergency suits!
[DAN] Mm.
[SPACE TERRORIST 8] Open up!
[SPACE TERRORIST 9]
Stand back. I'll burn it open.
[alarm sounds]
[SPACE TERRORIST 8]
Wait! Stop...!
That's the pressure warning!
[SPACE TERRORIST 8] Oh, shit!
[SPACE TERRORISTS yell]
[distant explosion]
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER]
What the hell was that?
Number Eight, Number Nine...
Report back. Do you copy?!
Dammit.
Don't let them
out of your sight.
[gunshots]
You're okay!
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER]
Number Eleven...!
Take your team to the dock!
[MARIA] What's wrong with you?!
Did you just completely
remove the main nozzle?!
Yeah and I was just
about to replace it...
...but I took an
unexpected nap instead.
[MARIA] Dammit, Willie...
The ship's boosters
are paralyzed
without the main nozzle.
Which means it's the four
of us against them
and the only weapons we have
are the two lasers we got off
those guys and my hand laser.
Try pointing the deep
space antenna array
at the loading dock.
What for?
So we'll hit them with a burst
of electromagnetic radiation...
Releasing locks!
Fire it up, Willie! Now!
[SPACE TERRORISTS scream]
Hah! Woohoo!
Fried 'em up like a
mouse in a microwave!
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER]
That's as far as you get.
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER] Now...
Before you make
another stupid move,
you should know that the
container we rode in on
is loaded with explosives.
And there's more than enough
to trigger the liquid proton
and destroy this entire station.
And guess what I happen
to be holding...?
The detonator to the explosives.
Ha, ha, ha...
Their ship's engines
are inactive.
We'll cut away the tank
carrying the proton.
Concentrate your fire on
the connecting locks...
Whatever you do,
don't shoot the tank.
Open fire!
Oh, shit...
The valve controls
are severed...
They've almost got it detached!
[MARIA gasps]
What do you think
you're doing?
Don't act like you
don't know. Heh.
I love you...
Both of you.
What are you doing?
We're going out to
release the valves.
I'd rather see all that
proton dumped into space
before I'd let them
get their hands on it.
[MARIA] You're not coming.
We've only got three weapons
and they're armed to the teeth.
You have other loyalties.
Your first responsibility
is to your crew.
You really think you can stop
them with just the three of you?
[beeping]
[MARK] Chief! We overpowered
the guards and got their guns.
What are your orders?
Chief!
[MARK] Chief!
[MARK] Captain,
we need your orders!
Mark, the rush-job
container B-Four-Oh-Four
is loaded with explosives.
I love you... Dan.
Charge the catapult and
get that container loaded...
Launch it ASAP!
[WILLIE grunts]
[WILLIE] Bastards!
If you think you can just
fly in and take our stuff
without an ass kicking,
you've got another thing coming!
[SPACE TERRORIST 3 yells]
[SPACE TERRORIST 4] Ahh!
[SPACE TERRORIST 12 yells]
[HAYES] Ah!
[HAYES grunts]
Hayes!
No...
Maria, just go!
Willie!
Get moving!
[WILLIE screams]
[SPACE TERRORIST 14] Ah!
[WILLIE] Ahhh! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
[SPACE TERRORIST 13 yells]
[WILLIE laughs]
[WILLIE] Ah!
Willie!
Sorry...
Damn you-- [gasps]
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER]
Don't move.
Don't even look at that valve.
Dan! Don't do it!
[MARIA] Baby, no!
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER screams]
[COMPUTER] Loading of
firing charge complete.
Three... Two... One...
Fire.
[SPACE TERRORIST LEADER yells]
[GROUP cheers]
[DAN] Without their
leader to guide them,
the remaining terrorists
simply surrendered.
The majority of
the liquid proton
was safely delivered to Earth.
You know, Dad...
I think I understand
how she must've felt.
Love...?
It shouldn't be something
that holds you back.
He was right.
That's how I felt.
It must be genetic.
[DAN] So... another
fifteen years, huh?
[MARIA] And thirteen
of those years
I'll be asleep in a
hibernation capsule.
[DAN] Which means you'll
only age another two years.
After forty-five years...
I'm still not used to it.
You were right earlier.
You are a cruel woman.
Good luck...
Wait for me, Baby.
Good luck.
[DAN] And once again,
she vanishes into the timeless
vacuum of the deepest cosmos...
Just like a comet following
its long elliptical orbit.
Or like a sudden memory
that fades before
I can clearly see it.
Leaving me alone, once more,
in its nebulous wake.
[DAN] Good luck
to you... Mother.