[MUNAKATA] The overseas
expansion is cancelled?
[BOARD MEMBER A]
Yes.
By order of the
board of directors.
I would assume so.
This is the first I've heard--
[BOARD MEMBER A] I'm afraid
the matter is non-negotiable.
[click]
What?
[MUNAKATA]
Damn it.
Has the enemy infiltrated
upper management?
[door opens]
Learn anything useful?
Something wrong?
No, it's... nothing.
Junko Enoshima... is innocent.
You're absolutely certain?
Yeah. Totally clean.
Crap ton o'
circumstantial evidence,
but she's got an alibi.
Nothing would stick.
Disappointing.
She's been my favorite
suspect from the word go.
We have no one else.
So you regret puttin' me
on the case or what?
Of course not.
If that's your finding,
it's good enough for me.
[JUZO]
Thanks.
Then take my word for it.
She checks out.
[JUZO]
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
Conniving bitch!
Never again!
When this is all over...
she's a dead woman!
Doesn't make sense. Who could
it possibly be if not her?
[door opens]
[MUNAKATA]
Yukizome?
Kyosuke, thank God!
I thought I'd never
see you again!
I'm so sorry. This moment
couldn't come soon enough!
Sorry it took so long.
I was so sure. So sure
you'd gotten killed or--
It's fine. Really.
I'm safe.
Listen, be honest with me.
[YUKIZOME]
Huh?
Is Junko Enoshima innocent?
According to Sakakura,
the evidence is circumstantial.
Would you agree, or not?
Um. Well...
[YUKIZOME] Yeah. That
jibes with what I've got.
She's got nothing to do with it.
What's the matter?
Nothing. It just...
seems I was mistaken.
[YUKIZOME]
Fair warning.
If you want a happy ending,
you'd better look elsewhere.
Just because Hope's
the central character
doesn't guarantee it'll
make it to the final act.
Sorry, kids. Reality doesn't
care one way or the other.
To win, Despair doesn't
have to work that hard.
Ha-ha!
Today, party people, I give you
the death of Hope's Peak High!
[HINATA]
You sound pleased.
And why wouldn't you be?
Your plan's come to fruition.
[ENOSHIMA]
Indeed it has.
This is where it all begins.
Can you hear?
A mighty wind is blowing.
Ready to knock it all down
with despairful Despair?
[YUKIZOME] This class
has been through a lot.
I'm just-- I'm just so proud
to have been your teacher.
This is what it's all about.
Aw, c'mon, Miss,
pull yourself together.
Soda, please.
Try showing some tact.
No, he's right.
We've made it this far.
I can't fall apart on you now.
Today is special, though.
So I've written a letter.
Great. I bet it's lame.
Probably.
But it seemed appropriate
under the circumstances.
I mean, for all intents and
purposes, this is goodbye.
They'll act in the
name of Despair.
It's all but a
forgone conclusion.
Imagine the crème de
la crème going sour,
the world's greatest
talents going rogue.
If this gaggle of geeks
is subject to Despair,
no one is immune.
Once these dominoes fall,
the world will collapse!
They have become me.
My poison proxies waiting
to be unleashed.
Ready to spread Despair like
a virus, infecting everything.
A virus?
Ugh!
It's a very simple
metaphor, dumbass!
I ain't spellin' it out!
No, I get it! We just
haven't had this talk.
Whore. Stop interrupting
my villain monologue.
Why can't you let me create an
atmosphere of unrest in peace
once in a while?
This school is a
sacred beacon of Hope.
A sun from which
all light emanates.
When it goes dark,
everything goes dark.
[HINATA]
Despair in mimetic waves?
Bingo. Everything is a virus.
Fashion trends, taste in movies,
social media hashtags.
Ideals, philosophy,
art, culture,
they live and die by the meme.
An infection.
Exactly!
And your classmates are about to
make Despair the next big thing!
Picture it!
Civilization swept away by
the fad to end all fads!
The world will be
like a playground.
One where everyone's free to
indulge the worst in themselves!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[YUKIZOME]
Bear with me, okay?
"As we come to the fork
in the road, have faith.
As both teacher and alumna
of this fine school,
I see your future."
"There'll be hardships,
yes. And heartbreak.
That's just the way
of things, I'm afraid.
Nevertheless,
I urge you to remember
the lessons learned here.
Don't miss an opportunity
to spread your wings.
The thought of saying
farewell makes us sad,
but remember,
you may not be
my class after today,
but I will always be
your cheerleader."
"Your very proud
homeroom teacher,
Chisa Yukizome."
[YUKIZOME]
Oh, you guys.
We've been incredibly blessed!
I'm so grateful to have
been in this class!
Yeah! I'm gonna
eat until I burst!
I'm gonna shake things up
with some J-rock power ballads!
Good luck with that.
I'm gonna make the
world a better place
with my traditional dance.
I'll take pics.
Smile for the camera!
I'll bring an end to war
and bloodshed!
[TANAKA] All this time,
you were my true friends!
I'll make miracle drugs
to cure the sick!
That's right! Illness will
be a thing of the past!
With Peko, I'm
legitimizing the gang.
No more racketeering
or petty larceny.
I swear to never kill again.
Large scale environmental
reforms for me!
I'll feed the hungry!
No one shall go without
proper nutrition ever again!
I can-I can become
whatever I put my mind to!
If I wanted, I could even
be president one day!
I'm gonna be a spotter for
everyone's life goals and shit!
However seemingly insurmountable
Despair may be,
when all is said and done,
Hope can't help but triumph.
That's how it goes.
Giving over to Despair is
just part of the process.
[cries]
[YUKIZOME]
Yes.
Right then.
Just so we're clear, officially
you'll have all died here
and will be removed from
the school's protection list.
Miss, you don't have
to keep repeating it.
We understand.
Hope's Peak has to
look after its rep
if it expects to survive.
Despairs can't be on the team.
Forgive me.
I've been in the teacher
mindset for so long,
it's hard to shake off.
[YUKIZOME]
Well, then. Goodbye.
Best of luck, kids.
[HINATA]
A woman of your word, I see.
Okay, so, why did I erase
their memories of you?
Strikes me as a long walk
for a short drink o' water.
I will meet them again.
And in the
not-so-distant future.
When that happens,
any knowledge of
a former encounter
will render them predictable,
ergo, boring.
So I'll be deleting my
memories of them as well.
Seriously?
I must know the truth.
Which of them is
less predictable?
Is Hope or Despair the
great undiscovered country?
It's possible that
simple sentiment
will outstrip your
expectations and spare them.
In which case, Hope
is the true wild card.
Despite what you might think,
anarchy may turn out to be
yet another species of order.
Ugh. Yeah, whatevs.
How much more screen-time
are we gonna waste
on me philosophizing at you?
Hope is harmony and the status
quo. Despair is total chaos.
So Despair's where it's at!
I'm talking!
Hey, at least have the
decency to argue your point!
Come on. Hit me with
something outta left field.
Say you love me!
[HINATA]
May we meet again.
Oh, it's a date, big guy!
I wish I could quit you.
You're just too useful.
[KIZAKURA]
Damn.
Scary how it happens
in the blink of an eye.
Everybody but the 78th
class... wiped out.
And what of the atmosphere
beyond campus grounds?
It's bad. Complete
and total disaster.
[NEWSCASTER A]
According to official sources,
the death toll has
climbed to 3,000.
We're told that estimate does
include terrorist casualties...
It all feels so coordinated.
As if... someone's pulling
strings from behind the scenes.
Is that a joke?
You really think some Moriarity
single-handedly
devised all this?
I mean, c'mon.
I don't know.
Either way, it's well beyond
the minds of ordinary folk.
What exactly are you
trying to insinuate?
My apologies.
I was trying to use my
daughter's detective skills.
I'd quite forgotten
your little girl
was a Super High
School-Level Sleuth.
She'd have seen this coming.
If only I'd enlisted her help.
[KIZAKURA] Hindsight,
my friend, is always 20-20.
If it's all the same
to you, gentlemen,
I'd rather focus on the present.
I believe an escape is in order.
Agreed. The two of
you should leave now.
[TENGAN]
Hm?
A principal has a duty.
Someone has to ensure the
survivors are protected.
If that someone's me,
then so be it.
Hope's Peak will
become a safe house.
[TENGAN]
And the students?
[JIN] They've given
unanimous consent.
[TENGAN]
I see.
[JIN] The Hope of this
generation must endure.
If the world's to be given a
second chance, the kids are it.
That's the entire point
of this institution.
Correct me if I'm wrong, sir.
Heh. That's irony for you.
Only after we've been
brought to our knees
does it dawn on us what
we should've stood for.
Carry on as you see fit.
As of this moment, I leave the
school's management to you.
[JIN]
I'll do what I can.
[TENGAN] Protect and nurture
Hope from the inside
for all you're worth, my friend.
I'll do what I can from outside.
And where will you
stand, Kizakura?
[KIZAKURA] Probably best
if I take my chances
on the outside too.
S'not exactly my style
to come between
a father and his daughter.
[chuckles]
Sure gonna miss those scary
looks of yours, though.
[JIN]
Listen.
Do me a favor. If the
Shelter Project goes bust--
Hey, don't you get
morbid on me.
Look, I know what
you're gonna ask.
If it comes down to it,
I promise to protect Kyoko
with my life, okay?
Welp.
I think they've done more
than enough, don't you?
"Way to go. Thank you
for all the hard work."
Send.
[beeping]
[music plays]
Why in God's name
are they doing this?
I don't recommend trying to
get your head around it.
You stare into the
abyss, it stares back.
[ENOSHIMA] Sure,
they were trash, but still,
you don't see this many
people die all at once
without feeling something.
I don't understand why you
couldn't just let them join us.
Say what? Ugh!
Because, pug-ugly, they have
too much in common with you.
They're all stupid.
Even if I could somehow
reprogram their basic IQ,
the overall specs would
be nowhere near mine.
Oh. That makes sense.
Y'know, they say blood's
thicker than water,
but I gotta tell ya, sis,
to me, that sounds like a tip
for keeping my knife clean.
Yeah!
Well, it's time we
were off, I think!
Class is about to start.
Don't wanna be late.
[MUKURO]
Looking good, Junko.
It's all going
according to plan.
A-doy.
'Course, every plan has
a wrinkle, even mine.
Take him, for example.
[NAEGI yelps]
[ENOSHIMA]
Huh?
[MAIZONO]
Are you all right?
[NAEGI]
Ow.
What's goin' on?
Oh, hey, Enoshima.
I'm okay. Just a little
bit of a klutz, maybe.
Yeah, well, no argument here.
Whatever, I'm just
glad you're not hurt,
'specially at a time like this.
[MAIZONO]
You sure you're all right?
[NAEGI]
Totally.
[MAIZONO]
Be careful.
If anything happens, treatment's
not that easy to come by.
Heh. I told you, I'm fine.
Don't worry. I'm sure we'll
only need to hold out for a bit.
Hope so.
[ENOSHIMA]
Makoto Naegi.
The proverbial fly
in the ointment.
[MUKURO] What are you
talking about? He's a loser.
Perhaps, but he has luck.
And not the way
Komaeda does either.
It comes and goes at random.
Very difficult to get a lock on.
So are you gonna kill him?
[ENOSHIMA]
Mmm...
Yeah, no.
Even the thought of that loser
ruining my perfect plan,
now that's the kind
of Despair I live for!
[KOMAEDA]
So, uh. This is it.
I'm not really sure what you're
s'posed to say about all this.
I guess... Happy graduation.
See you 'round.
I'm sure you'll all do great.
Yukizome!
Kyosuke, you're here!
Are you injured?
[YUKIZOME]
My class.
[MUNAKATA]
We were too late. I'm sorry.
[YUKIZOME] Stop it, Kyosuke.
This wasn't your fault. I--
Oh God!
Come on.
[YUKIZOME gasps]
You don't need it?
No. Nothing I can't
get by without.
[YUKIZOME]
"How boring."
Oh, yes.
That's what the long-haired
boy would say, I'm sure.
[YUKIZOME]
Here we are,
living in the vision of Junko
Enoshima's twisted mind.
[YUKIZOME]
My students are out there,
happily sowing
confusion and disorder.
[YUKIZOME]
Hopelessness reigns.
Despair begets Despair.
With their gifts,
it's no surprise.
The whole world is stained.
[YUKIZOME]
And me, you ask?
Well, I'm keeping
house, naturally.
Oh, God!
It's worse than
I ever imagined.
[JUZO] If I'd just
manned-up and told him,
none of this would've happened!
[YUKIZOME] Kyosuke!
We can't let them do this!
All this destruction
has to stop!
[MUNAKATA]
I know.
[YUKIZOME]
Rid the world of Despair.
If anyone can do it, it's you!
[YUKIZOME]
I believe in you...
[YUKIZOME] In your bottomless
capacity for Despair.
[YUKIZOME] Yep. No happy
ending here, boys and girls.
I warned you.
You're wondering if it
has to be this way.
Hmm. Good question.
For Junko Enoshima
and the deranged souls
who worship at her feet,
this is a happy ending of sorts.
Maybe that's the secret.
However the story ends, it's
all a matter of perspective.
[ENOSHIMA] Potential.
That's what it's about, really.
Despair as an adventure
of the spirit!
If it wasn't already a thing,
we'd have to invent it!
[laughing]
[HINATA]
Excuse me.
[NANAMI]
Oh. Sorry.
I'm way too focused on this
thing for my own good.
It's easy for me
to get distracted.
Hey, there. My name's
Chiaki Nanami.
And if you couldn't tell,
I'm the Super High
School-Level Gamer.
To be honest, it's
pretty much all I do.
Oh, it's a pleasure to
meet you, by the way.
[HINATA]
Hello.
My name's Hajime Hinata.
Good to meet you.
What's your thing?
[HINATA]
I have to know.
Hope or Despair?
Which can I not predict?
Which one is freedom?