[HINATA]
"Welcome to Hope's Peak Academy.
A one-of-a-kind campus
for one-of-a-kind talents.
It's a preparatory school
without equal in all of Japan."
[HINATA]
What would that feel like?
To harbor some special skill,
and walk through the gate into
the Academy's main school
'cause I belonged there?
One problem...
I don't excel at anything.
No sports. Or music.
Or cooking.
I'm just... average.
There's no shame in normalcy.
[HINATA]
Either way, I gotta decide.
[NATSUMI]
Hey.
Hey! Dumbass!
[HINATA]
Hm?
That's so weird,
the way you stare at
the Main Course building.
Why do you care what I do?
Bet'cha don't have
any friends here.
Guess we're alike
in that regard.
Honestly, your people
skills could use some work.
I don't know why they tossed
me into this classroom
with the rest of you
dead-end trash-fires,
but nice to meet'cha.
And I meant every word of it!
I'm a Super High
School-Level Little Sister,
and this place is Loserville!
Huh?
You've totally heard of us.
The chivalrous organization
with over 30,000 members,
the Kuzuryu-gumi.
Wait, you mean,
like the yakuza?
Uh-huh!
My dad's the one who's
calling all the shots.
But someday it's gonna
fall to my big brother.
The Super High School-Level
Gangster himself.
That's a talent?
And since big bro is
such a talented guy,
that means I've gotta be a Super
High School-Level Little Sister.
Go on. You can tell
me how right I am now.
But you're here in the
Reserve Course like us.
You'd be over with the
others if you were elite.
Just because they
haven't let me in
doesn't mean they're
never gonna!
Some of us haven't given
up on the future yet.
What the hell?
I'm not giving up.
--[STUDENT A] Check it out...
--Useless meatheads,
every one of 'em.
I'm getting into
that Main Course
and I don't care
who I gotta step on.
What if one of those guys
dropped out of the program
then there'd be
an open slot, huh?
There's a certain
freckle-faced bitch
who comes to mind right away.
Natsumi, I'm onto you.
Whatever crap you're planning,
just leave it alone.
Hey, Sato, long time,
no see. Small world, huh?
You weren't eavesdropping
on me, were ya?
Save the smile for
someone who buys it.
You're up to something.
I can see it in your eyes.
Wow. Paranoid much, Sato?
You two know each other?
[NATSUMI]
More or less.
She was in the Photography Club
at my last school, 's all.
[SATO]
I don't care who your family is.
If you hurt her,
I am gonna make you pay!
[NATSUMI] Don't you get in
my face and threaten me
like I'm some basic bitch!
[SATO] Leave Mahiru alone,
and we don't have a problem!
I'm sorry, I need
to get back there!
What are you gonna do?
Sic one of your yakuza
flunkies on me?
Please, Sato! Don't do this!
[growls]
Mahiru.
[NATSUMI] Well, well, we
were just talking about you.
I can't imagine why an
elite from the Main Course
would come down here.
I told Sato that we--
Wait, lemme guess!
You wanted to go slumming it
so you could mock these
talentless meat-sacks.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[chuckles]
Hey, come on! Enough already!
Ha!
[laughing]
Jeez, I'm pulling your leg!
Yeah, well, you'd better be!
Your brother's in the
same class as Mahiru!
[NATSUMI]
That ain't gonna save you.
Snitches get stitches.
Or they end up with
toe-tags. Catch my drift?
You haven't changed at all.
Oh, get off your high horse,
you simpering dishrag.
You're the same goody-goody
little twit you were
back in Photography Club!
You wanna get into
the Main Course so bad,
you don't care who you hurt!
How stupid are you?
The Main Course didn't
offer you a spot
because you're not special!
Get that through
your head already!
Stop acting like such a bitch!
You're no better
than anyone else!
--What did you call me?!
--No! Sato! Please just drop it!
[KOIZUMI]
Come on.
You shouldn't have
talked to her like that.
I know, but it felt really
good to take her down a peg.
Her aside, everyone from
the Photography Club
is rooting for you.
[KOIZUMI]
You say that, but...
The pictures I take
are just of whatever.
Doesn't matter. I believe
in you with all my heart.
Someday the world's gonna see
all the beauty you
bring into it.
[KOIZUMI gasps]
So, uh, I hope you like
what I whipped up
for our lunches today!
Hamburger steak for two!
[SATO chuckles]
Yeah, I love it.
[KOIZUMI laughs]
You haven't even tried
it yet, silly!
[MIODA] Dude, how did you
summon all these rabbits?
They're, like, cute and metal!
[PEKOYAMA] Wait, she's here?
In the Reserve Course?
[KUZURYU]
Yeah.
She wanted to be at
the same school as me,
so the old man cut a check.
Will it be all right?
My sister's been crazy since
the day they brought her home.
No tellin' what she
might try to pull.
Shall I bring you
some answers?
Stop bein' a dumb ass.
How many times do
I gotta say it? Jeez!
The gang retired you, Pekoyama.
Wh-- But still.
I brought it up
so I could tell you
not to do anything crazy
and half-cocked,
like every other damn time.
Uh! What?!
Well ain't this a sight!
I've never seen you
two talkin' before,
and here you are
doing it all secret like!
[KUZURYU growls]
[MIODA] Go ahead, you guys!
Just act like I'm not even here!
[KUZURYU] I'm outta here.
You two have fun.
You destroyed me, again.
You really are the Super
High School-Level Gamer.
Your focus was all over the
place. That's why you lost.
Did something happen today?
[HINATA]
Hey, Nanami,
if you, like,
sucked at video games,
would you still
bother to play 'em?
I wanna know how
bad I would be.
[HINATA]
Like if you always lost,
no matter how much
you played one.
Or the puzzles
never made sense.
I wonder if they'd still be fun
for you, if that were the case.
[NANAMI]
Hmm...
Even if I were horrible,
I think I'd love them.
That's how great they are.
But what if somebody else were
the Super High School-Level
Gamer and every time
they left your
score in the dust?
[NANAMI] There's more to
life than just talent.
Huh?
Miss Yukizome likes to tell us
stuff like that all the time.
She says, "Talent is
never a guarantee
of an interesting life."
Making memories with other
people leads to hope.
And hope is way more important
than ability in the long run.
The time we spend together
playing all these games,
I like it.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah! This is great fun!
In that case, let's keep going.
Huh? My thumbs are toast.
Can't we switch it up
for a little bit?
No way.
You're finally ready
for the world of co-op.
Yes, ma'am. Ready!
[HINATA] Even without
talent, there is hope.
Maybe things are
startin' to look up.
[SATO] Whatever you're
gonna spring on Mahiru,
forget about it!
Huh? Jeez, not this crap again.
How delusional are you?
All the scheming in the world
isn't gonna change anything,
so just give it up!
It doesn't matter that
your dad's a big shot!
He can't just buy you a talent.
But even if he could, Mahiru
would always be better than you!
Get bent!
You're just a lovesick hack who
trails after her all the time.
Like toilet paper on a shoe!
[SATO]
You bi--!
[HINATA]
Sato, no!
You just signed your
death warrant.
Natsumi!
Wait, hold on!
[SATO]
I always knew she was evil.
Mahiru, I swear I'll protect
you from that demon.
On my life, I promise.
No matter what.
[HINATA]
Natsumi!
Now what?
I know you and Sato
don't get along, but still.
You can't threaten
people like that.
What do you care?
You're just some rando
from the Reserve Course.
I can do whatever
I damn-well please.
They're not gonna scout you.
In fact, once they
catch wind of this,
they'll probably kick you out!
[NATSUMI]
Shut up already!
You don't know a thing!
I'm getting that
transfer no matter what.
I've got talent. I know I do!
Why does this matter to you?
Why's the Main
Course so important?
My brother's the Super
High School-Level Gangster.
If I'm not a Super High
School-Level Little Sister,
I'm left behind.
Not on my watch. Screw that!
[NANAMI] There's more
to life than just talent.
I get it.
Feeling like you're left behind
must be the worst thing ever.
But I-- I don't think you
have to be a top student.
Or an elite.
What does that even mean?
In this world, you either make
the cut or you don't. The end.
You love your big
brother, don't you?
Talent isn't even a factor.
Just stay with him and
make memories together.
My brother deserves
the very best,
and that includes all of
the people around him!
[gasps]
I want him to be proud of me.
Not looking down from above.
I wanna stand by his side.
As soon as I'm a Super High
School-Level Little Sister...
...I can be with him
again, no problem.
[HINATA]
"They deserve the very best.
Including the people
around them."
Why're the police here?
Some kid got murdered, I think.
[HINATA]
Huh?
[STUDENT A] Oh, yeah. We got
a straight up homicide here.
That new girl, supposedly.
Natsumi, or something like that.
[KOIZUMI]
Tell me the truth, Sato!
Please. What happened yesterday?
No. You couldn't have--
[SATO] I wanted... I wanted to
watch the life leave her eyes.
How could I just sit and wait
for her to spring
her trap on you?
She would've!
Look, if she hadn't died,
she would've killed you!
You remember this scar, right?
Remember in middle school
when the two of you
got into an argument
and I jumped in to stop it?
Later that same night,
someone did this.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
No, there's nothing
to apologize for!
Really! I don't blame
you for asking me!
You didn't kill her, then?
Honestly, I couldn't hurt a fly.
I said those things
to scare her off.
You do believe me, don't you?
Yeah. I believe you.
[KOIZUMI] Okay. I should
probably be going.
See ya.
[HINATA]
Sato.
What exactly were the
two of you talking about?
She's dead. And people
saw her threaten you.
Look, I didn't murder her!
Is that what you want me to say?
[HINATA] So where'd you go after
she stormed off yesterday, huh?
She was yakuza! Of course
she was gonna die young!
Or maybe she offed herself.
Ever think of that?
Maybe she couldn't
face another day
of being a talentless
harpy and gave up.
Suicide. Had to've been.
[HINATA] Natsumi hadn't
given up on anything!
Talented or not, she still
had hope for the future!
Hope that--
[SATO]
You're wrong.
You're wrong. You're wrong! No!
[SATO screams]
[TEACHER A]
All right.
Let's dedicate our
efforts to Kuzuryu,
who was taken from
us far too soon.
[STUDENT B]
Excuse me, but where's Sato?
[TEACHER A] Uh, I couldn't
tell you. Late, perhaps.
[HINATA]
Sato never did show up.
Not that day, or the next,
or the one after that.
Then, on the fourth day,
they finally found Sato's body.
[GUARD A] Freeze, kid!
That's a Reserve Course uniform!
The hell do you
think you're going?
I won't be long.
I need to ask Koizumi in
the Main Course a question.
[GUARD A]
No way!
But--
[GUARD A] No buts about it.
You know the rules.
Hey!
Look, I need to get in th-- Ah!
[JUZO] Rules don't apply
to you, is that it?
I... know you.
Then you know I'm in charge of
security for all of Hope's Peak.
I'll let it go, just this once.
Now get the hell outta here.
[HINATA]
Hold on!
I wanna know the truth!
Not the version they're
feeding us in class!
What happened?
Please, just tell me!
You want the truth, do ya?
In that case,
hold onto your ass.
Miss Kuzuryu was killed
by an unknown intruder
on school grounds.
And Miss Sato died from the
shock of losing a classmate.
Wish I had more to
tell you, but I don't.
[HINATA]
Don't lie to me!
You're just trying to sweep
the killings under the rug
to save your
precious academy!
There's a waiting list
for the Reserve Course.
Everyone wants a spot.
Their desks'll be filled before
their bodies have gotten cold.
What did you just say?
You bastard!
Only skill you kids
bring to the table
is getting Daddy
to cut a big check.
Useless in life,
and a hassle in death.
You bring down the
whole place either way.
Pitiful. Tch.
So what if they weren't one of
your precious elite students?
Our lives are all
worth the same!
[grunts]
[JUZO]
No. They're really not.
Grow up, kid.
You can't make diamonds
outta empty beer bottles.
Why don't you run
along and play?
Go crawling back to
your dead end buddies.
Go delude yourselves into
thinking you're someone.
Go on.
I can read you like a book.
Hung out with an elite,
and now you're all uppity.
Not gonna lie. S'what I hate
about you normals the most.
Get a little attention
from your betters,
and you cling on
to 'em like a leech.
[HINATA]
You're wrong. Can't you see?
What?
There's more to life
than just being talented.
I think you're onto something.
You're so right.
For a drone such as yourself,
there's all sorts of
things you can focus on.
Like toiling for the
sake of your masters.
Turn off your brain
and fit into your slot.
Anything more is futile.
Be a good little dog and take
to the collar and leash already.
We'll be sure to throw
you the occasional bone.
[HINATA yells]
I'm gonna send you
to the hospital,
you ballsy little punk!
[YUKIZOME]
Knock it off.
Yukizome.
Hinata. Are you okay?
[YUKIZOME]
You're bleeding.
We're staff now,
but I hope you haven't forgotten
what we came back here to do.
Munakata's orders
were very clear.
Investigate the dark
side of Hope's Peak.
There's no point in sticking up
for Reserve Course
burnouts along the way.
I've been investigating.
Don't forget who
you're talking to.
Also don't think I'm gonna
let you beat up a student!
That's inexcusable,
mission or not!
Ugh. Copy that.
I don't remember you
tilting at windmills
back when we were the students.
[growls]
[sighs]
I think Munakata hit the
nail on the head though
when he said the academy
has a sickness.
They're trying to sweep
the whole Kuzuryu incident
under the rug and it's working.
The other teachers have gone
into damage control mode, too.
I've been told to downplay it
to the kids when it comes up.
God, it pisses me off.
Instead of stepping
up in a crisis,
they're just covering
their asses.
Why were you so
brutal with Hinata
if you agree with him?
If he comes anywhere
close to the truth,
he'll be the one on
a slab in the morgue.
I can't argue with that logic.
But you can probably
save his life
without threatening to maim him.
Yeah, yeah. I'll play nice.
You know, it's hard to believe
how bad things have actually
gotten around Hope's Peak.
And Munakata...
is the school's one hope.
You're right. Its fate
is in his hands.
Huh?
[JUZO]
If you think you
can steal him away,
you, Mister Boxer, have
another thing coming!
Just 'cause I think he's
the school's salvation
doesn't mean I'm
gunnin' for a piece.
I should be getting back.
Hey.
[YUKIZOME]
Hm?
You were like a real teacher,
defending that boy
the way you did.
[gasps]
Hey, Hinata!
Look! I picked up a new
game for us to play.
I can't. It's just, I have
to go somewhere today.
Sorry. It's really important,
and I can't miss it.
Okay.
[NANAMI]
Hinata, wait!
Yeah? What's up?
I...
Nothing.
It was nothing.
[HINATA]
Nanami.
Are you making
memories at Hope's Peak?
Uh... I think so. Why?
I want you to make a
bunch of them for me.
There's way more to you
than just a Super High
School-Level Gamer.
Your character stats
are off the charts.
Well, then. See ya later.
Yeah! See ya tomorrow!
[HINATA]
Nanami.
When I saw you,
I wanted to be able to say,
"Hey, I have a talent. Look at
this crazy thing I can do."
I'm empty though.
I can't do anything.
But you can take something
empty... and fill it.
[JIN]
Gentlemen.
The subject has decided
to undergo the procedure.
I'm not a fan.
Ain't nothing good gonna come
of cooking up artificial talent.
Agreed. But what can
we do about it now?
[TRUSTEE A] Finally.
You've come to a decision, boy.
[HINATA]
Yes, I've made my choice.
I'll be their Hope.