[HINATA]
Miss Yukizome. You'd be proud.
I've worked out
what's important.
She was absolutely right.
In and of itself,
talent doesn't matter.
Because that was never the aim.
Still, I can live with
myself as I am.
Yes, I've used my power
for terrible things.
But by that same power,
I did bring everyone back.
So, it evens it out. A little.
You can wait for a miracle,
or you can make one.
So, you guys, are okay then?
Sha. Yeah, o'course!
Though Togster got
the worst of it.
[HAGAKURE chuckles]
I'll thank you to keep
your mouth shut.
[ASAHINA]
Where's Naegi?
He'll be fine. I provided
him an armed escort.
[SOLDIERS scream]
Good to be back.
You're kidding me!
No, sir! Enemy forces
are dwindling!
We got some unexpected back-up!
What'd he say?
It must be the 77th Class.
What?
[TOGAMI]
They came to our aid
when we were trapped
beneath the rubble
of Foundation Headquarters.
And evidently, Izuru
Kamukura is leading them.
Seems he's
single-handedly restored
our former upperclassmen
to the side of Hope.
You mock me, Remnant.
What is the meaning of this?
Overdue atonement.
[KUZURYU]
Y'know, I gotta say.
The bamboo suits you
better than a real sword.
Yes. I've noticed.
[TANAKA] When the seal upon
my true name is broken,
the rising sun will scorch
the multiverse to ash!
Prepare thyself!
It shall be the last
thing you hear!
The dread hour is upon us!
Heed well, ye hapless mortal,
for my name is Tanaka Gundham!
Shiver and sleep.
[NIDAI yelling]
Alrighty, then!
Full power it is!
[NIDAI]
Huh? What the--?
And Minimaru Troops, go!
[SODA]
Was that cool, or was that cool?
Did you see?
[SODA] Dang it, Sonia.
You're supposed to watch.
[SONIA]
Outstanding work.
Huh? Did you just say?
[OWARI]
Hanamura! Meat! Now!
Order up!
Yeah! Hey, it's Justin Bieber!
Ahh...
[OWARI]
Just how I like it!
Okay. If someone could
save me, please!
[yelps]
[WOMAN chuckles]
--[thud]
--[gasps]
I came as fast as I could!
Did she get you?
Way to take your
time, Pukey Pig.
[TSUMIKI whimpers]
Whatever. Thanks, I guess.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[singing]
[screams]
Rock 'n roll!
[HINATA]
Step aside.
Not long now.
[explosion]
[MITARAI]
What the--?!
[HINATA]
Hey. Mitarai.
[MITARAI]
Izuru Kamukura.
You're too late, so back off!
Hope will win if I have
to die protecting it!
The whole world is
only moments away
from never knowing
Despair again!
Sounds dull.
So that's the end
of feeling, then?
Hope is all anyone
will ever know?
Hope in place of, say,
grief over losing a loved one?
[MITARAI]
Ugh.
I don't expect a man
like you to understand!
Human beings are weak!
[footsteps]
Maybe we really
aren't that strong.
I have my share of regret.
That's something we
all have in common.
[MITARAI]
Yeah. I imagine we do.
I enabled Junko Enoshima
to do what she did!
Because of me...
...countless peopled died.
Even as we speak...
...I sow death!
[MITARAI] If not for me,
you'd have known peace.
The years you spent in school
would've been the
happiest of your life!
But no. I was a
coward and ran away.
So all of this is on my head!
If that's what you wanna
believe, go right ahead.
[HINATA] At least now we
know why you're doing this.
You'd rather the past be
forgotten. Wipe the slate clean.
I get it.
Stand your ground.
That's the idea. That's what
all of this is about.
If it hadn't been for me,
Junko Enoshima...
would never have turned you!
I'd erase the past if I could,
but it's not in my power.
[HINATA]
Some things...
Some things have
to be remembered.
Nanami was real.
I can't pretend like
she never existed.
We have her to thank
for still being alive.
Every day we survive's a gift.
One we can use to
undo all this shit.
[TANAKA] Do you not see?
Atonement is our destiny.
[MITARAI]
Not mine, not by a long shot.
Look at me!
Look at what I've done!
I'm beyond forgiveness!
As are each of us,
but forgiveness is not
what we're seeking.
Ya got that right!
I don't understand.
What--? What am I
supposed to do now?
[IMPOSTER]
Yes. You were wrong.
But then, so were we.
You made mistakes.
We made mistakes.
[MITARAI]
No. Don't do that.
Don't try to lump us together.
I'm alone.
The blame belongs
squarely on me!
Fine then. All the more
reason to join us.
Are you serious?
There's no need for you
to be alone. Not now.
He's right.
We'd be happy to have you!
The more the merrier,
don't you think?
Yeah, come join our team!
No pressure. Do what you want.
Those who join the path find
the Lord of War quite loyal.
[laughing]
Oh, man! I like that one!
Definitely among his
better non-sequiturs.
Quit sulking and get onboard.
I agree. Come with us.
My wiener thinks you'd
make a fine addition!
Ugh! Don't be gross!
Um, is it wrong if what
he said makes me happy?
[KOIZUMI]
Li'l bit, yeah!
I've always admired that
shining talent of yours.
Our team could
use a guy like you.
Thank you, but I don't have
the right to be part of a team.
Being our classmate's got
nothing to do with your rights.
No kidding, dude.
He's the in Reserve Course.
Hey.
You want me to be...?
You're sure?
Well, come on. Classmate.
[MITARAI crying]
[crying continues]
[footsteps]
[TSUMIKI]
Um, excuse me, Naegi?
Uh... I, uh-- Ah!
Wow! It's a real honor!
Forgive me, sir.
We-We share the
same good luck.
No, wait, that's not right.
Yours far outstrips mine.
Though I'm quite lucky
to have you as a colleague.
Sorry! Upperclassman, sir.
[OWARI]
Come on, time to go.
Okay, Nagito, hold it together!
Is it just me or is he
getting creepier with age?
[KOMAEDA]
Hope we meet again.
[chuckles]
--[ASAHINA] Naegi!
--[HAGAKURE] Naegster, hey!
How're your injuries? Better?
Typically what I
would ask, but okay.
[NAEGI chuckles]
What's that?
The 77th Class is broadcasting a
video to the Future Foundation.
[HINATA] Hope you got a kick
out of our little game.
You understand now, we assume.
The Future Foundation is boring.
You want your happy endings,
your perfect, ideal world.
Your heroes saved
at the last minute
by some deus ex machina.
Where's the fun in that?
Good thing we're here.
If we had a mission statement,
it'd be to make life
more interesting.
Let's face it. This world
may need a little Despair.
Ugh. Sounds like Junko.
They were the bad
guys all along?!
So, why'd they save us?!
Man, my brain hurts!
I don't know what's
more offensive,
your voice or your breath.
[TOGAMI]
Well, people now believe
the Remnants of
Despair were behind
the Future Foundation's
Mutual Killing Game.
No one ever need be troubled
with the knowledge
that our late Chairman
was responsible.
By and large a positive thing.
They did this for us?
Wow. That was nice of them.
Yes. Well done, Naegi.
[NAEGI]
Mh-hm.
Thank you, but I
didn't do anything.
In the end, those guys
were the heroes.
You sound as though heroes
are made in a vacuum.
I don't expect our friends
would've gotten far
without Hope.
And Hope is contagious.
Is it not?
Even when the cost is dear.
[IMPOSTER]
You look emaciated.
Are you eating enough?
[MITARAI chuckles]
There are only two
certainties in this life.
Yeah, carbs and high
fructose corn syrup!
Less talk, more stuff face!
[MITARAI]
H-Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
[chuckles]
Full disclosure?
Sure, I don't see why not.
That day, when you entered
the New World Program,
a cutting edge AI was created to
sort of keep an eye on everyone.
Codename: Nanami.
First, they mined
your hippocampus,
compiled memories of
esteemed authority figures.
The idea was to
fuse those memories
into a single personality
you could all trust.
Imagine the surprise
when it turned out
they didn't have to bother.
One memory overrode the rest.
It was the same for all of you.
Strange, yes, but
undeniably sweet.
There was one person you'd all
give anything to see again.
Of course, I'm not
a prefect replica.
But you know what they say.
If someone lives in our memory,
they're never truly gone.
What do you think?
Is this the miracle worth
believing in Hope for?
I don't know.
It's a happy ending
at least. So there's that.
Let's chalk it down as a win.
Thank you. For, uh...
Well, you know.
Not letting me die in vain.
So? Shall we?
The future calls. There's still
a lot of work to be done.
[KOMAEDA]
Hinata!
Better move if you expect
there to be any food left.
[HINATA chuckles]
I'm comin'.
Bye! Thank you again, guys!
Bon voyage!
[MUNAKATA]
This is your time, Makoto Naegi.
[NAEGI]
Munakata.
The burden of being the
hero now belongs to you.
You'll forever be the man
who fought the Remnants and won.
That is the Hope
the world needs.
I'll be that Hope.
Can you bear the weight?
Yeah. I think carrying
that is the least I can do.
Heh. The Remnants have their
bag of rocks, I have mine.
That's all well and good,
but what will you do with it?
I'm not sure.
Guess we'll see.
Best of luck.
[NAEGI]
Where are you going?
[MUNAKATA]
I have my own cross to bear.
[NAEGI] Hard as we try,
none of us can see the future.
The horizon we walk toward
is always obscured.
The future's always hazy.
Hope and Despair mingle.
We can't always tell
which is which.
It's strange.
Sometimes terrifying.
Still though, if all
you do is sit and wait,
nothing happens.
The trick is to take it
one step at a time.
See, you don't have to know
the future to move forward.
Just walk with your memories.
Look up at the sky,
and say to yourself,
"There's always Hope
for tomorrow."
[NAEGI]
Kyoko...
[KOIZUMI]
Hm?
Hey, what'cha got there?
Nothing much.
Just a drug that
delays the poison
those awful bangles were using.
Let me see that.
Wait a second. This is
Kimura's handiwork.
How about that? She was
much stronger than I knew.
Even in the middle of all that
death, she concocted Hope.
So it works kind of
like an antidote then.
Break your Forbidden Action
and you could still live?
Well, it puts you in a coma
until you can get help.
I took the liberty of reviving
someone who used it.
So they should be up
and about in no time.
[ASAHINA]
That oughta do it.
[KOMARU]
Thirsty, Touko?
Here.
Uh. Yeah, thank you.
[KOMARU]
Some for you, too, 'Hina?
Aw, you're so sweet!
'Scuse me, Mr. Principal.
They're waiting for you.
Thank you. I'll be right there.