[YUKIZOME]
Aw, bummer. Guess I died.
Had a good run though.
Saw a lot of important
moments go down first-hand.
Like the maid in
some murder mystery.
And, of course,
I was there for the
Biggest, Most Atrocious,
Despair-Inducing Incident
in Human History too.
Before the Super High
School-Level Despairs
sent this world to hell...
...they were just my students.
All of our lives, fated to
intersect at Hope's Peak High.
[YUKIZOME]
This is it.
The lead-in to that moment
when it all went bad.
The lead-in to the
Tragedy of Hope's Peak.
What begins as a tale of Hope...
...ends in utter Despair.
[YUKIZOME] Bet you're
wondering how it gets there.
Hmm.
Guess we'll find out!
[JIN]
Miss Yukizome.
You will serve as assistant
homeroom teacher
to the first group
of our 77th class.
Great! I'll give it
all I've got!
I know you just
recently graduated,
but I'm counting on you.
Good luck.
[KIZAKURA burps]
[grumbles]
[JIN]
Mr. Kizakura.
Uh. Yeah! Ready, boss.
Just nursing a bit
of a hangover.
[JIN]
Anyway, in all truth,
I wouldn't expect too much
assistance from that quarter.
Treat 'em like they're
your own class.
Whatever you do is fine.
Aye-aye!
Yukizome's on the ca--!
[YUKIZOME coughing]
[KIZAKURA] Let's just get
ya to the door, yeah?
Don't worry! I'm okay!
Yeah.
Same ol' spitfire she was back
when she was enrolled here.
Indeed.
More to the point, though.
I hear it was Munakata's pull
that got her hired on
in the first place.
Basically.
He insisted we take her on
if we were shorthanded.
For a young guy,
he's not wasting any time
shoring up his support.
Careful, boss. He's
got an eye on the big desk.
[JIN]
Duly noted.
Good morning, everyone!
Wait. There's only four of you?
Good morning to you, ma'am.
[KUZURYU]
Hmph.
What's this about?
Some stranger just came
waltzing into our classroom.
I'm sorry, can we help
you with something?
As of today, I'm your
new homeroom teacher!
Chisa Yukizome.
Isn't that great?
[SAIONJI] Ooh, this one looks
like she'll be fun to break.
Whad'ya think will go first?
Her social life,
her health, or her sanity?
Do your worst, kiddo!
I doubled down on
health insurance
before I took this job!
Thou art nothing
if not formidable!
That isn't really how we talk.
What the hell kinda
bait-and-switch
are you pullin' here?
Kizakura's our homeroom teacher!
He's nursing a bad hangover.
Bet he's barfing as we speak.
[KUZURYU]
Friggin' lush.
Sorry I'm late for
class! I fell down!
[yelps]
Aww!
Not again! Why does
gravity hate me?
No one can be as
klutzy as this!
Every single morning,
you end up on the floor!
[TSUMIKI]
Forgive me, Saionji.
You'll be okay.
Are the others late too?
Truth be told,
this may be all you get.
Really? What are your
classmates so busy doing?
I dunno. It's not like
I care either way.
Not to sound flip,
but at the Academy,
no one really cares
if you miss classes.
So long as you hone your skills,
and pass the exams, you're fine.
I was trying to go to class,
but I fell down.
Stop bein' such a suck-up!
[TSUMIKI]
I'm sorry!
[YUKIZOME]
What a mess.
This class is gonna need
some serious elbow-grease.
[YUKIZOME]
I guess this is your lucky day!
'Kay...
Wait, so you're an alumni?
[YUKIZOME] You're only young
once, you guys. Trust me!
You'll be adults
before you know it!
How can you just blow
off your classmates
like they don't even matter?
You know what you are?
You're a bag of rotten oranges!
[KUZURYU, SAIONJI gasp]
[TSUMIKI yelps]
Rotten what now?
Oranges! Big fat rotten ones!
All moldy and sticky
and squishy!
[TSUMIKI]
Ah! I'm sorry. I'm squishy!
[SAIONJI] What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about redeeming
your high school years!
Let's get out there and
find your rotten friends!
We're taking back your
youth right the heck now!
Even rotten oranges can
make a damn fine marmalade
if you have enough of 'em!
[KOIZUMI] Uh. I don't think
that's how marmalade works.
[KOIZUMI yelps]
I couldn't agree with you more!
This is precisely the sort
of camaraderie I longed for
when I transferred here,
Miss Yukizome!
[YUKIZOME]
Come with me, dear child!
It's time to fill these desks!
'Kay!
Count me out!
No one ever said
I had to be friends
with you sons-of-bitches!
Uh.
Look at you. Big woman
with a blade, is that it?
If it'll fix that attitude,
I don't mind engaging in
some remedial subtraction.
[KUZURYU] Can it, Teach.
You don't got the stones.
Chop!
I was wrong! You got the
biggest pair in the room!
Ain't it sweet? I think we
understand each other.
Huh. Crystal clear, in fact.
Lead the way, ma'am.
[YUKIZOME]
Onward! To glory!
The other rotten oranges await!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
Oh, wow!
I'm in an actual
Japanese men's room!
Yeah, that's great.
But why'd we take a
field-trip to the can?
Aww. And I was so sure
he'd be here, too.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Could be worse.
[BOTH gasp]
You guys... feel that just now?
Hey, whatever it is,
it's definitely gettin' closer!
[YUKIZOME]
Oh, God! Jurassic Park !
Whatever. It's just the pipes.
[BOTH scream]
[NIDAI]
More like Jurassic Shit!
Is everyone okay back there?
Yes!
Damn, it's like a bomb went off!
[NIDAI laughing]
[NIDAI]
Sorry, all.
Had a bit of a log-jam today,
if you know what I'm saying!
[YUKIZOME] Wow, more damage
than normal, Nidai.
[NIDAI]
Yeah, that's my bad.
When you gotta go,
you gotta go! Nature calls!
[KUZURYU]
You didn't hafta answer the call
with a damn megaphone!
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
[YUKIZOME]
All right! Next on the menu!
May I please speak to the chef?
[HANAMURA]
Coming!
Yes, my delectable
hors d'oeuvre?
If I can tame your hunger,
say the word!
Well, I wouldn't mind
some sort of a meat dish.
"Meat," you say?
Do you prefer it tender,
or would you like it hard?
Rock hard, like granite!
Hot and hard and thick!
Tied up? Like a trussed pig?
Even Super High-School Level
students can't just say
whatever springs to mind.
We'll work on that.
[HANAMURA]
And she's wearing an apron!
Ye gods, yes! Keep pulling!
--[NIDAI] Hey!
--Oh! You're quite the specimen!
[HANAMURA laughs]
I can work with this!
Just give it a yank!
[NIDAI] I'm not doing this
to get your rocks off!
[ALL]
Yeah... Same ol' Hanamura.
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
[YUKIZOME] Look alive!
We've got a slippery one.
[OWARI]
Aw, hell yeah!
Nailed it!
[laughing]
[OWARI]
Upsie-daisy, and...
Alley-oop!
Yes!
[sighs]
[OWARI] The breeze up
here feels great today!
I know that smell.
Meat! Glorious meat!
Ah! I think she took the bait!
Go, Nidai! Hit it!
[NIDAI yelling]
[KIZAKURA chuckles]
[KIZAKURA] The building's
shaking more than usual today.
Another classmate
brought back to the fold!
Hey! I'm gonna kick
your asses so hard!
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
My angel has arrived!
What a surprise!
Did you bring me a snack?
Oh, uh, does the oil smell bad?
I don't think it's the oil.
[SODA]
Wait, then is it me?
Aw, man! It is me, huh?
[YUKIZOME] Still plenty of fish
in the sea, my dear boy.
I ain't throwing
in the towel yet!
Who the hell're you?
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
[YUKIZOME]
Hello!
Hey, Tanaka!
We know you're up th--
[ALL scream]
[TANAKA laughing]
[TANAKA] Speak the name of
evil, and it shall appear.
You gaze upon Tanaka
the Forbidden One.
My Four Dark Devas
of Destruction
serve me at every turn!
Mark my words!
One day, I will stand astride
this corrupted planet!
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
[guitar hums]
[MIODA] Hormone! Hormone!
Love! Love! Hormone! Hormone!
Passion! Passion!
Yeah!
Whoa! Didn't know I was
playin' for a crowd!
Death metal barbeque, huh?
Let's stick it to the Man!
By attending class!
[MIODA chuckles]
[SODA]
Cool poses. Can we go now?
[YUKIZOME]
Yep! On to the next one!
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
Sorry, Pekoyama,
but class has already
started today.
Forgive me.
I so easily lose
track of the time.
I know your job's important,
but you do need to go to class.
Hey, Teach. how the hell
do you know about the--?
Eat some hormone-yaki and
get yourself hype, little man!
[MIODA chuckles]
All right!
We're down to our
final three, you guys!
Think of all the growth
we'll experience as a class!
Our new teacher seems
very... motivated.
Aw, this sucks!
I'm perfect as-is!
Part of me is growing right now!
[HANAMURA screams]
Now now, Hanamura.
That went a little overboard.
[HANAMURA]
Oh, it hurts so good!
[YUKIZOME]
Onward! Luck is on our side!
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
I know that boy's
around here somewhere.
I don't like him.
Whenever he's around, my day
goes south, like majorly!
[SODA screams]
[ALL]
Soda!
[KOMAEDA]
Aw, you've gotta be kidding me.
I put in a thousand yen and
push the button, but no drink.
I'm the unluckiest guy ever.
[SODA screaming]
[chuckles] Well, guess my luck
isn't that bad after all!
Hi.
[KOMAEDA laughs]
[KOMAEDA]
Hold on.
You wanted to meet
a no one like me?
What a wonderful
teacher you are!
[YUKIZOME] Oh, come now.
You aren't a no one.
You are a rotten orange!
[KOMAEDA chuckles]
That wasn't a
compliment, dimwit.
Now listen up! Two more
and we are finished!
Home stretch, you guys!
Gimme some hustle!
[SAIONJI]
Huh?
I'm not taking another step!
It already feels like my legs
are about to fall off!
Oh my God.
They can do that from
just walking around?
It's a figure of
speech, dumbass!
[TSUMIKI]
You don't have to be so mean!
Fine, if you're gonna
be lazy-butts...
I'll go wrangle your
last two classmates myself
if the rest of you stay here
and give the room
a good cleaning.
For real? Haven't we
suffered enough today?
You wanna talk suffering?
[SODA]
Nope! We're good! We're good!
Have fun! I'll see ya later!
Yeah, pull swords on the
guy who got hit by a truck.
[KOIZUMI] I think she's pretty
cool, all things considered.
Shove it, shutterbug!
his is what high
school's all about!
Oh, yeah! You called it!
[TANAKA chuckles]
Unleash your chaos, my Devas,
that we may cleanse
this Gehenna!
No choice, I guess.
Let's just get it
over with, yeah?
[clattering]
[screams]
[SAIONJI] How do you survive
the day, you klutz?
So when is this class over?
[ROBOT VOICE]
Danganronpa .
[knocking]
[YUKIZOME]
Hello in there!
I'm sorry! I'll be done
in, like, ten more--
No, five or six
more pages, okay?
[YUKIZOME]
No excuses.
Get out here, pronto!
Chop chop, Mitarai!
Time to make my
daring escape!
Wait, what?
Weren't you at the front
door just now? H-How?
Funny how that works.
Moral of the story?
Don't try to ditch your teacher.
[MITARAI] I don't wanna
wait for the Blu-Ray!
If you take me away now,
I'll miss the broadcast!
So! One more student to catch,
and my work here is done!
[HINATA'S CLASSMATE A]
He has no talent.
[HINATA'S CLASSMATE C]
His parents are stupid, too.
[HINATA'S CLASSMATE D]
You can just pay your way in.
[HINATA'S CLASSMATE E] They
want him to succeed that much?
Uh. Are you... okay?
[NANAMI]
Uh-huh.
[HINATA]
Gala Omega , right?
Uh?
So you know it?
You're the first, like, ever!
[HINATA]
Uh. Yeah?
It's a classic, don't you agree?
There's nothing else like
it in the whole genre!
Yeah, classic!
I New Game Plussed it
five times in a row once.
[NANAMI]
Are you serious?
Yes! Cross my heart!
I know how tough that is.
I did ten in a row once.
That blows mine
out of the water.
It's just, I've
never met anybody
who could play games
as much as me before.
Someday, I wanna see your
very best run, all right?
Sure. You got it.
[YUKIZOME]
Oh, there you are!
[MITARAI grunting]
You must be Nanami!
Pleasure to meet'cha!
Huh?
You can call me Chisa Yukizome!
As of today, I'm your
new homeroom teacher.
So who's with me?
Huh? That uniform.
Are you in the
Reserve Course?
Yes, ma'am.
What's the Reserve Course?
You haven't heard of it?
They only just rolled
it out last year.
It's an academic track
for regular students.
But those kids pay through
the nose for enrollment.
I get it.
[MITARAI]
Uh.
--[MITARAI screams]
--[YUKIZOME growls]
You're not gettin'
away that easily!
[MITARAI] Whoa! Time out!
I can't run that fast!
Ah!
Did you just throw
a sword at me?
[YUKIZOME] Oh, you're fine!
I didn't hit anything important!
Y'know, for being enrolled
in the Main Course,
that guy's kind of a mess.
I thought they'd
be way more elite.
But--
Quirks aside, all you guys have
incredible talents, don't ya?
Must be nice... being
good at something.
[NANAMI] Whether you
have a talent or not,
there's no point getting
so hung up over it.
[HINATA]
Huh?
I mean, it's not like
the be-all, end-all.
Yeah, but...
You have greater
freedom than we do.
All I have is a pile
of video games.
Somebody like you
can go anywhere,
and do whatever they
want with their life.
[YUKIZOME]
Sorry 'bout that!
[MITARAI yelling]
[YUKIZOME]
Come on, you.
Let's get to class.
Sorry to drag her away out
of left field like this.
Hey. You do what you gotta.
She's not gonna put down
that handheld willingly, huh?
Ups-a-daisy!
Well then, I guess
I'll see you around!
Uh, okay.
[YUKIZOME] Right on!
I caught the whole class!
[chuckles]
[HINATA] I've got more
freedom than the elites.
Huh.
[YUKIZOME]
Just look at you all,
sitting there in your
tidy little rows!
Also, good job!
The room looks
absolutely immaculate!
I can be kind of a bad-ass
when I give half a damn.
Cleaning is the one
thing I'm pretty good at.
Ugh! I'm so tired,
I think I'm gonna die!
But you literally did nothing!
Great!
And we'll pick up here tomorrow!
That is quite the presumption.
So long as one focuses
on their talent,
I heard we were free to
skip class as we deem fit.
[OWARI]
Freak-face is right!
Sittin' here is hell
on my glutes!
[MIODA] Lemme destroy the music
room, Teach! Everybody wins!
Technically, yes.
The rules say you can leave
whenever you want, but...
...there's more to life than
being good at something.
This time with your classmates
will build character.
Think of the memories
you'll make!
Just this once, let's put
something else front and center.
Like your hope.
Our hope?
That would be amazing!
[SONIA] Hardly! This is
all part of growing up!
[SODA]
Right you are, Princess!
[SAIONJI] Huh? Way to stick to
your guns there, grease-monkey!
[NIDAI] I think this new
plan is the shit, guys!
[TSUMIKI]
Me, too!
In that case, I'll round you
up again bright and early!
[CLASS]
Huh?
Thanks to all your help,
I survived day one.
Glad to hear it.
That's excellent news.
[YUKIZOME] So how are
things going on your end?
Will you be okay out
there without me?
[MUNAKATA] It's almost a letdown
how well things are proceeding.
Opening another Hope's
Peak Academy overseas,
hard to believe it's
finally coming to pass.
[MUNAKATA]
You thought it impossible?
Maybe so for a man
possessed of less resolve.
I'm made of sterner stuff.
[YUKIZOME] Aye-aye, my former
Super High School-Level
Student Council President.
Don't push yourself too hard.
You always did have a
tendency to overdo things.
[YUKIZOME]
Hey, Kyosuke.
Truth is, I really am grateful
to Hope's Peak High.
If I hadn't gone here,
we never would have met!
[MUNAKATA]
What brought this on?
[YUKIZOME]
Oh, nothing.