[ENOSHIMA]
Oh, I get it.
Real talk, snickerdoodle,
your class sounds like
a whole lotta fun.
[TSUMIKI]
I know, right? It's amazing!
Miss Yukizome's the
best teacher ever!
And our class rep,
Nanami, she's so sweet!
I've never seen anyone
work as hard as she does.
[ENOSHIMA]
Hmm...
Ya make a strong case, hon!
So, you miss 'em.
It's only natural!
If they're such a great class,
who'd wanna bail on 'em?
Can't you leave me alone?
Please, just go.
What're you even getting
out of that jigsaw puzzle?
[ENOSHIMA]
Ah. Surprised I'm into it?
For your information, this kind
of thing is right up my alley.
You spend so much
time putting it together.
Piece by piece, carefully
building order out of chaos,
when all of a sudden--
[ENOSHIMA]
Entropy.
Despair gets the last word.
Couldn't you just die?
[RESERVE STUDENT A]
"Hope's Peak"? What a crock!
[RESERVE STUDENT C] You took
our parents to the cleaners,
you thieves!
[RESERVE STUDENT B]
This whole place is a scam!
[TEACHER A]
Good lord,
this could spell the end
for Hope's Peak.
It's simply unthinkable.
Those children...
[TEACHER B]
The videos are getting around.
People are talking.
We're screwed.
[TEACHER A]
Only a matter of time
before the government steps in.
We have to find a way
to bury this, fast.
[MITARAI]
I don't understand.
Tsumiki's acting strange.
Like Enoshima's brainwashed her.
She's up to something, but what?
[MITARAI]
Movie Production?
[gasps]
Wh-What is this?
What am I looking at?
These... These people...
...are killing each other.
[MITARAI]
Oh my God. That isn't CG.
They're actually--
They're actually dying!
I see you clicked on the file.
You shouldn't have
done that, silly.
Heh. Don't peak! Must respect
the artists process.
Wait. You're saying
Enoshima did this?
Well, who else could?
Those kids were the trial run.
It's still a work in progress.
Tons left to do. Mutual Killing
videos take a lot of work.
"Mutual Killing"?
What does that mean?
[TSUMIKI]
Oh, right!
Everyone in that
class is dead now.
They massacred each other
while Enoshima filmed.
[giggles]
[MITARAI]
You're joking.
Why would anybody wanna
make a video like that?
That's sick. Just sick!
Yes, it is!
[inaudible]
[PROTESTERS shouting]
[PROTESTOR B]
Let us in!
[PROTESTER E] Why don't those
kids have to take entrance exams
like the rest of us?
[JUZO]
Quit whining!
You got what ya paid for!
Now ain't the time to start
bitchin' about fairness!
[MIODA] How long you think
they'll actually be able
to keep 'em out?
They have a right
to protest, I guess.
They're just so angry.
Yo, we're not allowed
to call it that.
A protest is something
people do elsewhere.
When students exercise their
right to assemble here,
it's billed as a parade.
Public relations and all that.
Like callin' it somethin'
other 'n what it is
means a damn thing.
Don't shoot the messenger.
'S not my line.
It's straight from the faculty.
They can call it a book
fair for all I care.
It's messed up either way.
Eh, hell with the turds.
Think they're the reason
Tsumiki didn't show up today?
Actually! I think you might
be on to something there.
Pukey the Pig's been run off!
But if she left,
why were all her things
still hanging out
in the dorm room this morning?
[SONIA]
That is cause for concern.
Hello, class!
Now why are we all staring
blankly out the window?
What our eyes should be
trained on is the future!
Straight-up, Teach.
Should we be worried?
I know it's not very rock n'
roll, but I'm kinda freaked.
Oh, sweetheart.
You'll be fine.
Just don't go outside
during the day.
[SAIONJI] Um, yeah, kinda
figured that out already.
Security knows their job
down to the last detail.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Is it possible-- I mean, do you
think that Hinata maybe?
[YUKIZOME]
If you're asking
whether he got
caught up in all this,
your guess is as good as mine.
I thought as much.
Hey. You're gonna be a good
boy and help us, right?
Please?
[MITARAI]
No!
This is wrong!
Aww. You're so adorable.
What's so wrong about it?
Are we talking about
the same thing?
Or is your mind on
something else entirely?
[ENOSHIMA]
What's the matter with you?!
Five whole minutes I was gone.
Stop acting like a pig in heat!
[TSUMIKI cries]
[TSUMIKI]
You raised your voice at me!
A no one! A girl of
absolutely no consequence!
You even kicked me in the face!
I'm truly unworthy!
Thank you! Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
[TSUMIKI screams]
Alrighty then.
I think we've lost one.
[chuckles]
You did this to her.
You drove her mad!
[chuckles]
Heads up.
Segue!
Allow me to present the specs
of our exciting current project.
To begin, as you so
observantly inferred,
the Mutual Killing
video is responsible
for Tsumiki's current
lapse in mental health.
However, having said that,
the scope of its impact
is rather, well...
...let's say insufficient.
My brainwashing skills
leave a lot to be desired.
This is where you come in.
The keyword here is "synergy."
I'm proposing we combine our
respective areas of expertise.
Together we'll tap into an
exponentially larger demographic
than either one of us
could secure on our own,
which not only maximizes
product reach,
but will incentivize a
market paradigm shift.
I need your magic, Michelangelo.
Do it for the sake of art.
You saw that ratchet little
piece of cinema verite.
Help me help you help me.
What do you want?
What's your endgame?
This might sound over-the-top...
[TSUMIKI screams]
...but I'm 'onna
plunge the world
into a maelstrom of Despair.
[MITARAI]
Let go! Let go of me!
If you wanna run,
don't let me stop you.
Just know that if you do,
I'll have no choice
but to make your school chums
the stars of my next video.
[gasps]
[NANAMI]
No sign of her.
I'm starting to have a
bad feeling about this.
[KUZURYU] I sent some of my
guys by her house to check,
but no dice.
She hasn't come back yet.
Behold my Twelve
Zodiac Generals!
Alas! even they could find
no discernable trace!
Huh, 'magine that.
[ALL gasp]
Speak of the devil! Hey, girl!
[KOMAEDA]
Yeah, sorry.
Still a dude.
It's been a while.
I brought gifts!
Now isn't the time.
Who're you?
Good to have you back, Komaeda.
I apologize if no one seems
in the mood to celebrate.
Tsumiki's missing.
We're starting to worry.
Okay.
Tell me you've forgotten her
and I'll punch you in the mouth!
Wow, what a coincidence!
I spotted her on the way here.
In the West District.
[CLASS]
Huh?!
I'm gonna need you
to be absolutely sure.
I, uh, don't think I recall
you being such a hardcore guy.
[IMPOSTER] O-Oh. Sorry. I, uh,
got a little carried away.
I'm sure it was Tsumiki.
Should we go get her?
Yes. I want to know why
she hasn't been here.
We're owed an explanation.
[SODA]
Damn straight!
Told ya she was just bein'
a pain in the ass.
[KOMAEDA]
Hey, Pekoyama?
Yes? What?
We, uh, kinda need to talk.
No. No!
Your students need you to
push them over the hump,
so that's exactly
what you'll do!
Now's the time for youth
to charge forward,
banners waving in the air!
You can do it.
Good morning, class!
[gasps]
[YUKIZOME]
What were they thinking?
I expressly said
not to go outside!
[STUDENTS shouting]
[PROTESTER F] We're takin'
the future into our own hands!
Everyone, follow me!
Damn it! Punks!
What the hell are you
trying to prove?
[MUNAKATA] Looks like
you could use some help.
Munakata.
This certainly swarmed out of
proportion to our expectations.
[JUZO]
It's my fault.
No. This falls squarely on me.
I made the two of you bite off
more than you could chew.
I put you at risk.
Feels a tad out of character
for you to say that.
Call Yukizome.
Have her join us when
this is under control.
Sure. Sounds like a plan.
[YUKIZOME]
Tsumiki! Class!
Can anyone hear me?
Call out and I'll come to you!
Tsumiki!
If you're close,
shout so we can hear!
Hades' moon!
Mayhap she was devoured.
The Gates of Purgatory
hunger for wayward souls.
Yeah, we get it, you're
saying something ominous.
Big help there.
Mikan!
You want me to twist
you like a pretzel?
Yeah, not the best way
to get an answer.
Did I just hear a reference
to Sapphic love?
Shut up! You're so gross!
I don't even know
what that means!
[OWARI]
Tsumiki!
Where the hell are you?!
[groans]
Man. Think there's any chance
she's hiding in the cafeteria?
Maybe?
Quit using your stomach
as a compass, huh?
[OWARI]
What?
Hey, Mitarai, what's goin' on?
You need somethin' to eat, or--?
No, I'm good.
[stomach growls]
Oops.
[NIDAI sighs]
All right, then. Fine.
We'll check the cafeteria,
just in case.
[OWARI]
Score! Ha-ha!
[NANAMI]
She's definitely not here.
[KOMAEDA]
Hold on.
[NANAMI]
What is it?
[KOMAEDA] Why put a statue
in a place like this?
Weird.
Komaeda, look!
What in the world is going on?
[KOMAEDA]
Whoa.
We found a secret passage. Cool.
I really am super lucky, huh?
Wait, you didn't
know it was here?
Not a clue.
Total chance. That's my thing.
[NANAMI]
I guess the real question is,
what would a school need
with something like this?
Right?
Well my guess is
someone's doing something
they don't want anybody
else to know about.
Yeah, but what would a
school have to keep secret?
Could be anything.
Human experimentation?
Mitarai? Is that you?
You've lost weight.
I didn't do anything.
You've gotta believe me.
I-I--
I was just making anime!
Please! I didn't know!
I don't wanna hurt people!
[ENOSHIMA]
There's our mini-Miyazaki!
How's it goin'?
Found your muse yet?
[KOMAEDA]
Um.
What's going on here?
[ENOSHIMA]
And who're you?
Better yet, how's an outsider
know about this place?
[KOMAEDA]
Luck of the draw.
Well, that's fascinating.
Officially, I'm Super
High School-Level Lucky.
So, y'know.
Oh. Now I get'cha.
Well, 's not like it really
matters one way or the other.
Tragically, you'll
never be in a position
to tell anyone where
that luck brought you.
[KOMAEDA] If you're counting on
backup from Mukuro Ikusaba,
I wouldn't.
So, my little horseshoe,
what do you know?
Honestly? Not much.
But I'm learning.
[MUKURO]
Why are you following me?
[PEKOYAMA] Someone asked me
to keep my eyes peeled.
Specifically for what
you were up to.
Ah. You and he must be
close then, I take it.
Adorable.
[PEKOYAMA]
Enough. Tell me what's going on.
I 'unno.
Only thing I can say
is I'm being stalked.
Which pisses me off!
[MUKURO]
Hmph.
You've done this before.
So have you.
I haven't done anything...
[ENOSHIMA]
I see how it is.
That's my flaky-ass sister for
ya. Always otherwise engaged.
This is for Hope.
I'm sure you understand.
See, I'm that kinda guy.
Whatever it takes, I'm in.
[chuckling]
Well go on, let's see you
derail the Despair Train!
What are you doing?
I happened to pick
this piece up overseas.
No idea it'd ever
come in so handy.
Wait! Stop! You can't do this!
You can't just kill another
human being! It's wrong!
It's not that I
disagree, class rep,
but sometimes, very rarely,
two wrongs can make a right.
[ENOSHIMA]
Huh?
At the end of the day,
Despair is just a
stepping stone to Hope.
Sometimes... you gotta put
all your weight into it.
Oh yeah?
[KOMAEDA]
I wanted to test myself,
see if I have what
it takes to kill you.
But let's be real for a second,
that's a pretty damn
big step, right?
It's not as simple
as just putting
one foot in front
of the other, oh no.
This only means something if
you're the epitome of Despair.
You may be the biggest
Hope fanboy I've ever met.
I'd be laughing if
it weren't so sad.
[KOMAEDA]
With any luck,
I'll make a hash of it
and you'll get out alive.
Maybe you'll go on to become
an even bigger stepping stone
for someone else.
[gasps]
[KOMAEDA]
Who are you?
[gasps]
Oh, crap! Why you gotta jam?
Good luck, is it?
Well, I have that too.
[NANAMI]
Komaeda, no!
Hang in there!
We'll get you some help!
Stay with me!
[MITARAI screaming]
[NANAMI]
Please be okay.
The student handbook?
[NANAMI]
Komaeda!
[HINATA]
Fortune smiles on him.
[ENOSHIMA]
You, sir, do not disappoint!
[ENOSHIMA chuckles]
[YUKIZOME]
Tsumiki! Children!
Give me a break. Where the
dickens could they have gone?
I am so sorry!
Are you all right?
Mitarai? Have you lost weight?
Help me, please!
You've gotta save her!
They're g-- They're
gonna kill Nanami!
Hey, calm down.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Just tell me where she is.
I'd show you, except,
I can't do anything.
I'm just a stupid animator.
Only thing I'm good
at is drawin' stuff.
[YUKIZOME]
There, there, now.
Look, it's my job to
protect her, not yours.
So, deep breath.
When I'm back, I wanna
see some of your work.
[MITARAI]
You mean... my anime?
Yes.
Now tell me where to go.
[YUKIZOME]
I have a bad feeling about this.
What am I gonna to do?
I'm a Super High
School-Level Housekeeper.
Still, something's
brought me here.
I'm in the right place at
the right time far too often
for it to be a coincidence.
Maybe... this is the big one.
Forgive me, Kyosuke. I have to.
[NANAMI]
Is that you... Hinata?