[NANAMI]
Hinata.
You look like him, but don't.
You are Hinata, aren't you?
Your hair's different now.
[HINATA]
You speak like you know me.
[gasps]
[ENOSHIMA] Okay, you crazy
kids, let's wrap it up.
As much as I'm a fan
of the slow burn,
I think you've stared at
each other long enough.
You. Then you must be--
I'm the one making
all you puppets dance.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
You're the representative
for Class 77-A, aren't you?
Your name's Chiaki
Nanami, Gamer Girl.
Wh-Why do you know that stuff?
[ENOSHIMA]
Hmm...
Because I wanted to
meet your ass!
Getting this kind of attention
from an upperclassman is crazy!
You takin' the time to come
down here? I can't believe it!
Am I free to go?
Now you're just gonna
watch a little movie.
It's gonna blow
your mind. Promise!
[YUKIZOME]
Heads up, Nanami!
[ENOSHIMA]
Jeebus!
You can't hit me with detention
like a normal teacher?
[NANAMI]
Miss Yukizome!
Take Komaeda and get to safety.
--What about you?
--Do as I say, dammit!
[ENOSHIMA]
Hmm...
Just leave this to me.
Whether you're in class or not,
I'm still your teacher.
[YUKIZOME] I think you could've
stopped them if you'd wanted to.
[ENOSHIMA]
Gee, ya think?
But who cares about them?
I got bigger game in mind!
Cut to the chase. Who are you?
Who, me? No one special.
I'm Super High School-Level
Despair, Junko Enoshima!
The girl who's gonna kick this
planet right in the teeth!
An' this is the one-and-only
Super High School-Level Hope.
Kamukura here's a big deal.
His name is Kamukura?
But that--
I've got a hunch you've been
looking for ol' Red-Eyes
for a while now.
Such a touching reunion
to end things on.
[YUKIZOME]
The end of what?
[ENOSHIMA]
You!
I probably should've led
with this, but whatever!
After today, you and
your students' minds
will be totally revamped!
[gasps]
In fact, I won't even
have to hunt 'em down!
Those cinnamon rolls
can't resist the urge
to save their teacher!
I can't believe Komaeda
got captured!
And what if that chick
wasn't Tsumiki?
Maybe it was another
bandage-covered school girl.
[NANAMI]
Everyone!
There's no time to waste!
Miss Yukizome's in trouble!
Oh yeah.
They're gonna trot right in
like lambs to the slaughter.
And after I scrape
out all their Hope,
I'll pack 'em full of Despair
like sausage casings!
You mean to tell us that
she's there with that maniac?
[NANAMI]
Yeah!
We need to go save
her right away!
Oh, it's on!
I'm gonna make that chick
my Super High School-Level
Punching Bag!
[TANAKA]
Hm.
At last, the time to use
my eldritch powers is nigh.
[ENOSHIMA] Your class was the
very personification of Hope.
Flipping the script is
gonna be such a coup.
They'll join Kamukura
in a new homeroom.
And by their powers combined,
the world will
smother in Despair!
Thank you so much, you guys!
[TSUMIKI] W-We wanna help
save Miss Yukizome, too!
[SODA]
Tsumiki!
What happened to Peko?
How come she looks
all beat to hell?
Please, sir. You need to run.
No. They'll never
agree to help you!
Cute that you think
they're getting a choice.
Your students are gonna be
my Super High
School-Level Despairs
no matter how they
feel about the matter.
And I know this for a fact
'cause I got something in mind
that'll drive 'em
clean outta theirs!
Spoilers, it starts with a "B"
and it rhymes with
"brainwashing"!
Brainwashing?
Sho' 'nuff!
And just in case you doubt
my ability to pull it off!
Be a doll and show Miss Yukizome
what you learned today.
Stop it. Please! I--!
I don't wanna die!
Drop the sa--!
I don't wanna do this,
but I don't have a choice!
No! It hurts! God!
It hurts so bad!
I can feel everything!
Stop! Make it stop!
I'm killing myself! Why am
I killing myself? Oh, god!
Grade-A nightmare-fuel, huh?
And the pisser is,
your students will feel even
more hopeless than him.
In the name of almighty Despair,
they'll mangle their own bodies
at the snap of my fingers.
They'll kill everyone
they've ever loved
with nary a second thought.
My Super High
School-Level Despairs
will have the power to
corrupt the whole world!
[ENOSHIMA chuckles]
[ENOSHIMA]
Don't look sad.
You'll be joining 'em.
[MIODA]
Hellz yeah!
It's Operation:
Take Back Our Teacher!
Whoever this Junko girl is,
I'm gonna tie her into a knot.
[KOMAEDA]
Not if you wanna live.
You're elites.
You've been praised your
whole life for being the best.
But you, you can't
hope to defeat them.
The depths of their Despair...
it's unfathomable.
Challenging them isn't heroic,
it's a suicide mission.
Coward!
Hell's that about, writin' us
off before we even try?
No, he's right.
I don't care how
scary this chick is.
No one smacks you
around like that!
Thank you, sir.
Understand, I'm only telling
you this for your own good.
You saw what they
could do, Nanami.
You know that I'm right.
Komaeda!
They'll die.
We'll die?
The only mort I wanna
feel is le petit one.
It's just none of us signed on
for a life-or-death
struggle today.
We're all Super High
School-Level at something.
Maybe it means you
have talent to burn,
but you have to know
when to cut your losses.
[ALL groan]
Really?!
You're all... okay
with abandoning her?
Miss Yukizome would come
save us in a heartbeat!
[NANAMI]
If she hadn't been there for me,
I'd be sitting somewhere
by myself right now.
I never would've gotten
to know any of you.
Video games with a big
group are so much fun.
I never would've learned that.
Through the good times,
and the sad times,
she was there with us.
Maybe I'm not strong enough to
save her, but I'm gonna try!
You're pretty persuasive
for weighing, like, nothin'.
Bad-ass chicks gotta
stick together!
Narrowly dodgin' death
would be quite the aperitif!
There's nothing we
can't do together!
All for one, right?
[TANAKA] A Warrior of the Void
who abandons his mentor
is unworthy of his dark calling.
I'll go, as well.
I am not what I seem. But...
I'm still one of you.
What the hell, dude?
[IMPOSTOR]
The one you call Mitarai
is nothing more than a Super
High School-Level Impostor.
I used his identity since
I lack one of my own.
But if you're just a fake,
whatever happened
to the real Mitarai?
[IMPOSTOR]
He must've been captured
by that she-devil Enoshima.
He let me be him.
The least I can do is try to
keep him alive as a thank you.
[KOMAEDA chuckles]
I knew you'd make
the right choice.
I never doubted
you'd pass the test.
Their Despair is great, but
I'm sure you all can persevere.
For you tread the path of Hope.
Jeez. If I wanted a riddle,
I'd eat a fortune cookie.
I'm sorry.
But I needed you to believe
in yourselves like I do.
Now then, let's go.
Komaeda! You can do it!
Be strong!
Making his way back here
probably took everything he had.
Soda, I hereby order you
to carry him on your back!
Roger! If it makes you
happy, Your Highness,
I'll carry him to
the edge of infinity!
I, uh, don't see how bringing
an unconscious person will help.
Courage! Fate has
guided us here.
And we must face the
coming dark united.
Okay.
All right!
Let's show those shits they
messed with the wrong teacher!
[CLASS]
Yeah!
[NANAMI] Please, Miss Yukizome.
And Hinata.
Just hang on!
[phone ringing]
[MUNAKATA]
No word from Yukizome?
Well, it is during class.
Soon as she checks her phone,
I'm sure she'll be here ASAP.
[MUNAKATA]
Noted.
Junko Enoshima was the first
to discover the bodies
in School Building 1A.
I need to know
what she's hiding.
She behind all this?
Yes. All the evidence on
hand points directly to her.
Enoshima's guilt in these
murders is a near certainty.
Get ready for an interrogation.
I'll drag 'er in by
the damn pigtails.
Try not to go too far.
I'm 'onna pretend I
didn't hear you say that.
[MUNAKATA] For spilling
the blood of my students,
I will bleed you in turn.
Weird. It worked on Tsumiki.
What's the deal here?
Yeah, that kinda sucks.
Listen, sis, I gotta go.
Riff for a while and
see what ya get.
"If the subject should
resist the imprinting,
use external stimulation."
Okay.
Stop it, please!
You don't have to do this!
[YUKIZOME screaming]
Closer.
Please no more!
[YUKIZOME screams]
Now we're talking.
[YUKIZOME]
No more.
Kyo... suke.
How pedestrian.
I hope we're not too late.
We're runnin' as fast
as we can here.
Save your breath for the fight.
Guys. Problem!
[RESERVE COURSE STUDENT E]
Check it out.
[RESERVE COURSE STUDENT B]
There, by the gate.
[RESERVE COURSE STUDENT E]
Yeah.
[RESERVE COURSE STUDENT C] Look
at those Main Course douchebags.
[RESERVE COURSE STUDENT D]
If they all die,
they'd have to plug someone
into those empty slots, right?
They think they're
so damn special.
Bet ya they bleed like we do.
[RESERVE COURSE STUDENT D]
Time to thin the ranks a bit.
Fools, every one of 'em.
I got a bad feeling about this!
I'll whip 'em into shape.
[TANAKA]
Their souls are forefeit!
The rest I leave to you.
Give 'em hell!
I wish you luck.
Maybe you don't know it yet,
but every last one of
you is in deep shit!
[TANAKA] I am known to man
as Tanaka the Forbidden One!
My soul-fire will blast you
beyond the Six Realms!
Punish them, my Twelve
Zodiac Generals!
[MITARAI screams]
Wh-What...?
What're you gonna do?
[ENOSHIMA] Way to leave
a girl high and dry, pal.
I-I panicked! Please, just--!
I guess it's time we
said our goodbyes, huh?
And after goodbye?
Oh! You think I mean
it figuratively,
like I'm gonna murder you!
Trust me, if I wanted
to cut your face off,
I so would've done it already.
Seriously, I owe you one.
Thanks to you,
my plan is chugging along
way smoother than I ever
could've hoped for!
What plan is that?
Duh! To spruce up that
video footage I brought in!
Way to knock it outta
the park, Mitarai.
In fact, I'm gonna make
your whole class watch it,
start to finish!
Just think of it!
Our little collaboration
will change the very
wiring of their brains!
Your tricks are gonna cut
through their free will
like a knife!
Those lovely classmates of
yours will soon be creatures
that wanna plunge
the world into Despair
more than they've ever
wanted anything ever!
Dig it?
Let's hear it for Mitarai!
Give him a big hand, everyone!
That was different!
I was gonna use all
those techniques
to bring about a better world!
Using them for the sake
of Despair... it's terrible!
[MITARAI cries]
Oh please!
You can play the
victim all you want,
but you were totally president
of the Junko Fan Club
like 20 minutes ago!
[MITARAI]
My-My life was in danger!
I was being held hostage!
Oh, right. That is so
what happened to you.
We threatened to kill you, so
you ran with whatever we said.
You haven't been responsible
for your actions since we met.
You could run off this campus
with your tail
between your legs
and no one would blame
you in the least.
I really thought
I was helping people!
[chuckles]
Run, coward.
For that Despair is yours,
and yours alone.
[MITARAI screaming]
[JUZO yells]
[ENOSHIMA]
Huh?
Hm?
Principal's office, now.
[MITARAI] All this...
just because I loved anime.
I truly thought..
...I could make the world a
better place with my talents.
What a fool I was.
Dig it?
Let's hear it for Mitarai!
Give him a big hand, everyone!
[MITARAI]
Because of me...
Because I... loved anime.
[MITARAI coughing]
[MITARAI]
Why am I... running away?
Why didn't I try to fight back?
Why am I useless?
Dammit, Mitarai, get up!
Be brave, just this once!
[MITARAI] I can't.
I'm nothing but a weakling.
[JUZO] Your flunkies,
they seem a little out of it.
Yep. Guilty as charged.
Munakata had your number.
So you were behind
all those students
killing each other off, huh?
Y'just figure that
out, Sherlock?
Give the man a cigar!
You got a smart mouth.
But it's gonna be down
a couple teeth in a sec.
Now, I'm 'bout to get all
kinds of unchivalrous!
[NANAMI]
Stay alert, you guys!
[KOIZUMI] We'll be fine.
We're here as a group.
[SONIA] What about Tanaka and
Nidai? They're all alone.
Don't worry about the big guy,
he can handle 'em.
Hell, he's prob'ly
knocked half of 'em out
and's makin' the other half
run wind-sprints by now.
And Tanaka's no slouch.
He gets it done in the clutch!
You're right, Soda.
He is a very capable
young man, isn't he?
Ugh. Way to talk up your
romantic rival, dumb-ass!
Anyone think Enoshima and
Hope's Peak are in cahoots?
Odd havin' her lair
hidden underneath
the statue of the
school's founder.
I just hope our
teacher's okay, yo.
For now, let's all focus
on doing what we can.
It's weird, but there's this
feeling in my stomach.
Like there's still time to get
the best ending in this RPG.
There's nothing to base it on,
but when you talk like
that, I believe you.
Hope I'm right then.
To be honest,
it was just a hunch.
You okay?
Can we talk alone
for a moment?
[NANAMI]
Uh...
You're kind of a
puzzle to me, Nanami,
did you know that?
You always used to be so
quiet and withdrawn before,
but then you perked up
and became the center
of the class's attention.
No. I mean, I talk
more than I used to.
You even serve as our
class representative.
You're the glue that holds our
classroom together, Nanami.
Tsumiki, what's up?
Please forgive me for this.
Huh?
Sorry!
[NANAMI screams]
[YUKIZOME]
Nanami! Please, wake up!
I need to know that you're okay!
Thank goodness.
Miss Yukizome!
What are you doing here?
[YUKIZOME] After you ran,
that long-haired boy let me go.
I don't think he's our enemy.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
[YUKIZOME]
Anyway.
What are you doing here,
and alone, no less?
But I wasn't alone!
The whole class came back
with me so we could save you.
Tsumiki pushed me and--
We need to find the
others right away.
They can't save themselves,
but we can.