Sweetie, try to pick
up the pace, 'kay?
I'm sorry, Miss, but are
we going the right way?
Seems like it's taking
a while to get there.
[YUKIZOME]
You're imagining things.
We really don't have
much farther to go.
C'mon. Everyone's waiting.
And I don't think they'll want
to see their beloved class rep
looking like so gravely
preoccupied, do you?
[YUKIZOME]
Right. Off we go, then.
[NANAMI]
Yes, ma'am.
You've gotta be kidding me.
[squeals]
Oh my god! You're so squishy!
You psychotic little--
[ENOSHIMA]
Sad-face.
I didn't even get a chance
to exploit your Achilles Heel.
What do you mean?
Ah, the world is cruel.
Alas, mighty Juzo
fell prey to the love
that dare not be spoken.
The heart wants what
the heart wants.
Yet the object of his affections
must never know the truth.
What the hell you talkin' about?
Adding insult to injury.
The apple of his eye is enamored
with his friend. The shame!
Woe betide him for wanting
what society won't let him have!
Why must love be such torture?
Surely 'tis better to have
never known its sting!
Sucks to be you.
Like, I know that
feeling of wanting
what's forever out of
reach, believe me.
Too bad we can't talk
ourselves out of desire.
Guess that's why
it's so powerful.
You got somethin' you wanna
say to me, you crazy bitch?
Come out and say it.
[ENOSHIMA babbles]
Your verboten love is
for none other than...
...Chisa Yukizome!
Ha!
Just kidding.
You gots the hots for
Kyosuke Munakata!
For future reference,
you might wanna pay
a bit more attention
to your surroundings.
You're supposed to
be head of security.
Yet, I took candid pics
of you in your own room!
[JUZO gasps]
[ENOSHIMA]
What's this?
His bestest friend in
the whole wide world?
Why ever is he starin'
at him like that?
[STUDENTS laughing]
So, uh, what do you
think Munakata'd do
if he ever found
out how you feel?
[JUZO]
No!
You can't do this!
Oh, I can't, huh?
Reality check:
You have no idea, son.
Now, if you were to ask
nicely, I might reconsider.
And by "nicely" of
course I mean beg.
[growls]
[JUZO]
Don't tell him. Please.
Aww, hon, it's not like
I'm devoid of compassion.
Tell ya what, since you grovel
so sweetly, we'll make a deal!
In exchange for staying
in the closet,
I want you to betray
the man you're gaga for.
Munakata's the reason you're
up my ass in the first place.
He told you to find
out what I'm up to.
Easy peasy! You lie a bit.
Write up a report, or whatever
it is you do for the man,
and assure him Junko
Enoshima is innocent.
You're outta your mind!
Not gonna happen! Period!
Maybe he'll be
touched to find out
he's the man of your dreams.
[STUDENTS laughing]
Fine. Okay. Whatever.
I tell him you're innocent,
just... he can't know.
Promise me.
What?
I didn't hear a please!
Go on! Say it!
Please let me lie
to Munakata for you.
Honey, glaring at me like that
isn't doing a damn thing.
You can't expect
people to recoil
at the sight of your fangs
after you've fallen from lone
wolf to lovelorn ingénue.
Where're you going? Wait!
I'm off to sink my fangs
into the main course!
Pathetic morsels like you
barely qualify as a paratif.
[screams]
[TSUMIKI] Wait up, guys!
You're going too fast!
[KUZURYU]
Hm?
Hang on. What the hell
happened to Nanami?
Oh.
I think she twisted
her ankle aways back
and decided to lie
down in a spare room
till she felt comfortable
putting weight on it again.
She'll catch back up
with us before too long.
[KOIZUMI]
Well, you are
the Super High School-Level
Health Committee Member.
[SAIONJI] So Pukey the Pig's
an osteopath all of sudden?
[giggles]
There's a place to lie down
and I've been carrying this
jerk for how long now?
[KOIZUMI sighs]
I'd be delighted to take him.
Komaeda's well within my
strike zone, as it so happens.
The hell's that mean?
In so many words, my-- Ah!
[screams]
[TANAKA]
Hm. Intriguing.
Was he exposed to
my Astral Pressure?
Tanaka, hey!
We're gonna be okay.
Thank goodness you're all right!
Tis a very simple maze barrier.
Child's play for Nidai and me
unfettered from
the Seven Chains.
[OWARI]
Yeah, sure.
Because we're supposed to know
what you're talking about.
[TANAKA]
Hm.
We are in your debt,
Tsumiki. Thank you.
Seriously?
She told us where to find you.
It's why we're here.
If it hadn't been for her,
we'd totally be up shit creek.
I'm just glad we were both
able to get good reception.
Yeah!
All we gotta do now is
take back Miss Chisa!
--Indeed! Let's!
--Kickass.
[NIDAI]
Yeah!
I think it's just
beyond this door.
Miss Yukizome, you're absolutely
sure this is the way?
[YUKIZOME]
Would you prefer to go back?
[NANAMI]
No.
I'm our class'
representative, after all.
Everybody's waiting on me.
That's what I thought
you'd say. Shall we, then?
Where are we?
We've been through a lot, huh?
You and me, side by side,
soldiering on.
Doing our best to keep
the classroom unified.
Holding them together.
At first, the only common ground
anyone had was raw talent.
But now, thanks to you,
they've become a team.
You're an extraordinary
young woman.
I just want you to know
how grateful I am
for all your hard work.
When I was transferred,
I thought for sure the
class would fall apart,
but no, you kept it going.
Thank you, Nanami.
You have done more for your
friends than you'll ever know.
[NANAMI]
Miss Yukizome?
So of course...
you were the obvious choice.
[ENOSHIMA]
Now, you may ask yourself:
"Why would my favorite
teacher do this to me?"
It's not as complicated
as you may think.
I made her watch a video!
Still workshopin' the title,
but for now we call it
the "Video of Despair!"
I don't know what
you're talking about.
[ENOSHIMA]
Oh, come on!
Don't tell me you
haven't heard! Ugh.
Okay, look, think
Manchurian Candidate .
Mitarai sort of co-produced.
You watch, you cave.
So now there's a 15 car pile-up
on Miss Yukizome's
synaptic superhighway.
How could you do that?
[ENOSHIMA] We're still grinding
through the prototype phase,
but the final product is
right around the corner.
Just needs a little more,
well, the technical term
is unmitigated Despair.
Tough to find.
But, I heard of you and
a light bulb came on.
Ding!
Oh yes. You're just what
my video's been missing.
You're gonna raise it
to the level of art!
[IMPOSTOR] No sign of
Miss Yukizome or Enoshima.
Is this really where
we're s'posed to be?
[KOMAEDA]
It's a trap.
[ENOSHIMA]
Heya, kiddos! Is everybody in?
Swell! Let's get started!
[CLASS]
Huh?
It's coming from up there!
[CLASS gasps]
What the hell's going on here?
What have you done to Nanami?
[ENOSHIMA laughing]
Every good show needs a
heart-stopping first act,
doesn't it?
It's punishment time!
[ENOSHIMA]
Okay!
She's already reached the
midpoint of my Death Dungeon.
How many more lethal traps
can the Super High
School-Level Gamer avoid?
'Cause so far
Nanami's doin' aces!
[ENOSHIMA] But uh-oh!
Here's where things get hairy.
Give it hell, girlfriend!
Eyes on the prize!
Your friends are waiting
for you at the finish line!
I've heard stories, y'know?
Apparently you're the glue
that holds the whole
shebang together.
Lines were drawn all up in that
sand 'fore you came along.
Your classmates were a ragtag
bunch of brats n' backbiters.
I can make it. I can make it.
I have to!
Huh?
[ENOSHIMA] And you made a
bona fide team out of 'em.
I'm drawn to that kind of
talent like a moth to flame.
Not like this.
Nice try, but you're
not gonna beat me.
Me, Miss Yukizome,
and my classmates
are gonna kick your butt!
This game is stupid!
Oh, yeah! There's the
Hope I wanna crush!
More of that, please!
When it's gone, you'll have
absolutely nothing!
Despair needs a springboard.
The grisly death of Hope
seems like the natural choice.
Hop-to, missy!
Get them legs a'movin'!
The sooner you perish horribly,
the sooner this video
can flip rock bottom
into prime real-estate!
Oh, my bad. Silly me.
I mean... Good luck!
We-We have to find her
and get her out of there!
Yes, of course.
But where is she?
How're we supposed to know?
Just start looking!
[NIDAI growls]
[SODA]
This is messed up!
Wait a minute! You said
you were gonna save Nanami!
Yeah, well, that was the idea.
There's just one problem.
My body.
I can't seem to move.
[IMPOSTOR]
Is the video doing this to us?
I don't care what you do
to me. I'm not... giving up!
[ENOSHIMA] As a reward for
that unsinkable spirit,
it's Take Your Chance Time!
Chin up, baby doll.
I'm told the power of
friendship can work miracles.
I'll give you a ten
second head start.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
--[thud]
--[NANAMI screams]
[ENOSHIMA]
Crap! My timing's off.
Safe to say the lesson here is
Despair's a fickle li'l beeoch.
What can you do?
Miracles are such a racket.
Your classmate's are not
coming to the rescue.
They are gonna watch
you die, though.
Heh.
So sad.
No Hail Mary for you, Class Rep!
No. Nanami, please.
[KOIZUMI]
Nanami!
I don't wanna watch.
Don't make me. I can't!
No! Make it stop.
Make it stop, please!
So much pain, so much love!
It's... Ah! This is incredible!
Watching Nanami go through
something so terrible
is binding our hearts
together as one!
Chiaki Nanami.
Trusted. Beloved.
Your untimely demise will
scar your friends for life.
Despair will corrupt
them to the bone!
[NANAMI]
I'll make it. I won't lose.
We won't lose.
[laughs]
[NANAMI]
Not to someone like you!
They'll come for me.
I know in my heart they will!
This is not how I die!
[ENOSHIMA laughing]
[NANAMI]
Told you.
Welcome back. Glad you made it.
You're a monster.
What you've done to
Nanami is unforgivable.
She was our greatest Hope.
This sight is more
than I can bear.
Like something in me
has broken its chains.
I've been released to Despair.
Is this... the Despair our
talents are meant to overcome?
Oh, Nanami.
You understand, surely.
In death, you become the
stepping-stone to Hope.
[KOMAEDA laughing]
Congratulations!
Welcome to the fold!
Now you'll all be
exactly like moi!
Doesn't losin' someone you
love just break your heart?
Suck up that Despair!
Sit back and let the ecstasy
of it wash over you!
Once you've had a
taste, you're hooked!
You'll wanna bask in it
every second of your lives!
Nothing will do but
to see the whole world
burn with the same feeling!
[ENOSHIMA] Say adieu to
your late cheerleader.
And hello to the incomparably
wonderful world of Despair.
Thank you for playing.
I look forward to
working with you.
[footsteps]
Hinata... Please...
[NANAMI] You're still
in there... aren't you?
Was that my name?
Is that whose body
this used to be?
[NANAMI]
You really...
You really don't
remember... anything?
[NANAMI] Not even...
that we used to be...
I'm afraid not.
All vestiges of
the former identity
have been erased
to make way for me.
Sure, maybe so, but
anything's possible for you.
If you dig deep enough...
[NANAMI]
Come on. You can do it.
I know... I know you can.
[NANAMI]
Oh god. This is it.
I wanted to help you.
I really did.
I'm sorry. I--
With death so close at hand,
you would still dedicate
yourself to helping others?
It's what I do.
My classmates... are my life.
I... I love them all.
[NANAMI]
No.
I'm not... I'm not ready to go.
I-I had so much
left to do and...
...I thought there'd
be enough time.
My classmates... need someone
to stand up and protect them.
[NANAMI]
Please. Just one more game.
One more round.
We-We had so much fun, right?