[HINATA] People without
talent are parasites.
Ticks.
Mindlessly gorging themselves on
the blood of larger creatures.
They pair off and reproduce.
That's it.
Once upon a time,
the ticks tried to catch
lightening in a bottle.
Front-loading every talent,
they could into
one of their own.
The Super High School-Level
Hope, they called him.
In reality, an
inextinguishable host.
[TRUSTEE A]
I wasn't impressed initially.
In fact, at first blush,
the boy seemed too indecisive
to be an ideal subject.
[WORKER A]
Rest assured his defects
will no longer be an issue.
All traces of the
former personality...
...have been deleted.
[WORKER B]
Heart rate normal.
[WORKER A]
Very good. Open the capsule.
[TRUSTEE A] You have been born
anew; a phoenix from the ashes.
I hereby christen you
Izuru Kamukura.
In honor of our school's
glorious founder.
[STUDENT A]
Catch ya later!
[STUDENT B]
Same time tomorrow?
[STUDENT C]
You know it.
[STUDENT D]
Oh my gosh!
[STUDENT G] I can't believe
she actually said something.
[STUDENT E]
Right?
[STUDENT H]
My bad, sorry!
[STUDENT I]
Come on, man. Pick up the pace!
Would it've killed you
to wait for five seconds?
Seriously, cut me some slack.
Teach was all up...
[NANAMI] Miss Chisa,
is Hinata doing okay?
Oh, yeah. No, uh--
Sure. He's, um, doing
just fine, actually.
[NANAMI]
Huh. 'Kay. That's good.
Well, then. See ya later.
[NANAMI]
Yeah! See ya tomorrow!
So much for that, I guess.
Peko, pick that up
for me, will ya?
[PEKOYAMA]
Of course.
What about the rest of it?
I dunno. That's Komaeda's
stuff, so whatever.
Ask Nanami about it later.
[PEKOYAMA]
Understood. And this?
[KUZURYU] Ugh. Will you
knock it off? Damn.
Why don't'cha worry about
luggin' your own crap?
Seriously, here.
Let's consolidate.
Kindly leave my
personal effects alone,
thank you very much!
Too late now. I got 'em.
This is weird! Extremely weird!
Yeah, something's not
adding up here!
Why are you two so
chummy all of a sudden?
[TSUMIKI]
I think it's lovely.
A bond between two
wayward souls.
[KUZURYU]
Wh-What're you talkin' about?
This ain't a damn thing!
Just a coincidence!
[MIODA]
Ugh!
Shenanigans!
You were acting like an old
married couple just now!
[HANAMURA]
Ah.
A sign of maturity.
Delish! You're ripening like a--
Whoops! Dear me,
I'm such a klutz!
Hey. Is this garbage?
[TANAKA]
Fie on thee, filthy cur!
I'll have you know
that is a sacred offering to
the fallen angel Satanael!
You are not worthy to change
the lining of that cage!
Remove thy impure hands
lest you court calamity!
You're an idiot.
I mean, C'mon! Calamity?
I've seen tougher stuff come out
of a vacuum cleaner bag.
Look at him.
[SAIONJI screaming]
Let the record show that she
was adequately warned.
There, there, li'l bun-bun.
'S rather odd.
Has anyone seen Miss
Yukizome yet today?
Yeah, she's in the faculty
office, moving her things.
I'd be surprised if
we see her at all.
[JUZO]
Careful with this.
Don't get caught with
a trustee's ID card.
I won't, thanks.
Listen, work fast.
At six A.M. on the dot tomorrow,
that sucker will
be null and void.
When the clock strikes,
it's game over.
I'm well aware. It'll be okay.
[JUZO]
Uh-huh.
You say that, but one
of the trustees is MIA.
So yeah, security staff's
a tad on edge at the moment.
You still gonna go
through with it?
Well, if I don't today,
I may not get another chance.
'Sides, no time
like the present!
Gotta take risks, right?
[JUZO] You're puttin' me on
the line here, too, ya know.
Sorry about that! I really
appreciate it though!
I just... wanna help Munakata
however I can, y'know?
His ideals mean the world to me.
Actually, I couldn't
care less about ideals.
Let's just say, it's kinda
nice to feel useful.
In general, I mean.
Yeah, that's it.
It's not like you're in love.
Full disclosure: I wouldn't
hesitate to die for the man.
So there!
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO] And I wouldn't
hesitate to die for you.
Make this work, all right?
Sakakura, you're--
Thank you.
Why do I put myself
through this?
I'm just a third wheel.
Like I haven't known
that for a while.
[YUKIZOME]
Okay, these are the new digs!
As of today, this building
is where you'll study
and enjoy the golden
days of youth!
Hop to, people!
It's time to get to work!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[TSUMIKI] We put ourselves
in your care, Miss.
Serve me well.
Yeah, excuse me.
What about the idiot?
He ever comin' back?
[YUKIZOME]
Uh...
I have it on good authority
he'll be joining us very soon.
You all really miss him, huh?
Eh, not so much.
Oh, wow. You're hilarious.
--No, actually.
--I hate the guy, a lot.
Now where's your
sense of camaraderie?
Komaeda's in this class,
like it or not!
[sighs]
'Kay, moving on.
So, no homeroom tomorrow
on account of the ceremony
commemorating the new building.
It'll be held in the courtyard.
Don't oversleep!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am.
[GUARD A] How 'bout them
festivities tomorrow?
[GUARD B]
Such a pain in the ass.
"Hey, guys. Why don't
you take an extra shift?
No overtime, though.
And you can't touch the food."
[GUARD A]
Yeah. If we're discrete...
[YUKIZOME]
A trustee's missing
and security's only got
a skeleton crew?
Not that I'm necessarily
complaining, of course.
Just seems strange.
Looks like this is
the right place.
Um, housekeeping.
Is anybody here?
Well I can't go
through everything.
I'd be here till morning.
[gasps]
[YUKIZOME] This belongs
to the guy who vanished?
[ENOSHIMA humming]
[chuckles]
Soup's on!
That's the thing about torture.
Use familiar, everyday stuff,
and it's so much worse.
How many potential weapons
d'you think we handle
on a daily basis?
The more harmless they seem,
the more the trauma
really sticks.
Lucky! That's Despair
you're feeling!
Say "ah"!
No way. Surely not.
What the heck? I'll give it try.
Okay!
[YUKIZOME]
What the--? What is this?
"This project
promotes the creation
and study of
humanity's salvation,
the so-called Super High
School-Level Hope.
The subject is imbued
with every talent
currently known to the
scientific community.
A byproduct of the process
involves the breaking down
of thoughts, feelings, and/or
psychological identifiers
commonly held to constitute
the subject's core personality.
Unfortunate, but in the larger
picture, a small price to pay.
As of this writing, the research
has been put into practice.
We are now in the testing
and observation phase
with regards to the
subject's capabilities."
This is awful!
We're talking about people!
Is Hope's Peak a front for...
...human experimentation?
[YUKIZOME]
Izuru Kamukura.
Izuru Kamukura!
What was that?
You realize you're just making
more work for yourself.
Moron. God help you if I
get blood on these boots.
Oh! Sorry, Junko!
I'll clean it up.
Damn right.
Make it look like
they decided this job
was over their pay-grade.
Worry about it later though.
We're on a schedule.
[MUKURO] Wh--? I'm supposed
to do that all by myself?
[ENOSHIMA]
'S what we call a "you problem."
We've been through this,
Miss Prissy Pants,
grunt-work is your domain.
[MUKURO] Oh. Okay.
You're right, of course.
[ENOSHIMA humming]
Um, this is a retinal scanner.
It's not gonna open with a card.
No problem.
I've got just the thing.
One of the trustees
was nice enough
to let me borrow it for a while.
Didn't even have to
debase myself to get it!
The Lolita aesthetic
doesn't mean I'm easy.
Open Sesame!
[BOTH gasp]
[ENOSHIMA]
Kamukura!
Shut up! It's really you!
OMG! This is awesome!
The Kamukura Project?
The board of trustees
can rot in Hell.
Trying to Frankenstein
a deus ex machina.
[YUKIZOME]
What does that mean?
Think clockwork god.
The bastards are creating a Hope
that'll do whatever they say.
[YUKIZOME]
So where do we go from here?
[MUNAKATA]
Does anyone else know?
Has this information
been leaked?
No, we're all good
on that front.
Hope's Peak knows if
this got out there,
it would be a PR nightmare.
They've taken all the
necessary precautions.
[MUNAKATA] Exposure's not
the worst-case scenario.
Imagine a creature with
every known talent
at its disposal turning hostile.
Human civilization would
be brought to its knees.
He's monstrous. A WMD
waiting to be misused.
[YUKIZOME]
Holy cow.
Hope itself would collapse
into a singularity.
Disappear, leaving Despair to
run rampant over the Earth.
[YUKIZOME]
That sounds pretty bad.
[MUNAKATA]
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Until then, listen
to your paranoia.
Apart from Sakakura,
trust no one.
Including the students.
From this point forward,
don't even let the name
Kamukura slip out.
[YUKIZOME]
Right. I understand.
[ENOSHIMA] Kamukura,
Kamukura! Yas, queen!
Gah! I'm such a huge fan!
Not to sound all stalker-y,
but can I get a hug?
Uh, Junko?
Seems like he might be
a little dangerous.
Yeah! I know! Duh!
Dangerously kickass!
Dangerously gorgeous!
[MUKURO]
That's not really what I meant.
Fat, stupid, ugly
people need to shu' up!
Fat? Stupid? Ugly?
That's me in a nutshell!
[ENOSHIMA]
Anyway--
Kamukura, good sir,
pleasure to meet'cha.
I'm Junko Enoshima
from the 78th class.
This may sound weird,
but you've been on
my mind a lot lately.
The muckety-mucks have you
squirrelled away in here
like a third-world
quarantine baby.
So not your style, pretty boy.
I mean, look at this!
You're virtually oozing
with potential!
So, like say... Heh.
Death could come for you
like a thief in the night,
leaving the world
awash in Despair!
[MUKURO]
Junko!
You son of a--
This is boring.
You do realize that nothing
you do has any meaning.
[ENOSHIMA laughs]
[ENOSHIMA] I knew you were
a fellow nihilist!
This is marvelous!
I've reached an all-time low!
But the thing is,
Kamukura darling,
no one person should claim
a monopoly on Despair.
It belongs to everyone!
[HINATA]
Despair?
From a logical perspective,
there seems no emotion
less essential.
Logical perspective!
You crack me up!
All right then, explain how
I come to be in this position.
What's your Vulcan
gestalt say about that?
Junko Enoshima.
Your capacity for
cold, hard reasoning
puts you at least 12 steps
ahead in any situation.
And yet, here you are,
knowing full well there's
no way you can win.
Aw, you really don't get it.
Guess when it comes
to cold, hard reasoning
not all roads lead to Rome.
You see, Despair is
the Great Unknown.
A girl can only be
this smart for so long
before ennui sets in.
That's the curse
of bein' bright.
Everyone goes on
and on about "hope,"
but what they really
mean is "status quo."
Ah, but Despair is a
big ol' mystery box.
There's nothing like it
to get the blood pumping,
the synapses firing,
the senses tingling.
It straight-up shatters
the status quo
and paves the way for chaos.
Think about it.
When a single assassin's bullet
can plunge humanity
into world war,
none of us are as
far from the abyss
as we'd like to tell ourselves.
Embrace that simple
fact, and voila!
You're in for the
ride of your life!
Look at me! Every nerve
ending is at 11!
Despair did that!
Come on, punkin' pie. Some part
of you has to understand.
They call you the world's
Hope, Izuru Kamukura.
And who am I to say
you're not the savior?
Therein lies the rub.
Hope only gets us as far
as what we think we want.
Safety, tranquility, boredom.
C'mon.
Nirvana looks great on paper,
but for someone with
your intelligence,
's more like Purgatory.
You're better than that.
[alarm blares]
They know we're here!
Junko, we have to make
a break for it, now!
You're a god among
insects, Kamukura!
Of course you're bored!
The world's an ant farm!
Embrace Despair and we'll
shatter the glass together!
I am your salvation! It's fate!
We were destined to
walk hand-in-hand!
Tell me you don't feel it!
[IMPOSTER]
Hey, Mitarai.
C'mon. Wake up.
[MITARAI]
Sorry.
[IMPOSTER] Don't tell me
it isn't done yet.
Nope.
But, hey, I've finally hit
the experimental stage,
so at least there's that.
You've lost me.
I'll explain when
it's more concrete.
You think maybe we can
stop with the hospital?
[IMPOSTER]
Out of the question.
You'll keep going till
the doctor gives you
a clean bill of health and
that's all there is to it.
[MITARAI sighs]
Fine, if I have to.
Oh, darn. You're not in a coma.
[MUKURO] No worries.
We're in the school infirmary.
'S okay, I covered for you.
I told 'em you fell
down the stairs.
'Course they bought it.
You're an accident waiting
to happen in those heels.
What happened to him?
[MUKURO]
Junko! No!
[HINATA] When she wakes up,
give her a message for me.
I'll be waiting. Here.
We're not in trouble at all,
so I don't think
he's told anyone.
We probably wouldn't
be in here if he had.
Uh-oh! I better hurry!
A lady doesn't keep a
gentleman in suspense!
There's something
about that guy.
He rubs me the wrong way.
Yeah?
Well snub-nosed, flat-chested
perverts only good
for killin' folks rub me
the wrong way, so there!
Wait, no! That didn't
come out how I wanted.
Junko, what are you doing?
They said you need rest.
You shouldn't be up yet.
Aww. Relax.
I can't remember the last time
someone gave me
such a thrashing.
Totes invigorating!
Being one-upped actually
has me on Cloud Nine!
[MUKURO]
W-Wait a second!
[yelps]
Can-Can I help you?
What is your name?
Uh, Ryota Mitarai.
And you are?
[ENOSHIMA gasps]
[ENOSHIMA laughs]
--Junko, stop!
--[MITARAI] Have we met before?
[ENOSHIMA] This may sound weird,
but for some reason--
In my head--oh God--
I keep hearing the words,
"Despairfully
fateful encounter."
Is today my lucky day or what?