[BULLIES]
Ready!
[BULLIES laughing]
--[BULLY A] You fit right in!
--[BULLY B] Trash!
--[BULLY C] You're dirty!
--[BULLY A] And stinky!
[BULLY B]
Do you smell yourself?
BULLY C]
Hey, get a picture of 'em!
[BULLY A] Aw, is the
garbage baby gonna cwy?
[BULLY B] Stop nerding up
our school already!
[MITARAI'S MOTHER] They bullied
him again so he came home.
What if he stops going
to school altogether?
[MITARAI'S FATHER] Look, I leave
the school stuff up to you.
[MITARAI'S MOTHER] God,
you're like a broken record,
you know that?
Whenever there's a problem,
you just check out!
He's as much your son
as he is mine!
[MITARAI]
So much left to do.
Every frame needs to pop.
That takes time.
Time I don't have.
Don't you dare stop!
The world needs this!
[YUKIZOME]
Here we are, self.
Our first day as a
Reserve Course teacher.
Come on.
[YUKIZOME] I'd give you
all the gory details
about my six months with
the Reserve Course,
but we'd be here all day.
The short version:
It sucked, big time.
The loss of my class!
The shame of exile!
Dark days and darker nights!
The embers of hope barely
aflicker in my heart!
Bending my every thought
to the redemption
that might forever
elude my grasp!
Oh, the humanity!
Yeah, for half a year.
[YUKIZOME]
March already, huh?
Time really does fly by.
[YUKIZOME] Thankfully, my
banishment to the Reserve Course
was coming to an end.
[JUZO]
Hey there, stranger.
About damn time they
brought you back.
[YUKIZOME] Sounds like somebody
was kinda worried about me.
Maybe a little bit.
So tell me,
what'd you dig up while
you were stuck over there?
[YUKIZOME]
Funny you should ask that.
Um, how tough would it be
to lift a Hope's Peak ID card
off one of the trustees?
Pretty freakin' tough.
The principal puts on
a good game face,
but they're the ones
running the show.
If I get caught,
they'll fire me. Or worse.
Have you ever heard of a thing
called the Kamukura Project?
I can't say it rings a bell.
[YUKIZOME] It's some
secret plan the principal
and board of trustees
have set into motion.
You know how Reserve Course
tuitions are sky high?
Turns out this thing is where
most of that money ends up.
The name's a red flag, too.
"Kamukura" refers
to Izuru Kamukura,
Hope's Peak's founder.
They wouldn't pin his name
to something mundane,
so whatever it is, it's big.
Look.
The only way to dig any deeper
is with an ID in hand.
Without it, we're
dead in the water.
When Munakata gives you a job,
you really don't mess around.
Oh, you're as loyal
as I am. 'Fess up!
Tch!
By the way, do you remember
that boy you beat up?
[JUZO]
Huh? Which one?
Hinata, from the
Reserve Course,
you caught him
trying to trespass.
[JUZO]
Yeah, him. Why?
Is he connected to your
investigation somehow?
[YUKIZOME] Back when I was
first hearing whispers
about the Kamukura Project,
I found out he'd been expelled.
[YUKIZOME]
Huh?
So I... I can return to
my first group of kids?
No one ever doubted your talent.
It'd be a waste to leave you
in the Reserve Course.
Starting today, you're their
official homeroom teacher.
Thank you, sir!
I've missed them so much!
I told ya she's tear up.
Typical Chisa.
Honestly, I should've taken
the blame for that bomb thing.
So, you're gonna focus
on scouting full-time
from now on, right?
Yeah. I'm way better
at that anyhow.
That class is all yours.
And see to it that your students
don't make the news again.
Hey, uh,
I don't suppose you've had
any luck reaching Komaeda.
No pun intended.
If I know that kid, probably
entered some contest
and won a cruise
'round the world.
That's unfortunate.
Yeah. 'Specially for
our esteemed principal here.
He's been trying to lift
that suspension for a while.
That is so kind of you!
Thank you. But we still
don't have a timeline for it.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'll come right back here
if you need me to,
but could I go see
my students for a bit?
Of course. Go crazy.
'Kay!
[KIZAKURA chuckles]
Look at 'er. All idealistic.
We need to prep the
entrance ceremony.
There's still plenty to do.
This year's bumper crop
made for multiple classes.
Next year is kinda slim
pickings by comparison.
[JIN] Blame it on the
talent scout, I guess.
Duly noted.
For whatever it's worth,
the few I got are absolute
top of the heap.
Trust me, you're not gonna sweat
an empty desk here or there.
We shall see.
I'm just that rookie teacher
who got busted down
to the Reserve Course.
They've probably
forgotten all about me.
You've got this!
If I let something
like this beat me,
Kyosuke will think I'm an idiot!
Now, as Kyosuke's
future beloved,
I shouldn't give him
any reason to...
Oh my gosh! Did I
say that out loud?
Damn the torpedoes!
Hey, you guys! Remem--?
[yelps]
[CLASS] Welcome home!
You're back where you belong!
[CLASS chattering]
Welcome back!
Finally!
Uh, Miss Yukizo--?
What is up, dawg?
Yeah! Get hype!
You were gone for so long.
I hope that you've been well.
Yes. Thanks.
Why ya so flustered,
Teach? It's just us.
Grab a plate and go nuts!
I was hardcore pining for
your return all these months.
Don't tell me you're
gonna be all like,
"Yeah, Ibuki, whatever!"
No. I mean. I'm glad
to be back. Honestly.
I just thought that maybe
you forgot about me,
having been gone for so long.
Thank Nanami. She's the
one who planned all this.
This is wonderful.
Thank you so much!
It's nothing.
I only knew when 'cause Mr.
Kizakura was talking about it.
[NIDAI grunts]
Don't you dare sell
yourself short!
You were the glue that
held this class together
the last half a year!
As the resident Super High
School-Level Team Manager,
I say that you're the shit!
This girl was truly unstoppable.
She held game tournaments
and picnics and what not
for us all the time.
Anything we needed
to raise morale.
She's quiet, but her
work is meticulous.
Hey, Miss Yukizome check it!
Even our little yakuza
came to the party!
Ugh. I was already here!
[HANAMURA chuckles]
At first, he wanted nothin'
to do with our current soiree,
but when he saw how
hard Nanami was workin',
his delinquent heart defrosted.
Shut it, pervert!
That's amazing! You really
gave this your all!
I'm super proud of you!
It was more like a speed
run than a boss fight.
Honestly, having
you back again's
what makes it a
good party for us.
You perfect cinnamon roll!
While I was gone,
you leveled up so much!
That's a bit of an exaggeration.
[YUKIZOME gasps]
[YUKIZOME]
By the way, where is Saionji?
She's in the can! Bad time
to have to pee, am I right?
Ugh. She swore up and
down she's be here.
[door opens]
[SAIONJI] Hey! It's
Miss Yukizome! Welcome back!
Oh! You must be Saionji's...
older... sister?
[SAIONJI chuckles]
[SAIONJI]
C'mon! It's me!
Uh... huh...
Her growth spurt was legendary.
Getting bigger has
been a wish come true!
I'm finally strong enough
to tie Tsumiki's body
into a big cry baby pretzel!
What did I ever do
to you, Saionji?!
[YUKIZOME] Same old Saionji
on the inside, I guess.
My friends, our mentor
has returned unto us.
This truly is a day for revelry!
With a toast to the Lords of
the Nine Circles of Hell...
...let our abyssal feast....
[BOTH]
...brook no delay!
Don't tell me
you're in sync now!
Looks like Sonia's picked
up your mannerisms
while I was gone.
Here. Have a cup.
Ready, and...
show her some love!
[CLASS]
Welcome back! We missed you!
Ma'am!
You guys.
I'm home!
[MITARAI] Friendship? I have no
time for that kind of thing.
I need.... I need to dedicate
every breath to my art!
You gotta chill out,
Mitarai. I mean it.
[MITARAI]
I've lost another day.
Every frame needs
to inspire hope.
Failure comes at
too high a price!
[MITARAI]
It needs to serve as a beacon.
This show needs to offer its
viewers a chance at redemption.
[OTHER MITARAI]
Of course.
Well at least take
a food break.
I wouldn't dig through
his browser history,
but you can't beat
Hanamura's cooking.
People flake out
and let'cha down,
but carbs are always there.
His talent eats away at him.
What is that like, I wonder...
[ENOSHIMA]
Thank you so much.
'N keep the change, buddy.
[CAB DRIVER]
Wow! Must be my lucky day!
[ENOSHIMA]
Aw, you jinxed it.
[ticking]
[chuckles]
All right, hold onto
your butts, people,
'cause Junko Enoshima is
ready for her epic entrance!
He-he!
[ENOSHIMA] "A ravishing
young girl sits at the airport,
waiting.
Her name? Junko Enoshima.
Just then, a familiar face.
Yes, the other of the Despair
Sisters, the smelly one.
Mukuro Ikusaba."
Hey, Junko.
I'm grateful you came to meet me
and all, but what're you doing?
Duh! I'm doing the narration!
Oh. Okay. Cool.
"And so the event which would
later bone the whole world,
the Biggest, Most Atrocious,
Despair-Inducing Incident
in Human History,
was finally set into
motion that afternoon.
Nobody realized it just yet,
but they would soon enough."
Oh, Junko.
Ah!
Tell me the truth!
Do you have more freckles now
than you did the last time
we got to hang out?
What? Do you think I do?
It's a fact, not some
half-assed opinion!
I'm testing your
honesty, dumbass!
Then no. I don't.
My vision's 10,000
over 20! I see 'em!
Bet that comes in
handy as a fashionista.
[MUKURO]
Wow!
Junko's trying to stab me
to death with an ice-pick.
She's such an artist.
Trying to murder her
sister with her own hands
to taste of that despair.
[explosion]
[MUKURO]
Oh, Junko.
What an effect my bloody
corpse would have on you.
[ENOSHIMA]
Good Lord, you're rank!
It's like if swamp ass
and Shark Week had a baby.
Would it kill you to
take a friggin' bath?
What? But I bathe.
Well, then you must
have B.O. strong enough
to kill a horse, 'cause damn!
Anyway, why did you want me
here in the first place, Junko?
'Cause tomorrow's our high
school entrance ceremony.
High school?
I'll spell it out for you
so your remaining brain cells
don't burst from
the exertion, okay?
There's an elite high
school in our future.
This place is so
far up its own ass,
they actually call it
"the High School of Hope."
They want me, of course,
and your dumb ass is
comin' along for the ride.
Double trouble;
they want us both!
Look at that smile.
You're really happy about this.
Yeah! I'm friggin' ecstatic!
My heart is beating a mile a
minute just thinking about it!
[MITARAI]
Never been good at sports.
Or people skills,
for that matter.
My only solace as a kid...
...was drawing.
You know, it's good
to have goals,
but it's a waste
if you fall over dead.
Seriously, man, pace yourself.
[MITARAI] Animation...
gave me something to live for.
Yeah, I gathered that.
When I'm done,
my suffering will give other
lost souls their solace...
Mitarai?
[MITARAI] I wanna...
save the world... with my art.
'Less I do something quick,
I don't think he's
gonna make it.
[giggles]
It's crazy that as of tomorrow,
I'm an upperclassman in high--
You're coming with me.
[TSUMIKI]
Huh?
[OTHER MITARAI]
I need you, right now.
You need--? Like how--?
This is it. Now? Why?
My life is about to turn into
a late night cable movie!
How is he?
Well, he's overworked.
And he's got a case
of malnutrition.
If he starts eating right
and getting some rest,
he should feel better
soon, although...
What's going on in here?
I basically kidnapped
you earlier.
Making sense of all this
is the least I can do.
Feel free to be vague!
Or if you don't wanna tell
me anything, that's okay!
[OTHER MITARAI]
Here's what happened.
It was back around the
start of the school year.
I'd be hanging out
in my room alone
and I'd hear these weird
noises out in the hall.
When did I...
eat something last?
Who're you?
That's the question, isn't it?
There's no proof that I
exist and I have no family.
[IMPOSTER] All I have in
this world is my ability
to pass as other people.
Comes in pretty handy.
I haven't lived as me in forever
now, and no one's the wiser.
That said, this one's got
an expiration date on it.
Clock's ticking.
We've never met before, but
I've done my homework on you.
[MITARAI]
What did you find out?
You're not what I'd call
a well-rounded person.
Animation is all you
give a damn about.
If it were an option,
you'd chain yourself to that
tablet and draw forever.
[MITARAI]
Uh, yeah. You're not wrong.
Every waking moment, I just
wanna make more anime.
[IMPOSTER] I could run
interference for you.
Take ol' Ryota Mitarai
out for a spin
and leave you free to create.
[IMPOSTER]
There was Mitarai,
who wanted to mothball
his existence for art.
And there was me, who
needed a makeover anyhow.
It seemed like a
good deal all around.
[IMPOSTER] So yeah,
now you know our secret.
What's the matter?
I've-- I've stumbled into
a secret conspiracy.
I've seen enough movies to know
this is the part
where you kill me!
[sighs]
No one's gonna kill you.
[TSUMIKI] Then is this the part
where I show how grateful I am?
[IMPOSTER]
Hm?
It's just... I've never done
this sort of thing before,
so you'll have to
be patient with me.
[IMPOSTER]
No need for that.
I know that I can
trust you, Tsumiki.
You just said... you trust me.
Thank you so much for telling
me that, whoever you are!
Really, it means...
I don't get why you're
so worked up over it.
That was the single nicest thing
anyone's said to me
in my whole entire life!
[crying]
As of tomorrow, you're a
bona fide upperclassman.
Have more faith in yourself.
[TSUMIKI]
O-Okay!
[NAEGI]
Wow.
So, Naegi. Are you ready?
Let's go!
[ENOSHIMA] "A fateful gust
of wind blew past.
In that moment, the pair who
would plunge the Academy,
and later the whole damn world,
into the depths of Despair...
...first laid eyes on the powder
keg they'd soon ignite."
That's impressive.
You've really taken to
narration, haven't you?
Well, I had. But now, done!
Drink it in, Mukuro!
This is where our lives are
truly gonna kick into gear!
[laughs]
[ENOSHIMA]
Man, I can't wait!
Maybe Fate will even drop
someone into my lap!
Turn off your brain
and fit into your slot.
Anything more is futile.
Be a good little dog and
take to the collar and leash.
If you're lucky, we'll throw
you the occasional bone.
[HINATA]
Well then, see you later.
[NANAMI]
Yeah! See ya tomorrow!
[HINATA]
Nanami.
I just...
Time to go.
[MAN A]
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
You may feel a tad out of sorts
when you regain consciousness.
But that will pass soon enough.
In exchange, you
become a young man
who embodies the lofty
ideals of this academy.
[HINATA]
I accept.
So I can live the
life I wanna lead.
So that I can become
the hero of my own story.
So that I can hold my head high.
Next to her.