[YUKIZOME]
'Kay, have the handouts made it
all the way to the back?
It's very important
everyone has one.
This is the schedule
for the practical exams.
They start tomorrow so whatever
you need to be ready,
get on it.
As you all know,
we don't do final exams by
term here at Hope's Peak.
So in lieu of that,
the school holds targeted
practical exams once a year.
Now keep in mind, if your
results are below average,
you might not be
allowed to stay.
Having said that,
I'm sure you'll be amazing!
Put those talents on display.
Show us teachers the
kind of awesomeness
our students are capable of!
Y'know, just do your best!
[YUKIZOME]
You want me to cancel the exams?
Please.
[YUKIZOME]
Look, I get it. I do.
We're all feeling kinda down
after what happened.
Normally it wouldn't
be a problem.
Compared to me,
everyone has enough talent
to pass with flying
colors, sure.
But, I mean,
wouldn't it be a better
gage of our abilities
if we waited till
we were in top form?
I'm a team player.
The sort of guy who wants
to see his classmates shine
as brightly as possible.
Well, we're on the same page
as far as that's concerned.
But I'm sorry.
I'm told we're expecting
a bit of media coverage.
A cancellation would
gum up the works.
[KOMAEDA]
I see. Never mind then.
Oh, are you sure?
[KOMAEDA]
Of course.
Thank you for your
time, Miss. Good day.
[chuckles]
Meh. I was going out
on a limb. Oh well.
No need to fret we
can always move on...
...to Plan B.
[NANAMI] Hinata. You're
not coming today, either?
[HANAMURA gasping]
I'm overjoyed to see
that you like it, my friend.
[HANAMURA]
This is outstanding!
When it hit the street,
Sayaka Maizono's photo album
sold out in record time!
Mere seconds!
To think that I would ever
possess my own copy!
Weird it was just lying there
at the side of the road.
[HANAMURA]
You happened on this by chance?
Yes, well, no matter.
Thank you, my friend.
I am in your debt!
A Manchu Imperial
Feast awaits you!
If you wanted to thank
me actually, uh...
What was that girl's name?
The one who helped you?
Sorry.
I believe she gave you the
stuff for your Doping Corn Soup.
The Super High
School-Level Pharmacist.
[KOMAEDA]
Hi.
[SEIKO screams]
Why would you surprise me?!
Do you have death wish?
[KOMAEDA]
My apologies.
Unless I'm mistaken,
that's the laxative I ordered.
[SEIKO] It's called a
Re-activator, to be precise.
A drug that promotes
peristalsis of the intestine.
Ah! Wonderful!
Well whatever the name,
it'll be great to get
things moving again.
How lucky am I that
we were introduced?
Yes, the Fates smile--
[RURUKA] Hey, come on!
I know you're in there!
I will break down this
door if I have to!
[SEIKO]
It's unlocked.
[RURUKA]
Let me in!
Um.
[SEIKO]
Don't worry about it.
Very back of the storage room.
Top shelf. Far right.
Help yourself.
Use in moderation.
It's strong stuff.
Top shelf. Far right.
Jeez, took ya long enough.
Okay.
[RURUKA] Anyways, not to
bore you with details,
but that's why we need
your signature
performance-enhancing drug.
Delicious, babe.
[giggles]
[SEIKO] Strictly speaking,
it's not a performance enhancer.
That's just a side effect.
Re-animators are complicated.
Sometimes they boost metabolic--
Ah, a side effect
is still an effect.
If it gets the job done,
no need to sweat
the particulars.
[SEIKO]
But I'm--
I'm planning to
unveil it for my exam.
Huh?
So what I'm hearing is, you're
not gonna give me what I want.
[KOMAEDA]
Top shelf. Far right. Let's see.
Ah. Here we are.
[SEIKO] Why do you always
pick the worst times
to ask me for help?
Yeah, I know.
We rely on you too much.
It's a burden,
but we are totally sorry.
I get it.
My timing stinks.
You've got a lot on your plate.
But if I can't turn to
a childhood friend,
what can I do?
[SEIKO]
Please don't.
[RURUKA]
I'm begging you.
You're the only
one who can help.
That is what friends
are for, right?
And I mean. We are...
...besties.
Forever.
[KOMAEDA]
Huh.
Okay.
[chuckles]
Might as well
leave it to chance.
My luck being what
it is, why not?
This one.
[SEIKO]
Fine. I'll give you the drug.
Yippee!
[RURUKA] Thanks, doll!
I'll grab it myself.
[SEIKO]
Uhh...
You know, you never
eat my sweets.
Hurts a teensy 'lil bit.
[yelps]
Excuse me.
Who're you?
[SEIKO] One of the First Years.
He came for a laxative.
[KOMAEDA chuckles]
[SOHNOSUKE]
Hmph.
Well you got what you need,
so get out of here, freak.
[RURUKA]
Hey, so...
Which one of 'em's
the good stuff?
All your fancy containers
look the same.
[SEIKO] They're clearly labeled.
Very back. Top shelf. Middle.
[RURUKA]
Duh!
[RURUKA] Thanks a billion,
Seiko. You rock.
[RURUKA giggles]
[sighs]
[TEACHER A]
Who would do this?
[TEACHER B]
We should let security know.
Can't be too careful these days.
Our job gives us enough
to worry about as it is.
[TEACHER C]
"Flames of Judgment"?
Are we talking arson?
[TEACHER E] Knowing these kids,
it could easily be an explosive.
[TEACHER D] Oh, surely it's
just some stupid prank.
[SEIKO] Oh! I knew I'd
sleep through the alarm.
I shouldn't have pulled
an all-nighter!
Damn it, Ruruka!
This is all your fault!
[SEIKO yelps]
Ugh, right in the--
Uh. Kimura, what are you--?
[SEIKO]
Oh, no. Not again.
Sorry. You okay?
[SEIKO]
Yes.
Tough break. Seems luck
has it in for us both.
[SEIKO]
How is the, uh, issue?
[KOMAEDA chuckles]
That concoction of
yours is a miracle cure!
Must've lost five pounds!
[SEIKO]
Huh?
[giggling]
[SEIKO]
Ah! I'm late!
So much for that, then.
They don't call me
the Super High School-Level
Lucky Student for nothing,
I guess.
Good. Shall we begin then?
And you are the Super High
School-Level Confectioner?
This should be great!
Thank you.
[clears throat]
I present to you, Sky Blue
Heaven Days Choux Crèmes!
If I had to sum them up in
a word, it would be "divine."
Just wait. They're more than
just ridiculously delicious.
With one simple tiny bite,
however exhausted you might be,
you'll perk up and feel
like a million bucks,
ready to face the day!
In fact, it's not uncommon
to feel the urge to fly!
Prepare yourselves! These choux
crèmes are très supreme!
[TEACHERS chuckle]
[TEACHER B] Well, all
right, then. Let's dig in!
[RURUKA] Seiko's performance
enhancers are the bomb.
Pack it in, folks: I nailed it.
Behold my Doping Choux Crèmes!
That's right.
Quake with ecstasy at their
unparalleled scrumptiousness!
[gasps]
Unbelievable!
It's like I'm soaring
through the stratosphere!
Oh my word!
I'm plunging headlong
over Niagara Falls!
That's it, yes!
You're exactly right!
[groans]
[TEACHERS groaning]
[RURUKA]
Huh?
You said... Oh, God.
What on earth did
you put in these?
Um. Uh.
That's not supposed to happen.
[SEIKO gasps]
[SOHNOSUKE]
Ruruka.
What the hell is going on?
[SEIKO] I don't understand.
What went wrong?
I don't know! I just--!
[SEIKO]
Oh no.
You gave them... a laxative!
[TEACHER A]
Excuse me? A what?
[TEACHER B] Good Lord!
Why would you do such a thing?!
You didn't. Is this a joke?
[SEIKO]
Huh? No! I... uh--
[RURUKA]
I don't believe it.
I've been thrown under the bus.
You did this on purpose!
[gasps]
[SEIKO] There's been a mistake.
I would never--
[RURUKA] Don't try to play
innocent! Look as this!
Did you or did you not tell
me this specific drug?
[TEACHER B]
I see.
Well, at least we know who's
responsible for the threat.
[SEIKO]
What? No!
Traitor! What are you
trying to pull here?
[gasps]
[SEIKO]
Look, it's gonna be okay.
I can mix up an antidote real--
[SEIKO]
What the...? When did...?
[TEACHER B] That--
That looks like a detonator!
Did she say detonator?
[CROWD mummbling]
[CROWD shouting]
[SOHNOSUKE]
Kimura. Why?
[SEIKO]
Wait! This isn't mine!
And the drug in the pastries
should've been different.
This was all for Ruruka!
Just ask her! We're besties!
[RURUKA]
How dare you.
[gasps]
Why would you set me
up to fail like this?
You're a horrible person.
We're not besties
and we never will be.
I'd have been better
off putting myself
at the mercy of a stranger!
You conniving, subhuman trash!
[gasps]
[SEIKO]
You don't mean that.
After everything
I've done for you...
I never complained,
never asked questions.
Don't even try!
I trusted you!
I put my heart in your hands
and you squashed
it like an éclair!
[SEIKO]
What are you talking about?
You just use me!
That's all you've ever done!
I bend over backwards for you.
I only gave you the drug
because you asked for it!
I should've known better
than to believe in someone
who won't even try my sweets!
This entire debacle
is your fault!
You're a filthy traitor!
[growls]
You're outta your damn mind!
How is the mess you
got us into my fault?
Ugh! If anyone's a
traitor here, it's you!
[KOMAEDA]
Laxatives: Check.
Explosives: Check.
All ready to deal
with the examiners.
[KOMAEDA]
Uhh...
I wouldn't do that.
[DOG yelping]
I don't think that
was a laxative.
Ugh. 'Least I still
have the bomb.
Or a carton of medicine.
The ol' switcheroo.
Just my luck. Fantastic.
Bad dog! No!
[DOG barking]
[SOHNOSUKE]
Huh?
'Course I'd get the wrong drug.
Why not the wrong bag
while I'm at it, right?
My luck.
Could it be any worse?
Imagine this happening to me.
The Super High School-Level
Lucky Student himself
experiencing such disaster.
Wow. I'm so fortunate!
Huh. And here I thought
nothin' was gonna go my way.
But look at this.
Lady Luck graced me after all.
Guess it doesn't matter
how you get there.
[sirens wailing]
This is so bad. Extremely.
[KOMAEDA]
There are those who are worthy
and those not so worthy.
We're in one group or the other
from the moment we
draw our first breath.
If a person isn't
one of the chosen,
there's not much they can do.
No one's anointed
by elbow grease.
It's clear. Inborn talent
is simply all that matters.
That's our world and
I wanna help the worthy
shine as brightly as possible.
When two species
of Hope collide,
I wanna be there to
watch the fireworks.
Imagine what a
privilege that'd be.
The chosen ones
going head-to-head
as they come into their own.
Hope isn't supposed to be
a battlefield, not like that.
I understand, Miss.
Don't pay attention
to what I say,
just the philosophical
musings of a no one.
[slap]
Don't ever talk about
yourself like that.
You're not "no one."
You're my student. Understand?
I'm your teacher
and darn proud of it.
Miss Yukizome.
You're all graduating together.
You have my word.
[KIZAKURA sighs]
Three exceptional students
all expelled on the same day.
Wounds my sensibilities
as a scout.
[JIN] The bombing garnered
quite a bit of media attention.
The public's clamoring
for the perpetrator.
[KIZAKURA] Yeah, with
something this off the rails,
I suppose we don't
have much of a choice.
So what's the story
on Komaeda?
[JIN] I understand the boy
was an innocent bystander,
unwittingly caught up in
someone else's mischief?
You're sticking by
that assertion?
[KIZAKURA]
Thing is,
there are more than a
handful of eyewitnesses
who'll swear he was
the mastermind.
They're rattling for
his expulsion too.
My negligence is to blame!
If they need someone
to scapegoat,
point the finger at me!
[JIN] Even if your student was
the plot's chief architect,
he didn't administer
the laxatives
or for that matter
trigger the bomb.
Period.
We have to look at
the bigger picture.
If he brought about
a measurable result
without direct intervention,
that's a talent we
don't dare let go.
[JIN sighs]
That said, of course,
the boy has to be suspended.
And his homeroom teacher
placed on probation.
As the assistant
homeroom teacher,
you will be transferred
to the Reserve Course,
which I trust is a
satisfactory compromise.
Very much so. Thank you, sir.
[JIN]
Good.
The practical exams
will be postponed.
[sighs]
Luck is a terrifying thing.
Way to go, kid. Way to go.
[sighs]
Hey, there! Good morn--
So you've, uh,
heard the announcement.
[chairs scraping]
C'mon, Teach!
Somebody screwed up, right?
What's this bullshit
about you being transferred
to the Reserve Course?
They want us to finish out the
year with some substitute hack?
D'you hear about Komaeda
gettin' suspended?
He'll return eventually.
He just, uh, got swept up in
unfortunate circumstances.
[SAIONJI] Gee, you think?
The gym was totally destroyed!
[SODA]
What'd the genius do now?
[YUKIZOME]
He was thinking of you.
His only thought was
helping his classmates.
Sure, his methods
were questionable.
Wait, he did all that for us?
That's right. Bear that
in mind when he comes back.
And give him a warm
welcome for me.
[TSUMIKI whimpers]
Do you really have to go?
[SONIA crying]
There's no need for tears.
Officially they're
calling it a transfer,
but it's more like training.
I'm not through with you yet.
Oh no?
You haven't seen the
last of me, kiddos.
I'm your teacher.
Don't you ever forget it!
I know me going on hiatus isn't
ideal, but I'll come back.
Look forward to that day
and don't lose heart.
We're all in this together.
Class Representative,
in the meantime,
protect everyone.
Yes, ma'am. Of course.
Hey, hey. Good news.
They busted me down
to the Reserve Course.
So yeah, should make
the investigation easier.
You don't sound
terribly pleased.
There some sort of catch?
[YUKIZOME] Oh. Heh...
Nothing like that, silly.
[YUKIZOME]
It's just...
I don't know. Tough saying
goodbye to the kids, I suppose.
Real professional, huh?
What's gotten into me?
I'm conducting an investigation.
[MUNAKATA]
Yukizome.
Sorry. Anyway,
the Reserve Course.
Here we go.