[ENOSHIMA]
So what'cha got, Mitarai?
Come on!
Show me what awesome talent
you got hidden away.
[MITARAI]
Uh. Who, me?
Just the Super High
School-Level Animator's all.
[ENOSHIMA] Really?
They let you in for that?
Wow, if I were a gigantic weeb,
I'd probably be impressed by ya.
[MITARAI] You think anime's
just for nerds?
Well, duh.
Anime is an important
part of our culture!
[ENOSHIMA]
Aw, look at him tremble!
He's gonna burst a blood vessel
'cause I dissed his waifus!
Yeah?
Once my project is done, you
won't get to laugh like that!
[yelps]
[ENOSHIMA]
Is that so?
Okay. Challenge accepted.
[MITARAI]
So, uh, what's the verdict?
I mean, it's a work in progress.
Half of it's just line-art.
Damn! That's gonna
redefine the genre!
Now that I've laid eyes
on your magnum opus,
no other animation will
ever do it for me again!
All the other series
and movies I watched
were just so much trash!
We don't need you anymore,
garbage-tier anime!
You're dead to me! Dead!
[MITARAI screaming]
What're you doing to
my precious collection?
[MITARAI screams]
What the heck's wrong with her?
Don't look so shocked.
My simpering A-cup of a sister
was touched by your genius too.
Hey! How'd your movie get
under our skin like that?
'Fess up! You put a 'lil sump'm,
sump'm in there, huh?
Look at it.
The smoking gun's right there
if you know what to look for.
How I influence
my viewer's brain.
[ENOSHIMA]
So mental manipulation?
That's pretty broad.
What's your jam?
Oh, subliminal!
I'm right, right?
[MITARAI]
I use it all.
[ENOSHIMA]
Keep talking.
[MITARAI]
Subtle changes in coloring
trigger the visual cortex.
Guiding the eye
in certain directions
enriches the viewer's memories.
Use of sound can
heighten one's focus.
Any trick I know,
I've put it in here.
Some of them are considered
brainwashing, technically.
Kinda like gunpowder.
You can make a bomb,
or a beautiful firework.
I wanna use my anime to make
the world a better place.
[chuckles]
[ENOSHIMA]
Sa-wing, batta!
[MITARAI yelps]
[ENOSHIMA]
What a coinky-dink.
I was just thinkin' to myself
I wanted to make the
world a better place!
[TANAKA grunting]
Ka!
[roars]
Whoa.
[KUZURYU]
What the hell?
[SODA]
Dude brought a bear in.
I think it's adorable!
Just don't go tryin'
to pet it or anything.
[TANAKA]
Fear not, Princess.
Grizner will only loose his
ursine rage against a demon
many levels higher than himself.
I'm a low-level demon?
I had no idea!
Well, yeah. 'Course you are.
It's 'cause you're such
a high-level angel!
[SODA chuckles]
I'm still not sure why there's
a bear in the classroom. Hm?
That's a good spot for it.
[KOIZUMI]
Uh... What's the orchid about?
Wow. Cold. It's in memory
of poor dead Komaeda.
[KOIZUMI]
Stop saying he's dead!
All they did was give
him a suspension!
Eh, true enough, but no one's
been able to get a hold of him.
What a flake. 'Least he
could do is call us.
[KOMAEDA] ♪ I just count the
hours till we get to meet. ♪
♪ But every minute is a
lifetime when I'm alone. ♪
[chuckles]
[KOMAEDA]
What're the odds of finding this
steps away from the crash?
My luck is the stuff of legend.
[SAIONJI] Hold on. Don't tell
me the klutz is a no-show.
If you're lookin' for Mikan,
she totally peaced-out
with Ryota earlier.
It's kinda weird, them
hanging out all the time.
What if right this minute,
the two of 'em...
...are gettin' extracurricular?
Here!
[SODA]
Huh?
[HANAMURA] Oh, somewhere within
the academy's hallowed halls,
Tsumiki's delectable
doughnut will face...
...the manly ministrations
of Mitarai's banana!
Yes!
[SODA, HANAMURA scream]
[TANAKA] Karma, thou perverts.
May darkness consume you!
Still wondering why
there's a bear.
[TSUMIKI] Wait, Mitarai
vanished without a trace?
[IMPOSTER] Not so loud.
I wanna keep it under wraps.
[TSUMIKI gasps]
It's been a week now,
give or take.
I went into his room
and found a note.
Said he was leaving
to focus on work.
But nothing since.
Uh. I guess I could check his
room for clues or something?
Maybe he came back
in the meantime.
Y'know, to grab his stuff.
[gasps]
You look angry.
What's going on?
Yeah, angry is an
understatement.
We've got 20 missing
staff members.
All of 'em disappeared.
As though they'd never even
been here in the first place.
But that's... that's insane!
And that's not all.
The trustees are
pissing themselves.
They had me beef up security
around you and the kids.
Do you think it has to do
with the Kamukura Project?
[JUZO]
Who can say?
They've circled the
wagons so damn tight,
I have no idea what's
really going on.
Whatever. At the end of the day,
you're still sniffing around
some dangerous people.
Stick your head out any further
and you're gonna lose it.
[YUKIZOME]
I'm ready to pay that price.
Hey! It's not a game!
If they were to hurt you--!
[YUKIZOME]
I told you, silly.
I would gladly lay down
my life for Munakata.
Don't let emotions mess with
the job you're here to do.
You sound jealous. Careful!
Ya got me.
Huh?
Oh! That's sweet of you, but--
Why are you getting all
flustered, huh? It was a joke.
[YUKIZOME]
What?!
Ugh! You can't say stuff like
that to a girl! You butthead!
Hey, you!
So, buddy, ya likin'
the new digs?
Yeah.
The equipment's top-drawer,
and I'm all alone.
I've never been more productive.
[ENOSHIMA]
'Course you haven't!
I got this room all
dolled up for you
by the Hope's Peak
trustees themselves.
I told them not to half-ass it,
and boy did they deliver!
Oh, and speaking of "deliver,"
my sister found this
little "souvenir"
when she went over to pack
up the rest of your stuff.
[MITARAI]
Hm?
[MUKURO] This girl,
have you seen her before?
[MITARAI]
Uh!
Tsumiki?
[ENOSHIMA]
Well, fancy that.
I figured she was
just some rando.
Thank goodness!
They-- They didn't
hurt you, did they?
No, I'm fine.
[TSUMIKI]
I was so worried, Mitarai.
Why on earth do they have
you locked away here?
[MITARAI] They, uh, gave me
a new work-space, that's all.
Ah...
[chuckles]
[ENOSHIMA crying]
I'm sorry.
I get so damn emotional.
What a heartfelt reunion.
That's okay. But who are you?
[ENOSHIMA] One of Mitarai's
anime friends, naturally.
Boom!
Let's celebrate you cuh-razy
kids finding each other
by watching Mitarai's
masterpiece!
Cue up that bad-boy, dude!
We're not gettin'
any younger here!
[TSUMIKI crying]
[TSUMIKI] I've never seen
anything so moving before!
[ENOSHIMA chuckles]
[MUKURO]
Having already watched it once,
Junko was able to analyze
it this time through.
Her mind can parse any
information in a flash.
That trait, is my sister's
most formidable skill.
Did an animal die
in your mouth?
[MUKURO]
Huh?
[ENOSHIMA]
Hmm. I got this on lock.
Hey! What time've you got?
[MUKURO]
Uh, 6:50, give or take a minute.
Oh, man, how did the day
get away from me like that?
And why does your breath
smell like a hot stockyard?
So, we gotta go,
but you have fun!
Have Mitarai give you
the ol' mouse-pad
or body pillow treatment!
It'll perk ya up! Bye!
[MITARAI]
Uhh?
[ENOSHIMA]
Oh, Kamukura!
Feel like going... on a date?
--[thud]
--[GUARD screams]
[HINATA] I hope you have
a compelling reason
for dragging me
out here like this.
Oh, I do!
There's something
I wanna show you,
something oh-so-special to me.
I'd get quite the reputation
if you told anyone
about this though.
I want this to be perfect.
I've been so worried about it.
I've barely gotten
a wink of sleep!
Or--
I just made that up!
Boy, I'm a hooker for innuendo
at inappropriate times!
We're out here so I can show
you the wonder of Despair
on an epic scale!
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER A]
You! Talk!
I don't know where you
get off threatening us,
but it's not gonna to work!
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER M]
Th-That video... was it real?
Why'd we have to hold
this dumb meeting so late?
This is not at all
how we operate.
Student council members,
in accordance with
my sister's will,
you will now murder each other.
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER B]
Huh?!
Are you crazy?! Why the hell
would we do something like that?
That's enough! It's essential
that we all remain calm!
Should we succumb
to panic here--
[gunshot]
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBERS scream]
[MUKURO] You have two options,
and only two options.
Attack your classmates
and hope for the best.
Or end up like
your friend there.
What's up? I'm your
host, Junko Enoshima!
I brought a little something to
help get this party started,
if you know what I'm saying.
What the hell?
[ENOSHIMA] You're gonna
be way less kumbayah
once I pop these puppies open!
Show 'em what they've won!
Family secrets, hidden scandals,
dirty money, sex,
lies, good stuff!
Each tape is weapons-grade
blackmail.
And you'll notice that I've got
one for every person here.
Gosh. Be a shame
if they got out.
You... You want us to use these?
Everyone listten!
None of us are going
to kill each other!
We stand together through
thick and thin, right?
Yeah. He's right.
We're all friends!
And friends don't
abandon each other!
We're better than that!
You talk a big game about
meeting your end together.
But I know for a
fact you're gonna be
murdering the ever-living
crap out of each other
in like a minute, tops!
Hit it, sis!
[MUKURO]
You want me to... sing this?
[ENOSHIMA chuckles]
With feeling!
[MUKURO]
Huh?
What if we all just run?
Maybe they kill three or four of
us, but the rest get to safety!
[clatter]
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBERS gasp]
What do you think
you're doing?
Those two girls need to die!
I have to avenge her murder!
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER I]
Easy!
Don't you "easy" me!
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER I]
Just put down the gun, man!
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER C]
Why? Don't you trust me?
Hey! Both of you, put it down!
'Kay, I'm sorry!
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBERS scream]
God, no.
How could you do such a thing?
They kidnapped my mom.
They have her.
You may be my friends,
but I'll kill you.
I have to!
For my mother!
[STUDENT COUNCIL
MEMBER J screams]
Stop it! Stop it!
I don't wanna die!
I've got ya.
--[thud]
--[screams]
[yelling]
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER E]
Die! Die! Die! Die!
[ENOSHIMA]
Hope is a state of harmony.
Righteous and bright,
and all that other BS.
Despair is more fun.
And it grows so quickly.
Like mushrooms,
over a single night.
[STUDENT COUNCIL
MEMBER M yelling]
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER M]
Stop running and lemme kill you!
[ENOSHIMA]
Despair is messy and confusing.
And it ain't much
of a picky eater.
It devours love, hate,
the whole shebang.
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER G]
My darling.
If we must die,
then let us do it together.
We can turn death into
something beautiful.
[thud]
[ENOSHIMA] Despair takes
the plans you've put
all your faith into
and rips 'em to shreds.
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER H]
Why...?
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER I]
You want together?
I'll give it to you!
[screaming]
Oh my God, it hurts!
It hurts so much!
Please! Just leave me alone!
[STUDENT COUNCIL
MEMBER I laughing]
[ENOSHIMA] You may think you're
above petty human desires,
but you need Despair.
When it's calling the shots,
all bets are off.
You don't wanna be
bored outta your skull
for the rest of forever, do ya?
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER N] Don't
do it. Please, I'm begging you!
--No!
--[gunshot]
[laughing]
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER E]
I did it.
Last man standing.
Them or me, right?
[laughing]
[retches]
[gasps]
[STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER E]
You. You're with them, huh?
[HINATA] Even armed,
you will not survive this.
[yelling]
[STUDENT COUNCIL
MEMBER E screaming]
[ENOSHIMA laughs]
So, how did you
like the overture?
[ENOSHIMA]
Buddy.
You ain't seen nothin' yet.
Despair is gonna
rock your world.
Once we've had our second date,
this'll seem like nothing.
[YUKIZOME]
H'llo? Yukizome here.
Huh?
Whatever you do,
I need you to make sure the
students don't catch wind of it.
[JIN] This is not over!
I promise you that!
Damn it!
They're planning to
sweep it under the rug?
[JIN]
Those spineless cowards
are going to act as though
it never happened!
I wouldn't say it's the
most ethical choice,
but it might be the
best course of action.
[JIN]
Seriously?
Think of the project.
It was already inhumane enough
when everything went as planned.
If word of tonight's
massacre were to spread,
this academy would
cease to exist.
Covering this up is the only way
Hope's Peak survives the night.
We're as guilty as them.
[TENGAN] I've already
tendered my resignation.
Unofficially though,
I'll do what I can.
The choice, ultimately,
is yours to make.
What are we doing here?
[KIZAKURA]
You gotta try to calm down.
You're a logical guy so
flippin' tables won't help.
My daughter. Promise me you'll
look after her if... you know.
Huh?
[KIZAKURA]
I know what you're getting at.
Fine, I'll marry her.
Guess I'll have to live forever.
High time we let folks know
what's really going on
here at Hope's Peak High.
An' who better to start with
than the mediocre hacks
who are footing the bill
for all these shenanigans?
Sent!
[ENOSHIMA] "Hope's Peak High
School has been performing
unsanctioned human experiments.
In fact, these
experiments are funded
by your Reserve Course tuition.
And bleeding that cash
out of your parents
is the whole reason the Reserve
Course was implemented.
This behavior is
inexcusable on its own.
But it's not the worst thing
going on here by a long shot.
This very night, 14 academy
students were massacred.
The victims, the entirety
of our student council,
represented the best and
brightest we had to offer.
Their killer?
The guinea pig from those
unsanctioned experiments.
Hope's Peak is
actively suppressing
all this information.
"Why would they
do this," you ask?
Simple. They don't
care about you.
Your parents' hard-earned
cash was squandered
on dangerous, unethical
pseudo-science.
But the bigger cost
was the human one:
14 corpses awash
in their own blood.
Seeing as how your
money led to this,
you're all accomplices
to murder."
[ENOSHIMA sighs]
[ENOSHIMA] Now to watch
the butt-hurt blossom.
[STUDENTS shouting]
[RESERVE STUDENT A]
"Hope's Peak"? What a crock!
[RESERVE STUDENT C] You took
our parents to the cleaners,
you thieves!
[RESERVE STUDENT B]
This whole place is a scam!
[MIODA] I know pissed when I see
it, and those dudes are pissed.
[IMPOSTER]
Now she's gone.
Where'd you go, Hinata?