[SHIDO] Thirty years ago, the
Eurasian continent was attacked
by a massive "spatial quake."
There were 150 million victims
of this unprecedented event.
And now...
[alarm rings]
[SHIDO groans]
[loud crash]
Whoa! What on Earth was that?
Tohka, what's wrong?
[TOHKA] Oh, Shido.
Look, I'm sorry.
I accidently got the notes
I borrowed from you dirty!
[SHIDO] What?
I lost control when I thought
you would hate me for it.
[sobbing]
Don't worry, it's all right!
I won't hate you because
of something like that!
What? Really, you won't?
Course not, silly.
[SHIDO] Yoshino!
Oh, Shido. Look there.
Yoshinon is...
Yoshinon. Yoshinon.
Calm down, Yoshino!
If it freezes any more,
I won't be able to save her.
[YOSHINON] Yay!
[YOSHINON] Hey, Shido!
Thanks for saving me, as usual.
Yes, Shido.
Thank you very much.
[crashing noise]
[TOHKA] Sorry, Shido!
This time I spilled the kinako!
[SHIDO]
It's all right. I promise!
That's not going to
make me hate you, either!
[KIRIYA]
Master Sergeant Tobiichi.
We'll be taking
disciplinary action.
Wait, you can't!
Just let me--
Sorry. Is this
a bad time for us?
[KIRIYA] Mr. Westcott?
[KOTORI] Am I not always
telling you to be careful?
The Spirits' powers
will return to them
if their emotional
states are unstable,
so you gotta keep them happy.
This is all because
you slept in too long!
Give me a break, sis.
I was up late last night because
I had to study for a test! Gah!
Whatever.
I still have work to do, so I'm
gonna head out in just a minute.
Make sure you
spend time with those two
since you actually
have a day off.
And don't forget the intercom,
just in case, okay?
But I have so much
studying to do.
And on top of that,
prepping for the school trip
is driving me nuts.
[TOHKA] Our "Sugar tripnut"?
Is it sweet? It sounds sweet!
How did you get
"sugar" from that?
Anyway, I'm counting on you bro!
[MIKIE] Well, you must be
really relieved, Origami.
[MILDRED] That's true.
Honestly, it's a miracle
that you got off with only
a two-month suspension
after everything you did.
[ORIGAMI] Yes. I agree.
Although,
I have to say I'm curious
why such an
important person at D.E.M
would take the time to help you.
[TOHKA, YOSHINO gasp]
[TOHKA] What's wrong, Shido?
I'm fine.
Just need to
go shopping for a bit.
What do you want
to eat for lunch?
Oyakodon.
I'll go with you. 'Kay?
No, stay.
Enjoy your breakfast.
I'll be right back.
--See you later!
--We'll see you later, then!
[YOSHINO] Oyakodon.
Hey, Yoshino!
Guess what's almost on TV!
It's our favorite soap opera!
That's it for sports.
Now, on to today's weather.
Last night, two strong,
fast moving hurricanes
appeared in the middle
of the Pacific without warn--
You're really leaving, then?
I have to.
I can't stay here anymore.
I'm tired of my life with you.
[SHIDO] Uh,
What are you doing, Origami?
I just found you.
Yeah, because you
told me to come out.
Forget that.
What all's been
going on with you?
After that incident, did--
Origami...
Shido.
It's kind of
hard to talk out here.
Why don't we go somewhere
where we can be alone?
[SHIDO] Wait!
Why are we in
the women's restroom?
[ORIGAMI] No one
will get in our way here.
[SHIDO]
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
Well, why else
would you bring me here?
We are in a bathroom, Shido.
[SHIDO] You're the one
that brought me here!
I wanted to go somewhere private
so we could talk about
what happened last month!
I mean, I haven't been able
to talk to you since then.
So um...
What happened
with you after that?
[ORIGAMI] I had a hearing
and was sentenced
to a two-month suspension.
I see.
Although, I am still
not yet satisfied.
The Flame Spirit, Ifrit.
I know you said she was not
the one who killed my parents.
But, you have no conclusive
evidence to prove that.
Yeah, technically,
that may be true.
Please, though,
you must believe me!
--I would never lie to you!
--No, do not misunderstand.
I really do want to believe
what you are saying.
I do.
And if it is at all possible,
I want to avoid
killing your sister, too.
[SHIDO] Origami. Thanks.
I should be
the one thanking you.
After all, I'm...
I'm grateful you're
treating me like normal.
I did sort of try to
kill your little sister.
No... more than that.
I practically killed you
three months ago.
Guess I can't say,
"Don't worry about it."
But even so...
Origami, I want things
to stay the same between us.
Is that a problem?
Well, then.
I'd better get going.
[ORIGAMI] Wait...
Shido. Tell me something.
Are you human?
[TOHKA] I'll make Shido's
room nice and clean
to thank him for
making us breakfast!
[SHIDO] What a good girl!
Thank you, Tohka!
Right! Let's get started!
What is all this?
I can't stay here anymore.
I'm tired of my life with you.
It can't be!
[NAKATSUGAWA] Oh no!
Movement on Tohka's
happiness meter is dropping!
It's going into Pattern C now.
That's a danger sign!
[KOTORI] Tell me what
Shido is currently doing.
[MIKIMOTO] He left
the house to go shopping
about twenty minutes ago.
[KOTORI] What?
I told him to be careful!
[WIFE 1A] Wait. Wait!
Please think about this
more carefully!
[HUSBAND 1A]
I did think about it...
Which is why I'm leaving.
Face the truth.
I can't be with you anymore.
So goodbye.
[SHIIZAKI]
Tohka rushed out of the house!
[MINOWA] Her happiness meter
is entering the danger zone!
[NAKATSUGAWA]
She's heading in the direction
of the supermarket.
[MIKIMOTO] Speed: thirty-eight
kilometers per hour,
with a tailwind!
I think she's probably
heading toward Shido,
since he's gone shopping.
Is Shido's location
the supermarket?
[KAWAGOE] Actually,
location is unknown!
[KOTORI] What did you say?
[SHIIZAKI] We can't connect
to the intercom, either!
[KAWAGOE] It looks
like it's been sabotaged.
[KAWAGOE] It's either the AST
or something more powerful.
I always thought it was
more than a little strange.
I know without a single doubt
that I shot you that day.
And as far as what happened
during the last incident...
Don't worry. I won't
report it to my superiors.
[ORIGAMI] Because if they
decide that you are a Spirit,
I may be ordered
to put you down.
I'm a human, okay?
At the very least...
That is what
I believe I truly am.
[ORIGAMI] I see.
You mean you believe me?
I already told you.
I do want to believe
what you say.
Someday, if you ever feel
like telling me everything...
I would appreciate
all the details.
Shido...
I was wondering if you're free.
[SHIDO] What for?
[ORIGAMI] I have to buy energy
drinks for the school trip.
I want you to
choose them with me.
Drinks for the school trip?
Hold on a second, why would you
want me to choose them?
Because I want you to.
[SHIDO] How come?
[ORIGAMI]
Because I want to you to.
[SHIDO] As long as
I can go home first.
[TOHKA] It's all right.
It's all right!
Shido's not going anywhere!
I'm only checking on him!
I just want to ask Shido!
[TOHKA] Shido!
What? Tohka?
[TOHKA] Weren't you going
to the supermarket?
Did your stomach start
hurting or something?
[SHIDO] Uh, no. Not exactly.
So, uh, Shido...
There's something I kinda wanted
to ask you, if that's okay.
[gasps]
Origami Tobiichi!
Hello, Tohka.
What do you think
you're doing here?
[TOHKA] No, that's what
I should be asking you!
Talk!
Why were you in the
same bathroom as Shido?
[SHIDO] Tohka,
there's a reason for that.
It's our little secret.
Don't worry about it.
[TOHKA] What?
What is the meaning
of this, Shido?
Meaning of what?
Oh no!
Were you planning to raise
money to go somewhere?
Huh?
Wow. How did you
figure that out?
No! It's true!
[sobbing]
Why, Shido?
I don't understand!
Are you tired of me?
[TOHKA sobbing]
[SHIDO] Tohka!
I'm sorry!
I'll see you later!
[SHIDO] Hey, Tohka!
[TOHKA] Don't touch me!
You like Origami better
than you like me, don't you?
Um... no, I don't.
[KOTORI] Shido... Shido!
Great. Yeah, Kotori?
[KOTORI]
We finally got through!
What in the world
are you doing?
[SHIDO]
Well, that's... complicated.
[KOTORI] Anyway...
Tohka's anxiety has been going
through the roof recently,
which means her Spirit powers
are starting to return to her.
Because her powers
have flowed back to her
so many times now,
It's extremely likely
that the spirit path
is starting to waver.
[KOTORI] The bottom line
is at this rate
there might even
be a spatial quake.
You need to do something
to make Tohka feel better!
You want me to
make her feel better?
Okay, but how?
Come on,
it's what we've been doing
this whole time, isn't it?
Don't act as if you've
forgotten everything.
It's the basics of how we
choose to fight the Spirits.
Where the AST tries
to annihilate all Spirits
by attacking them
rather violently.
[KOTORI] We at Ratatoskr,
on the other hand...
[SHIDO] ...take Spirits on dates
and make them fall in love.
Aw, you remember, after all.
Well, then.
It seems to me
that it's about time
to start our date!
[TOHKA] A date? Really?
That's right.
Do you maybe want
to go shopping
and walk around town
for a little bit?
What for?
I mean, aren't you, like,
tired of being with me?
No, of course I'm not.
Look, I promise to buy you
anything you want to eat
while we're out.
How does that sound?
Really?
You think that'll work?
Well then,
what about kinako bread?
[SHIDO] You can have
as many as you want!
I guess. Yeah.
Just for a little while, okay?
Uh, sure thing.
Let's get going.
[SHIDO] Oh, good.
It looks like this'll work out.
[SHIDO gasps]
[TOHKA screams]
[KOTORI] Shido!
Tohka's happiness meter
is going down again!
Do something!
Hey... It's totally
all right, Tohka!
Trust me, there are plenty
of other bakeries around here.
All the stores
can't be sold out,
so we'll find you
some bread soon enough!
[SHIDO]
They can't all be sold out...
[SHIDO] Really?!
[TOHKA] Shido...
Where'd the kinako bread go?
Listen to me!
I'm gonna take care
of this for you!
How can every store
be sold out at once?
Maybe they all had
them on sale or something?
Hello, everyone. I'm back!
We can't have Tohka
going out of control again
like she did this morning.
So I bought out
all the kinako bread,
just in case of an emergency.
[ALL] That was you?!
[KANNAZUKI] Yes...?
[KOTORI] Go take those
to Shido right now, you idiot!
Yummy!
Kinako bread
is really delicious.
Shido, where did you
get all of these from?
Actually, you don't
want to know that, 'kay?
Okay. I don't
want to know that!
[SHIDO] We're home!
I'll start cooking
dinner right away.
[YOSHINON]
Welcome back, Shido!
Oyakodon! Hooray!
[YOSHINON]
Man, I gotta tell ya,
I was really surprised
when you ran off
out of the blue
like that, lady.
[TOHKA] You were?
Weird. I could've
sworn I closed this.
Wait, the lock's broken.
How'd that happen?
I spent all that time
packing for the school trip.
Man...
I guess since Tohka's
calmed down a bit,
I might as well
get this thing fixed.
I have to meet Origami, anyway.
[SHIDO] Hey, I'm going out
for a while, okay?
[YOSHINON] See you later!
Later, gator!
Yeah, hello?
Oh, hi... Origami.
Yeah, it's fine now.
[TOHKA growling]
[SHIDO]
Where do you want to meet?
[MISTRESS 1A] You have to keep
this a secret from your wife.
This is our little secret.
[HUSBAND 1A] Yes, I know.
[MISTRESS 1A] She hasn't
found out, has she?
Clueless.
Today, I brought home
her favorite treat,
so she was happy and
didn't suspect a thing.
No, it can't be!
[WIFE 1A] Dear,
why are you doing this?
[HUSBAND 1A]
I thought I told you.
There's no particular reason.
Our love wasn't real.
It was just an illusion.
No! Oh, Shido!
[TOHKA]
It can't be. It can't be!
Shido isn't going anywhere!
He isn't. He isn't!
[SHIDO] Sorry, is it
all right if we take this
to the repair shop, too?
Yeah, sure.
[SHIDO] This is
our chance to get away.
I can't stay here anymore.
I'm tired of my life with you.
Goodbye, forever.
[TOHKA screams]
[TOHKA sobbing loudly]
[SHIDO] Origami!
Hurry and get to a shelter!
[sobbing]
You won't let me
listen to the end, huh?
You are such a tease,
my little Miku.
--You know I can't get enough!
--Sir, run away!
[AI] Are you kidding?
Like, why now?
I didn't even get my change!
Boo! That's so lame!
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Shido! Shido!
[NAKATSUGAWA] It's no use.
He's not wearing the intercom.
[SHIIZAKI] At this rate,
we won't be able to tell
him where Tohka is heading.
That stupid Shido!
I specifically said wear it!
Can we get him an intercom?
[KAWAGOE] Please wait!
Shido is heading in the
same direction as Tohka!
[SHIDO] I know her.
Tohka is definitely here.
She has to be!
[SHIDO] Tohka!
Shido? But how did you know?
[SHIDO] How could I not know?
I mean, this is the place
where we first...
[TOHKA] Do you want
it back that badly?
[SHIDO] What?
[TOHKA]
You're going no matter what?
[SHIDO] Going where?
You don't have to pretend!
I know everything.
If you say you're
going no matter what...
...then you can go
once you've defeated me!
[SHIDO]
What are you talking about?
I'm not going anywhere!
You're not?
There's no way I ever would!
I mean I still
have to make dinner
for you and Yoshino, don't I?
And I have a test to study for!
[TOHKA] But aren't you...
Aren't you tired
of being with me?
[SHIDO] I never said
anything like that!
If that's the truth,
then why do you
have your case packed?
Isn't it the "goodbye box"
that means we can't
be together anymore?
You brought this with you
to go meet Origami Tobiichi!
It's just as I thought!
[SHIDO]
No, it's not as you thought.
It's... the suitcase
I was planning to take
on the school trip
with you next week.
[TOHKA] What? With me?
Yes, with you.
Okay, then, does that
mean you really aren't tired
of being with me?
It's all right for us
to be together?
[SHIDO] Of course it is!
[TOHKA] Shido!
Tell me you're not hurt!
[SHIDO] What was that?
This is bad.
There is too much power
flowing between them.
I was afraid this would happen.
What did you say?
Unfortunately, at this rate,
the overflowing spirit power
will destroy the town
and eventually, Tohka herself.
[ALL gasp]
Right.
Then this is an emergency.
We must retrieve Shido
and discuss a strategy
to make sure we keep
everyone safe.
We don't have
that kind of time.
No matter what,
Shido cannot disappear
right in front
of Tohka's eyes.
We don't know what effect
that might have on her.
All we can do now
is bet on Shido.
Come on, brother.
I believe in you!
[TOHKA]
Shido, what's happening?
I swear I'm not doing this!
[SHIDO] I know.
I'm sorry, Tohka.
[TOHKA] Shido! Stay back!
It's not safe!
You shouldn't say that, Tohka!
There's no way that I won't
make it over there to you, Okay?
[SHIDO] I'm the one
that made you anxious.
Even after promising
I would always accept you,
I couldn't ease your worries.
At least...
At the very least..
I'll make it to you!
Oh, Shido.
Tohka! Take my hand!
Everything'll be fine!
It seems we're in the clear.
The spirit path
has been stabilized.
I don't think we'll have
a problem for a while.
What did you expect?
That's my big brother for you.
[chuckles]
[SHIDO] Hey, Tohka.
So I was wondering, there was
something you wanted to ask me.
What was it?
[TOHKA] Nothing.
Besides... I have my answer.
[WESTCOTT] Oh?
You found Princess, have you?
Interesting.
She was supposed to have
disappeared from Tengu City
three months ago,
is that correct?
[ELLEN] Yes.
In addition,
there is this report.
Fascinating.
It says the Princess
is attending high school.
[ELLEN]
Her name is Tohka Yatogami.
She is a student at
Raizen Municipal High School.
The time she transferred in
matches the time all traces
of the Princess disappeared.
[WESTCOTT chuckles]
You're kidding me.
Very unexpected.
I think we should
check this out our way, then.
I wouldn't want my most capable
asset to get rusty, now would I?
I am counting on you, my dear.
Ellen Mira Mathers,
mankind's greatest Wizard.
[KURUMI] It's not
nearly enough yet, is it?
Oh... Didn't expect to see you.
Yes, it was just wonderful.
Who knew someone
like that actually existed?
I can't believe it.
Sadly, now, I have to store up
time before I can go back again.
But still...
There's no way I'm giving up.
[gunshot]
[KURUMI] In order to use
Zaphkiel's final attack...
Yod Bet...
I need that person's
particular power.
[chuckles]
And I will get it.
Don't doubt me on that.
I will never, ever give up.
Then I'll kill
the origin Spirit,
the earliest one to appear
in this world thirty years ago.
The source from which all other
Spirits came, the First Spirit.
I'm going to take it out
with my own two hands.
[gunshot]