[NARRATOR] Spirits...
How do we deal with
trans-spatial life forms
that cause disasters?
Strategy one: Destroy them
through overwhelming
military force.
Or strategy two: Date them
and make them fall in love.
[groaning]
[doorbell rings]
[TOHKA] It's pretty simple,
Miss Okamine.
Yes... I am totally a boy now...
So I can stay in
the same room as Shido
when we go on the school trip!
I don't think so.
You can keep wearing
those clothes,
but it doesn't change
the fact that boys and girls
have to stay in separate rooms--
Excuse me...
I think you should approve
Tohka's unusual request.
Or at least consider it.
--Huh?
Hold on...
What are you after?
I really admire
that you have the courage
to come out
in front of everyone.
I think you deserve to stay
in the boy's room, no question.
Look. I'm not saying thanks.
None needed.
Stop wasting time!
The issue is non-negotiable!
But it is still pretty
uncommon for a girl
to want to become a boy.
To keep things balanced,
we'll make Shido into a girl.
That literally makes no sense.
Then we could bathe together.
Tastefully.
How's that tasteful?
Wait a sec!
If he becomes a girl,
he won't be able to stay
in the boys' room with me!
You're a man now.
You need to stay strong.
Then this must've been
part of your plan all along!
You are both being ridiculous!
Boys and girls will
be in separate rooms!
And no more
gender swapping, got it?
Um, well...
Putting room assignments aside,
you can choose your seats
for the plane ride.
You can spend time
together there.
[BOTH growling]
[KOTORI] The location
for the school trip?
Yeah, Shido told me about it.
They were going to Okinawa,
but now it's Arubi Island.
We're talking a
last minute change, here.
[REINE] It seems a
certain travel agency said
they would cover all expenses
in order to get publicity shots.
With all financial
burden lifted,
the school quickly agreed.
However...
Sounds suspicious.
Perhaps I'm reading
too much into it.
But the agency, Cross Travel?
It's a subsidiary
of DEM Industries...
[TOHKA] This was your game
from the beginning, wasn't it?
You tricked me into the seat
farthest from the window!
I won't be fooled again!
[ORIGAMI] You never specified
which seat you wanted.
[TOHKA seething]
[TAMAE] I'm sorry!
Super sorry! Triple sorry!
[TOHKA] Everybody knows the
aisle is where the action is!
It's pretty cool.
The clouds look
just like a carpet!
Well if you like carpet,
I've got what you want!
Right here!
Look at it, Shido!
If I pretend to nap,
maybe they'll stop...
[ELLEN]
Pardon the Candid Camera...
But I had to capture
such a priceless expression.
[stammering]
Shido, who was that?
The teacher introduced
her to us earlier.
She's the pro photographer
the travel agency
sent along with us.
[ELLEN]
A Spirit... Princess...
[AI]
Your camera is making me jelly!
It's top of the line!
Must've cost thousands!
That's so lame!
[AI, MII, MAI chattering]
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT 2A]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
please put your seats
and tray tables
in an upright
and locked position
and prepare for landing.
[TOHKA] Wow!
[TOHKA] Wow! No way...
Is that the ocean?
Yeah, I guess this is
your first time to see it.
[TOHKA] Uh huh!
The water park we went to
with Yoshino
and Kotori was amazing.
But this place is even better!
[SHIDO] More than you know...
[SHIDO] Is something wrong?
Odd...
I feel like
someone's watching us.
We'll have them take our
luggage to the hotel first,
understood?
It was probably just the camera.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Incoming from Adeptus One.
They've reached Arubi Island.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2B]
Target confirmed!
Akaru Airport, North District,
camera number six.
It's Princess, sir;
we found her.
That was anti-climactic.
The girl doesn't
look like a Spirit.
[ELLEN] You must not
let your guard down.
Intelligence indicates
that she is a Spirit.
That alone is reason enough
to be on Level One alert.
[PADDINGTON] Roger that.
Set alert to Level One.
By the way, aren't we supposed
to have a Wizard on the ground?
[TAMAE] All right,
Class Four! Gather round!
That would be me.
We met earlier.
I'll report
back to you later on,
but for now,
the kids are on the move.
Right, come on!
Eyes forward, Class Four!
Since this is a school trip,
we'll start the learning now!
We're heading to the Arubi
Island Records Office!
How exciting!
Seriously?
It sounds, like,
stupid boring.
That's so lame.
Hey, get it out of
the way now, have fun later!
Am I right, sexy beast?
[TAMAE] Okay, gang!
Everyone follow the flag!
It's time.
Come on! Let's book it!
But I know someone's
been spying on us!
Hang on, Tohka!
Aw, man!
[ELLEN]
Adeptus One to Arbatel...
Princess has broken off
from the group.
Track her movements for me.
Also, activate Ashcroft Beta
and set to standby.
Then cut off the island
from outside communication.
Be ready to strike at any time.
Hey, you're gonna
get left behind.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Ashcroft Beta...
Shouldn't you be
taking pictures of us?
So what?
Did you just come for
some photos of the scenery?
--That's so lame.
--[OPERATOR continues talking]
[ELLEN]
No, that's not it at all...
--[MAI] Can we go already?
--[AI] You're working, Ellen.
[ELLEN yelling]
Being a field agent
can be rough,
but these precautions
seem a bit extreme.
Spirit or not, she's just a
teenage girl.
Once we introduce
her to the Bandersnatch Unit,
capturing her
will be child's play.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Captain? We've got a problem!
[PADDINGTON] The hell?
Weird! This weather
came out of nowhere!
Look, if we don't
get out of this storm,
it could get really bad!
Sorry I ran off...
But I know someone
was watching us.
I could feel it!
[SHIDO]
I bet it was just the locals
giving a bunch of annoying
students the stink eye.
Now which way
to the Records Office?
[SHIDO, TOHKA yelling]
What's going on?
This came to a head
way too quickly!
Shido... Get down!
[SHIDO] Tohka! Are you okay?
Just my luck...
A Spirit? Or the AST?
But the spatial quake alarm
never sounded...
[SHIDO yelling]
[SHIDO] Spirits? Two of 'em?
I can't believe you!
Please choose me, darling!
[MAN 2A]
It doesn't matter--
[TWINS] Yes, it does!
[KOTORI]
Well, I'll be going then...
This isn't exactly the best
timing for a meeting at HQ...
But it's a rare chance for the
Rounds to meet up in person,
so I'm expected
to make an appearance.
[KANNAZUKI] Go.
You may leave it
to me, Commander.
[SHIIZAKI] Don't worry.
You can trust us
to hold down the fort.
[NAKATSUGAWA] Just promise
that you'll hurry back
when you're done.
But lo, the unbridled
passion of youth
set free during a school trip...
And I, Kyohei Kannazuki,
will chronicle this page
of Shido's salad days
with every juicy detail
during your absence!
Right. I reiterate.
Please hurry back.
Sure. I'll try.
Okay!
As acting commander
of the mighty Fraxinus...
Plot a course for fifteen
thousand feet above the island!
[laughing]
Not too bad, Yuzuru...
Although, I expected
as much from my other half.
Too bad it will
all have been in vain!
Rebuttal.
Much has been learned
from our ninety-nine battles.
The advantage is clearly mine.
Such sad prattle.
We both know the only
Spirit even suitable
to be Yamai's
successor is me.
Negative. I am the one
who will persevere.
The name Yamai does not fit
one as lowly as you.
Your words are hollow.
My future devil sight
has already shown me
the inevitable end.
It gave me a
vision of you, Yuzuru,
impaled and dying on
the end of my Sturm Lanze!
Refute.
Your devil sight has never
been accurate in the slightest.
Shut up!
It has so worked before!
And don't you dare
make fun of me!
[REINE]
Shin... Can you hear me?
Reine?
Good. I finally got through.
Where are you
and Tohka currently?
Umm... Not sure.
[YUZURU] Request.
Kaguya, please
provide information
regarding the
combat capabilities
of your Sturm Lanze.
[KAGUYA] Ha! The very font
of language dries up
trying to describe the
scope of its awesome power.
Tangible yet intangible.
Visible yet unseen.
Only able to sate its thirst
with stabbing and piercing.
Summary.
Just like you,
it is devoid of meaning.
That's not true!
It does have meaning!
Maybe you're just too stupid
to really understand!
Derisive.
Your Sturm Lanze
is laughable. Ha!
How dare you!
To punish you
for such insolence,
perhaps I should rip
that smirk off your face
right here and now!
[SHIDO] We're gonna
get caught in the middle!
Sink into darkness!!
Retort... Hi-ya!
Stop it!
Wait. Is that a human?
Wondrous.
I cannot suppress my surprise.
Uh... Hi?
Why have you
brought our sacred duel
to a standstill, human?
And what are
your intentions for us?
Depending on your answer...
I'll, uh...
...turn your body into a jelly
with my Schatten Lanze.
[YUZURU] Discrepancy...
Your weapon's name
has changed completely.
Unimportant!
Now be quiet, already!
[YUZURU] Query.
Since you are the one
who is confused,
why must I be quiet?
[KAGUYA] At this rate,
we won't resolve anything.
Unless...
I think I know how we
can settle things. For good.
Question.
What did you have in mind?
A new trial.
We've had many contests,
haven't we?
We've each had
twenty-five victories,
and come to a draw
forty-nine times.
The list of events to compete
in is rapidly dwindling.
However, there is
still one competition
which hasn't yet determined
a victor between us.
Doubtful... Explain.
Hey, uhh... We're back.
There's no denying...
I'm obviously more lively
and charming than she is.
Seduction.
I'm more fully developed.
What gives?
[REINE]
They're transfer students.
[TAMAE]
This is highly unorthodox...
The school never informed me
they were coming.
[REINE] It was so sudden
they were probably worried
that they couldn't
contact you in time.
Don't worry about the new girls.
Leave them to me, okay?
Please focus your energy
on the other students.
[TAMAE] Oh... Thank you.
[KAGUYA] So Shido...
All you have to do is make
a simple little choice.
Just say "Kaguya!
You drive me wild!
Let me give myself to you,
body and soul forever."
[YUZURU] Wrong...
Kaguya is a poor choice.
She is quite needy and childish.
However, I would
strongly recommend me.
Feeling a little
smothered, are we?
Yeah...
[KAGUYA] Putting our
feminine wiles to the test...
We haven't tried that yet.
Surely the true heir
of the hurricane child Yamai
would possess enough
grace and charm
to make all of creation
quake in jealousy!
Reply. I believe
I follow your logic.
In truth, it may be
the only attribute
which we have not
put to a competition.
Yuzuru...
Do you agree to pit our
beauty against one another?
Of course,
my victory is certain.
Negative.
There is no chance
that you could ever beat me.
After all, I am the cutest.
To be frank, your looks
are average at best.
What do you mean by that?
It doesn't matter.
This will be
our decisive battle!
Whoever gets this man to fall in
love first will be the winner.
Come on now, handsome.
Just spit it out.
Which of us has
more feminine charm?
Me, or Little Miss Boring there?
Question.
Do you prefer a beautiful woman
or a cheap floozy like her?
Look, I'm not a floozy.
You take that back right now!
No. I am prettier
than that trollop, Kaguya.
Stop! That's even worse!
Would everyone shut up
for five seconds, please?
Let me ask you
something first...
Why are you ladies
trying to duel each other
for the hundredth time, anyway?
Uh... Oh, did we
not mention that already?
Apologies.
We forgot to tell you.
As the arbitrator,
you have the right to know
all of the pertinent details.
You see, Kaguya and I were once
combined as a single Spirit.
The name of
the Spirit was Yamai.
[TWIN 2A]
Just pick me!
[TWIN 2B]
No, you have to choose me!
[SHIDO] So basically...
For reasons yet to be announced,
someday soon you'll
both have to go back
to being a single Spirit.
And when that happens,
the two different personalities
won't be able to coexist,
is that right?
Correct.
The personality of the original
Yamai was lost ages ago...
Thus, Yuzuru or I
will become the new Yamai.
For there can be only one.
Correct.
Explanation: In order to
determine who that will be,
we have fought tooth
and nail for many years.
Fistfight...
Footrace...
Kendama...
Eating contest...
We competed in
a variety of ways.
Those last two
were way less dramatic...
What happens to the
personality that loses?
[KAGUYA]
It will cease to exist.
No way!
[KAGUYA] We really
appreciate you, Shido.
Thanks to you,
we can compete in a way
we've never been able to.
[YUZURU] Affirmative.
I have no objections
if this match
is what makes
the final decision.
That can't be good...
Is there
some kind of problem?
Yes... Fraxinus
hasn't sent any updates
or status reports in hours.
The reason is unknown,
but I will investigate.
Anyway.
And now ladies, if you
would both follow me, please.
Shin is more wily than he looks.
I'll give you some tips
to deal with him.
[SHIDO]
Well, that's just great.
Two new spirits pop up, and
Reine and I have to fly solo.
What kind of tips is she
giving for them to deal with me?
Ah! Oh, hi, girls!
Shido,
I give you permission
to cleanse the impurities
that have accumulated
on your puny mortal body.
Confirmation. Please
feel free to enter the bath.
Okay...?
Hey... What made you
think it was all right
to take a bath with me?
Duh...
How else am I going
to make you go crazy
for my pixie-like
feminine charm?
Scornful.
Feminine charms, you say?
Were you planning
to buy some here?
Because you didn't bring
any with you, sister.
I swear I'll make you
pay for that later, you cow!
Accepted. Now bring it on.
Excuse me!
This is the men's bath!
Which means neither
of you are even
supposed to
be on this side!
Better prepare yourself, stud.
I will make you realize
that you can never be satisfied
by anyone but me.
Negative. Just think...
There's only a flimsy white
towel separating our flesh...
Joystick... Game on!
Here we go. Ready?
Out of the kindness of my heart,
you can have the
first seduction attempt.
Negative. Not needed.
However, you could use any
handicap you can get, I'd wager.
Then the gloves are off.
The moment I make my big move,
Shido's eyes will never
stray from me again.
I just wanted to be charitable
and let you
have a glimmer of hope.
Skeptical.
You have no idea what it takes
to seduce a young man, do you?
You bet I do!
I'm super foxy!
Plus I've got a ton
of sexy techniques
that a bore like you couldn't
dream up in a million years!
Doubtful. Care to demonstrate?
All right. Just you watch!
How do you like that?
[giggling]
I'm confused...
Hey!
What are you laughing at?
Derision.
Just as expected,
your feminine charms
leave something
to be desired.
What did you say?
As if a girl without
a shred of passion
would have even
the foggiest notion!
Falsehood.
My worst would
still be better than you.
Why don't you
show us how it's done?
Accepted. Here we go.
Hi, handsome.
Uh... Thanks.
Hahaha!
Wow. You sure showed me!
Can't believe
you had me worried!
Livid.
I am not interested
in your opinion.
[KAGUYA] Same here!
[YUZURU] Noted.
Your childish figure is not
as effective at seduction
as my womanly curves.
Nonsense.
You know that we're identical!
Rebuttal.
Even if the
measurements are the same,
they feel completely different.
You're underestimating
the attractiveness
of a slender body.
Haughty.
Slender body, you say?
Change the words to sound
better all you wish,
but you cannot
alter the sad truth.
Are you seriously bragging
because you have
more fat on your chest?
Indignant.
These breasts are pristine,
but your jealousy is ugly.
And who's jealous of you, cow?
I'm not, you understand me?
Shido thinks I'm cuter
than some fatty like you
any day of the week,
no ifs ands or buts.
Wrong.
When attempting
to appeal to men,
being flat chested
is a bad thing.
Chicken bones like yours
wouldn't rate a second glance.
They aren't chicken bones!
Riposte.
Don't ever call me a "fatty"!
You have more
split ends than I do!
Snark. You're smellier than
I am whenever you get sweaty.
Oh?
Well you have more
body fat than I do!
Pity.
You're not intelligent enough
to find another fault of mine
to comment on.
Puffity fatty-fat puffball!
Counter.
--Flat-as-a-board flattenstein.
--Hold on!
The others might
show up at anytime.
It won't look good if you're
caught in the men's bath!
Ha! What are you
talking about, Shido?
Confirmed.
There's no need to worry.
Uh... But why?
[TOHKA laughing]
I love being
first in the bath!
[TOHKA, SHIDO screaming]
Hey!
What are you thinking,
being in a place like this?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing
in the men's bathing area?
What are you talking about?
I went in the room
with the red sign,
just like
everybody told me to.
And how'd that happen?
Well...
We might have switched the
signs right before you came in.
Supplement.
Once you came in,
we put them back.
Like we would sink
so low to use the men's bath.
Figures...
I got here early to be
the first in the bath,
but now I'm the fourth!
Uh... My mistake,
I kinda got tricked!
I'll get out right now!
[screaming]
[AI] Check it out!
The ocean is like right there!
[MAI] We would never get
a view this good at home!
[MII] That's so lame!
Gotta make a plan,
and quickly.
[TOHKA] Shido!
I'll obstruct their view.
You can hide behind me
then try to run away!
You sure?
Those girls tricked you into
coming into the wrong bath.
So I'm gonna get you out!
Thank you. I owe you one.
Hey...
Tohka, I didn't
know you were here!
Don't hide over in the corner,
come and join us!
OMG, you have,
like, perfect skin!
[MII] That's so lame...
[squealing]
Something wrong?
No! No, everything's fine!
[TOHKA] Look!
Is that a giant piece
of kinako bread in the sky?
--[TOHKA] Back and to the left!
--[MAI] I don't see it...
--Above the hotel!
--Wait! No...
[AI] Are you feeling all right?
[TOHKA] You just have
to look up, and away from me!
Over that way!
[SHIDO screaming]
Isn't it a little early to
sneak into a woman's bedroom?
[ELLEN] We were delayed
by unexpected circumstances.
But we will strike tonight.
Have Bandersnatch standing by
and ready to move.
[TWIN 2B]
You chose me over my sister?
[MAN 2A] It doesn't
really matter, does it?
[YOSHINON] Yoshino?
[YOSHINO] Yes?
[YOSHINON] They gave us a lot of
free time on this school trip.
Uh huh.