[TSUKAMOTO] Master Sergeant
Origami Tobiichi.
Your suspension
is lifted as of today.
Ma'am...
There will be no second chance.
See that it
doesn't happen again--
[MIKIE] Captain, please stop!
Major Tsukamoto!
Would you care
to explain this order?
Captain Kusakabe?
This calls for
an independent unit
from DEM Industries to the AST
and for them to be granted
discretionary powers
during emergency situations.
Forming a unit
like this is absurd!
The AST might as well
have been bought and paid for
by those jerks at DEM!
I agree.
[FEMALE VOICE] This area
has had more spatial quakes
in the last year
than anywhere else.
Yet you've all been
too busy playing house
to capture even a single spirit.
That's why we're here.
[RYOKO] Who are you?
We're the DEM soldiers
assigned to the AST.
And I'm Jessica Bailey.
So nice to meet you.
[NARRATOR] The annual cultural
festival is just another battle.
Performers fight it out
on stage with their rivals.
Vendors compete with sales
from their stalls.
And some wander the grounds
by themselves,
combatting loneliness.
And now the results
of our nomination battle
for self-preservation!
Rumored to work way hard
even in soul-sucking
sweatshop conditions,
our committee selection for
this year's Tenou Festival is...
...Shido Itsuka!
Super glad it's not me!
Huh?!
Nice. Couldn't ask for
a better sacrificial lamb.
What's this Tenou Festival
thing-a-mabob?
It's the joint cultural festival
held by the ten high schools
here in Tengu City.
[SHIDO] Those guys are
already working my butt off
and it's only the first day.
Sorry you had to come all
the way out here to meet me.
It's okay.
Tohka was so hungry
that she collapsed.
I had to go before
she took a bite of me.
[chuckles]
[alarm sounding]
That's the spatial quake alarm!
Kotori?
[KOTORI] Acknowledged.
Withdraw to the
Fraxinus immediately.
We'll take you to the scene.
[MIKU]
♪ Let me sing you a song, ♪
♪ and let's sing along ♪
♪ The greatest gift of all are
all the stars up in the sky ♪
[KOTORI] Is it really her?
[MIKU continues singing]
[KOTORI] That's Diva?
[KOTORI] This spirit was first
sighted six months ago,
and hasn't been seen since.
Basically, we have zero
information about her
or her abilities.
I advise you to exercise
caution when approaching her.
[singing stops]
Who's there?
[KOTORI]
Oh, great. Nice job, idiot!
[SHIDO] Sorry, I can barely
see where I'm going.
[MIKU] Hello? Do I have
an audience out there?
I can't see you,
wherever you are.
If it's not inconvenient, would
you care to talk for a while?
Kotori?
[KOTORI]
Right. Move in closer.
We'll help you out
with what to say.
Okay.
The choices just popped up.
Selections, everyone!
[MIKU] You climbed all
the way up here just to see me?
Lovely night, isn't it?
It's nice to meet... you...
Oh, hello there, Miss!
Huh?
[SHIDO] I didn't mean to
eavesdrop on you singing,
but your voice is beautiful.
[SHIIZAKI] Happiness level,
mood, mental state--
All parameters are
plummeting fast, Commander!
[KOTORI]
Guess that was the wrong choice.
We have to keep trying.
Let's go with number 1!
Has anyone ever told you
how gorgeous you are?
I mean, wow!
[SHIIZAKI] Happiness levels
are dropping further!
It's almost as if
she's disgusted by Shido.
[KOTORI] Damn it!
It looks like number three
is our last resort!
The view from below
was very uh...
[SHIIZAKI] Now she thinks
he's lower than a cockroach!
[KOTORI] But he didn't
even get to finish the line!
[SHIDO] You okay?
[screams]
[MIKU]
Well this is rather unexpected.
Why haven't you fallen down yet?
Why aren't you dead?
[MIKU] Disappear from
this stage, this world,
and this confluence
of time and space.
Do it as soon as possible,
you wretched plebeian!
[SHIDO] Hold up. You serious?
I said disappear, not talk!
I'd rather you not
even expend the energy
unleashing your
halitosis-laden breath!
Are you too stupid to realize
that your mere presence
contaminates the
purity of the air?
Okay. That's rude.
[MIKU] You're not very good at
following instructions, are you?
Can you even begin to comprehend
why I wouldn't stomp
on your hands right now and send
you falling to your death?
Because I care about the
bottom of my shoe too much
to let it touch
filthy scum like you!
[SHIDO] The AST?!
Oh wow! Cool!
Their armor is tres chic!
Talk about perfect, it's just
the audience I was looking for.
You in particular.
Yes! More!
It's exciting and new!
I'm having so much fun.
Would you like me
to sing for you?
Fine!
But you could
have just said 'no'.
Once again,
they're too busy playing
to get anything done.
Guess I'll have to step in!
That kid...
Shido!
[SHIIZAKI]
There! I found him!
[KOTORI]
That's enough for now.
Bring him back!
[MIKU yells]
[SHIDO yawns]
[SHIDO] Why do I have
to be here on a Saturday?
We have to practice
for the talent show,
so we'll leave the joint
meeting in your capable hands.
And don't worry,
we've arranged escorts!
Back off already,
you're smothering the poor guy!
I was about
to say the same thing.
[ALL gasping]
Hello, everyone!
Thank you for coming
to the meeting.
Let's get started!
[SHIDO] What? No way!
[NAKATSUGAWA]
One of my contacts
brought this
hidden camera footage
from one of her secret concerts.
Miku Izayoi, huh?
I never would have guessed
that she was a Spirit.
[SHIDO]
Well, she's the one I saw.
Hold on, do you know her?
No, but I've
heard of her before.
She's done some songs
for commercials
and TV shows and stuff.
She debuted six months ago
already has several hits,
and her voice has been
described as "Audio Ecstasy".
But she still remains anonymous:
A mysterious idol who has never
revealed herself to the public.
The fact that's
she's stayed off our radar
for this long means
she's good at hiding out.
Hold on, there's that
other Spirit like you.
[KOTORI] For convenience, we've
given her the codename Phantom.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
According to the internet,
Miku has an extreme
distaste for men.
Only girls were allowed
into this concert.
That's not all!
Rumor has it at some
of her prior events,
she even took some
female fans home!
Whoa! What're you saying?
[KOTORI] It's entirely possible
that Little Miss Popstar Spirit
prefers to swing the other way.
If that's true,
I won't be able to do
anything about her, will I?
[KOTORI]
Rest assured. We have a plan.
Best of luck!
You'll need it, Sis!
[KOTORI] Remember,
you'll have to contact Miku
while everyone is busy
setting up, understand?
[SHIDO] Do you really think
this plan is going to work?
[KOTORI] Sure!
If Reine's
hypothesis is correct.
But don't worry
your pretty little head.
The entire crew has given your
charm their stamp of approval.
Be confident and you'll be fine.
How'd I get roped
into this crap?
[KOTORI] Voice changer!
Yeah.
Okay. Ready! Let's go!
So, um...
That Shido guy?
Said there was
something important
that he had
to go take care of.
And so he asked me
if I would mind
going to Tengu Square
with everybody in his place.
That bastard!
Like what a loser!
That is so lame!
By the way, who are you?
Oh, right. Hello there.
I'm Shido's first cousin.
My name's... Shidomi?
No, scratch that. I'm Shiori.
Shido, what are you up to?
I'm on a mission.
Can you pretend
like you don't know me?
Sure. You can
always count on me!
Nice to meet you,
girl-who's-not-
Shido-in-disguise!
[ORIGAMI] Look over here.
That's nice, Shiori. Very good.
Now take something off.
No! What are
you doing that for?
Don't worry.
I'll still respect you.
[SHIORI] Stop! Hold on!
[SHIORI] No!
[KOTORI] Rindoji's booths
are in the first building.
[SHIORI] There she is!
I'm following her now!
[KOTORI]
Perfect. It's now or never!
Right.
Well hello.
So what's your name?
Uhh... I... forgot.
[MIKU] You forgot?
[KOTORI] You forgot?!
I freeze up
when I get nervous!
[MIKU] There's no need for
you to be nervous around me.
[laughs]
But... It's also
irresistibly cute.
[SHIIZAKI] Happiness and mood
levels haven't dropped yet.
They're actually staying stable!
I guess she prefers her
women dumb as a doorknob
and helpless as a kitten.
Should be easy for Shido.
We have our choices.
Make your selection!
[KOTORI] Number 2 makes sense,
but why is number 3 so popular?
[NAKATSUGAWA] Sounds perverted
coming from a man.
But it might be just the thing
for the quirky Shiori to say.
[KOTORI] Hmm...
It would help us determine
Miku's tolerance level.
Are you serious?
[KOTORI]
Try saying it like it's a joke.
[SHIORI] I wonder...
What's up?
Would you be
willing to sell me
the panties you're wearing
for thirty thousand yen?
I have a counter bid.
I don't want
to sell them to you,
but I'd consider trading them
for the ones you're wearing!
Whoa, what?
I was just joking with you.
Besides, shouldn't I be the
one freaked by that question?
[SHIORI] Totally.
I was joking around, too.
[MIKU] Your uniform.
You go to Raizen, don't you?
[SHIORI] Yeah. That's right.
[MIKU] Well then,
let's try this again.
I'm Miku Izayoi,
and I go to Rindoji!
Right on.
It's nice to meet you.
My name's Shiori Itsuka.
[MIKU]
That's a very pretty name.
[KOTORI]
The numbers are looking good.
You should try asking
her some questions.
[SHIORI] So, uh...
I thought this place was
supposed to be off limits?
What were you doing
in here by yourself, Miku?
[MIKU] I love the stage.
I have a hard time keeping away.
You love the stage?
Yes!
I love feeling like everyone
needs to hear my voice.
When I sing, I can almost
feel the excitement
crackling through the air!
But not from you,
which leads me to believe that
you may never have heard of me.
Oh. Well, I...
[giggles]
[MIKU] I seem to have
put you on the spot.
Don't worry about it.
I won't tell that we were
in here if you don't tell.
It will be our little secret.
[SHIORI]
Uhh... uh-huh...
[MIKU] Now. Let's get
back to work, okay?
[SHIORI] 'Kay.
[SHIORI yelling]
Are you all right?
Oh. Thank you!
You're quite welcome.
C'mon, bro, are the
hamburgers ready yet?
[SHIDO] Almost!
Go ahead and set the table
for me, would you?
It's so relaxing to just cook
and not pretend
to be a girl.
You say that like
you've already forgotten
how liberating it feels
to wear a skirt.
You're being ridiculous.
[KOTORI] Never mind.
Fortunately, we have an excuse
for you to meet up
with Miku again.
Apparently she likes to have tea
with the girls she's taken
a shining to once a week.
That's what we'll aim for next.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 5A] And now
Miku Izayoi will sing her hit,
"Mermaid Love Story."
[MIKU]
♪ Early in the afternoon... ♪
She has such a lovely voice.
I want to do that, too!
You want to go do karaoke?
[TOHKA] No, I want
to do what she's doing!
[SHIDO]
What? You mean the drums?
Ba-dum. Ba-dum!
Bum bum ba-dum.
Ba-dum. Ba-dum.
Ba-da-boppa ba-dum!
[KOTORI] They're here.
Is there something
we can help you with?
Uh, yes please.
I met Miku in
Tengu Square yesterday.
[FEMALE STUDENT 5A]
What, are you another fan?
Not exactly.
That's what they all say.
I'm sorry, but this is supposed
to be her private time--
Hello again, Shiori!
Yo! Wassup?
[chuckles]
I wanted to say thanks.
You really shouldn't have
gone to all this trouble.
[MIKU] No trouble at all.
I just had a very delicious
tea blend delivered.
And it was so sweet of you
to come all the way out here
to my school just
to return my handkerchief.
I had to share a cup with you.
This was supposed to be for
those girls earlier, wasn't it?
Feels wrong to take their place.
Please, don't worry about them.
They're very obedient girls
who always do
what they've been told.
Wow! This really is good!
[giggles]
[KOTORI]
Everything's going smoothly.
We might be able to get her
faster than we anticipated.
[MIKU] You know...
You really are amazing.
I've never had
anyone like you before.
[MIKU] Shiori...
Don't you feel like there's
something special between us?
I think that you should
become a student at Rindoji.
[SHIORI] What?
Now don't you
worry your pretty head
one little bit about
your grades or the cost.
I will personally request
that you be passed through.
Hang on a second!
It's kinda sudden to decide
on something like that!
Please reconsider.
I... The answer is still no.
Hey, Shiori?
What can I do for ya?
Please take off
all of your clothes.
Hey, I think you're great,
but I can't do that.
[MIKU] I'm confused.
Why aren't you doing
what I tell you?
So what does that mean, then?
Are you a Spirit, as well?
[MIKU] There's no point
in trying to hide it anymore.
After all, there's no way
an ordinary person
could disregard
a direct order from me.
And so I wonder:
What in the world are you?
Are you a Spirit? Or worse?
Are you working
for those Wizards
who have been trying to
track me down and take me out?
I um, uh...
[KANNAZUKI]
What should we do?
[KOTORI] If we try to cover
it up, it'll make things worse.
It's gonna be risky,
but we should try
negotiating with her.
[SHIORI]
Look, I'm not a Spirit.
I'm not a Wizard, either.
Just human.
That is so unfortunate.
Lying doesn't become you.
[SHIORI] But...
I do have an ability that
seals Spirit powers away.
[MIKU]
What is that supposed to mean?
Just what it sounds like.
So far, I've successfully sealed
the power of five Spirits.
As long as your powers
are completely sealed,
the AST won't
be able to find you.
Trust me, there is a way
you can live
peacefully in our world.
I give you my word you won't
have to be alone anymore.
Miku...
Trust me,
I just want to help you.
[MIKU] You know something?
I believe you!
Seriously?
[MIKU] But...
I don't need you to
seal my powers for me.
The way things
are right now,
I don't think I could
be much happier.
I have my powers
and a life of luxury.
what more could I possibly need?
Just keep on pushing.
You have to convince her.
Look, Miku...
You caused a major spatial quake
in front of the train
station a few days ago!
But why?
I'm not sure you have total
control of your powers
like you think you do.
[MIKU] Oh? So you know
about that nasty incident.
Your concern is touching,
but honestly,
you don't need
to worry about me.
I've got absolute
control over my powers.
The spatial quake
I caused the other day
was not by accident, sweetie.
What could I do?
I'd never gotten the chance
to sing at Tengu Arena before.
So naturally,
when I passed it in
front of the station,
I suddenly felt
the urge to sing.
And I decided to let it go!
That's the reason you did it?
Yeah, I just
couldn't help myself.
The desire to make music
completely took me over.
If your friends
had been there,
they could have died!
Did that thought
even occur to you, Miku?
I suppose I would
have been upset.
Really, you would?
[MIKU] Then again, All the girls
totally adore me no matter what.
I'm sure they
would be satisfied
knowing that
they had died for me.
[SHIORI]
Because they totally adore you?
[KOTORI]
Shido! Try to calm down!
[MIKU] Yes!
I have legions of fans that
love me with all their hearts.
They do whatever I ask,
whenever I ask them to do it.
[SHIORI]
Then you might want to know...
I hate you.
[MIKU] Why's that?
You're intolerably
arrogant and prideful.
Even if everyone in the world
chose to accept
a spoiled brat like you,
I'd still hate your guts.
And as much as they'd love you,
I'd hate you more.
[MIKU] Hearing such
harsh words from you...
They make me
want you even more.
I have a burning desire
to tease you mercilessly.
Until you come to me, crying,
your face streaked with tears...
And shout, "I love you, Miku."
Dream on!
I will never belong to you!
[MIKU] Oh?
[chuckles softly]
Then why don't
we play a little game?
If your school somehow
manages to win first place
at the Festival, then...
...I'll agree to
let you seal my powers
right then and there.
[SHIORI] The Tenou Festival?
[MIKU] That's right!
I'm already participating
in the stage portion,
so you should put together
a performance, too.
But... You've got
a serious advantage!
Well, that's your opinion.
The way I see it, I'm already
doing you a big favor
by allowing you to compete.
Now, the other side of the coin.
If Rindoji wins,
I will have you.
Oh, and I also want
each one of the Spirits
that you already sealed.
Will you agree to my terms?
Or do you want to run away?
[RYOKO]
Is this some kind of a joke?
[JESSICA] No.
We're quite serious about it.
And if you have
any issues with that,
then you can simply
go wait outside.
[RYOKO]
Did you say human targets?
Oh, hell no!
What is this crap?
We're after Spirits, here.
We don't hunt down people!
And not only that,
the operation is in Tengu Square
during the school Festival!
You want to fight
Spirits in a place
where you're
guaranteed a crowd?
[JESSICA] This is
a part of the ceremony.
A cordial greeting to
our admired adversaries.
Wait, what are
you saying? Hold on!
[JESSICA] One more thing.
Make sure Origami Tobiichi
doesn't find out
about any of this.
[RYOKO] What?
That's also a direct
order from the top.
If you have any concerns,
feel free to tell them.
[RYOKO]
What on earth was that about?
[RYOKO] Shido Itsuka.
Where've I heard that name?
[RYOKO]
No. Wasn't he Origami's...?