[SHIDO] Kurumi?
This might've been a mistake.
[groans]
[SHIDO] A time-eating castle?
[KURUMI giggling]
[MIKU] Wait...
Who is that with him?
Don't tell me
she's a Spirit as well.
She doesn't seem
the slightest bit affected
by my performance.
[SHIORI] But...
I do have an ability that
seals Spirit powers away.
[MIKU] Impudent fool...
As if I'd ever
give you the chance!
If I did, it would
be just like before.
They can't stop us.
The show must go on!
[NARRATOR]
Two stand against many...
To save the trapped Spirits...
To bring them to his side...
To the side of the one with
the strength to subdue Spirits.
[SHIDO] Miku!
[sighs]
Your voice really
grates on my nerves...
Can you please refrain
from contaminating
the eardrums of these
lovely Spirits or myself
with that obnoxious clamoring?
I find it most unpleasant.
You're so beyond worthless
that it makes me nauseated.
Shut your foul mouth
for a moment,
--you ambling monument to filth.
--[SHIDO] Miku. Listen up!
I have to go save Tohka.
She was kidnapped by the people
you should actually
be worried about.
--Understand?
--I thought I just told you.
Shut your mouth!
Gabriel... March!
They're starting to wake up!
Well, color me impressed.
I didn't think ordinary
humans would be able to move
while under the
effects of my shadow.
Of course they can.
The power of Gabriel
makes people adore me,
then shapes their will to
match my own wants and desires!
Your shadow is too weak...
And now, I'm not going to
tell them to just capture you.
No, quite the contrary!
Come along, my darlings!
Go forth.
And that means rip
that man to shreds!
Stop! You're making me laugh.
It seems a tad premature
to pat yourself on the back.
You'll have to
do better than that
if you expect
to beat me, got it?
Careful!
I haven't killed anyone yet.
Stop worrying so much.
--[KAGUYA] Raphael, El Re'em!
--[YUZURU] Raphael, El Nahash!
[KAGUYA, YUZURU yelling]
Thanks. Helluva catch!
No problem.
You can reward me
when this is over.
Kaguya! Yuzuru!
I'm starting to find
your persistence annoying!
I will not take it easy
on anyone who intends
to harm our Mistress,
no matter who they might be!
Admonishment.
Continue defying us, and
I will be left with no choice
but to eliminate you.
[ghastly laughter]
[YOSHINO]
I'm really sorry, but...
I won't let you
lay a finger on her!
Yoshino...
You have got to be joking!
Don't expect an attack like that
to work against
hurricane children!
I call forth... Zaphkiel!
[KURUMI] Now then, Shido...
I think that you and Miku
should have some alone time.
And whatever you do,
make sure you convince her
to keep out of our way
when we rescue Tohka.
[KURUMI] Zaphkiel... Aleph.
Well then,
I'll leave it to you.
Good luck, Me.
Thanks.
I'm not gonna let
either of us down, Me.
[gunshot]
[KAGUYA] No way!
[YOSHINON]
What is your deal, weirdo?
No, don't let her sing!
Wait...
What are you doing?
I've kept the promise I
made to you, Shido, my sweet.
Now all you need to do is figure
out a way to change her mind.
You kids have fun!
[KURUMI giggling]
[MIKU] I have nothing
to discuss, do you hear me?
And what is it with
this strange place?
Something gets in the way every
time I try to use my powers!
Then to top it all off,
I'm stuck here with
an icky plebe like you!
I'm really sorry
about tricking you, Miku...
But those other people didn't
have anything to do with this!
Please, let them go, you don't--
Shut your mouth!
Just be quiet!
Not a single word!
The last thing I want is
to talk to a creep like you
after you humiliated me!
[SHIDO]
Fine. You can stay mad at me.
Just listen...
Do you remember Tohka?
The girl who was singing
on stage with my band?
She's a Spirit, too,
as I'm sure you've noticed.
During the uproar in the arena,
she was kidnapped
by a DEM wizard.
I'm going to do
everything I can to save her.
And I brought you here
to ask for your help.
[MIKU] What?
[SHIDO] Even with Kurumi's
powers added into the mix,
it still might not be
enough to get Tohka back!
But if you were to join us,
it could be the extra
push we need to win!
I refuse!
Why would I do such a thing
for a jerk like you?
[SHIDO] Please!
[MIKU] I'm tired of this!
I no longer wish to
listen to your nonsense!
To your lies!
I know you have
an ulterior motive,
because human beings
are selfish.
None of you are capable
of caring about someone
the way you claim to!
Why do you hate
humans so intensely, Miku?
Even you were one--
[KURUMI] Sorry to interrupt in
the middle of your little chat,
but we're about to
reach the time limit!
[SHIDO] No, wait!
Mistress, you're back!
Are you all right?
Relief.
We were worried about you.
[KURUMI] Come on, Shido.
Up on your feet, my dear...
My power over Time unfortunately
has finite limits.
Retreating would be a good idea.
No, not yet, Kurumi!
I was getting so close--
You threaten my Mistress...
I won't stand for it!
But Yoshino...
Are you starting
to see the situation?
Zaphkiel. Aleph.
[SHIDO] Sorry, Kurumi.
I didn't change her mind at all.
I just made her mad instead.
And after you did
so much to help me...
[KURUMI] The last thing I ever
thought I'd hear from you
are words of gratitude.
It actually made me happy.
Now pat my head
in a manner of approval.
[KURUMI]
Anyway, from everything I saw,
she doesn't seem like the type
who would put herself in danger
just to try and stop us.
And more importantly,
I gave her a sample platter
of some of my abilities.
[SHIDO]
Yeah. I guess you're right.
There is one thing...
What's that?
You were asking Miku
to join your side
while you were in
the shadow, weren't you?
So, are you trying to insinuate
that my help isn't
going to be enough for you?
That... wasn't my intention--
I was just teasing you.
We don't know how powerful the
enemy we're about to face is.
You made the right
decision when you tried
to increase the power of our
assault force, my handsome hero.
Thank you...
But that said...
Never, ever try to
lie to me, sweetheart.
You're not very good at it.
Okay.
[KURUMI] Oh, that's right...
I have some more news for you:
I have tracked down Tohka.
What? Really? Where is she?
[giggling]
DEM.
Deus Ex Machina Industries,
in Building One
of their Japan branch.
[WESTCOTT] I'm excited
to finally meet you
in person, Princess.
Or should I say
Tohka Yatogami instead?
I'm Isaac Westcott, the Managing
Director of DEM Industries.
[growling]
I wonder why she
doesn't like me?
You probably should
have taken your approach
into consideration
if you wanted her approval.
[TOHKA]
Are you the one behind this?
What is it you
people want from me?
[WESTCOTT] Good question!
It's actually rather simple.
I want to harness the
powers you have as a Spirit.
I'm planning to unleash them
to create total chaos.
Chaos? You can't!
Unfortunately, your
presence in this world
is far too stable
at the moment.
I'll have to find
the perfect trigger
to push you
towards despair.
[TOHKA] What do you mean?
[WESTCOTT]
What do you think, Ellen?
Physical pain is probably the
fastest way, wouldn't you agree?
Electric shock...
Oxygen deprivation...
Pulling her toenails
off might work...
We could always
file your teeth down.
Don't even get me
started when it comes to
completely destroying
your dignity as a woman!
Do you have any friends
or lovers out there
in the real world?
I wonder how
you'd feel if we killed
someone close to you right
in front of your eyes?
Who's out there?
[ELLEN]
The person she feels closest to
is most likely Shido Itsuka,
whom I mentioned.
During my initial interrogation,
her biometric readings
practically went
through the roof when
I mentioned his name.
[WESTCOTT] Very good.
Then we'll wait for him
before we continue.
You scum!
If you hurt one hair
on Shido's head, I'll--
Struggling will
only make it worse.
No... Shido!
[KURUMI] Every one of the
buildings in front of us
belongs to DEM.
Building One is the tall
skyscraper in the middle.
Unfortunately,
I'm not able to determine
exactly which part
of the building she's in.
As long as you're
sure that she's in there...
Shall we go over the
plan one more time, then?
First course of action:
You and I make our way
to the target building.
Then I call in the other mes
to create a distraction
by attacking the
outlying facilities.
[SHIDO] Which will help disperse
the enemy's attack power,
and lessen the guard
on Tohka at the same time,
theoretically.
Don't worry.
It will work like a charm.
The spatial quake alarm!
[alarm sounding]
Why now of all times?
Is there another
Spirit out here?
[KURUMI] That doesn't seem to
be the case this time around...
I wouldn't be at all
surprised if DEM themselves
set off the alarm.
And if that's true...
...it's a good bet
they're trying to minimize
the number of eyewitnesses
to their orgy of violence!
[SHIDO] Bandersnatch!
Come out and play, girls!
[ghastly laughter]
Whoa, that's amazing...
These are the hors d'oeuvres.
Just wait for the main course!
[SHIDO] What?
[KURUMI] Let's change the plan
up a bit, what do you say?
Why don't I sic the other mes
on the dolls and Wizards?
Then we'll waltz past, using
the cover created by the chaos.
Now then, Zaphkiel. Aleph!
[SHIDO wheezing]
[KURUMI] Are you going
to be all right, Shido?
[SHIDO] Yeah.
Don't worry about me...
We're running out of time.
We should get moving!
[KURUMI] Sure... fine.
Whatever you say.
[SHIDO] Mana?
Brother!
Another violent
welcome from you.
It's nice to see that
some things don't change.
Don't shoot!
[KURUMI] Did you actually
think a cheap shot like that
could finish off
the likes of me?
No, but I saw the
chance and I took it.
Maybe next time
I'll be lucky enough
to permanently erase
that creepy smile of yours!
[KURUMI] It's really adorable
when you get all
worked up like that.
Maybe you're just
too dumb to remember
how badly I beat you.
Or did the terror
of our last encounter
make you suffer
hysterical amnesia?
[SHIDO] We really
don't have time for this.
Actually, this works
out perfectly for me.
There's an entirely
different matter
I'd like to settle
with DEM before we go,
so we should split up
for the time being.
You should be fine with
Mana keeping an eye on you.
What about our strategy?
[KURUMI] Don't worry
your little head about it.
My doppelgangers will continue
creating a diversion for you.
Bye-bye, Shido!
I'll see you later!
[SHIDO] Kurumi! Wait!
Uh, I don't know
what kind of arrangement
you had with that girl...
But her leaving's for the best.
[SHIDO] C'mon, Mana,
she's not that bad.
I almost forgot!
Here. Take it.
[KOTORI]
Shido, can you hear me?
[SHIDO] Kotori?
Are you back to normal now?
[KOTORI] Yes. Fortunately.
I want to apologize.
Apparently, I told you to die
and some other mean stuff.
But I didn't mean any of it.
[SHIDO] Yeah, I knew that.
Forget about it, okay?
[MIKU] Come on!
This is starting to
become really annoying!
What are you, simple?
There's no way a mere human,
especially a filthy,
stinking male,
could ever hold anything more
dearly than his own stupid life!
[MIKU] It isn't possible!
But if it is true, then I...
What's wrong, Mistress?
Say... My dears...
I want you to give me a concise,
honest answer, all right?
What do you know about Tohka
and Shido's relationship?
Do you think he was
telling me the truth?
Is she really that
precious to him?
No. That dude is
like way superficial!
I bet that he's all talk.
Ugh. That is so lame!
[MIKU] I thought I told you
girls to answer me honestly.
I hate girls who tell lies.
So like If I'm
being perfectly honest,
I don't know what kind
of relationship they have.
They aren't dating, but I think
they're more than just friends.
I've seen them spend a
lot of time together, and...
And when Tohka's with him,
she seems really happy.
Even though he's a total dork,
I think he cares for her a lot.
It seems true, Mistress.
That's so lame.
Then, if the
situation got desperate,
and he had to sacrifice
himself in order to save Tohka,
what do you think
Shido would do?
Shido would never give up.
He wouldn't hesitate
for a moment.
I know he'd do whatever
it took to save Tohka.
Yoshino's right,
and he'd pull it off, too.
That idiot would stare
death square in the face
without thinking of
himself for a second.
He did it before,
when he saved me and Yuzuru.
Agreement.
There must be
something wrong with him.
I'm certain he would
do anything for Tohka,
no matter what he might
be forced to sacrifice.
I will bring Tohka back,
no matter what happens,
or what I have to do!
[KOTORI] No way.
I won't accept it.
[SHIDO]
What are you talking about?
Tohka's been kidnapped!
And you told me that DEM
was a dangerous organization
trying to kill off all Spirits!
[KOTORI] Exactly!
They're extremely dangerous!
Excuse me for trying
to keep my moron brother
from infiltrating
a freaking lion's den!
And by the way, your life
is just as important
as the people you're protecting!
[SHIDO] Are you suggesting
I just leave Tohka?
[KOTORI] We need time
to properly prepare!
[SHIDO] That'll take too long!
Kurumi is out there stalling
the Wizards for us right now.
We won't have another
chance like this.
Trust me!
I know I can save her.
I just need more time! Please!
[KOTORI] All right, fine!
Not like you'd listen if
I tried to stop you, anyway.
Thanks. I suppose
you know me too well, Kotori.
I should hope so.
I've been your sister
for over a decade now, jerk.
After you've made it
inside the building,
they'll most likely
jam all communications.
The only thing
the Fraxinus can do
is provide support
on the outside.
That will be more than enough.
Thanks, Kotori.
[KOTORI] Seriously...
The things we little
sisters have to deal with
because of big brothers
who never listen!
Right, Mana?
But to be fair,
I would also never accept
having a weakling big brother
who could turn tail and run.
That's pathetic.
[KOTORI] If you're going
to go through with it,
I won't allow you
to half-ass it.
I won't consider it a
success until Tohka is saved
and you and Mana are
back on board the Fraxinus.
Deal.
[KOTORI] Now...
[KOTORI, SHIDO]
It's time.
Let's begin our date!
No, Origami,
you can't, please stop!
[ORIGAMI] Let me go.
If Shido is on the battlefield,
then I must help him.
That's impossible!
Don't you know that your ID
has been totally frozen?
You aren't even allowed
to use the wiring suits,
much less the CR units!
Then I'll just have to
use conventional armament.
I should be able to find a rifle
somewhere on the base.
Are you crazy?
You think you can enter
a battlefield of Wizards
and Spirits without
your own Territory?
And on top of all that...
Shido is Nightmare's accomplice
in attacking D.E.M Industries.
He's become the AST's enemy.
[ORIGAMI] Don't you understand?
That's exactly why
I have to go.
I've lost everything
else in my life.
He's the only thing
I can rely on now.
If he dies,
so will part of me.
I'll no longer
be myself anymore.
You have to let me go.
What if I told you
I would commit suicide
if you left this building?
I'm confident you would
never do such a thing.
I know you know how sad
I would be if you did.
But this isn't fair.
I'm a little bit jealous of him.
Because it seems as if you
would do anything for him.
There is one thing...
I just thought of it...
But I don't know if
you can use it or not.
[ghastly laughter]
[MANA] Time to move, brother.
[SHIDO] All right.
I guess now is as
good a time as any.
But with such a
large facility,
it would be nice to at least
know which floor Tohka is on.
[REINE]
If they have Tohka confined,
it is probably in their facility
to quarantine Spirits...
Like the one
we have on Fraxinus.
Are you okay?
[MANA] Yeah, yeah.
I'm fine, don't you worry.
Wait, isn't that...
...White Licorice?
[MANA] You sure know
your hardware!
But this one is a
little bit different.
It's the sister unit
to White Licorice,
which was made for testing.
DW-zero-two-nine-R,
Scarlet Licorice!
[SHIDO] Mana!
[KOTORI]
Shido, it's too dangerous!
Don't move on your own.
Wait for Mana!
[SHIDO] But their defense is
getting stronger every minute!
And if I'm outside,
I might get in Mana's way!
[KOTORI]
That's actually a good point.
Wait, Shido!
There's an intruder!
[MALE WIZARD 8A]
Halt, who goes there?
Where did you come from?
[MALE WIZARD 8A]
Stop! Stop or I'll shoot!
[SHIDO]
You're already shooting!
[SHIDO] Damnit...
I can't let it
end here like this!
Tohka... Tohka... Tohka!
I need you!
[WIZARDS gasping]
An Angel?
[SHIDO] Oh yeah. About time!
Let's go and save
your master! Agreed?
[TOHKA]
You summoned Sandalphon.
You brought forth its power
with your desire, Shido.
You see...
It answered your call,
and only you have the power
to command it now.
[yelling]
[stabbing noise]
[SHIDO] Get out of my way,
you bastard!
[SHIDO choking]
I'll save you...
Tohka... Tohka!