['Monochrome Sky' playing]
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
And now,
here are your results
for the 25th annual
Tenou Festival stage
performance competition!
[ANNOUNCER 6A] In third place,
Senjo High School!
[CROWD cheering, jeering]
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Next up,
the surprise hit of the contest.
[ANNOUNCER 6A] In second
place, Raizen High School!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 6A] And the
school that receives first place
for the stage portion is...
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
As expected,
the strong performance of
Rindoji Girls' Academy
brings home the gold!
[CROWD cheering]
[song continues]
[giggles]
[NARRATOR] The beautiful
and wild songstress
with a temperamental nature...
Why does she hold people
in such complete contempt?
No one knows her true desires
hidden behind
that perfect smile.
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Next up,
we will announce the total
results from the first day!
[TOHKA] Shido?
[MIKU] There. You see?
I'm afraid you lost the contest
because you were too
dependent on your friends.
And a promise is
a promise, my dear...
Now you and all five
of the Spirits you sealed
are mine to do with as I please.
Isn't that right?
Oh, you don't need to
feel apprehensive, though.
I'll most definitely be taking
care of you all properly.
[ANNOUNCER 6A] ...goes to
the hard-working kids
at Raizen High!
First place? We won? Really?
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
In the food booth portion,
Raizen High's maid cafe received
an incredible number of votes,
helping them win from behind
at the eleventh hour!
[MIKU whimpering]
[TONOMACHI] It's way simple.
Miku cranked up
the pressure big time
during the stage
performance part...
However, Rindoji's true
worth usually lies in their
food booth's
excellent ultra-hotties
per capita ratio, which,
unfortunately, was
completely neglected this year.
[laughs nervously]
Shido!
Well, duh.
Of course we're winners!
Agreed. They never
stood a chance against us.
[SHIORI]
We won... We really won!
You've got to
be kidding me...
It doesn't make sense.
There's no way they're
actually serious about this...
Don't you know?
I'm Miku Izayoi, you fools!
Understand?
Don't they understand?
[SHIORI] Miku...
Just stop.
My song won first place.
I was supposed to win!
Look...
The reason that we won
may sound corny,
but it has to do with that
"dependent on friends" thing.
[MIKU] What do you mean?
Simple...
I could never beat you
with my singing.
And so
the other students at
Raizen worked extra hard
to help cover
for my shortcomings.
Which means the humans
you arrogantly look down on
can defeat you when they
come together as a team.
Come with us.
Don't be alone.
Shut your mouth.
Friendship? Teamwork?
Give me a break.
I've got news for you.
You face me,
and those platitudes
become meaningless!
Gabriel!
[ALL shriek]
[organ music playing]
Miku, wait!
Listen to me, please!
[organ music continues]
Sing... Singing...
Sang... Gabriel!
[organ music continues]
No... Did you...?
Miku...
You can't do this! Please!
[MIKU giggles]
[MIKU] They were your friends,
weren't they?
So darn reliable...
So earnestly committed...
[giggles]
And so easily
bent to my will.
Let me go!
[MIKU] I don't even care about
the stupid promise anymore.
Because I will have my way,
and there's nothing in
this world that can stop me.
Now, then...
You know what I want.
Sweet Shiori, the Spirits.
Everyone... You are all
my personal property...
What?
[SHIORI whimpering]
What did I just touch?
No. You can't be...
Come check underneath
this one's skirt!
No!
[screaming]
[MIKU screaming]
If you're a man,
that means just now...
I touched...
That's so gross!
Wait! Miku, please.
Just calm down!
So gross!
[organ music playing]
[shrieking]
[MIKU] How dare you!
You tried to fool me!
The gall to play
with my feelings!
[SHIDO] Crap! Where can I go?
[SHIDO] Nowhere!
My only option
is to stop Miku...
[YOSHINON]
Uh uh uh! That's dangerous.
You can't hurt her anymore.
I won't let you.
[SHIORI]
Yoshino? Not you, too...
You idiot.
Did you really think we'd
disobey our Mistress' commands?
Scornful...
We won't let you
lay a finger on her,
so forget it.
[MIKU laughs]
[MIKU] That's a spot of
bad luck for you, little Shiori!
I can't believe you brought
so many Spirits here with you!
Plus...
They're all the types
of girls that I like!
[SHIORI] No way...
Not you too, Tohka.
Not you, too.
[SHIDO yells]
[TOHKA] Shido!
What in the world
is going on here?
[SHIORI]
Tohka! You're not hypnotized?
Huh? I can barely
hear you at all...
Oh!
[SHIORI]
Your in-ear monitors...
Wait... You left them in?
[TOHKA] Yep!
I couldn't pick up the rhythm
very well with only one.
So what's going on?
Well...
Miku is pretty much
in control of everybody...
Kotori!
[KOTORI]
Yes. What's the situation?
Things have gone
downhill in a hurry...
We're heading outside.
Please bring Fraxinus
to pick us up.
Huh? What are you saying?
If you're dumb enough
to go against our Mistress,
then you should stay
and get torn to shreds.
But... What the hell?
[NAKATSUGAWA laughing]
[NAKATSUGAWA] Stupid!
[KAWAGOE]
You dared to trick Miss Miku!
Death will be your atonement!
He's right!
Drop dead where you stand!
What's going on?
[SHIIZAKI] Hey.
You're not affected, are you?
While I was analyzing
the sound on stage,
everyone suddenly
started acting weird...
[ANNOUNCER 7A] Basic Realizers,
parallel driving force...
Replenishing magic power now.
Preparing the converging magic
power cannon, Mistilteinn...
Target: Tengu Square,
central stage.
Commander!
Why is it powering up?
Because I'm planning
to evaporate anyone
who might oppose my
Mistress Miku in one fell swoop.
But you can't!
Vice Commander,
help me stop her!
I'll ask you
not to interfere...
I can't let this end...
I have finally found my utopia.
[SHIIZAKI] You mean you're
not under her mind-control?
[KOTORI] Now all I have
to do is push this button...
Don't do it!
Boom.
[gasps]
[MANA] Anyone want to tell me
what's going on here?
And start from the top;
I've been asleep for a while.
[JESSICA] Not so hot now?
Shame there isn't enough
time to really work you over...
But there are more
important things to do.
So let's put an end
to this, shall we?
Shido...
[JESSICA] What the hell?
[ORIGAMI] Mana?
[MANA] Long time no see,
Master Sergeant Tobiichi.
And my, my...
Fancy bumping into you
like this, Jessica.
[JESSICA] Adeptus Two?
I demand to know why
you're attacking us!
[MANA] I don't think I'm going
to go by that code name anymore.
It's no longer needed, since
I'm quitting DEM Industries.
I won't let you
betray Master Westcott!
Vanargand, huh?
I guess it's not too shabby for
something that's brand new...
[MANA]
I'll let you go this time.
Did I stutter?
That's your cue to turn tail!
[TOUKA yelling]
Stop, guys!
Snap out of it already!
Miku...
We stop her, they'll wake up!
[TOHKA screams]
Tohka!
[TOHKA]
Okay! Now you've done it!
[MIKU sings]
[TOHKA screams]
Tohka!
[MIKU] It's no use, silly.
[ELLEN] I take it Bailey's
team failed their objective?
Not that it really matters...
I anticipated as much.
[SHIORI]
Hold on... I know you!
Why have you come here?
What do you want with us?
[ELLEN] Acquired Targets:
Tohka Yatogami,
and some girl that matches
the readings for Shido Itsuka...
Apprehension underway.
Go! Right now!
[screaming]
Smart move,
tactically speaking.
[TOHKA] Coming from you, that
means absolutely nothing to me!
[ELLEN] Caledfwlch!
Oh my.
Your attack seems to be less
powerful than it used to be...
[ELLEN] I'll take care
of you in no time flat!
[coughing]
That's Tohka...
Come back!
[REPORTER 7A]
This afternoon, around five PM,
the mysterious disturbance at
the site of the Tengu Festival
spread throughout
the city like a wildfire.
Its numbers have swelled
to the tens of thousands...
Damn it... Tohka...
What am I going to do?
I'm just... so lost!
[FEMALE giggling]
Poor Shido.
You look like someone just
walked over your grave...
How can I help?
[KURUMI] You seem like
you're in way over your head.
Come on, Shido.
Why don't we have
ourselves a little chat?
That's fine.
What about...
[KURUMI]
Yoshino and the Yamai sisters
have been taken from you
by a new rogue Spirit.
And Tohka has been kidnapped
by the Wizards from DEM.
You seem to be heading down
a path of absolute despair...
I know about everything
that's been happening to you,
my darling...
[SHIDO] You're not being
controlled by her, are you?
[KURUMI]
No. But sweet of you to ask.
It's so cute that you think I'm
innocent enough to be swayed
by that supposed Diva's
level of supposed performance.
Hey, Kurumi?
I've got a favor to ask.
Lend me your strength,
and please help me save Tohka!
[KURUMI] Well...
[SHIDO] I know why you've
come looking for me!
But before that, please!
You're the only one
I can count on now.
Will you please help me?
[laughs]
What a surprising turn
of events this has been!
Yes, yes, I must say
it is very unexpected!
[TOHKA] Morning already?
First, I have to open my eyes.
After I get out of bed,
I have to wash my face.
Then, I eat breakfast and
head off to school with Shido.
[TOHKA] Where am I?
[ELLEN] Are you awake?
It's you!
[ELLEN]
Please remain calm.
Breaking those bonds wouldn't be
advisable in your current state.
[TOHKA] Don't mess with me!
Hurry up and take these off!
I have to get out
of here and save Shido!
We have operatives
searching for Shido Itsuka
as we speak.
It should be a matter of days
before he joins you here.
But that said...
If he resists too much, he may
arrive with a broken arm or two.
[TOHKA screaming]
[ELLEN] My Territory
is the most accurate
of all the DEM Wizards.
Any attempt to resist is futile.
[ELLEN] Now then.
I'm going to ask you
a bunch of questions,
and I want them
answered immediately.
[SHIDO] Hey, Kurumi...
Why go to Miku's
place right now?
No one's home.
I mean, our time would be better
spent trying to save Tohka!
[KURUMI] Don't worry,
we'll go save Tohka.
But we need to deal with
the Miku problem first.
[KURUMI] Wow, Shido!
Take a look at this!
Oh, god.
[KURUMI]
Look at how humongous it is!
I could almost fit my whole head
in one of these crazy cups!
[SHIDO]
Come on! What are you doing?
This is hardly the time!
[KURUMI giggles]
You're so serious...
Here, take it.
Why don't you try
to put it on, too?
[SHIDO] Uh... no?
I'm not into that kinda stuff.
I apologize.
I must've been mistaken.
Just thought it would
look great on Shiori!
Oh, you saw that, huh?
That's right.
I just never had
a good opportunity
to see it up close
and personal...
I was hoping maybe you could
fix that situation for me!
Hey!
Would ya' cut it out already?
[KURUMI]
Don't be such a wet blanket.
You only have to wear it
for a little while.
I really want to see the
adorable Shiori's angelic face
trembling with
carnal humiliation.
Stop it! Stay back!
Leave her alone!
--Leave Shiori alone!
--[KURUMI] Do it for me?
It'll be our special secret...
That hurt...
You okay, Kurumi?
Yes.
I'm perfectly okay...
Because there was a big brave
knight who took the fall for me.
No sweat...
Oh no. You're hurt!
Looks like something
scratched your cheek.
Huh? Oh wow... That's weird...
It's all right, though.
A little spit should
clean it right up.
[SHIDO] What do you
think you're doing?
You said it would
be fine with a little spit,
now, didn't you?
What's that?
[KURUMI]
Is something the matter?
[SHIDO] Tsukino Yoimachi?
Well, now,
isn't this interesting?
Look what I found.
But isn't that--
[SHIDO] Hey. Hold on!
[KURUMI] Zaphkiel, Yod shot!
Kurumi!
[KURUMI] Don't worry about me.
Yod's power is recollection...
A powerful technique that
gives me a special inside-look
into some of the
target's recent memories.
Memories like what?
Like recollections
of a past life.
[AI]
Reporting in, Mistress Miku!
Have you found that boy yet?
The gross imposter?
Yes, Mistress!
There's no mistaking it!
That is so lame!
Oh. Is that the case?
He was more elusive
than I'd expected...
Well...
Who finally tracked
the pervert down, then?
I hope it's a pretty young lady,
so I can dote on her lovingly...
But if it was a man...
Oh.
I guess you can give him
a piece of candy
and send him on his way.
He, uh...
Got found by like
a whole crowd of people...
It's hard to pick
just one person to reward...
That is so, so lame...
[AI] He's outside.
Like he just showed up.
Facing her head-on is crazy,
no matter how you slice it.
Even if you thought
of a more certain way
to get you sent
straight to Miku,
it's too late because
we're already here...
Which means, at this point,
your energy is better
spent figuring out
how to persuade her.
Okay, fine.
I guess you're right.
[MIKU] I've had all these
people out searching for you.
Instead, you come
to me on your own.
You must have a great deal of
confidence in yourself, Shiori!
Or should I say...
...Shido Itsuka!
Miku...