[FEMALE VOICE]
Where am I?
Why am I not dead?
This isn't making any sense.
[MAN 6A]
Miss Mana Takamiya?
That's right,
and who are you?
[NARRATOR] Yuri...
The mysterious world of
aesthetics and perversion...
The forbidden door opens right
in front of Shido's very eyes.
It's all right.
It will only scare you
for a little while.
[AI] No way.
It's an attack on
Shiori's awesomeness!
Get ready!
We're gonna do everything we can
to make sure you win this, girl!
Our band's lost some people.
Mainly because Ai is so selfish
and such a nightmare
to work with.
But, we're glad to have
the band back together!
That is so lame!
We have to beat them!
I'm afraid losing
is not an option.
Thanks a lot, guys!
Wait a second--
Origami, you're performing too?
Let's do it.
I just need to know
who plays what!
I can play a
little guitar, I guess.
I can rock the bass.
I can play the drums!
No!
The boom-booms are
supposed to be mine!
[TOHKA sobbing]
Did she say
"boom-booms?"
That is so lame.
Oh. That's right, you
wanted to play the drums, too.
I'm sorry, Tohka, but Mai is
pretty much an expert drummer.
Don't worry.
We'll find something
for you to play. Cool?
Wait a sec.
Do you even know how
to play anything else?
[AI] I know!
Tohka, this is like way huge.
But what is it?
A legendary instrument
that's super hard to play.
The key to any band's success.
That is so lame!
Wow! It's incredible!
So, do you like it?
Just you watch!
I won't let you down!
[cheering]
Now all we need
is a lead singer.
Origami?
Wow, that was totally amazing!
I didn't know you could
sing like that, Origami.
That is so lame!
So you'll be singing!
It'll be my
"drop the mic" moment.
I am so exhausted after having
to bust my hump dealing with
that awful chick all day long.
I just can't keep it
to myself anymore.
What a relief no one's
around to hear me talking.
Tomorrow.
September twenty-third, at
precisely fifteen hundred hours.
The 3rd battle squad will
charge into Tengu Square.
A difficult mission.
Our primary goal is to
capture Tohka Yatogami,
a girl thought to be a Spirit.
And secondly, we aim
to capture Shido Itsuka,
second year student
at Raizen High School.
Oh boy,
tomorrow's operation
is incredibly annoying.
I'm so exhausted
and unmotivated.
I'm worried I might forget
to lock the back door
to Hanger Number Two!
Did you catch that?
Hope so.
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will now commence
the twenty-fifth annual
Joint-High School
Cultural Extravaganza:
The famous and beloved
Tenou Festival!
[CROWD cheering]
[TOHKA laughing]
[TOHKA] It's so frilly!
[KAGUYA laughing]
My...
I gotta hand it to you, Shido.
You look surprisingly good
in lady clothes!
Agreement. I would like
to take you home with me.
[SHIORI] Um...
So about this Maid Café...
This'll be fun.
We gotta take down
Rindoji, right?
With a beautiful but
surprisingly innocent girl,
a set of twins,
and a tall yet
timid and bashful type.
Come on!
The boys'll love us!
Except for the ones
who like older girls
or are into other dudes!
That is so lame!
[SHIORI] Wait...
Origami...
Does anyone know where she is?
Doubt. I have not
seen her at all.
Who knows, maybe she slept
straight through her alarm.
Anyway, "Poster Girl," you
better get your game face on.
We're counting on you
to bring in the customers!
[SHIORI] Whoa!
Cool! This is
gonna be so much fun!
Stand by.
We will follow your instructions
and commands, Shiori.
Because after all,
you're our Head Maid!
Huh?!
Your wish is our command!
Wait... What?
Well, I uh...
I guess my command
is that we all work hard!
--[MAIDS] Yes, ma'am!
--[TOHKA, KAGUYA] Yeah!
Step right up!
Don't be shy, boys!
[SHIDO] I'm so stressed
I'm seeing things.
[SHIORI] Miku...
Good morning, Shiori,
how are you today?
From the looks of things, I'd
say you're doing quite well.
How nice of you to say.
[MIKU giggles]
I've gotta admit...
Those clothes suit you.
In fact,
it might be interesting
for you to wear
that outfit everyday.
Who knows, over time
you might start to enjoy it.
And then you can be
my maid slave all the time.
What? No way. You...
Wow, can't take a joke, huh?
Why don't you all
go somewhere else?
[SHIDO] Of course.
That's Miku's power.
[MIKU] This is better,
wouldn't you agree?
For someone
who's scoping the enemy,
you're not very discreet.
[MIKU] Oh, I'm not
doing that at all.
If you wanna know the truth,
I came here to
ask you out on a date.
A date?
Here! Enjoy!
[SHIORI] Oh. Thanks.
Mmm!
Goodness, this is really tasty!
[KOTORI] She asked her out
after just one day?
I can't tell if she's
really into Shiori
or just that
full of herself.
Well...
Regardless, her happiness level
going up doesn't hurt us.
Just do me a favor and
don't say anything like
"I hate you" this time!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It's good.
Oh, I'm glad you like it!
[MIKU] Here...
This way we'll be even.
[KOTORI]
Why are you hesitating?
Go ahead! Take a bite!
[giggling]
You know,
that's almost like we kissed!
Shiori, look! Over here!
It's a ring toss!
These are so much fun!
So which prize do you want?
You just name it
and I'll get it for you.
[SHIORI] The cat, I guess.
Okay.
Watch, I'll get it
on the first try!
[MIKU] Ha! Ha!
Take that!
Oh man. That's way
harder than I thought.
[SHIORI laughing]
[KOTORI]
What are you, a clown?
Stop laughing and
win the prize, dummy.
Right.
Hey, Miku.
Why don't you let me try?
You are going to give me
that plushy cat at once.
Of course!
Here. It's all yours.
[MIKU] Here you are, Shiori!
Why did you do that, Miku?
--It's wrong.
--[KOTORI] Shido!
Oh. Is this not
the one you wanted?
'Cause I'm happy to
--[SHIORI] That's not it!
--exchange it for you.
What's wrong with you?
That's not how things work.
[MIKU] Oh. Well...
In that case,
what am I supposed to do?
If you want a prize,
you win the game
fair and square. 'Kay?
Okay...
But what happens if I lose
and still want the prize?
[SHIORI] You give up
or keep trying!
Just think about the
people who work here!
Don't you think it
would make them sad
to know they've
been manipulated?
[MIKU] Sad?
They should be over the moon
that I would even accept
a stupid prize
from their silly
Cultural Festival!
You're kidding, right?
Listen, don't worry about them.
They're my playthings,
nothing more.
They're my dumb little pawns
and I use them
to get whatever I want.
You should know I think
very highly of you, though.
So it's not something
you need to worry about.
[KANNAZUKI]
How incredibly sad.
[SHIIZAKI] Vice Commander?
[KANNAZUKI] She's missing out!
It's way more fun
to be a plaything
than to play with others!
[ALL groan]
And you should know,
I'm definitely
going to beat you.
'Cause someone
needs to teach you
what being human's all about.
[MIKU] You're saying
some very strange things.
It's not something
you need to worry about.
But don't underestimate us.
If you think everything will
always just go your way,
then you're in
for a big surprise!
Oh? Then why don't
we test it and find out?
[MIKU] I'd say our date
is officially over now.
I'll be waiting
for you on the stage.
Of course, that's
assuming you're actually
able to perform at all.
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Attention, all performers.
Please gather in the
Green Room immediately.
The stage portion
of the Tenou Festival
will be starting shortly.
It's no use.
I can't reach Origami!
I don't see
Ai, Mai and Mii, either.
Where the heck could they be?
What's wrong, Origami?
Feeling intimidated by my
epic tambourine skills?
Well even if they
don't come, we'll still jam.
I know it!
[dial tone]
[AI] What's up?
Why aren't you here right now?
The thing is about to start!
[AI] Oops, totally
forgot to tell you.
We decided we're
not gonna perform.
Why?
Well, duh!
Obviously because Miku
told us we weren't allowed to!
That's so lame.
This is not good.
Miku used her
power against our band.
[TOHKA] Shido...
[SHIORI] What should we do?
We can't perform
with just the two of us!
[KOTORI] You're right.
We'll have to get
through the performance
with you lip-syncing.
I can't cover
all the instruments,
but I'll send reinforcements.
[SHIORI] Is that gonna fly?
[KOTORI] It'll have to.
We don't have any other choice.
Yeah. True. We'll make it work.
[KOTORI] You're not giving me
enough credit, Miku.
And that's a huge mistake.
If this is the way
you're going to play it,
then just wait, cause
I've got tricks of my own.
[music playing]
[CROWD cheering]
Oh, wow...
[music playing]
[CROWD cheering]
[music stops]
We may have
a situation here.
[KOTORI] Relax. I played with
the facilities a little bit.
Don't worry.
I'll turn the power back on
once the crowd
has chilled out.
Wow, that's pretty
hardcore even for you, Kotori.
[ominous music plays]
Shaddai El Kai!
That's her spirit armor!
Inconceivable!
Hope you're ready
for some fun!
'Cause the real show's
about to begin!
[CROWD cheering]
♪ When skies are turned
from monochrome ♪
♪ to an excess of tones ♪
♪ the world is sure to begin ♪
♪ And if I have you by my side
anytime day or night ♪
♪ then I am sure to smile ♪
♪ I can't stop loving you
every day, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ I can't stop loving you ♪
♪ Holding your hand in mine
and squeezing it so tight ♪
♪ Don't wanna let you go ♪
♪ My heart is open wide
You are my one desire ♪
♪ I hope you feel it, too ♪
♪ Anytime that I
can have you near me ♪
♪ Every worry that I have
is disappearing ♪
♪ You melt my cares away ♪
♪ I hope that we
are growing closer ♪
♪ Just a little every day
I'll know you better ♪
♪ Much more than yesterday ♪
♪ When rainbow wind
blew through air ♪
♪ Lining the road with flare ♪
♪ The trees all smiled
with such happiness there ♪
♪ Like being wrapped up
in a love story ♪
♪ A journey that
has only begun ♪
♪ When skies are turned
from monochrome ♪
♪ to an excess of tones ♪
♪ My heart will race
and my pulse will beat on ♪
♪ Having you near me
feels so astounding ♪
♪ You make every day
so colorful ♪
[CROWD cheering]
That was incredible!
We're screwed.
But Shido...
There's no way I can
follow an act like that.
I'm gonna look like
a total idiot up there.
[KAGUYA] Wow, did you just
walk out of a funeral or what?
Seriously, if I were you,
I'd turn that frown upside down.
[YUZURU] Disappointment.
You've given up before
you even started fighting.
You guys!
[JESSICA] Adeptus Four through
Twelve, move to your positions.
Be ready to attack.
All Bandersnatch,
standing by in Outer One.
Prepare to move in!
[SOLDIER 6A]
Yes, ma'am!
Wait! There are
AST-like readings
in the sky above Tengu Square.
It looks like we've got company!
[KOTORI] Why did they
have to show up now?
What is that? A Spirit?
No way...
White Licorice?
While pursuing
extraordinary performance,
an enormous number of
testers were crippled by it.
The strongest defective machine!
Why are you using it,
you bastard?
Change of plans, team.
Bring her down now!
[DEM WIZARDS] Yes, ma'am!
[SOLDIER 6A] Oh no!
A Targeted Territory?
I can't move at all!
Damn her!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIER 6A]
Captain! Help us!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[JESSICA]
We have a problem here.
Send reinforcements!
[RYOKO] We're sorry.
But unfortunately, this line is
currently unavailable for use.
I sincerely apologize
for any inconvenience,
but Ryoko Kusakabe's
not available.
Please leave a message.
Or I suppose you could hang up
the phone and try again.
[JESSICA] This is no time
to be joking around, Ryoko!
[RYOKO] Like I said, I'm sorry,
but Ryoko can't come
to the phone right now!
If you're too pushy,
I'll have to hang up.
So what,
this is your doing?
I'm gonna make you regret the
day you ever crossed me!
[KOTORI] Reine...
We've got a little situation in
the sky above the stage.
Any chance you can come back?
On my way.
I'm sorry, I have to leave.
Would you rather stay or go?
I think I'd like to stay.
[YOSHINON] Yeah, we don't want
to miss Shido and the others
rocking it out on stage!
Understood.
You guys,
are you sure you're gonna
be all right up there?
Hmm? Of course
we will, silly!
I'll have you know,
Yuzuru and I are pretty much
expert musicians.
[YUZURU] Rock and Roll.
In our seventy-second match
titled "Drumming
to Call a Storm,"
Kaguya was the clear victor.
And in our eighty-fourth match,
"Award for Best Bassist,"
I was the winner.
I jam out a tasty bass lick.
[TOHKA] You guys, look!
I was entrusted with
this fine contraption!
Wow!
You know, the only thing more
important than the tambourine
is the cowbell.
Agreement.
But I think the tambourine
suits you well.
You will rock.
Kotori?
Did something just happen?
[KOTORI] It's nothing.
You need to focus on
your performance, not me.
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Next up, ladies and gents,
is a band performance
from Raizen High School.
[SHIDO] This would be
awesome if we weren't
playing for our freedom.
You're joking, right?
[SHIDO] Man, I haven't
been this nervous
since I went out on dates with
everyone for the first time.
[music playing]
[SHIDO] The vocal
track isn't playing!
[KOTORI] What's going on?
It's the
DEM Wizards' attack!
They've ruined the
wiring in Tengu Square!
We won't be able to
use the vocal track, ma'am!
[KOTORI] Shido!
You'll have to sing live!
But there's
no way I can do that!
[TOHKA] ♪ Taking care to
keep my baggage with me ♪
♪ Loading more and more when I
should be unloading ♪
♪ Always seem to
repeat my mistakes ♪
♪ Just to save my own pride ♪
♪ I'll go on ignoring
all of my faults ♪
♪ Spreading rumors
about everybody else ♪
♪ But I don't feel
so great about it ♪
♪ Going through the motions ♪
♪ Robotic tic and tac ♪
♪ "Go for it," they say ♪
♪ But how do I? ♪
♪ Attention! ♪
♪ One question! ♪
♪ I seem to be caught up
in a mess of things ♪
♪ Is the grass much greener ♪
♪ When on the other side? ♪
♪ Yes and no, yes and no ♪
♪ The moment I finally
stopped and looked around ♪
♪ When time was stilled
then I could clearly see ♪
--♪ in color ♪
--Dammit!
What in the world are you?
Tell me!
[song continues]
[CROWD cheering]
[TOHKA] We did it!
[SHIORI] Yeah!
[CROWD cheering]
Fire! Fire!
[ORIGAMI]
There are too many of them!
What? Blood?
[JESSICA] Well, well!
[laughing]
It appears your time here
is almost up,
Miss Wizard Extraordinaire!
More of them!
[JESSICA laughing]
[JESSICA] I'm afraid
the tables have turned.
I promise you this much:
you're not leaving here alive.