[SHIDO] Um...
What are you doing, Kaguya?
[KAGUYA]
I'm joining you tonight.
You adore sharing
your bed with ladies
according to my kinswoman.
Your kinswoman?
[SHIDO gasps]
What? Yuzuru?
Implementation.
According to my master,
this is the best method
to get rid of sweat.
[SHIDO] Your Master?
Stop that, Kaguya!
Wait. You mean
that you don't want me?
Why would she
need to lick him
in order to get off sweat?
You obviously
do not know anything.
[BOTH growling]
Understood.
My master said in order
to warm you up properly,
I would need to have
skin-to-skin contact with you.
Hey!
What are you snuggling up
to him like that for?
[YUZURU] Ignore.
This action is
none of your business.
The space under the blanket
belongs to adults.
What?!
Don't you underestimate me!
[KAGUYA] Oh yeah...
Now, Shido, isn't this much
warmer than what she was doing?
After all...
Yuzuru gets cold so easily.
[YUZURU] Negative.
Since Kaguya's
chest is lonelier,
she cannot produce
very much heat at all.
[KAGUYA]
What did you just say?
[SHIDO gasps]
[TOHKA] Hold it!
I will take care of Shido
when he is not feeling well!
Let go. Shido is
waiting for me right now.
[BOTH growling]
[AI] Oh my gah, wait!
We're here, guys.
We can decide
this thing for you.
This is Adeptus One.
I can confirm that the
target has entered the room.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Roger.
Shall we deploy
the Bandersnatch?
Have three units
outside the room
just in case they're needed.
Know that Master Sergeant
Tobiichi is in there, too.
Make sure that
the range of Territory--
Did the target notice me?
Ellen?
Where in the world
did you come from?
[SHIDO yelling]
Stop moving!
It's hard to undress you!
Agreed.
You're acting like a
little baby going night-night.
[SHIDO yelling]
[TAMAE] Everyone is
so energetic tonight.
I suppose there's no harm
in letting them have their fun
until lights out.
Shido?
I heard that you were sleeping
because you had a fever.
--Are you okay?
--Please leave me alone!
[CHORUS]
Hey, hey, hey, ho!
[SHIDO, TAMAE screaming]
[NARRATOR] The school trip.
The children are permitted
to buy wooden swords
and then go to the girls' rooms.
They worry about getting
caught by the teacher,
and wind up falling asleep
on a quiet bus the next day
because no one got enough sleep.
That single moment
can twinkle for a lifetime.
[PADDINGTON] Any word from
Miss Implementation Manager?
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Not since earlier, sir.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2B]
There's no movement
within the building, either.
[PADDINGTON] Bring the
Bandersnatch back, then.
Nothing is going
to happen tonight.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 3A]
Sir!
[PADDINGTON]
That little girl...
[REINE] All right.
Let's review the plan.
[SHIDO] Okay.
[REINE]
We'll have the Spirit Berserk.
That is to say the Yamai
sisters, Kaguya and Yuzuru,
spend today's free time
with you at the private beach
where you are currently waiting.
I'll tell them what to do.
I've given them intercoms
to make that happen.
The rest is up to you, Shin.
[SHIDO] Got it.
From there I just, like,
pretend I don't know about them
and let them win me over?
Yes, exactly.
If they understand and believe
that all they have to do
to make you fall for them
is follow my directions,
I'll be able to control
their actions to some extent.
At least that's the idea.
In other words,
as long as everything
goes the way you think,
there's a chance we could seal
both of them at the same time.
[REINE] Correct.
Judging by the girls'
current dynamic,
if you kiss one of them,
there's no way to know
how the other one will react,
but the assumption
is it won't be positive.
[REINE]
Communications with Fraxinus
have not yet been restored.
However, if we do not seal
the elusive Yamai sisters now,
we may never
get a second chance.
So we have to make our move.
You realize there
are many risks involved?
[SHIDO] Yes, I understand.
I'll do what I can to seal
them without any fighting.
[KAGUYA] Thus, Yuzuru or I
will become the new Yamai.
For there can be only one.
[SHIDO] What happens to
the personality that loses?
[KAGUYA]
It will cease to exist...
[SHIDO] I'll try my hardest.
I'm scared I won't
be able to do it, though.
[REINE] I believe in you.
They're almost done changing.
In order to avoid confusion,
I'm going to cut this line
of communication for now.
Don't forget to compliment
them on their swimsuits.
[KAGUYA] Ah hah!
So this is where you've
been hiding out, Shido!
[YUZURU] Discovery.
I have finally found you, Shido.
[SHIDO] Oh, hey there,
ladies, how are you doing?
Those swimsuits are incredible.
You both look very pretty!
Yeah. You better believe it!
Acknowledge. Thank you
for saying such kind words.
Right. Understood and on it.
Duly noted.
I understand as well.
Hey, Shido!
I demand you apply
divine protection
from the miasma
of light on my body.
Request. Will you please
put sunblock onto me?
[SHIDO] Um... sunblock?
[KANNAZUKI] Oh, it's a chore
to work up much enthusiasm
when there's nothing to do.
I did what cannot be undone
and had counted on a good,
abusive scolding
from the commander,
and yet, here I am
un-abused and alone.
And as expected,
he's useless.
If only Analyst Murasame
were here instead of that.
Well, maybe we should
try contacting her later.
[ALL sigh]
This is steamy. Way steamy.
[KAGUYA] Now, Shido.
I am turning my back
to you with full trust.
Don't let me down.
[YUZURU] Request.
Please do this for me.
Yeah. Sure thing.
Let me take a wild guess.
This means I have to touch them
directly, doesn't it?
Hey, Shido's not applying it!
That is not what
you said would happen!
Inquiry. What
am I doing incorrectly?
Um... Okay, here I come!
[chuckles]
Okay, Shido! Now!
Put that protection on my back!
[YUZURU] Negligence.
Didn't you hear me? Jeez.
[gasps erotically]
Crap. I'm sorry.
That was cold, wasn't it?
No. I'm perfectly fine.
Keep going. Don't stop.
[SHIDO] Whatever you say.
[KAGUYA moans erotically]
Counterattack.
I saw an opening.
Petition. Apply.
Hurry and do me. Please, Shido.
Uh, right. I'm on it.
Wow. Cold...
Oh my.
[moans erotically]
Um... You okay?
Wonderful, yes.
You are very good at that.
Thank you.
No fair! I get to be next!
[YUZURU] Counterattack.
I will not allow it.
[KAGUYA] Oh yeah?
What are you going to do?
[SHIDO] I guess that I'll uh...
[gasping erotically]
[SHIDO] Um...
Are you two all right?
He doesn't know how
good he is at all.
[YUZURU] Tremble.
God-like fingers...
He's such a wolf.
[SHIDO] A wolf? What?
[ELLEN] Arbatel.
The target is now on the move.
Can you follow her?
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
She seems to be heading
to a private beach point-eight
kilometers northwest
of your current location.
[ELLEN] Then I will
head that direction.
Please have the
Bandersnatch follow--
Whoa!
[AI] Haha! Oh my gah,
we so got you, Ellen.
Why would you do that?
Because!
It's never not hilarious!
I can't believe
we got you again!
That's so lame!
I'm sorry.
I don't have time to play
around. I have to go.
Whatever, girl.
And since
you're already there...
I know you
must think its fate
that we've been buried here
together like this,
but I already have
a phone girlfriend.
But, with being all
buried and everything...
I can't exactly bring
her out to show you.
I understand.
It's simply a coincidence
that you guys are out here
all by your lonesome!
You bet!
That's what happened for sure!
Mmm-hmm!
Yes, that's my kinswoman, Tohka!
Hastening right
to her master's side.
Very nicely done!
Good work. Wonder.
I did not think Master Origami
would ever come
to a place like this.
Kinswoman? Master?
[KAGUYA] Yes, she seemed
to have a bright future.
So we performed a baptism
of darkness yesterday
and exchanged bonds.
[YUZURU] Explanation.
I was moved by
Master's coquetry.
I then asked to be her disciple.
[SHIDO] Right. I get it now.
Moving on, what were the
three of you doing together?
[SHIDO] Um... Well, that's
a funny story actually...
[REINE] I thought we could
play a little beach volleyball.
[SHIDO] Reine!
[SHIDO] Why did you
show up like that?
I'm confused.
[REINE] Since Tohka
and Origami are here,
we needed to change the
original plan we had discussed.
Now, you, Kaguya, and Yuzuru
will strengthen your bonds
by playing on the same team
and working together.
Gregor, Jackson, and Spencer
are on this side.
Alexander, Abraham, and Anthony
are on the other court.
[SHIDO]
What's she talking about?
I wonder if this'll work.
I don't think Kaguya and Yuzuru
will do well together.
For that matter, neither
will Tohka and Origami.
[REINE]
Don't worry about that.
Yah!
[REINE] I told them that I
would tell the winning team
an embarrassing
secret about you.
So they have the incentive
to work with each other,
even if they don't want to.
[SHIDO]
Why would you do that?!
[KAGUYA]
What are you doing, Yuzuru?
[YUZURU]
Rebuttal. That's my line.
Don't get in my way, Kaguya.
[KAGUYA] What do you mean?
You were in my territory.
Don't overstep your bounds!
[YUZURU] Rebuttal.
I didn't think dim-witted
Kaguya would make it in time.
[KAGUYA]
What did you say to me?
Hey, calm down, girls.
Calm down.
All they do is fight.
I don't think they're going
to be very difficult to defeat.
I'm disappointed.
They don't know their place
if they think they can beat us
while acting like that.
[KAGUYA]
Well, Yuzuru. Shall we?
[YUZURU]
Agreement. Let's do it.
[KAGUYA] Nice, Shido!
[YUZURU] Kaguya! Set up, now!
[KAGUYA] Understood!
[yelling]
[KAGUYA] All right!
Did you see that?
[YUZURU] Delight. Yahoo!
[KAGUYA] That was perfect
just now, wasn't it, Yuzuru?
It went "whiz"! "Whiz!"
[YUZURU] Affirmative.
That's my Kaguya.
[KAGUYA] No, no,
that's my Yuzuru...
I mean...
Don't get too excited, peon!
You should be grateful that I
allowed my feet to step on you.
Nasty. Now my hands
are extremely smelly.
They stink.
You know what it reminds me of?
The smells of old, dried,
and fermented fish.
[KAGUYA]
My feet don't smell like that!
[REINE]
Shin, are you all right?
[SHIDO] Yeah, I guess so,
but I'm starting to
think this won't work.
[REINE] Honestly... So am I.
Shido?
[SHIDO] Kaguya?
There's, umm...
There's something I
want to talk to you about.
Is that okay?
[SHIDO] Yeah, sure.
Hey, Reine, are you still
telling the girls what to do?
[REINE] No, I didn't
say anything to either one.
I just ...
I wanted to say that, uh...
[SHIDO] Uh... Why are
you talking normal?
Ha! So you were taken
in by my little farce,
were you not?
Do you realize how
ridiculous you looked?
Dancing in the palm
of my hand like a fool?
[KAGUYA] Hey, don't
look at me like that!
I can't help the way I talk!
This is normal for me, you know!
Funny, 'cause you
stopped doing it again.
Ugh! Well, yeah.
Since I am a Spirit,
I'm super amazing.
And I gotta sound
like I can wield
a bunch of power and stuff.
Like how is that
not obvious to you?
[SHIDO] Seriously?
Whatever! It's annoying,
so I'm changing it!
Now tomorrow you have to
choose me or Yuzuru, right?
You know, to decide our battle?
[SHIDO] Oh... yeah?
Shido, I want you to
choose Yuzuru, and not me.
Petition.
Shido, please choose Kaguya
to win this match instead of me.
[SHIDO] But why?
Explanation.
It is because Kaguya
is so much better
than I could
ever hope to be.
Surely, you must realize
how incredibly lovely she is.
[KAGUYA] I mean, Yuzuru's
super cute, right?
She's not like overly
friendly or anything,
but she does mean well.
Her boobs are huge and
she's like a moe character
come to life!
[YUZURU] She likes to act as
though she is extremely strong.
And the truth of the matter
is that she's in earnest.
Even so, she still looks like
one touch will break her,
and I'm sure holding that body
can only be
described as heavenly!
[SHIDO]
But... but then, you'll...
Of course.
I'll disappear.
[SHIDO] I don't understand!
[KAGUYA] Well, come on, it's
not like I want to disappear.
But to me there's
something more important.
I want Yuzuru
to get to live.
Desire.
I want Kaguya to get to live.
I want her to see and
experience more of this world.
You know I'm right.
Kaguya is the Spirit most
suitable to be the true Yamai.
I decided on a battle of charm
because, well, because
no matter how you look at it,
Yuzuru is cuter.
Certainly.
No matter how you look at it,
Kaguya is the cuter one.
I only accepted
the battle of charm
because I knew
she would win over me.
Reminder.
Shido, you have to
choose Kaguya tomorrow.
If you do not...
Then I'll attack
this whole island
and your friends who are on it.
--I'll blow them all away!
[REINE]
Well, that was unexpected.
I sensed no ulterior motive
behind what they said.
This must actually
be how they feel...
[SHIDO] To wish for
her own disappearance
so that the
other one can live...
[SHIDO]
What the hell is going on?
Shido.
I want you to choose Yuzuru,
and not me.
Petition.
Shido, please choose Kaguya
to win this match instead of me.
[TOHKA] Shido. Shido!
[SHIDO]
Tohka...
You finally heard me.
I was calling out
for you this whole time.
Sorry 'bout that.
Hey, Shido.
Do you maybe wanna
go see the ocean at night?
[SHIIZAKI] Analyst Murasame,
please respond.
This is Fraxinus.
Analyst Murasame!
It's no use.
I can't get through.
And I can't get through
to Shido's line, either.
That's strange.
Looking at these readings,
I doubt it's as simple as
a transmission malfunction.
Artificial interference, huh...
Then who could be responsible?
[KANNAZUKI] Hey, guys.
What's going on?
[ALL] Huh?
[ELLEN]
Arbatel, can you see her?
The target is
currently on the move
along the coast
with a male student.
I will now commence the attack.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Roger that.
Also, have a
Bandersnatch on standby
as close to
the hotel as possible.
I'm concerned about
Master Sergeant Tobiichi.
We can't afford for her
to see any suspicious movements.
[TOHKA] Sorry, Shido.
[SHIDO] Huh? What for?
[TOHKA] When I said
I wanted to go for a walk
to see the ocean at night,
it was kind of a little lie.
[TOHKA] Even though we came
on this school trip together...
I don't feel like--like we've
been able to talk that much.
And so I wanted some time alone!
Just the two of us,
if that's okay?
But if you're angry,
I understand.
[TOHKA] Anyway, Shido,
what happened earlier?
[SHIDO] What...
Uh, what do you mean?
[TOHKA] I don't know why,
but I feel like
you've been worried
about something recently.
But, uh, if it's nothing,
then that's great!
Tell me, Tohka.
Did you bring me out here
just because you were worried?
Yeah.
Well, I guess not entirely.
I still wanted some alone time.
You can't blame me for that!
Tohka, can I...
ask for your advice?
Sure!
By all means, ask away!
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
Bandersnatch,
deployment complete.
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 3A]
Captain, we have reports
of a mysterious source
intermittently communicating
with Arubi Island, sir.
We do?
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 3A] I believe
it is trying different patterns
in an attempt to get
around the interference.
[TOHKA] Seriously?
Like Kaguya and Yuzuru do?
That's right.
They both separately told me
they want the other to live.
Even if that means that
they will no longer exist.
It's weird.
As much as they argue,
I never thought they felt
that way about each other.
Well, who would have?
Though I must say
I understand it...
If I were told
that if I didn't die,
you would, then
I'd probably do the same.
Tohka...
Uh... Just forget I said that!
Please continue!
Okay.
So then, now that
I've been told that,
what do you think
I should do about them?
[KAGUYA]
What are you talking about?
[SHIDO] Kaguya!
Yuzuru?
I don't buy that.
It doesn't make any sense.
Hold on. Just calm down!
[YUZURU] Demand... Repeat!
[SHIDO] Yuzuru?
Kaguya...
She told you to choose me?
Is that really what she said?
[TOHKA]
Uh oh. They look mad.
Please, girls.
You have to listen to me!
--What the hell?
[KAGUYA] Raphael, El Re'em!
[YUZURU]
Response. Raphael, El Nahash!
[ORIGAMI]
A Territory has been deployed.
What's going on?
[REINE] Origami Tobiichi?
What are you doing out here?
[ORIGAMI]
Miss Murasame! Run away!
[KANNAZUKI] I see.
It's a little dangerous,
but let's send personnel
to communicate directly.
Bring us to one thousand
meters above ground level.
Deploy the Yggdrafolium.
[ALL] Yes. On it, sir!
[MINOWA]
Approaching target coordinates!
[MIKIMOTO] No reaction
to the Permanent Territory.
Very well.
Now. Ready the Yggdrafolium!
Deploy!
Captain!
The radar's
picking up something!
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2B]
Is it an aircraft?
No, wait a sec!
Sir, it's an airship!
[ARBATEL OPERATOR 2A]
The signal's gone!
[PADDINGTON]
The Ratatoskr Organization...
When you see that ship again,
I want it taken down.
Fire at will!
Yes! This is my lucky day!
Prepare the main artillery!
Have Ashcroft beta devices
ten through twenty
start producing magical power!
Our target is a warship
of unknown affiliation!
So what the hell
was all that about, huh?
A joke?
Why tell him to choose me?
Rebuttal.
What about you?
What is your intention?
It's no use.
I thought this method
would give us the chance
to finally decide
fair and square,
but I guess that I must have
forgotten to add your idiocy
into the equation.
Agreement.
I cannot take any more of your
immense stupidity, either.
Perhaps it was asking
too much to have someone else
end a duel we started ourselves.
After all,
look where we've ended up.
[KAGUYA]
Looks like we're gonna have to
take care of it ourselves
no matter what...
The dueling method is...
Naturally, I already know.
[BOTH] Whoever falls first
is the winner!
[SHIDO]
No, they have to stop...
Please stop!