[NARRATOR]
Feelings... Feeling...
Feeling too much... Still...
[SHIDO grunting]
What the hell is going on?
[SHIDO gasps]
[SHIDO]
Holy crap. Is that Sandalphon?
No way. It can't be.
Where am I? What is this place?
You. Answer me. Where am I?
Oh! I think that, um...
Well, as far as I know,
we're in the Japanese branch
of DEM industries.
[TOHKA] I have never
heard that name before.
Can you also tell me
why I have been brought
to this strange building?
[MIKU]
I can.
You were kidnapped
by that Wizard
standing right over there.
[WESTCOTT]
Wonderful!
This is the first time I've seen
such an excellent Inversion.
Look, Ellen. That is
our dream, our dearest wish.
Now. It's time to work.
Someone who is worthy
for you to defeat
has finally appeared.
My strongest Wizard.
The moment has come
for you to take the head
of the treasonous demon king and
lay the foundation for our path.
Yes. The hour is
at hand. I'm ready.
[laughs] Time to die!
Time to die! Time to die! Die!
[JESSICA]
Oh, Mana! Mana Takamiya!
No, not this time!
I won't lose to you anymore!
As long as I have the Licorice,
I cannot be defeated!
[gasps]
Get ready for Blastark!
[MANA]
How naïve.
[gasps]
[MANA] You've reached
your limit. Jessica.
The match has been decided.
Come quietly.
[JESSICA] Mana! Adeptus Two!
I'm still right here, Mana!
I never liked you;
did you know that?
You poor fool.
One wrong turn, and I
would've been like you.
[JESSICA]
Why?
Why did Master Westcott and
Implementation Manager Mathers
appoint a little girl like you
to such an important post?
Why you?
I was definitely better suited
to be Adeptus Number Two!
I... I don't understand why
they didn't choose me!
Why have you always been
like this toward me, Jessica?
Why're you so unbelievably
hateful and jealous?
You go out of your way
just to be cruel.
[MANA] I still respected
your loyalty even though
I hated you in return.
But that doesn't mean
you deserved this.
No one deserves what's
happening to you. No one.
[JESSICA]
Mana!
[JESSICA grunting]
[MANA gasps]
[JESSICA]
H-H-He... H-Hey. Mana?
I'm strong. I'm strong, right?
I won't lose to
anyone anymore...
Do...
Do you think Mister Westcott
will acknowledge me now?
Oh, I want it to be
my turn this time.
Yeah. I know he'll
acknowledge you.
I-I hope you're right, Mana.
[MANA] Isaac Westcott!
You'll pay for this...
[ELLEN] Fine! Get ready!
Go, Rhongomiant!
[SHIDO, MIKU gasp]
[SHIDO]
No... Tohka, no! Tohka!
[TOHKA] I see. I suppose
you weren't all talk.
[ELLEN]
I won't let you!
[ELLEN gasps]
Nehemoth.
[yelps]
[SHIDO grunting]
[MIKU sings]
Thanks Miku. Are you all right?
I, um-- Yeah. Fine.
But don't think for even a
second that I was trying
to save you or anything
like that, Mister!
Just a coincidence!
[SHIDO gasps]
Is that really... Tohka?
[WESTCOTT] Thank you, Ellen.
That was close.
[ELLEN]
No problem.
We can't exactly have you
getting killed right now.
So, tell me.
What do you think of Princess?
She's grown much
stronger than before.
My opinion is, she's at
least a Triple-A rank.
Really? All right then,
can you still win?
[ELLEN]
I'm not sure.
Nothing that lives on
this Earth can beat me.
If I'm at my very best,
that is. Which I'm not.
I was distracted while
defending us earlier
when my wound opened up.
I've been controlling
my pain threshold.
So I am at a slight disadvantage
when facing that Spirit.
[WESTCOTT]
Hmm. Understood.
It seems we've no choice.
Let us retreat, then.
We still have some time left.
[ELLEN]
Only if you're certain.
[WESTCOTT]
It's fine. I'm used to waiting.
It's good enough
that we were able
to draw out
Princess' Inversion.
On top of that.
We were able see someone
rather unexpected.
My apologies, but you'll
have to excuse us for now.
Let us meet again,
if you survive.
Takamiya. I mean, Shido Itsuka.
[SHIDO] Hey! Hold on a sec!
Do you know who I am?
[WESTCOTT]
Oh, no. I haven't the foggiest.
Not about Shido Itsuka, anyway.
[SHIDO gasps]
Hey!
[TOHKA]
You bastards are next.
Uh, what the hell is going on?
I thought you two jerks
knew each other.
And besides that.
She looks super strong,
so I don't get why you
had to come save her
to begin with.
I am so confused right now.
[SHIDO]
Yeah, well, you're not alone.
I'm not sure what's up, either.
[MIKU]
By the way, I didn't forget
that you got stabbed in the
chest! Why are you still alive?
[SHIDO]
It's, uh... an idiosyncrasy...
[MIKU, SHIDO yelp]
[TOHKA]
This is Sandalphon...
I demand that you to tell me
why you have that angel?
[SHIDO]
Tohka! What happened to you?
Do you not remember who I am?
Tohka? Are you talking to me?
[gasps]
[KOTORI]
Shido! Shido! Please respond!
Kotori?
[NAKATSUGAWA] 3D wide-range
investigation system is back.
[MIKIMOTO] Incoming data from
surface observation equipment!
[SHIIZAKI]
Turning on the image.
[KOTORI] Thanks to the
building being blown away,
the jamming is finally gone.
What in the world
happened in there?
[SHIDO]
I don't know!
I took a sword to the back,
and then Tohka turned crazy town
out of nowhere!
Was it because of the
reverse flow of spirit power?
Can she be sealed?
Doubtful. This is
something very different.
Unfortunately, I can't tell you
if she can be sealed
or not at this point.
Either way, a sealing
would be impossible
with Tohka's feelings
for Shido right now.
[SHIDO]
Then what am I supposed to do?
[KOTORI]
You'll have to make Tohka aware
of who you are again.
If you do that,
then her happiness levels
will go back to normal.
No pressure, bro, but we've
got one shot at this...
Of course we do.
In the end, being myself
is the only thing I can try.
[SHIDO] Come on, Tohka...
Let's go home and eat.
If you say sorry right now, I'll
make all your favorite foods
for breakfast,
lunch, and dinner.
[TOHKA]
You talk too much.
[SHIDO grunts]
[SHIDO groans]
[MIKU]
Gabriel... Rondo!
[SHIDO]
Miku!
You're a gross idiot.
But you still managed to get all
the way here for Tohka's sake,
so I'm giving you just one
chance to make this right...
Get ready, Shido.
All right. Now it's go time
[sings]
How irritating.
[singing continues]
[silence]
[SHIDO gasps]
My... You are an insolent one.
[SHIDO grunts]
How dare you try
to bind my body?
Know your limits.
[MIKU] I never had
anything but my songs.
My music. I had nothing.
I always believed if
I didn't have my voice,
I was worthless.
That nobody -- and no thing
-- would protect me anymore.
But honestly. I wanted
to see it at least once.
I wanted to see a person who
truly loved another person
from the bottom of
their heart. If only...
If only I had met you sooner.
Things would've
been so different.
[SHIDO]
Miku!
[gasps] What was that?
[YOSHINON]
How strange.
Hey, Yoshino, you don't
by chance remember
why we're here, do you?
[YOSHINO]
You don't know either?
[YOSHINON] Somehow,
I feel kind of strange...
Like my power is slowly
being sucked away...
Attack!
[KAGUYA laughs]
That was nothing!
Did you see how we just
blew those girls away?
Question. Is this
a serious fight?
Yoshino? Yoshinon?
[YOSHINO]
Kaguya! Yuzuru!
Hey, so do you maybe
know where we are?
[ORIGAMI yells]
[yelps]
Um, Master Origami.
What's going on?
It's... Shido...
[SHIDO]
Yo, Miku. You okay?
[MIKU]
But, why? I don't understand...
I always keep my promises.
[gasps] Yeah well, so what?
It doesn't make
any sense at all...
Are you trying to tell me
that if I ended up
in the same bind as Tohka,
you would try to save me, too?
[SHIDO]
You bet I would!
[MIKU gasping]
He kept his promise. He kept it.
This man... Shido Itsuka...
kept his promise!
[MIKU]
Shido...
[TOHKA]
Sh-Shido!
Ugh... Shido? Shido...
[MIKU] Could she be
coming back to her senses?
[TOHKA grunts]
[gasps]
What is this feeling...?
Are you trying to
trick me, human?
Are you? Very well... My turn!
I shall crush you!
Nothing will remain
but dust, and memory.
This is bad.
[TOHKA]
Now, face my Paverschlev!
Also known as the
sword of demise.
[SHIDO, MIKU gasp]
[sings]
Huh? Miku? Go, please!
You have to run away!
[MIKU] I don't want you
to break your promise.
Save Tohka! I know you can!
Now, die. Wretch.
Tohka!
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
You little impudent fool.
[MIKU gasps]
What, I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna go
save the princess.
Keeping my promise.
[MIKU whimpers]
[YOSHINON grunts]
What amazing power!
Please, Tohka, stop!
You have to wake up!
[TOHKA grunts]
[SHIDO]
Tohka!
Huh?
[gasps]
Now, Nehemoth! Paverschlev!
It's time to die!
[grunts]
[TOHKA laughs]
[TOHKA]
He's gone! He's finally gone!
I'm forever free of that
human and his trickery!
[KAGUYA] And what precisely
are you laughing at, servant?
Isn't it a little early
to be celebrating
your so-called triumph?
[YUZURU] Protection. Our
foresight is quite admirable,
if I do say so myself.
No joke. Thanks,
you two are awesome.
[KAGUYA laughs]
Don't worry about it, Shido.
It's not like
it was hard for us.
Agreement. I am glad
you're safe. However...
[SHIDO]
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
But how? How are
you still alive?
[gasps]
[SHIDO]
Tohka!
Who's... Tohka?
[SHIDO] Hey there, Tohka!
I'm here to save you!
[gasps]
Huh? Oh...
[TOHKA]
Uh? Disarming yourself? But why?
Because I don't need
a sword to do this.
Huh?
[TOHKA]
I don't understand.
What in the world
is this man doing?
He's kissing the enemy...
...on the battlefield!
Why? This doesn't make sense.
My head is spinning...
Shido!
It feels... like my body...
...isn't my own anymore.
Shido...
Every time I hear
that name, I feel weak...
Shido!
But. It doesn't
put me in a bad mood.
[TOHKA] Oh! How could
I have forgotten him?
The one who gave me my name.
Shido.
Who turned my
existence upside down.
Shido...
[SHIDO]
Yeah. That's me.
I'm so sorry.
[SHIDO grunts]
Shido, are you okay?
Somehow yeah, I guess I am!
What about you;
are you feeling okay?
What in the world was that?
"That"? What are you
talking about?
Nothin'. Forget it.
It's probably best
if I leave that
to Reine and
Kotori, anyway.
In the meantime...
Welcome back, Tohka.
[giggles] I'm back, Shido!
Thank you so much!
[ALL sigh]
[NEWSCASTER 10A] The
large-scale uprising involving
many citizens in
Tengu City that was created
with some as of yet unknown
hallucinogen is nearly resolved.
In spite of its scale, there
were miraculously no casualties,
and those involved are report--
I'll keep looking.
It seems as though this isn't
the right place, either.
Good gracious.
Where oh where could
the captive spirit be?
[MIKU]
Oh, yay, you came! Darling!
Whoa. Who's Darling?
Did you knock a screw loose?
What's going on, Miku?
I thought you hated men!
[MIKU giggles] Well, you're
not all men, Darling.
After all, I do kinda
owe you my life.
Yeah. Is that why you
sent me this random letter?
It says you wanna talk about
something alone, so what is it?
Wow. You work fast!
[SHIDO]
Huh?
[gasps] What?
How did you do that?
Darling, I didn't know
you were so perverted.
No. That's not it! This is...
I'm just teasing you.
I asked the other girls,
and they told me
everything, so I knew.
Oh. You mean about
sealing your powers?
[giggles] Yeah.
You haven't forgotten what
you promised me have you?
You said to me that you
would still listen to me sing
if I lost the voice
my powers gave me.
And even if everyone
else chose to ignore me.
Yeah. I remember.
You're good.
You keep the promises
that you make.
You're the only one
who's okay with me.
You're the only one that,
that I can really trust.
So even if I've lost
the voice that I had.
And even if no one
bothers to listen to me
or my songs anymore.
As long as you're there,
that will be enough...
And if that happens, well...
Then I'll sing just for
you as long as you want.
Miku...
--Shido!
--[SHIDO gasps]
So this is where you've been!
It's getting crazy out there.
I don't know if they're
shouting anko or encore.
I was sent to get Miku...
Oh, hey, Tohka, what's up?
I don't know. Why don't
you try telling me?
Quickly!
Whoa! Calm down.
There's a reason for this!
Hey. Darling...
[SHIDO]
Yeah?
"Dar-wha?"
Will you please watch my encore?
Sure.
[TOHKA]
Hm?
[CROWD cheers]
Thank you all so much!
Tonight, I'm going to sing a
very special and important song,
so I hope you like it!
[SHIDO] Well, girls...
It looks like she's back.
♪ Singing in the shower, ♪
♪ me believing I
am on a stage, ♪
♪ hearing my voice
resound in the room. ♪
♪ La-la-la, la-la-la,
I sing on. ♪
♪ Reverbres bouncing
off each wall around me. ♪
♪ Every echo sounds so
special and so astounding. ♪
♪ Even though I am
happy I hope that I ♪
♪ won't forget how I
felt once before. ♪
♪ Let me sing you a song ♪
♪ and let's sing along. ♪
♪ The greatest gift of all are
all the stars up in the sky. ♪
♪ Millions sparkle above ♪
♪ and light the night. ♪
[applause]
Thank you so much!
Everyone out there, thank you!
Thank you, Darling!
Thank you so much!
I love you!
[CROWD gasps]
[SHIDO gasps]
What's "Darling"?
Yes, please. Answer.
Darling?
[YOSHINON]
Wait, don't tell me that...
Speaking of which, Miku called
you that earlier, didn't she?
Shido. We'd like to know
what "darling" means.
Well, that's, uh...
Shido.
Confirmation. Shido.
Um, Shido.
[YOSHINON]
Oh no, Shido.
What does it mean?
[SHIDO]
Uh...
[KOTORI giggles]
You're so popular, Shido.