[footsteps]
[MEI]
Check it out!
Crazy big news, you guys!
Are you ready? I managed to get
into the Cartado Festival
for the first time!
[ALL]
Huh?
Once a year, the Tarkas,
who are the only manufacturers
of Cartado in the world,
host a super-cool
Cartado Festival!
It's a private event so
not just anyone can show up,
so it's become a
big secret thing
that most people
only read about!
And now, finally, I have
been officially invited!
[DODO]
Muh!
So, um, who's your new friend?
[MEI] Oh! This is Dodo,
the Tarka I met
and ended up bonding with at one
of my favorite Cartado shops!
We got to talking, and now
he's letting me participate!
Muh!
[ALL]
He's so cute!
[FAI]
Here, have a seat!
[SEIRA]
Would you like a snack?
[YUSHA]
Please enjoy some tea!
[GIRLS]
How adorable!
Muh!
--Nice to meet you! I'm Seira.
--[MEI] So, um.
Anyway. About the festival...
Wow, guys.
I'm really glad you were
able to hit it off so fast.
Freakin' extroverts. Took me
literally months to do that.
[DODO]
Muh, muh!
Muh, muh, muh.
He says,
"The path to the village...
is through here."
So, I guess we'll assume this
cave leads to the festival.
Farewell, then. 'Fraid this
is as far as you girls can go.
[GIRLS]
What?!
Look, don't "what?" me!
There are tons of evil merchants
out there who would love to know
how to get to the Tarka Village,
the birthplace of Cartado!
It's not a place
outsiders just waltz into.
It was practically a miracle
that I received permission
from Dodo at all!
So I've got to go on my own!
I cannot do anything
to mess up this chance!
Muh, muh, muh.
He said that we can come, too!
That's fixed!
Not cool. Don't say that just
'cause you want to come!
"You all come. Village.
Come. Welcome."
'Kay, you're right...
How'd you understand him?!
Not really sure.
Wild instincts, maybe?
So you're saying we can come
to the village with you now?
Hooray!
Muh. Muh.
Yes! [laughs]
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
You guys have zero idea
how lucky you are.
Is it just me, or is
this a dead end?
[YUSHA]
Wow, how'd you do that?
[SEIRA]
Huh? Where'd it come from?
Muh, muh.
It sounds like he's
telling us to jump down.
[MEI]
Mm... Yeah, she's right.
Huh?! No way!
I am not doing that!
--Muh! Muh!
--[GIRLS gasp]
He really did it!
Well, all right, then--
here I go!
Wait for me!
[MEI] This is for
the Cartado Festival!
[whines]
Fine!
[SEIRA cries]
Jeez! How were you guys able
to jump without hesitation?
I mean, what, am I
high-maintenance?
[MEI] Yusha and Fai are
both totally fearless.
Not just them, you're
not panicking, either!
Well, I'm actually panicking
quite a bit.
Okay, I don't see that at all.
I'm the type to drown in a
river without anyone noticing.
Well aren't you just a
little ray of sunshine!
Uh? What now?
If I had to guess, I'd say
it's some kinda gate
that will eventually
lead us to the village.
Maybe we'll be there as
soon as we pass through!
[FAI]
Yahoo! We're here, village!
[YUSHA]
Heh!
[DODO]
Huh!
[YUSHA]
Ah!
[SEIRA cries]
[crash]
[YUSHA, MEI groan]
Couldn't it have set us
down a little bit more gently?
Muh. Muh!
There they are.
Those are some
weird-looking trees.
It kinda seems like they
grow paper instead of fruit.
[MEI]
They do!
Those are the Cartado trees I've
dreamed of seeing all my life!
And now they're right
in front of me!
It's almost too good to be true!
[SEIRA, FAI, YUSHA]
What?!
I had no idea that
Cartado grew on trees.
You know, I'm not sure
where I got this from,
but I always kinda had this
idea that a powerful mage
used some kind of special magic
circle to concentrate his power
and imbue the spells
into the cards.
Yeah, that's exactly
what I thought, too!
No! That's a big part of what
makes Cartado so unique!
They aren't manufactured
items created by mankind.
They're a product of nature,
grown from the soil itself!
[YUSHA] Wow. There are
all different kinds
of Cartado growing
from a single tree!
That's another part
of their mystery.
From everything I've come
across in my research,
the strongest theory
seems to be that the land
in this region is what produces
Cartado, not the trees.
Wow, to think,
I had no idea! Huh?
Hey, are those Tarka children?
[YUSHA]
Oh my gosh!
Would you just look at
their cute little outfits?
Muuh, muh.
Muuuh. Muuh, muh.
[MEI] Mm... Do you
understand what he said?
Uh-huh! He said their
clothes are special.
They're wearing them because
of the festival today!
Yeah, makes sense.
Look at you!
Taking her word for it.
Well, when logically
speaking it's easier
having an interpreter
than it is to use a book.
Muh!
Muh.
[MEI screams]
Hey!
[TARKA CHILDREN]
Muh?
[MEI]
What's wrong with you?!
Those are precious and should be
treated with the utmost care,
so you leave 'em alone!
Sacrilege!
Muh-muh. Muh-muh.
He said it's not a big deal,
since they grow every year.
Muh-muh, muh.
He also said that we can
have some, too. If we want.
Huh?! Are you serious right now?
In that case, I'll take one of
these, and one of these,
and that one! This is amazing!
Calm down, would ya?
It's gonna be okay!
Careful or you're gonna
break your staff, Mei!
[MEI]
Sorry, girls.
I think I might've kinda lost
myself for a minute there.
[TARKA VILLAGERS chattering]
Ah! So, this is Tarka Village!
I can't believe I'm
actually setting foot
in the forbidden place
no outsiders ever see!
Everyone, best behavior!
Don't be rude to the villagers!
Muuuh! Muh, muh!
Muuh, muuh!
It feels like they're
welcoming us!
They're amazingly friendly,
aren't they?
Muuuh, muh, muh, muh.
Muh-muh.
He said everyone's
really excited
'cause they so rarely
get any visitors.
They seem really nice.
Even more of a reason
to make sure others
don't find out about them!
We'll keep the path a secret!
No one will know.
Although, it would be fun
to brag about this a little bit.
Be careful. Keep that
fanaticism in check.
You're right, I have to!
My lips are sealed!
[DODO]
Muuuh, muh.
Muh, muh, muh.
[FAI] He said, "let's get you
changed into festival attire!"
Aww! We all get to
wear that, too?
I can't wait to
put that on!
Huh?
Uh-oh, it doesn't want
to go up any higher.
[FAI grunting]
Aw, man, it's catching
at my chest!
[YUSHA]
Oh, crap.
[grunting]
Ah, yes! Got it on!
A-Ah!
Wow, great.
[DODO]
Muuh, muh, muh.
[FAI] He says they do
have some larger ones!
[YUSHA]
I love it! It's so cute!
[FAI]
This is perfect!
And easy to move in!
[MEI]
I hate to admit this,
but I was worried there
for a minute.
[SEIRA]
I don't get it.
Why'd they need bigger ones?
The first one fit me fine.
[TARKA VILLAGERS chattering]
[DODO]
Muh, muuh, muuh, muh, muh.
[FAI] He says this is the main
area for the festival.
Muh-muh, muh!
And that it's about
to start right now!
[YUSHA, SEIRA]
Yeah!
The moment is finally here!
I can't believe I'm present for
this incredible, legendary event
that Cartado fans worldwide
would drool over:
The Cartado Festival!
The only harvest
festival in existence
that celebrates and honors
a crop of Cartado!
[TARKA VILLAGER 9C]
Muuuh, muuh, muuuh.
[TARKA VILLAGERS cheer]
He says they're gonna sing
the Cartado Festival song now.
--Huh?
--[YUSHA, SEIRA] A song?
[TARKA VILLAGERS singing]
[DODO]
Muuh, muuh!
He said, "sing along!"
Huh? But how? We don't
even know the words.
I guess it doesn't
really matter!
We can sing along anyways!
Yeah, why not?
Yay! I'm so ready
to sing something!
[GIRLS singing]
Muuuh, muh-muh,
muh-muh, muh.
Muuhh-muh, muh.
He just said, "now's
the time we compete
to determine who will be
this year's Cartado King."
There's a King of Cartado?
I've definitely read
about this before.
It's the main event
of the entire festival.
Every year, they compete to
collect Cartado from the wild
Cartado trees growing
around the village.
As opposed to the
cultivated ones, I mean.
And then, whoever manages to
harvest the most interesting
specimens becomes
that year's Cartado King!
Basically, the star of
the whole festival!
Stop it! That sounds
like so much fun!
You do like that sort
of thing, don't you?
Muh, muh, muh, muh!
He wants us to know
anyone can participate!
All right! Let's do it!
I'm so psyched!
Muuh, muh, muh.
"Ready," he says.
[TARKA VILLAGER 9C]
Muh!
[TARKA VILLAGERS chatter]
And "start," he says!
Yeah, Fai, we got it!
Girls, it's time
to get this done!
All right, let's be King!
Heck, yeah! Woo!
[MEI]
Here we go!
[DODO, MEI]
Muh, muh, muh!
Muh-muh!
[TARKA VILLAGERS chattering]
There's one!
[DODO]
Muh, muh! Muh, muh, muh.
Huh?
You can't become King using
the Cartado around here.
I guess they've got
to be rarer, he says.
Right. That makes sense
according to my research.
The more rare it is,
the more difficult to harvest.
And even in the wild,
they tend to only grow on trees
in hard-to-reach places.
[SEIRA] I guess you can learn
a lot from reading, huh?
[MEI] Yep! Generations of
Cartado fans have continued
their unyielding pursuit to
record every detail about them.
[DODO]
Muuh, muh!
[FAI]
He says, "this way!"
[SEIRA] Are you saying
we have to climb this?
Muuh!
Welp! That's a "yes"!
Shocking.
[GROUP grunting]
Man! This challenge
is my jam! Yahoo!
That looks like so much fun!
[BOTH grunting]
Those two sure have some
crazy energy, don't they?
It's impressive... Mei?
Seira. I almost don't know
what to do with myself because
my heart's dancing so hard
that I really may not survive
to experience harvesting
the rare Cartado!
I mean, if I manage to
become Cartado King
at this legendary festival,
then I'll have major
bragging rights with other
fans for the rest of my life!
If you say so.
But, uh, where's this tree
supposed to be, anyway?
Oh! There it is!
[MEI] Not that!
Don't bother, it's not rare.
[SEIRA] Huh? You can tell
that from this far away?
[MEI]
Yeah, of course!
I can tell rares from commons
even when they're so far away
they're nothing
but little specks!
For your information,
that one's Toad Voice.
So you can ID the card, too?
What kind of spell
is "Toad Voice"?
[MEI] It just makes your voice
sound like a frog.
That sounds very... handy...
[YUSHA]
Hey! I found one!
[MEI, SEIRA gasp]
[YUSHA]
Mei. Is it rare?
[MEI]
Mmm...
[gasps] Yes! That one's
a legendary rare!
Huh? Really?
Right! Here I come!
[BOTH gasp]
Just leave it to me!
[FAI]
I got it!
[screaming]
[ALL]
Oh my gosh!
Okay, that was close.
[BOTH sigh]
[TARKA VILLAGER 9E]
Mu-Muuuh.
Huh?!
He's taking it!
Well, that sucks.
Not on my watch! Dodo! Come on!
[DODO chirps]
[FAI yells]
[DODO grunts]
[GIRLS]
Huh?
--[TARKA VILLAGER 9F] Muh!
--[DODO] Muh!
[SEIRA gasps]
[MEI gasps]
[YUSHA gasps]
[FAI gasping]
[TARKA VILLAGER 9F]
Muuh. Muh-muh.
[SEIRA] Oh, wow. I guess that
makes him Cartado King?
Do you think so?
I mean, that's a legendary rare.
It's not like you're going to
find two or three of those.
But it doesn't look to me
like Mei has given up yet.
[MEI]
That's a common.
That's a common, too.
And that's an ordinary rare.
Mei, are you just looking
for legendary rares?
Hey! Maybe we could
find a mythic rare
kinda like the one Rona has!
Impossible. There are only a
few mythic rares in the world.
The ones that exist are said
to be gifts straight from God,
and then passed down
for generations
since ages and ages ago.
There's no written record of
any of them growing on trees
like the others do.
But there's still a chance
that we might find
another legendary rare.
And besides, even if I
don't become Cartado King,
I still got to participate
in the Cartado Festival
of my dreams!
I'll keep going till time's up.
I wanna enjoy this
thing I love so much
as long as I possibly can!
That was beautiful.
It was.
Mei, if that's what you wanna
do, then I'm gonna help you!
Yeah, same! Mei is never
like this! So passionate!
Whaddya need us to do?
You name it!
Muuh, muuh!
He'll help too! Cool, huh?
Oh, you're all the best,
thank you so much!
[MEI]
Uh... Uh... Uh.
Guys, it's time to
call it quits.
Muuh?
You're really giving up?
We're searching for something
we're not that likely to find,
anyway, and the sun's about to
set, so we're close to the end.
Thank you all so much for
coming along with me though.
It made it even more fun. So...
Wait what is that?
You okay?
[FAI]
Hey! It's a Cartado!
Yes, it is.
It must have gotten buried
in a landslide or something.
Wonder what type it is.
Uh. Wait, it's so big!
Huh?! What the...?
It's a huge Cartado!
Muuuh!
I wonder if it's a mutation.
How are you this
calm right now?
That's an incredibly rare
Cartado in your hands!
You might even become the
Cartado King with this one!
[MEI] Mm... I mean, yeah--
it is rare, all right.
But at the end of the day,
it's still really just
a one-star common.
Still, though!
We should at least try entering
with it, since you found it!
It's sure to stand out!
[MEI]
Mm... Yeah, I guess.
Muuuh, muh, muh.
Muh, muuuh. Muh!
[TARKA VILLAGERS cheer]
Fai? What is this?
Muh, muh. Muh-Muh.
Muh-muh-muh, muh!
He says he sees legendary
rares crop up every few years,
but he's never seen a
Cartado this big before!
It's so cool! You won!
We did it, guys!
Oh my gosh! Mei,
you're the Cartado King!
Is this...
Is this really happening?!
I'm the Cartado King?
[TARKA VILLAGERS cheer]
[YUSHA] Do you get some kind
of bonus for becoming King?
Muuh, muuh!
He says, "no, this is it."
Huh? That's why we
worked so hard?
I thought she'd get a prize.
[FAI] Well, who cares? Look!
Mei couldn't be happier.
[YUSHA]
Yeah, you're right!
[SEIRA]
Sure. I guess.
[TARKA VILLAGERS chatter]
[DODO] Muh, muh.
Muh-muh-muh-muh-muh.
He says it's about time
for the festival's finale.
Are those all Cartado?
That's right, they're the
ones everyone picked out
in the wild earlier today.
They arrange them in a pile
like this in order to offer
them up to the gods.
That makes sense. It's
technically a harvest festival.
I'm so excited to see
what the finale is!
Huh?!
They lit them on fire?
Wha-- What's going on, Dodo?
Muh-muh, muh. Muh, muh.
Muh-muh, muuh.
[FAI] Uh, he says the reason
they do this is to offer
the Cartado everyone's gathered
to the heavens as kind of
a prayer for a good harvest
in the coming year.
Huh? Even the legendary
rare Cartado?
That's a terrible waste!
That means Mei's jumbo
Cartado is gonna burn!
[FAI] Can't we take
that one back, at least?
[MEI grunts]
No way!
[GIRLS]
Uh?
As one of the true fans,
I have respect for the Cartado.
Therefore, I respect
the festival,
as well as Tarka Village,
where everything is produced!
If this is part of their
culture, then we have no right
to come in and try
to change them!
Of course.
Mm! You're right!
And that's our smart Mei!
[music plays]
[GIRLS singing]
[singing continues]
[MEI] Ah, it's so beautiful,
and I'm so thankful.
I still can't believe I'm here!
The world of Cartado is
deep and full of wonder.
[MEI]
But still, let's be real.
That fire's such a waste.
[SEIRA]
"Snowy Mountain Dream!"