Oh, wow.
I don't think I'll ever
get enough of reading
the old Hero legends!
Learning about
the great achievements
of past champions
is just the best,
but I also love the
stories about all their
different companions!
Their talents and skills
only make each of the
Heroes that much better!
Now that I think of it,
I really don't know anything
about the companions
of our current Hero,
the 999th one of her kind.
This is terrible. If I
profess to love our Hero,
then I must make an effort
to know her companions!
[ALL]
A... choo!
That was crazy! You all
sneezed at the same time!
[SEIRA] I wonder if
someone's talking about us.
Yeah, that sounds
highly unlikely.
The only person who knows
all three of us is... Yusha!
Was it me? I do think of
you guys kind of a lot!
So your brain was
running its mouth.
Got it.
So, what were you
saying about us?
Gimme a sec.
I bet I can try to remember.
Wow, Yusha, it was
literally 30 seconds ago.
[YUSHA] But, I mean, so much
has happened since then!
[FAI, MEI laughing]
Uhh...
So, anyway. If it's agreeable
to you, I would very much
like to further my acquaintance
with your companions.
Possibly starting with Eleanor?
If you would be so inclined.
Uh, sure.
What does "further my
acquaintance" mean?
I think she just wants
to become better friends.
Oh, cool, we'll get
to hang out, then!
[bell tolls]
[SEIRA]
Mm...
[RONA laughs]
Sorry to ask again,
but remind me
what our next class is gonna be?
We've got Basic Magic Studies.
Ah, that's right!
[MEI grumbles]
Mei, that's the wrong one!
You want the blue book, instead,
that's the textbook
on magic history.
Oh, crap, I forgot my
friggin' textbook!
Don't worry, I brought a spare,
you can borrow this one.
You're pretty amazing, Seira.
I mean, who carries spare
textbooks around?
Me, because there's
always at least one of you
who forgets yours.
[GIRLS laugh sheepishly]
And because of that, I own
two full sets of textbooks.
How impressive!
That's so like you,
Ellenoar of the Hero's party!
And you know what? The Priest
of the 18th Hero's party
was a fastidious maker
of plans, as well!
You two have a lot in common!
Isn't that wonderful?
Uh, that's interesting,
thank you.
Hey, Seira, Here, you can
totally have my peppers!
You can have my carrots,
too, if you want.
Are you gonna eat that
fried chicken, Seira?
Okay, okay. But you guys
should still eat one, each.
And Fai, please chew.
[GIRLS]
Okay!
[RONA]
Impressive, again, Ellenoar!
It's so like the Priest of
the 132nd Hero's party.
He showed great concern for his
companions' health, as well.
It's just wonderful!
Oh, kinda random
but thank you.
[SEIRA sighs]
Today was beyond exhausting.
[SEIRA]
Uh? Uh!
Be careful, Princess!
What the heck are you
doing out there, anyway?
You have things strewn
everywhere around your room.
Oh, yeah, that, well, I've just
been so busy, you know?
Between practicals, homework,
and the Hero's Festival, it's
like there haven't been enough
hours in the day to clean!
You continually impress me!
The Priest of the 571st Hero's
party was just the same way.
He had, shall we say, quite a
unique sense of aesthetics!
Just wonderful!
Uh?
[RONA]
Hi there, Mather! I'd like to
spend today furthering my
acquaintance with you!
Yeah, that's fine, but
understand that my errands
might not be very interesting
to the uninitiated.
--[RONA] Huh?
--There's the first one.
[RONA] Ohh... Oh my, so,
this is a Cartado shop?
Who knew there were
so many different kinds?
Yeah, it's true, this one has
a pretty large selection,
but there aren't any
treasures here.
It's geared towards
the casual customer.
Hello.
How are ya, Mei? Welcome.
[MEI] Have you gotten
anything good in?
We have a few new
rares in stock,
but nothing I think you'd
find very exciting.
[MEI]
No problem.
[bells jingle]
Wow, you're leaving already?
I was only dropping by to
check on their latest shipment.
I don't really have the time
to waste browsing around.
Why is that? Do you have
other big plans after this?
[MEI] I'm going on my usual
rounds to all the Cartado shops.
So, don't feel like you
need to come, since--
I'd expect nothing less from
a member of the Hero's party!
[MEI]
Huh?
[RONA] The Mage of
the 36th Hero's party
was also said to be a scholar,
and he was known
for constantly researching
Cartado, just like you!
Isn't that wonderful?
[door slams]
'kay, let's go.
[door clicks, bells jingle]
This seems a bit different from
the shops we've visited so far.
This is like, the promised land.
It's a hardcore shop
that draws true aficionados
and sells the rarest
Cartado in town.
[RONA gasping]
[door creaks]
[PATRONS chattering]
My, this is interesting.
It's got fascinating clientele.
Yes, because it's where
the strong gather.
[RONA]
Huh?
[MEI]
Battle me.
Very well, then.
Battle? No, you can't battle
in a place like this!
And not with an
elderly gentleman!
You don't have to worry.
It just means we're showing
off our rare Cartado.
Ready, set.
Behold, this beauty,
the rare Mega Blizzard!
And it's a five-star
class Cartado.
[PATRON 7A]
You might wanna take a good look
at mine before you crow!
[MEI]
Huh?! Whoa! Are you kidding me?
That's the legendary
rare Dragon Breath"
[laughs] After last time when
I lost to your "Imperial Feast,"
I decided it was time to
bring out the big guns
and show you this baby!
I'd say I win this round, eh?
[RONA]
Ohh...
If it helps at all, I have
one of those, as well.
[MEI, PATRON 7A]
Huh?!
Are you being serious,
Princess?
[RONA]
Sure!
[PATRONS gasping]
Come to think of it, you do have
a mythically rare Cartado,
--don't you?
--Yeah!
[PATRONS]
Mythically?
...so they really do exist!
Well, I guess so, I received
that one from my father,
but here are the ones I was
given for self-defense.
I actually have plenty more
that I left in my room
since I couldn't carry them all.
Princess, can I please come
visit your place sometime?
Yes, of course!
Oh my goodness.
How could I not have
thought of this before?
Huh?
[RONA] If you please,
I'd like to purchase
all of the rare Cartado
in this store.
Mather, these are yours now,
to do with as you will.
This isn't real.
[RONA] Well, you are the Mage of
the Hero's party, aren't you?
Seems to me, you should
have lots of good Cartado
at your disposal! Go ahead!
[MEI squeaking]
[PATRON 7A]
Hold it!
If you accept that pile of
cards, then you're finished
as a legit Cartado collector!
That stack is a thing of beauty
and something Cartado collectors
everywhere would
weep and drool over
and wish for all of their lives,
but if you accept this now,
you'll be spitting in the face
of the years of effort that
it takes every true collector
to gather them!
So, go ahead!
Can you live with yourself?
Knowing the truth?
[MEI screams]
Sir, you've opened my eyes!
I was so very wrong!
Well, so long
as you understand.
For the serious collector,
there are no shortcuts!
Understood!
[RONA]
I'm so impressed, Mather!
The Mage of the 888th Hero's
party turned down something,
too. It was the esteemed
position of Head Royal Mage.
He wanted to join
the Hero's party instead!
That firm resolve,
it's so wonderful!
Oh, um, thanks for that.
Your acquaintance with me?
Yes! It's your turn, Fai!
I've already gotten
to know Ellenoar
and Mather much better,
I think, so, here I am!
[FAI]
Uh, it's just...
I'm heading out on a
little trip tomorrow.
Could it wait until I get back?
A trip? How wonderful!
And it bears resemblance to
the Warrior of the 337th.
He used to go on short trips
with his companions
to deepen their bonds.
Will you allow me
to accompany you?
Well I guess we could go
on the trip together!
[gasps] Yay!
[BOTH]
Heh. ENDRO!
[FAI]
See, I grew up in the woods.
So I go on trips like
this to reconnect
with my inner wild child!
Fascinating!
It actually brings to mind
the Warrior of the 674th.
He was also said to
treasure his homeland.
You're so delightful!
But wait, where is all your
luggage for the journey, Fai?
Oh, I never like to
mess with luggage!
Huh?!
[FAI] The point's to get in
touch with my feral side!
Feral... Okay...
[FAI]
C'mon, let's go!
[gasps]
[RONA gasps]
[FAI] Yahoo! Wouldja
look at that view?
Yep, yep, yep, yep, I see.
You're just like the Warrior
of the 70th Hero's party.
He loved high places,
so he could look down upon
on his enemies.
How... How wonderful!
--Here!
--Huh?
[FAI bellows]
[RONA screams]
[FAI grunts]
[RONA groans] So much fun,
the Warrior of the 92nd party
would also weave vines.
Ones just like these.
[FAI]
Here, this is next!
Huh?
[FAI]
Yahoo!
[screaming] Hey, Fai,
that's a river!
I know! Here we go!
Huh?
[FAI]
Yahoo!
[RONA screams]
[RONA] I'm afraid. I'm not
a very good swimmer!
Help, I think I'm gonna drown!
Nah, just hold onto me!
[sighs]
It's pretty fun to be out
in the wild, isn't it?
Yes. It's the best.
I keep thinking about
the Warrior of the 927th
Hero's party, he was said to
fight while riding dolphins.
It's so impressive,
Fai! And wonderful!
So, on that note,
I do believe it's about time
for me to be heading back.
We've only just started
our journey, though!
Maybe so, but we have
furthered our acquaintance!
I feel like I know
you very well, Fai!
Oh, yeah? Okay,
then, see ya later!
[birds chirping]
[animal growls]
[RONA]
Now that I'm by myself
I don't think I know the way
home! And I specifically
told my knights not to follow
me, so I'm truly alone.
And I'd have to repeat such
acrobatics to travel back
the way I came, only to then
drown when I reached the river!
[RONA gasps]
Wh-Wha--
[RONA screams]
[FAI]
Uh? Oh, hey.
Didja forget something?
[RONA] No, I can't make
it home on my own!
I know it's an inconvenience,
but could you please escort me
back to the entrance
of the jungle?
Sure! No prob!
Thank you so much, new friend!
[FAI] But I have stuff
to do tomorrow,
so it'll have to be after that.
Huh?
If you wait for me right here,
I'll come back and take you!
[RONA]
I... I can't do that!
I'll go with you!
Please, let me go with you!
[FAI]
Sure, suit yourself!
[RONA screaming]
[RONA gasping]
[FAI]
Uhh...
[panting]
It's starting to get dark out.
We should probably call it a day
and try to get some sleep.
Oh. I really am
grateful to hear that,
but are we
sleeping right here?
[FAI]
No, if we sleep down here
we'll definitely be attacked
by wild animals.
Huh? Then, what on earth
are we going to do?
[FAI]
We'll be sleeping up there!
Huh?
[FAI sighs]
[RONA] Ahh... This really is
a lot more comfortable
than I thought it would be.
It is, isn't it?
After a little while, I started
calling them sleeping bag buds.
I just climb in here and start
feeling sleepy right away.
What impressive
survival knowledge!
I can't believe I'm
friends with Fai,
companion of my dearest Hero!
Hey, Princess, tell me
something, do you love Yusha?
Huh?! How were you
able to figure that out?
Well, it helped
that you just said
she was your "dearest Hero."
So you know my secret feelings!
What am I gonna do, now?
I mean, she's just such a
wonderful person, isn't she?
So, it's only natural for
me to admire her, right?
She's gallant and strong, and so
reliable, and occasionally wild.
And yet, she's still
kind enough to escort me.
She's so wonderful!
Huh? Who're we talking about?
What do you mean, "who?"
Why, the Hero, of course!
You sure say some
strange things.
Her ambition's higher
than the mountains!
Her kindness as
vast as the sky!
And then, as for her-- Huh?
She literally fell asleep.
I was just getting to
the good stuff, too.
We made it! Woo!
[FEMALE VILLAGER 7A]
Welcome to Andas Village!
Those participating in the Andas
Melon Eating Competition,
please sign up right
over here real quick.
[FAI]
There it is!
I came here just to
compete in that!
Oh, I see!
So, this was your destination
for your trip into the wild.
I happened to come
through here last year
when I was making another trip.
I won first place and earned a
year's supply of Andas melons!
So, I thought I'd come
back again this year!
I love 'em!
When you bite into them?
Red bean paste comes out!
Oh my, is that so?
I'm gonna win 'em again!
Sign me up!  I'm here, guys!
Oh, hey! Wondered if you'd
be back this year.
[FAI]
I am! Back for my second win!
You must really love some
Andas melons, don't you?
Oh, right.
Do you know about the change?
What do you mean?
[MALE VILLAGER 7A] Well,
they've decided to try something
different this year. Everyone's
competing in pairs.
No! Really?
Uh. Hey, Princess, come here
and pair up with me!
Huh?!
Welcome, everyone,
to the preliminary
round of the Melon-Eating
Competition!
If you can finish eating ten
entire melons in ten minutes,
you win the preliminary round!
Ten in ten minutes?
I've got this, Princess.
You don't need to force
anything down for me!
[MACHO BROTHER 7A]
Looks like last year's champ
is feeling pretty confident.
How long do you think
you can keep that up?
Oh yeah, you guys placed
second and third last year!
That's right, we did.
Before that, we'd finished first
and second five years in a row.
We're the Macho Brothers!
How dare you try to knock
us down a peg, li'l girl!
Thankfully, this year's
a pairs competition.
Too bad for you, huh?
'Cause you better believe
we're gonna win this time!
Bring it! I don't
plan on losing!
You guys ready to
destroy some melons?
Then, let's begin!
Here we go, time to dig in!
Thanks for the snack!
[RONA]
Huh?!
[BOTH gasp]
[VILLAGERS cheer]
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
The Fai and Rona pair
have passed the
preliminary round!
Now, the time has come
for the Andas Melon-Eating
Competition Finals!
Eating ten in ten minutes
must've been a pretty high bar.
Three of our pairs ran
out of time and failed!
That means, this year,
we have two pairs advancing
to the grand finals!
[MACHO BROTHERS laughing]
I don't know about this, Fai.
Uh-oh!
Look at your crazy stomach!
Oh, yeah. Well, I suppose
ten whole melons
did fill me up a little, but I'm
kind of a bottomless pit!
You may've pulled ahead
in the prelim,
but we're not gonna
lose in the finals!
Truth be told, we've always
been better at the last round.
Oh, really?
For the finals,
the pairs will be in
fierce competition
to see who can eat
the most freshly picked
Andas melons in 30 minutes!
Freshly picked?
[BOTH]
Huh?
--Oh, man!
--[yelps]
Are these melons moving?
[laughing] Don't you know
about the special dish
of this village? It's Andas
Melons served live!
[RONA]
Huh?
Don't you worry about a thing!
I happen to be
great at this, too!
[MACHO BROTHERS grunt]
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
Now, are both teams ready
to begin the competition?
Let the Andas Melon-Eating
Competition Finals...
...begin right now!
Time to dig in
you guys! Ha!
Um, hey, melons?
Could you please
stay still for me?
[MACHO BROTHER 7A]
An...
[MACHO BROTHER 7B
...das!
[RONA whines]
At the top, we have
Fai and Rona,
who have cleared ten already!
Second: the Macho brothers,
they've done seven!
Seriously?!
That's impossible speed!
Uh! I don't think
I can do this, Fai!
Wow! We're approaching
the exciting climax!
There are only
two minutes left!
With 29...
...Fai and Rona lead!
The Macho brothers are putting
up a respectable fight as well,
with 20 melons of their own,
but it sure doesn't look
like they're catching up!
What the hell, man?!
Are we really gonna to lose
this freakin' thing again?
Check it out, her partner hasn't
eaten a single one, either!
--I'm sorry!
--[FAI groans]
Uh-oh, what's the matter,
are you okay?
No, I think I finally
hit my food limit.
Huh? Oh my gosh!
[ANNOUNCER 7A] What's this?
Competitor Fai is down!
This is our hour, Brother!
You got that right,
bro! You n' you!
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
The Macho brothers are at 23
and seem to be
catching up! That's 24!
And 25!
[ANNOUNCER 7A] There's very
little time left now!
[RONA]
Fai?
Well...
I guess we're about
to lose, aren't we?
Sorry, Fai... Mm...
No. Not yet!
[yells]
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
The Macho brothers are at 28!
They only need one more to tie!
Time for a last push, bro!
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
They're finally tied at 29!
The Macho brothers
have caught up!
Only one to go!
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
Oh, hold on!
Rona's just eaten the
30th melon, everyone!
Contestants, time's up!
The winners of the annual
Andas Melon-Eating Competition
are Fai and Rona!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
[RONA gasping]
[FAI]
Princess!
Uh. Heh!
We did it!
You know, we won these together,
so we should really split
them up when we get home.
No, you can have all of mine.
Huh?
The thing is...
...I'm really not that
fond of Andas Melons.
What? And you still
participated, anyway?
[RONA]
Mm.
[FAI gasping]
Thank you, friend!
I can't believe you worked
so hard just for me!
Thank you! It means a lot!
What's this?
[RONA] Why am I feeling
so unbelievably happy?
[YUSHA] Hey! We're so glad
you guys are back!
Welcome home!
Hey there! Glad to see
all of you, too!
Guess what!
Guess what happened!
The Princess was so
incredible on our journey!
She was all,
"ahhh-ahhh-ahhh",
and then "zoom!" and
"sploosh!" and "hoppity-hop",
and "sleep-sleep"
and "nom nom nom!"
Wow, great.
Princess, you really must be
incredible if you were able
to keep up with Fai on one
of her wild journeys!
Those trips are so crazy
that even we usually have
to turn her down!
Wow, Rona! Amazing!
No. It wasn't...
It was a fun trip,
dontcha think, Princess?
[gasps, laughs]
[RONA]
Yes!
"My Yusha-sama!"