[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[SEIRA]
You know what guys?
I think this is
getting out of hand.
[MEI] Mmm! It's kind of
unsettling to remember things
that we haven't experienced yet,
like a weird sorta déjà vu.
Yeah, but they're
only memories.
We're still the same strong
girls we always were.
Okay. What should we do, Yusha?
Huh? Well, I guess
we have no choice but to go
after her and rescue Rona.
Fight Miss Mao? I mean,
uh, fight the Demon Lord.
I'm not certain,
but I do know that we can't
just stay here and do nothing!
Still though, we don't even
have the faintest clue
as to where they might be.
Okay then, perhaps I could
be of some assistance!
[GIRLS]
Teacher!
[WARRIOR]
I couldn't help but overhear
what you were talking about.
Well, yeah, there
aren't any walls.
I'll give you this
Chaser Cartado.
If you use it, then it should
lead you to Miss Mao.
I've used it a couple of times.
Now that's a Cartado that
really gets my heart racing!
Please show us the correct path.
Chaser!
Look, it already
managed to locate her!
Yay! Let's go get our princess!
Huh?
Uh. Right.
[WARRIOR]
Yulia.
Yes ma'am?
Have you ever been inside of
a dungeon and lost your way?
It's not uncommon. So,
sometimes the best thing to do
in that situation is to go
back to the beginning.
Back to beginning, huh?
[MAO laughs]
Soon I'll destroy
those loser heroes
like a true Demon Lord!
Then I'll turn Naral Island
into my personal playground
of chaos, ha, ha, ha!
Don't do this! It's never too
late to change your mind
about destroying everything!
Yusha and the other girls
are still your students!
Enough of your chatter! Sheesh!
Surely even you must
have had an idea
about how this was
all gonna go down!
Huh?
C'mon. For real? You remember!
That means...
They could be closer
than you think.
Looking forward to class.
This is but another fate
laid forth by the world.
Surely there was a
point behind saying
those super ominous
things to me.
Ah! Oh those things!
They were quotes from a
previous character called
"the Dark Night." I think it
was chapter six in volume 82
of the Tales of Heroes .
[MAO, DEMON LORD]
Seriously?!
My grandfather said
obsessing over that stuff's
a phase all people go through!
And you're one to talk--
it's not as if you don't have
your own little secrets.
It's you that's hiding
your scary form
in that adorable little
body, remember.
Actually, this is my real form!
But the thing is, it doesn't
look Demon Lord-ish enough.
So, it's just a front
to look scary?
Who asked you?!
Here's a fun fact.
The Demon Lord also enjoys
composing poetry
--in her secret room.
--[MAO] Hey, hey, hey!
How would you know that?!
Because. It's my job to know
every single intimate detail
about the Demon Lord.
Really?
I had no idea that spying was
in a golem's job description.
Well, seeing as I have
the capability to operate
semi-permanently, I am aware
of many different truths.
I know things about Heroes
and Demon Lords you don't.
Everything.
What did you just say?
That's so interesting!
Won't you please share your
valuable knowledge with me?
[MAO]
Like it matters.
The current Hero
is way too careless.
Nothing you know
would be relevant.
[MEIGO]
Of course.
It's still hard to believe
that we're going back there.
[YUSHA]
Rona. We're coming for you!
Pey!
Pey-pey!
Pey-pey-pey-pey-pem!
Pem.
Pem-pem.
Pem... Peh.
Pem-pey!
[sighs] That was
an intense convo!
Negotiating fees
with a higher penguin
isn't for the weak, y'know?
Looks like we made it.
Except this time it's
the real deal castle.
Man, that was such
a long journey,
and those penguins don't
mess around with surcharges.
Now that we've made it,
there's only one thing to do!
Camping outside the
Demon Lord's castle?
This is gonna be super fun!
The moon is especially
beautiful tonight.
How are you so calm?
We are practically sitting right
on the Demon Lord's doorstep.
[sighs]
Hey, you guys. Do you think
we'll really have to fight her?
[ALL]
Uh.
I mean, that is why
Heroes exist.
[YUSHA]
Yeah. I know, but...
This might sound weird,
but sometimes I wonder
why I wanted to be the Hero.
[YUSHA gasps]
[CHIBI gasping]
Welcome, Hero's party.
We've been expecting you
for quite some time.
Meigo, you're here!
So, you've decided to
still use that name?
Even though I'm a loyal
servant of the Demon Lord?
So that must mean...
you remember?
Well, to us you're
still the same Meigo!
I see.
Then Miss Mao is still Miss Mao
and not the Demon Lord?
[gasps]
Such predictable behavior.
Heroes are so naïve.
How typical. No matter...
I will proceed to share this
critical information with you.
[MEIGO] A long time ago,
on Naral Island,
a tremendous, destructive power
appeared without warning.
The people called it
"a Demon Lord."
[MEIGO] Eventually, a Hero came
along and destroyed that power,
and restored peace
to the island.
However, the Demon Lord
revived once again,
and at the same time,
another Hero.
This event has
occurred 998 times,
leading to the 999th Demon Lord.
Are you serious?
Is it just me, or does that
seem like a big problem?
That's the Demon Lord's destiny.
[GIRLS gasp]
[MEIGO] It's because their
strength knows no boundaries.
Even when they're defeated,
they eventually regain their
power and are reborn once more.
That's why
they're destined to revive and
be defeated, constantly.
To prevent regaining
their true power.
Now hold on. Are you
saying that these generations
of Demon Lords aren't
reviving on their own?
Yes, though I am unsure
of who determined
this destiny for them.
All I know, is that the Heroes
have spent a long time fighting
against the Demon Lords.
It's part of a valiant effort
to keep them from
reviving prematurely.
Both of their destinies
are intertwined.
That's the reason why
the two are always
conveniently revived at
the exact same time.
[YUSHA]
Huh?
Meaning, you are
the last Hero, Yusha.
For real?!
What exactly are you saying?
That after 998 generations
of constant fighting,
the Demon Lord
has been worn down.
She's weaker.
To put it rather simply,
once you win this battle,
the Demon Lord will be
defeated permanently.
Never to be revived again.
Huh? So Miss Mao will vanish?
[MAO]
There you have it!
I'm the last one of the set!
I'm only born to be defeated, so
it's probably better if the Hero
just gets it over with already.
[RONA] The Heroes that
I've always admired.
They're just slaves to a destiny
of defeating the Demon Lord.
Over and over in an
unbreakable chain.
But, if for some reason,
Yusha and the others
don't fulfill that destiny.
If they don't manage to
overthrow the Demon Lord,
Miss Mao... then she'll
regain her full power
and try to destroy
Naral Island once again.
[MAO grunts]
[RONA]
Yusha...
I'm having a hard time
making sense of all this.
So, basically, we either have to
defeat the Demon Lord and make
Miss Mao disappear, or it's
game over for Naral Island.
Sounds like checkmate to me.
Why would you go out of your
way to tell us these things?
And now that we know--
Right. You won't want
to fight anymore.
Not given who you are.
That's low! How dare you!
With the current level of
your abilities, you would fail
to stand up to the
Demon Lord in battle.
However, you are the Hero so the
improbable is always possible.
And now... How will you proceed?
You're a naive girl
with a big decision to make.
[YUSHA gasping]
[MEIGO]
Well then. I must return,
but know the Demon Lord
is awaiting your visit.
Uh! So? What are
we gonna do then?!
We either fight Miss Mao,
or the island's history.
Seems like no matter what,
it's a tough call.
Sounds like we lose either way.
What do you think about it?
Yusha?
[YUSHA gasping]
--[SEIRA] She's broken!
--[FAI] Oh no!
[MEI]
Get it together, girl!
Ah... Uh!
I'm sorry, that was just a whole
lot of information to process.
Guess your brain must have
reached its capacity.
Well? Do you have
any good ideas?
Not one.
My head feels, like,
super spinny.
You guys, I really have no clue
what we should do next!
That's normal.
Life can be a real maze.
Is that your way of saying it's
normal to feel lost or whatever?
[CHIBI chirping]
Thanks, Chibi.
Yeah. I am feeling lost.
I wonder what a Hero would do?
Have you ever been inside of
a dungeon and lost your way?
Hey, that's it.
We'll start over.
They're late!
What's their darn deal?
It's super rude to
keep people waiting!
Excuse me, but I happen
to find a letter
from the Hero addressed
to you in the mailbox.
What the heck,
we have a mailbox here?
Okay, let's see.
"Dear Miss Mao..."
[YUSHA]
Dear Miss Mao!
We kinda sorta got lost.
So we're going back
to the beginning!
That dummy!
Impressive! Yusha's actions
are truly unpredictable!
Like the 518th Hero!
You're actually impressed?
You do remember
you're a hostage, right?
I'm sure that Yusha
believes in you!
Deep down, she knows you
possess a heart of gold
and would never harm me!
[gasps]
I didn't raise her to be an
adventurer who chickens out
at the first sign of trouble.
She leaves me no choice but
to bring the fight to her!
Let's do it! Princess and Meigo!
Uh.
Yes. Miss Mao! [hums]
What's the matter, you okay?
[gasps]
C'mon. Let's make
tracks already.
Yes, as you wish.
Guys! We finally made it.
This was the very beginning!
Both before and after we were
all flung into the past,
this place is where
we formed our party.
All because we met in class,
and then as if bound by fate,
we sat next to each other.
That was probably more of
a coincidence, you know?
Even so.
It's how we found ourselves
facing the Demon Lord together.
It's all because...
...we met right here.
[YUSHA]
Hey, Seira.
What made you want
to be a priest?
To be honest, I think it's
because both my mother
and grandmother come from
a long line of priests.
It's like a bond that ties our
family together, you know?
What about you, Fai?
What made you decide
to become a warrior?
That's easy! I wanted
to protect the forest
and my furry friends
from bad people!
What about you Mei, why did
you want to become a mage?
Actually, I'm almost positive
your answer involves
Cartado, right?
Hey, you never know, there
could be another reason!
Anyway, I think the more
important question
is why Yusha decided
to become the Hero!
Thing is... I hadn't
thought about it.
Not for a while.
But then, when we got
back I remembered!
It's 'cause...
It sounded so cool!
It's not exactly in-depth.
But it sure sounds
like our Yusha!
It doesn't have to be
super meaningful.
[CHIBI chirps]
[laughing]
Oh, hold on! There was
one more, though!
So this is where you were?!
[GIRLS scream]
Hi, Yusha!
The Princess!
Does this mean you're okay?
[RONA] Yes! I'm so glad
you're all safe!
Uh, shouldn't that be our line?
[DEMON LORD] I swear, what
terrible students you've become!
How dare you make me
track you down!
Miss Mao!
[YUSHA yelps]
[DEMON LORD]
Who's ready for a pop quiz?
The time has come for you to
finally take on the Demon Lord
that you've all been
longing to fight!
Hold on! Please listen!
[DEMON LORD grunts]
[YUSHA gasps]
The time for talk is over.
Prepare for battle, Hero!
Please Miss Mao! I don't-- No.
None of us...
We don't want to have
to fight against you!
[GIRLS]
Mm!
You imbecile! You're the Hero,
so that means you have
no choice but to fight me!
No way. Because...
You're still Miss Mao!
You're still our
beloved teacher!
That's right! You cared enough
to teach us valuable lessons.
Even though we're
the Hero's party!
You taught me about
all kinds of Cartado
and how to use them properly!
Sure, sometimes you got mad, but
you always rewarded us, Teach!
You made us happy!
[gasps, growls]
Having class with you
every day was so much fun!
You know it! Right, Miss Mao?
You fools. That was all just...
[DEMON LORD, MAO]
That was...
That was fun!
And I enjoyed every
single moment
of every single day, okay?
[MAO] But, if you don't
hurry and defeat me,
then I'll regain my power and
this island will be destroyed!
And all that will remain
is my isolation.
Lonely... and cold.
Without anyone else...
I can't stand it. Not anymore.
And that's why...
I wouldn't mind if the students
I spent my happiest days with
are also the ones
who take me down.
Oh, Miss Mao.
I understand.
--[SEIRA] Yusha!
--[MEI] Wait, Yusha!
[YUSHA] I always...
wanted to be a cool hero.
One who'd fight the Demon Lord,
and take them down for good.
So!
Thank you. It's for the best.
[YUSHA yells]
Right! Time for dinner, Chibi!
[ALL gasp]
Catch!
[CHIBI]
'Lil burp.
[CHIBI chirps]
[YUSHA sighs]
All done!
[ALL]
What the heck's wrong with you?!
You served the Hero's
Sword for dinner!
Now what are we gonna do?!
And what's more!
Without it, you can't be
recognized as a true Hero!
It's okay you guys!
I never got to tell you
the second reason I
wanted to be a Hero!
It's because I wanted everyone
to have fun and be happy!
I really mean it!
So of course that
includes Miss Mao, too!
[gasps]
If my job is to
make someone sad,
then I don't want to be
the Hero anymore.
Are you serious,
Yulia Chardiet?
You mean it?
[laughs]
Listen, I really hate
to bring down the mood
in the middle of this
tender moment.
But if we don't have the Hero's
sword, we're sort of in trouble.
Because now Teach can
recover her true power,
and go all Demon Lord-y on
the entire island or whatever.
Huh? Nah, no way!
Miss Mao won't let that happen.
Right? You tell 'em!
[MAO]
Mm...
Oh, no!
[MAO]
That's what we've been saying!
[MEIGO]
Looks like it's my turn, then.
[MAO gasps]
[screams]
[CHIBI]
'Lil burp.
[ALL screaming]
Bad Chibi! No eating people!
Yeah, you don't know
where she's been!
And she could upset your tummy!
You can't just eat things raw!
The real problem is
she ate our teacher!
[CHIBI grumbles]
[MAO groans]
Miss Mao!
You're alive?
[MAO panting]
Hey!
It's incredibly rude to
just eat people, y'know!
Don't ignore me!
Please calm down, madam,
and just listen.
Think about it.
Can you still feel
the Demon Lord's power?
Say what?
Yeah, of course,
it's right here inside of me.
It's gone!
[GIRLS]
Huh?!
During the previous battle
between the Demon Lord
and the Hero's Party,
I also managed to get
caught up in the effects of
the Hero's forbidden spell.
[chirps]
[MEIGO]
Afterward...
While I was drifting in
the dimensional gap,
this little dragon saved me.
Really, Meigo?
It sounds like it ate you.
Nice one, Chibi. Good goin'.
[chirps]
You see, ordinarily,
it would be impossible for
a golem to move on its own.
But then, this one, made it
possible for me to do so.
[MAO]
Whoa, back up!
Are you seriously trying to tell
me that thing was able to eat
the concept of "golem"
which bound you?
Yes, and because of that,
I thought she might be able to
help you by erasing the concept
of the Demon Lord, as well.
Thus, hopefully breaking
the circle of destiny
that has bound you and
the Hero together.
At last, it's over.
Wow that was a super
awesome call, Meigo!
Although...
This only worked because Yusha
cast aside her role as the Hero.
You have my gratitude.
It's no prob! I just wanted
everyone to be happy.
In the end, that's all
that really matters.
So that's why you told us that
stuff back in the forest,
because you were really
looking for a way
to save Miss Mao, huh?
You must have been so very
worried about her, Meigo!
You really do care!
Even though I couldn't
move on my own,
I've always been
watching over her.
Uh, more importantly,
being able to erase
an entire concept from
someone is kind of
Creator-God level
stuff. So fess up.
Why are you all keeping such
a mysterious beast as a pet?
Yeah, why are you keeping
Chibi as a pet, Seira?
Me? Chibi belongs to Mei!
Huh?
No way, if anything I assumed it
was one of Fai's forest buddies.
Nah. There's nothing
like Chibi in the forest.
Besides, out of all of us, she's
always hangin' out with Yusha.
Huh. That's so weird.
How long has Chibi
been with us, anyway?
[SEIRA]
Now that you mention it,
she wasn't with us when we
faced Miss Mao the first time.
[MEI] She was just
kind of there one day.
[GIRLS]
Hm...
Well, she's ours now!
Uh... I swear.
What am I gonna do
with you four?
Huh?
It's morning! [yawns]
I'm feeling wiped out
all of a sudden.
We just pulled an all-nighter,
so it makes sense.
I vote we go take a nap.
If you do you'll be
late for first period,
so sorry but hard no.
[GIRLS]
Huh?!
[YUSHA]
That's so mean, Miss Mao!
[SEIRA] We were on an
important quest, you know!
[FAI]
Meanie-head!
[MEI] You really are
an evil Demon Lord!
Not anymore, now I'm
just an Evil Teacher!
But... There is one thing.
You know.
Go on. Just say it.
Uh. So I wanted... to say...
Thank you! For your help!
[GIRLS laughing]
No problem!
That's what friends do!
Okay. Hold down the fort!
[MEIGO]
As you wish.
Thanks!
Take care, and I have a
good day at work, Mao.
[MAO]
Thanks, see you tonight!
[WARRIOR grumbling]
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Huh?
[MAO] As teachers we should at
least try to be there on time.
[gasps] Right.
[MEIGO laughs]
Hey, look!
I heard that they cleared an
advanced quest the other day!
Well, that's the
Hero's Party for you.
I bet they could even
defeat a Demon Lord!
Everyone keeps saying things
like that. Little do they know
that both the Demon Lord
and Hero are history.
Doesn't that mean
Yusha's classless?
[whines] Why did you have
to go and remind me?
You know., you have to have
a job to accept new quests.
Duh, of course I
know that, Seira.
Everyone, hi!
And good morning!
I know it's early,
but look at my new book!
Looks awesome!
So, what's it about?
Oh, right. It's the
newest volume in
Tale of a Hero created by me!
[GIRLS gasp]
[YUSHA]
Can I see?
Huh?
The only thing I have
done is the cover.
[GIRLS groan]
I was so focused on
perfecting the binding
that I didn't even
finish the rest.
Makes sense.
Yes, I agree. Sometimes
you just get hyper focused
on something, like finding
the perfect Cartado,
but it's more than
just a collectible!
And the only way to truly
appreciate your new treasure
is to make use of its power!
Only then can one achieve
true Cartado nirvana!
For that reason, I feel
like I failed my...
It's totally blank.
[RONA]
I do apologize, Yusha.
Thanks, Rona. It's perfect!
Huh?
[MAO] Okay. It's time to
take your seats, class.
It's Miss Mao!
[MAO]
What now?
Our future is still
blank, right?
So I was thinking,
can we be whatever we want?
Uh. Yeah, I don't see why not.
[YUSHA]
Well, in that case,
I'm going to be the Hero!
Typical Yusha...
That's a great idea.
Duh, of course it is!
It's Yusha's!
Okay! I'll pal with you!
'Cause that's just what pals do!
Great job! You are amazing!
--[CHIBI sighs]
--[GIRLS gasp]
[chirps]
[YUSHA]
Aw, Chibi!
[SEIRA]
When did you get here?
[FAI]
Maybe she can teleport!
Oh my goodness. [sighs]
The problem with Heroes is they
never know when to give up.
Well, you'd better give
it your best, Yusha!
Right! I promise.
I won't fail!