[YUSHA] We finally get to do
our quest practical tomorrow!
[FAI]
I know!
I totally can't wait!
I mean, quests are what
adventuring is all about, right?
And the Heroes are
the people who accept
the challenges before them
to help out their fellow man!
This is just part of
our lessons, though.
So, I'm pretty sure they'll only
be giving us basic quests.
What kind of quest do you
dream about taking on, Yusha?
[YUSHA] Hmm... Well,
whenever I think of Heroes...
...I think of dragon-slaying!
Sure, and at our current level,
we'd get wiped out
in five seconds.
I mean, what part
of the word "basic"
don't you understand, huh?
Fine, then, what kind of quest
would you all like to go on?
Wow, lemme think.
Oh! On my dream adventure,
we'd get to eat
lots of yummy food!
Being charged by someone
with a mission to find
a rare Cartado would be amazing!
Yeah, I don't really think
that's a thing that happens.
[FAI] Kay, smarty-pants, what
kind of quest do you wanna do?
Uh! I guess I don't know. Hmm...
Ah! It would be
something like a quest
to stop a horned gorilla
on a rampage!
So, like, you're talking about
a horned gorilla slaying?
No, no.
Not a quest to slay one.
It would just be to
find it, soothe it,
and to persuade it to chill.
[FAI] Like you do with
a thief in a holdup?
"Just think about how
your mother would feel!"
That's what they would
say to those guys.
Yep.
In the end, the horned
gorilla would return home
thanks to our gentle
encouragement.
And the gorilla
that we persuaded--
he's a candidate for
Horned Gorilla King!
And he's caught up
in an epic battle
for power between factions!
So, of course, I join
up with my new friend
to fight for the throne,
and aid him as he battles
corruption in the
horned gorilla world!
But, then! His long-lost nephew,
the former king's
illegitimate son, appears!
He claims that he's the
rightful heir to the throne,
and he takes over the kingdom!
After being driven out,
we go searching all through
the hidden land
of Horned Gonglia
for the legendary,
sacred sword Exgorilla.
But along the way, we get
caught up in a twister!
It's so scary! Our cart
gets launched into the land
of Goth in another
world, where we meet
the Horned Gorilla
Witch of the West!
[PEOPLE chattering]
I can't believe we're assigned
a quest from an actual guild.
So cool!
Wonder what kind of
mission we'll have.
Like I said, it's only
a practical quest,
so I'm sure it's like...
"Go to the store across town
and purchase the
things on this list."
Or, "deliver this message
the next town over,"
or something similar.
So, it looks like this is the
quest we have for you guys.
"Obtain the whisker of
a flying ocean sunfish
from the shores of Star Coral."
Got it!
Here's the quest
we have for you:
"Obtain the fruit
of a wind piper
found inside
Black Elm Forest."
Right!
Those quests sound
pretty legit to me!
Maybe we can get our hopes up.
Wouldn't hold my breath on a
horned gorilla quest, though.
You're hilarious!
[YUSHA, FAI laugh]
[YUSHA]
Yay, our turn!
Uh? A party of only women?
That's unusual.
So, you're a priest.
You're a warrior.
And you're a mage, right?
And what're you?
I'm a Hero!
Ah, sure, of course.
Will it help you
if I play along?
[YUSHA whines]
Hey, don't worry!
Who cares if you're an official
Hero, as long as you're Yusha?
Either way, "Yu" shine!
No, you don't get to be
smug about that pun.
[MEI] Now is the time you
choose to call me out?
Okay, I have it right here.
[GIRLS gasping]
[RECEPTIONIST 3A]
Your quest will be...
...to find a cat.
[meowing]
Oh, look. You've
found him, then.
Excellent job.
Your reward.
There's still more to
the practical, though.
So be ready to work tomorrow.
[ALL sigh]
Here's a good question:
Do adventurers really
look for cats?
Well, by definition, a "quest"
is a search for something,
so they're not wrong
in that respect.
Yeah, now that you mention it,
it's actually exactly
what adventurers do.
Searching for lost treasure,
finding captured princesses,
and going to find
legendary monsters.
Then I guess in the end
adventurers aren't so much
professional combatants
as professional seekers.
Right!
Oh, hey, maybe next time we lose
our room key we can just ask
some adventurers
to find them for us!
[SEIRA]
I think you're forgetting that
we're those adventurers.
Man, so we'll have to find
them ourselves, anyway?
Wait, once we become
adventurers,
it won't be about getting to
eat lots of yummy foods?
It'll just be about going
on quests to find it?
[SEIRA] Yeah, that's much
more likely I'm afraid.
How'm I s'posed to do that?!
If I find something yummy,
I just gotta eat it!
I agree! When I come across
bread in Seira's bag,
I can't help but
eat it on the spot!
Yeah! Dude, me too!
[SEIRA] You ate my food?
You guys eat too much!
[FAI, YUSHA]
Huh?!
[SEIRA]
You're both hopeless.
Even Mei wouldn't use a
Cartado she just picked up
off the ground, would you, Mei?
No, I wouldn't.
Not even a really rare one?
No, course not.
Well, that's convincing.
Fine, Seira. I hear you.
Even if we accept a quest to
hunt down something delicious,
I swear to you that
I will not eat it.
[SEIRA]
Are you... crying?
[PEOPLE chattering]
Here's your group's
quest for today.
"Go obtain a fire
lizard and it's egg
from Red Ice Mountain
and bring it back here."
Awesome!
And here's the quest
for you guys.
"At the Pond of Poison Mist,
locate a Micah frog
and obtain its oil."
Yes, sir, understood!
I'm so curious. Wonder what
quest we'll get today.
Let's hope, for Fai's sake,
that it isn't a quest
to find anything super
tempting or delicious.
[gasps] I can do it.
I can control myself,
I can. [panting]
[YUSHA]
Our turn, please!
[RECEPTIONIST 3A]
Oh, it's you girls.
Yes, sir!
Well, let's take a look at what
fate has in store for you today.
Interesting.
[ALL gasping]
[RECEPTIONIST 3A] Looks like
your quest is: "Find a cat."
[ALL]
Not again!
Excuse me, but do you think
you could maybe give us
a different one?
Sorry, nope.
Nobody here gets to
choose their missions.
We're required to assign
them completely at random.
But that's twice in a row
that we've had to find a cat.
If you don't like it,
feel free to drop out.
We don't wanna do that, though.
[sighs] I know!
We can pick up another
quest on the side!
We learned the best ways
to catch a cat yesterday,
so it'll be easier this time!
Makes sense to me!
Really? Is that wise?
[YUSHA laughs sheepishly]
What are the chances that
we'd pull "find a cat"
five times in a row, huh?
Yeah, it's kind of incredible.
I still don't understand
why we didn't just stop
after the third one.
Uh-huh. We went a
little overboard.
At this point, all we can
do is find those cats!
[meowing]
[YUSHA grunts]
Oh, great! You actually
found the five, then!
You should be proud.
Here you go.
We'll see you again tomorrow!
[ALL sigh]
I don't like to complain,
but today was really rough.
[grunts]
Yeah, I know. But just think,
we've for sure gotten the
hang of finding cats now.
Truth! If we keep this up,
I bet we probl'ly could even
find cats professionally!
Oh! That sounds like a fun job!
And we'd know right away
whenever any cute kitties
were in the area!
Hey, now, let's back up.
We're committed to being
the Hero's Party regardless,
aren't we? Once the
Demon Lord revives,
how can we fight him if we're
too busy being cat finders?
Huh, that's a good point.
[DEMON LORD]
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
You will bow down before
my enormous power!
[YUSHA] Attention, all the
cute kitties I'm friends with
throughout the kingdom!
The time is now!
[CATS meow]
[DEMON LORD] Ooo! How have
I been living without
sweet wittle furballs?
[YUSHA]
Listen up, you!
If you keep doing evil, I'm
taking all these kitties home!
[DEMON LORD]
What?!
Please, no, don't do that!
I can't possibly go on
without pussycats now!
[YUSHA] Then you won't be
doing evil anymore, right?
[DEMON LORD] No! No more
bad things, I promise!
[YUSHA]
And we live happily ever after!
See? Like that!
Eh... What a nice
little fairy tale.
That would be so great!
Am I right?
If that's the case, then
I'll need to gather up
every Cartado that
deals with cats.
[SEIRA]
Are those a thing?
[YUSHA]
Good morning!
[RECEPTIONIST 3A]
Oh. You four.
So, give us the scoop.
What kind of cat will we
be looking for today?
Calico? Spotted?
Bring it on, dude.
After six times, we
might be overprepared.
I did some research
last night and found
a Cartado with a catnip spell.
[SEIRA]
Unbelievable.
Well, here's your
quest for the day.
"Go obtain some moonlight moss
from Silver Bone Cave
and bring it back."
'Kay, so, that's a long
name for a cat.
'Cause it's not a cat!
This is your quest, okay?
Go obtain some moonlight moss
from Silver Bone Cave right now!
So, you're saying...
...we're actually...
Could it really be...
We're not looking for
a cat this time?
You aren't. That is correct.
[ALL]
Wow...
Hooray!
[YUSHA]
Silver Bone Cave, huh?
Where was that again?
[SEIRA] If I'm remembering
correctly, I think it's about
two hours south of
here, give or take.
Oh, that sounds pretty far.
It does. We'll need
some gear. And food.
Oh, should I maybe bring
our barbeque set?
What are you even talking about?
We're not going
there for a vacay.
[YUSHA]
Huh?
[TOWNSGIRL 3A cries]
[YUSHA]
What's the matter?
[TOWNSGIRL 3A] Michael's gone.
I can't find him.
Oh, who's Michael?
My cat. He's all white, with
black on the tip of his tail.
Huh?
[TOWNSGIRL 3A] He's been with
me since the day I was born.
But when I woke up this morning,
he was missing, and I don't
know where he could be!
[sobs]
[YUSHA sighs]
All right! Don't worry anymore,
we'll find him for you!
Really? You will?
What?! We will?
Let's do it, okay?
[ALL]
Uh...
Don't you worry. We're, like,
professional cat finders.
You're in good hands.
We found five of 'em
just yesterday!
Look, I even have my
catnip Cartado at the ready.
Aw, guys!
Rest assured, we'll find
your little Michael for you.
Leave it to us.
Thank you so much!
Just leave it to us!
ENDRO !
Sorry, guys.
We wound up looking
for a cat, anyway.
[SEIRA]
Wait, what are you saying?
Remember, a Hero is someone
who helps people in need,
and that's exactly
what we're doing!
Oh! You praised Yusha for once!
Of course I did.
It's not like I hate her
or anything, you know.
When she kills it, I say so.
My gosh! I freakin' love the
heck out of you, too, Seira!
Same here,
I'm obsessed with you!
I am also a fan.
You're both trying to
embarrass me, aren't you?
No way, I mean it so hard!
I mean it harder.
Uh! Well, thanks, but we should
get back to finding the cat.
Come on, let's get going.
[GIRLS]
Right!
[roars]
Do you really think a little cat
would hang out around
a creature so gross?
Some people in town said they
had seen one that matched
his description in this area,
so we had to check.
Apparently, when one cat
enters another's turf,
they get chased around
and driven farther
and farther away.
At this point,
I'd say he's not lost,
he's on a long journey.
This will be easy.
Look how slow it is.
Let's take it down.
All right!
[yells]
[FOREST SPIDER 3A groans]
Is that it? Well, guess we won.
[YUSHA]
We did it!
You guys, look, it's
a treasure chest!
Oh. Great... Grass...
[SEIRA]
It's a medicinal herb.
That's not gonna be
very yummy, FYI.
Because it's medicine,
not food, you weirdo.
Oh. The sun's
already going down.
[SEIRA]
You're right.
Think we should
head back to town?
[YUSHA]
Hm...
I say we sleep right here
like real adventurers!
Who would've guessed we'd
ever end up camping out
while in search of a cat?
Yeah, seriously.
But you guys, at least it feels
like we're legit adventurers.
It makes me excited
about the future!
[stomach grumbles]
Oh, crap.
Uh-oh. Should we go ahead
and make dinner?
Heck yeah!
Put that grub in mah belly!
[YUSHA gasps]
Uh. Huh? What's this?
You were officially in charge
of our provisions for
the quest, weren't you?
Something's off here.
Oh, I get it. You brought
this along 'cause you're
going hunting to bring us
some fresh meat, right?
--So cool!
--Wow, are you really?
Huh? No! No way.
Just a second!
First of all, it's nighttime,
and I can't see!
Second, I'm not good at archery
even when I can see!
That's actually a good point.
You always use a hammer,
even though you're
an elf. It's weird.
Thank you! I know!
Wait, then, I don't get it,
why did you bring a bow and
arrow instead of food?
[gasps] I guess I just brought
the wrong thing by mistake.
[FAI, MEI, YUSHA]
What?!
Sorry.
So, there's... no food?
I'm so sorry! Don't worry,
I'll go back right now
and get dinner for us!
I'll probably make it
back here by dawn.
[FAI]
No way.
I won't last that long.
And the thought of
having no food--
it's already freaking me out.
[SEIRA]
Wait, no! It's okay, Fai!
Mei, I think you showed me
an "Imperial Feast" Cartado
the other day,
do you remember that?
Do you have it with you now?
Of course I do.
Oh my gosh, then, use it!
I'm sorry, I can't.
Huh? Why not?
What happened, did you forget
to fill up your mana?
No, it's a legendary rare
Cartado that's way beyond
just awesome, so I want
to preserve it, unused.
[SEIRA, YUSHA]
What?!
[FAI]
Oh yeah, it's happening.
I'm so hangry!
[ALL scream]
[groans]
Okay, do you think
that's enough?
Honestly, I think if we're
smart we'll let her chew
till Yusha comes back
with the food.
So, there's still no chance
you'd consider using your
"Imperial Feast" card for us?
I'd rather fall headfirst
into the swirling miasma
of a dark world,
turn the entire planet against
me for the rest of time,
and start a bloody war
that may never end
than defile this
precious beauty.
Guess that's a no.
Augh! Yusha, come
back and save me!
Well, one thing is for sure--
I will never forget to
bring food ever again.
I don't remember much
about last night.
Did anything weird go down?
[YUSHA gasps]
I can see a tower!
[SEIRA] That must be the one
the townsfolk mentioned.
Gotta hand it to Michael,
he got lost in a pretty
incredible place.
It's just like something you'd
see on a real adventure, huh?
Probably so.
All right, then.
Off to save the day!
Woo-hoo!
Hey, be careful!
You guys are such nerds.
[GIRLS laughing]
Welcome travelers--
good afternoon.
This is the Red Spider Tower.
So, um, did you happened to see
a little white cat around here?
One that has black on
the tip of his tail?
Yes, as a matter
of fact, I have.
I saw a cat that
looked like that
up on the top floor
of this tower.
Oh, did you really?
Thanks, we appreciate it.
That seemed kinda strange.
Why do you think that guy's
standing out here, anyway?
I dunno, I just assumed
it must be his job.
[YUSHA]
Huh. Well, I'm grateful.
[TOWER MONSTERS growling]
I can already tell that there
are traps hidden everywhere,
and I think I hear
monsters inside.
It's probably going to be
really difficult for us
to reach the top floor.
But you know, that was
an especially average guy
we just talked to and he said
he'd been up to the top floor,
so maybe it's a whole lot
easier than we think.
Huh. Maybe you're right.
But guys, it doesn't
hurt to be careful,
so just keep your
guard up, okay?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
[sighs]
This is bad.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What. Oh no.
[thud]
[SEIRA]
Yusha! Are you okay?
Yeah, I think I'm
gonna be all right.
Hold on. Do you think
these stairs...?
Search Cartado... go!
It would appear that these
stairs go all the way up
to the top floor. They seem
to be free of traps, too.
Yippee! Lucky us!
You really do have kind
of a Hero's talent
for things like this, don't you?
[YUSHA]
Uh. We're here! We made it!
That climb totally wore me out.
[gasps] Hold on! Careful!
There's something here!
[MEI] So, that must be
the boss of this tower, huh?
[roars]
That's our cue, everyone!
Let's go!
Whoa, is it just me, or is
this guy a color variant
of the monster that was
so easy yesterday?
Piece 'o cake, then!
Come on, let's go! Charge!
No, wait. Fai!
[TOWER SPIDER 3A roars]
Easy peasy breezy!
Huh?
Huh? It's fast?
Watch out, everyone!
So, even when monsters
share the same form,
if their colors are different,
their strength level's
also completely different.
Had to find out the hard way.
Good to know.
Come on, girls, we're still
gonna get this guy!
[MEI, FAI, SEIRA]
Yeah!
[YUSHA yells]
[SEIRA grunting]
[FAI]
Bam Bam Punch!
[MEI]
Magic Arrow!
[YUSHA yells]
[TOWER SPIDER 3A groaning]
Yes! We won!
[FAI] Ugh, what a super
crazy strong monster.
[SEIRA]
I'm officially exhausted.
This was somethin'. I even
sank a rare Cartado on him.
[MICHAEL meows]
[GIRLS gasp]
[YUSHA]
It's Michael!
[SEIRA]
How'd he get up there?
[YUSHA] Aw... And how're we
s'posed to rescue him?
[YUSHA grunting]
Looks like I can't reach.
All right!
[FAI grunting]
[FAI]
Nope.
I don't have any more Cartado
that I can use right now.
[YUSHA]
What do we do, then?
[MICHAEL meows]
It's up to me.
Oh, right! You could use that
to cut through those
threads, couldn't you?
Hold on!
I thought you said you weren't
very good with a bow earlier!
That was a lie.
I'm a good shot, it's just
that my eyes aren't great.
I've spent so much time reading,
now I'm nearsighted.
[YUSHA]
Hooray!
[meows]
Seira, that was totally amazing!
Hey, if you're that good, why
not wear glasses all the time
and just be an archer, huh?
No, absolutely not!
But why would you not?
Well, 'cause, then people will
just think I'm a bookworm.
[FAI, YUSHA, MEI]
Uh...?
[FAI, YUSHA, MEI laugh]
[SEIRA]
Why are you laughing?
I'm serious! Stop it!
[YUSHA]
Here.
Oh, Michael!
I have you back.
Thank you, friends!
You really saved the day!
Totally our pleasure.
Okay, bye!
Thank you all again!
Well, we went through a lot,
but it turns out quests
are really fun.
They sure are!
I'd say they're not half bad.
Oh my gosh, hold on!
[FAI, YUSHA, MEI]
Huh?
This wasn't our official
quest, you guys!
[ALL yelp]
We forgot about the
Silver Bone Moss!
[FAI] I can't believe we didn't
finish our real quest!
[MEI]
This is bad!
[YUSHA] We can do it!
Come on, let's hurry!
[YUSHA] "Ocean, Swimsuits,
and Slaying Evil Gods!"