Wait for me, everyone!
What a beautiful day,
don't you think?
Good morning, Hero!
Hey, Rona! Good morning!
Everyone should really
have one of these.
You'd be surprised
how handy a staff
can be when you're
dungeon crawling.
Any idea why that is?
How about you, Princess?
Huh? Well, um...
[SEIRA] They can be very useful
in searching for traps.
They're great for poking
around in dungeons.
[RONA]
Oh my gosh, thank you.
They can be very useful
in searching for traps!
They're great for poking
around in dungeons!
You do realize I heard
every word of that?
[RONA, SEIRA laugh]
It's vital for adventurers
to know about Cartado,
and how to use
them effectively.
They can be used for
offensive magic such as this,
or for carrying items around,
or a million other things.
[RONA]
Miss Mao?
I've never really understood
what Cartado are.
[MEI grunts]
I see. Where to begin?
[MEI] Cartado date back all
the way to the ancient times,
when heaven and earth
were first created!
[MAO]
Huh?
There are different
theories about that.
Like, for example, one theory
says the great creator appeared
back when our world
was nothing but chaos.
There was no light,
darkness, heaven, or earth,
and he raised up a single
card and said,
"Car-Tado!"
In Ancient Lapanestan,
that translates into
"world, be filled with light!"
and that is how the wonder
that is Cartado came to be!
Wow! Is that really true?
Yeah!
Hey! How 'bout if
I teach the lesson?
[FAI munching]
So good!
Yes, I can tell you like it
from how much you're eating!
You should have
some, too, Princess!
Thank you, I think I will!
Wait, what is happening?
It looks like Fai
is sharing food.
I guess they must
be super close now!
[YUSHA]
Aw, this bow is so cute!
It would look really
great on you, Hero!
I think it would look
even better on you.
Huh?
Well, yeah, 'cause you're
already so cute anyway!
Oh my.
[laughs]
[RONA laughing]
Well, I must admit,
I had a very fulfilling day!
Although, I do feel as if
something is missing.
[RONA gasps]
Oh, gosh, that's right!
Well, then,
what brings you here?
And on your day off?
Miss Mao.
It bothers me that the Hero
isn't even slightly heroic!
Huh?
What the heck are
you talking about?
Heroes are really special.
They save us all from the
good-for-nothing Demon Lord,
otherwise he'd bring
total chaos and destruction
to the world as we know it.
So, heroes should be the
strongest, bravest people ever.
Who're you calling
good for nothing?
Sorry?
Nothing! W-Was that out loud?
Continue.
All right. So, anyway,
our Hero's different.
She attends classes, eats
boxed lunches, goes shopping
with the rest of us, and lives
like a fairly normal girl.
[MAO] So, basically she
does all the same things
that you do, and you
don't like that?
It's not that I don't like it.
It's really fun to
hang out with her!
I don't get it then.
What's the problem?
Not a problem. It's just
always been my wish
to get to see the Hero
doing heroic things.
Gotcha, so you wanna see
big acts of bravery.
Come to think of it,
she did say something
about defeating an evil
god over summer break.
Who knows if it's true, though.
Defeating an evil god?
That's perfect!
Give me more of that, thank you!
Are there any of those villains
that're just ripe for
destroying out there?
[MAO]
No, of course there aren't.
And don't talk about evil
gods as if they're fruit.
Besides, even if
Yusha is the Hero,
you have to keep in mind that
she's still just a fledgling.
She can't go on proper
Hero quests yet.
Well, but can't you do
something about that?
I said no, that means no!
--[jingling]
--Huh?
[KNIGHT 8A]
Mm-hm.
Uh... [gulps]
I'm begging, is there really
nothing you can do?
No, there's not! I'm a
responsible teacher now!
[KNIGHT 8A grunts]
Yeah, all right.
I'll help you out.
Oh, thank you!
You've made me so happy!
[MAO] Oh, no, this is terrible!
The Demon Lord has revived
himself, and he's
kidnapped Princess Rona!
[GIRLS gasp]
The resurrected
Demon Lord has built
a new Demon Lord
castle for himself
and he's lying in wait
for you there, Hero!
Since this is the
actual Demon Lord
only you, the wielder
of the Hero's sword
can save the princess!
Go, Yulia Chardiet--
go and save Princess Rona!
Right!
[MAO] I can't believe I got
myself dragged into this.
Everyone! It's our
duty to save Rona!
He can't get away
with kidnapping her!
The real Demon Lord.
We have to make sure
we're prepared!
At last, the day has come.
The day when not a single
Cartado will be held back!
[MAO] Ugh, I feel so guilty
watching them get all worried
and worked up. So,
here's my apology.
Sorry!
[clattering, banging]
[MAO]
Hey, anybody home?
Yes, I'm so glad you're back!
So, how did it go?
Everything is all set.
Yusha and the others should
already be on their way.
Yay!
I can't believe I'll finally get
to see her being truly heroic!
I have to say, Princess,
I'm pretty amazed you
built this structure.
[RONA]
Well,
I always thought that a day
like this might come.
So I built the
Demon Lord Castle!
You're a ridiculous human being.
Looks like they just got here.
They really came
for me! How sweet!
Everyone, let's go.
[SEIRA, FAI, MEI grunt]
Rona, just hold on!
We have to be cautious,
an enemy could
attack at any time!
[yelps]
[SEIRA]
Oh no, it's a trap!
Shoot, I knew we should've
brought that stupid staff!
Come on, we gotta run!
[YUSHA]
Get to the door!
[MEI gasping]
Mei!
I think I twisted something.
Take this!
What the...?
[MEI]
This presence, it's a monster!
Seira and Mei,
you guys stay back!
Here it comes!
[POMURUNS]
Pompom pompom!
[SEIRA]
Huh? Pomuruns?
[MAO]
Look at that!
They're really taking
this seriously!
The Hero does seem
to be fighting
as hard as she
possibly can for me!
Though, this is
pretty unsatisfying.
The Pomuruns aren't
working for you?
Well, after all, they really
are the weakest monster,
aren't they?
And the boulder trap
was obviously made out of papier
mache, and besides that...
Hold on!
Oh my goodness!
You even prepared
recovery points for them?
I'm sorry, but this
doesn't feel serious!
Uh... Okay, then what did
you have in mind?
To demonstrate her true power,
I think the Hero should
have to face trials
just like the ones spoken
of in our legends!
For example, a falling trap
that'll flatten even trolls!
An army of demons from the
demon realm lying in wait!
Cursed evil spirits that'll
steal their souls if they dare
to let their guard down
for even a minute!
Y'know, things like that.
Jeez, even I didn't think to set
up hardcore stuff like that!
Pardon me?
[MAO]
Nothing! What? Nothing!
Hey, Princess.
It sounds like you
won't be satisfied
until they're put
in actual danger.
Huh? Well, doesn't danger
just go with the territory
when you're the Hero?
Unless, wait a minute...
I guess when I think about it,
the one who's putting
the Hero in danger is...
Oh dear, oh my. Could it be?
[MAO] Look! Here we go, they're
approaching the next room.
Oh yes! I'm finally about
to witness the real-life,
marvelous deeds of a Hero!
Look at you! So confident!
I am!
Because guess what is awaiting
them in the next round?
The Demon Lord's Four Generals!
His Four Generals?!
Are you crazy?!
You actually brought them here?
[GENERALS laughing]
Who's there?
Wait! Hold on,
what're those costumes?
[RONA] They're the Demon Lord's
Four Generals, see?
Look at this. Perfect replicas!
[MAO]
No, that's not...
The author of that book may have
taken some artistic license.
They're really big.
And they're strong!
Great eye.
Guess that's just the
Four Generals for ya, huh?
This is nuts. They're
almost freakishly strong!
Of course they are!
The ones in the costumes
are my personal bodyguards
so they're the very best,
and the pride of our nation!
[RONA]
Sword Master.
Grappler.
Archer.
And Arch Wizard!
They're the four
strongest people
in the whole Lapanesta Kingdom!
Yes, I'm ashamed to say it,
but they might be stronger
than the real Four Generals.
[GENERALS laughing]
You guys feelin' okay?
This might be a bit too much.
They're out of our league,
it's not a fair fight.
The way this is going, we won't
be able to save the princess!
[SEIRA, MEI sigh]
[YUSHA]
Not yet!
[BOTH gasp]
It's too soon to give up!
Because we decided
we were going to save
our friend Rona no matter what!
[GENERALS gasp]
[RONA]
Oh. Hero...
[GIRLS grunt]
We're with you.
She's our friend, after all!
And that's the kind of thing
friends do for each other!
Ready, then? Let's go!
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[yelling]
[SEIRA yells]
[MEI grunting]
[yelling]
Stay out of our way!
We are saving her!
Do you understand me?
Rona is our friend and
she's coming with us!
Huh?
[SEIRA]
Wait, what?
Seriously, what's going on?
Yeah.
[SWORDMASTER 8A grunts]
[gasps] Are you letting us pass?
[SWORDMASTER 8A]
Mm.
[SWORDMASTER 8A] The four of us
have served the Princess
ever since she was just
a little slip of a thing.
Thank you all
for protecting me!
You're the best!
[SWORDMASTER 8A]
The Princess's happiness
is all that any of us
could ever wish for.
To have people who would risk
their very lives for yours--
well, we think you've made
some good friends, Princess.
[RONA, MAO]
ENDRO!
Well, it was pretty
wonderful getting
to watch the Hero fight,
but it ended right when
it was getting good.
I wonder what could
have happened
to make everyone
stop fighting like that.
Uh! Do you think maybe they all
suddenly got stomachaches?
Princess Rona.
What is it?
I think it's time to
stop this, don't you?
[RONA]
Huh?
Come on, haven't you
already gotten your wish
to see all of them fight
like real Heroes?
They did well, considering.
So, aren't you satisfied?
Not yet! Right after this comes
their final battle
against the Demon Lord!
Which you know is the
climax of any Hero's tale!
I mean, it would
just be unthinkable
to shut it all down now.
[MAO] Hm... What was
going through your mind
as you watched them fight today?
Huh?
[RONA]
When they first came for me...
...I was simply elated!
I did get nervous when
they set off the traps.
But I was so thrilled to see how
truly wonderful
their fighting was!
[RONA]
But, then...
Because we decided
we were going
to save our friend
Rona no matter what!
Rona is our friend,
and she's coming with us!
[RONA] I wonder what this is,
this prickling in my chest.
I thought this was all I wanted,
to get to see a real
Hero in action.
Heh.
[MAO grunts]
[RONA gasping]
[DEMON LORD] If that's true,
then pay attention.
As the Demon Lord
and the Hero spar.
Miss Mao?
[thunder crashes]
Hang on, friend!
We're here to save you!
Thank you, Hero!
[DEMON LORD]
You've done well, Hero,
making it all the way here.
Shut up! Give Rona back,
Demon Lord!
[laughing]
You fools!
[GIRLS gasp]
[YUSHA]
Huh?
What is this?
[grunts] Come on!
It's a barrier. One that's
dangerously strong.
Don't worry! I'll get you
outta there guys!
[DEMON LORD]
If you want to save her,
I'm afraid you'll
have to defeat me.
[DEMON LORD]
One more thing.
You must use your
own power, alone.
Be careful.
It'll be okay.
I've got this.
I promise I'll save you!
[YUSHA yelling]
[yells]
I ask you this, now.
Why is it you seek the Princess?
For wealth? For status?
Or perhaps, for fame?
No!
Then is it just because
you're the Hero?
Your strong sense of duty?
Because it's your
destiny to defeat me?
No, none of that!
It's not because she's
the princess, or because
I'm the Hero. None of that
matters. It never did!
It's about her!
Because Rona is one
of our precious friends
and she's in trouble now!
That's why we've all
come to save her!
[gasps]
[RONA] Oh my gosh, now that
I look back, I see it all!
[inaudible]
Hang on, friend!
[RONA] She always thinks
of me as "Rona, her friend."
I don't remember the last time
she called me "Princess."
And what did I do?
I only thought of
her as one thing.
You better give Rona back!
[RONA] No, you have
to stop this, please!
[YUSHA]
Huh?
[DEMON LORD]
I'm so sorry!
I'm responsible for
every single bit of this.
The Demon Lord
isn't really back.
My kidnapping was a big lie.
It's true. I did this!
I'm so incredibly sorry!
[GIRLS]
Uh?
What?
[GIRLS]
Why?!
I've always admired
the Hero in our legends,
even way back when
I was a tiny thing.
I just knew that, one day,
I would meet a Hero
who was as lovely and triumphant
as the ones in the stories.
But now, I can see that I was
a little hung up on the stories,
and I tended never to look
at what was really there.
What was really there?
You, Hero, you were
there the whole time.
No. I mean Yulia Chardiet.
I feel like I've constantly
imposed my ideal Hero on you,
and I haven't been looking
at the real you at all.
So you're saying,
you got a fake Demon Lord
to make Yusha act heroic?
Because she hadn't done
anything like that yet
and so you felt like you
were missing out?
I mean, on one hand, it's true,
Yusha is hardly heroic.
Yeah, can't really blame her.
Huh?! Come on,
that's not true, you guys!
Yeah! She's right!
Yulia is a wonderful person,
and she is heroic!
[gasps, sighs]
[laughs]
So, anyway, seems like there
wasn't a real Demon Lord.
Indeed.
[YUSHA]
That's good!
Huh?
Honestly, I'm just
really relieved
that you weren't
actually kidnapped!
Hey but, do you know what?
If the Demon Lord
ever did do this,
or anything even
remotely like it,
I wouldn't hesitate
to save you again!
It's true!
Absolutely!
We should probably come
up with some strategies
to try to keep her safe.
[gasps] Thank you,
everyone! So much!
[YUSHA]
Hey, w-wait!
[SEIRA]
Just out of curiosity...
[FAI]
...who is the fake Demon Lord?
[MEI] Thank you,
I thought we'd never ask.
So um, who are you, exactly?
It's me, you crazies!
Wassup.
--[FAI] It's Teach?!
--[SEIRA, MEI] It's Miss Mao?!
No way!
I can't believe I
didn't sense that!
Transformation Cartado,
and a very powerful
one at that, I think.
I was seriously doing my best
to cut straight through you!
I'm so sorry!
Heh. It'll be a hundred years
before a weakling like you
has the skill to slay me.
Well, I'm off.
You girls better not be
late for class tomorrow!
[ALL]
'Kay!
Everything worked out!
Now, let's go home!
[gasps]
[RONA]
Yes!
I made you all some lunch,
as kind of an apology.
Please, help yourself
if you'd like.
[FAI]
Heck, yeah!
[SEIRA] You didn't have to go
through all the trouble.
[MEI]
A royal lunch, though, you guys.
I bet it's gonna be
super gourmet!
[RONA]
No, it's...
It's the first thing
I've ever made,
so I just really hope
you like them.
Wow! Incredible!
Yeah, I'll have some!
May I have some, Princess?
[FAI]
Mm-mm! So yummy!
They seriously are good!
Oh, yeah, these are
actually really tasty, Rona!
Oh! I'm so happy!
I was really worried.
Thank you, Yulia!
--Huh?
I mean, "Yusha" is fine,
you don't need to use "Yulia."
It's... so casual.
[YUSHA laughs]
[RONA laughs]
Okay. Yusha, it is!
[MEI]
"Secret Cartado Festival!"