Leave it to me,
girls! I got this!
Faster-Than-The-Eye-
Can-See Punch!
I'll seal his blades
using Seal Weapon!
Looks a lot like
"birdlime" to me.
Which is perfect for the birds.
Get it, you guys,
"for the birds"?
I saw that coming.
[caws]
Oh, no, you're
not getting away.
I'll do Breeze times three
for a Tornado Combo!
Basic Cartado are great
if you know how to use them.
Yusha, finish it!
Where is she?
I found her. Look over there!
[laughing]
[SEIRA]
Stop playing around!
[YUSHA]
Three, two, one!
[yells]
Sweet!
[SEIRA] Hey, we've gotten
a lot stronger, haven't we?
[MEI] Funny, I was actually
just thinking that.
[FAI]
Same here!
[ALL] We are really strong.
Love you guys!
[FAI]
Yeah! Yahoo!
[GIRLS laughing]
[RONA]
Congratulations, friends.
You of the honored Hero's party.
As someone who's witnessed
everything you've ever done
and even went so far as to
record it, which might be weird,
I'm so incredibly thrilled
I got to see this!
So, what do you think?
[GIRLS]
We'd like a Hero's quest.
May we have one, please?
Anti-Chaos... Go!
[ALL grunting]
Whoa, what in the heck did
you do that for, Miss Mao?
Good, looks like you're
back in your right minds.
Honestly, you girls should
be able to cure yourselves
when you've been
inflicted with Confusion.
We've been in our right minds!
Also, I'm so sorry, but I have
to ask, did you really just
cast magic without using
any Cartado at all?
Uh.
Well, never mind
about that right now.
I thought you were
here to talk about
a Hero's quest, weren't you?
We sure are!
Hold on.
Take a look at this, Miss Mao!
An advanced quest receipt,
for the purpose of
defeating a Criffon?
Oh, I see. Well, then...
Good luck with that, kiddos!
[GIRLS shouting]
If necessary, I have proof!
It's right here if
you'd like to see.
That's where she keeps
her cards? In there?
Guys, this is nuts.
That's the legendary rare
Cartado that records everything
around it, referred to as
the "Truth Recorder"!
Thanks for breaking that
down for us, Mather.
Very well done. Now, I'd
like for you to watch this.
It's some footage of
Yusha and the others.
I think you'll be surprised
at what you see.
[gasps]
I can't believe that you
four defeated a Criffon,
and you actually cleared
an advanced quest, to boot.
Oh, weird. Why'd you record us?
I wanted to keep a historical
record of what you've done.
Our newest Hero deserves
to be remembered.
I've recorded
everything I've seen.
And it's been an honor
to do so as your friend,
and as your truest
fan, of course!
--[YUSHA] Thanks so much, Rona!
--[FAI] Rona, that was so nice!
[MAO]
I guess they really did it.
Now that I think about it,
both Yulia Chardiet's group
and the "Hero-fanatic" princess
have grown by leaps and bounds.
You deserve the
credit, Miss Mao!
Because this is obviously
due to everything
you've been teaching us!
[MAO] Wow. This must be what
it feels like to help others.
So, are you gonna give
us a Hero's Quest?
I can't.
[YUSHA]
What do you mean? Why not?
Because the Demon Lord
hasn't even revived yet.
So why would a Hero's
Quest even be available?
That makes sense.
Guess we can't have a Hero
without a Demon Lord.
You say that as if there was
some kind of secret pact
between Demon Lords
and Heroes of the past
or something like that.
[FEMALE WARRIOR]
You know, Mao.
Sometimes I think
education requires
both the carrot and the stick.
I get it. That's helpful
to keep in mind.
And just so you know,
if you were the one offering,
I'd be equally thrilled with
both the carrot and the stick.
Thanks for sharing, though
that's not helpful at all.
[MAO]
Hmm.
Well... I suppose that
since you've finished
an advanced quest,
I could consider gifting
you a special reward.
[YUSHA]
Reward?
That's right. Anything
within my power to give.
I wanna defeat the Demon Lord.
[MAO]
Dude, this girl's terrifying.
Look how badly she
wants to beat me up!
Look, she just told you
there is no Demon Lord.
Is there anything else you can
think of that you'd like to do?
[YUSHA]
Hmm...
I know!
Ha! It's been a while since
we've been to Miss Mao's house!
[CHIBI grunts]
Honestly, I never expected you
to ask to come over here again.
[YUSHA]
Of course!
It's always fun being
invited to a friend's house!
Right?
It's inappropriate to refer to
your teacher as your friend.
I wish that the princess
had come over with us, too.
Rona said she
would've loved to,
but she felt like
she should focus
on organizing the footage of us.
I can't wait to see what kind
of book she ends up writing!
I think that's a long way off.
Okay, just don't get too
crazy in this cramped space.
Come. Right this way.
I should warn you,
it's a little messy.
[GIRLS]
That's okay!
[ALL] This is way more
than a little messy!
[MEI] I never would've guessed
that entering this room again
would mean we'd have
to clean it like before.
Yeah, that time, I just
assumed it was like this
because she was so sick
with the Demon Lord fever.
We were apparently wrong
to blame it on that.
Hey, Miss Mao. I've been
thinking about something.
I believe everything that has
form will one day fall apart.
That's right.
Likewise, any beautiful
room will get dirty.
I'm afraid that's just
the nature of things.
[SEIRA]
You get me.
I sure do, Ellenoar Seiran.
Hey, now! Don't you slobs
start bonding over there!
[SEIRA, MAO gasp]
[MAO]
Oh, no!
At this rate,
my dignity as a teacher
will plummet right
through the earth!
[YUSHA] Seira, didn't
I remember you saying
you were gonna clean up
your room the other day?
Yes! I have been cleaning, okay?
And I should finish in about
a hundred years or so.
[FAI laughs]
I love a good elf joke!
Well, I guess I'll take care
of the cooking again
if nobody has any objections.
Come on, food!
[YUSHA]
I wanna help! What can I do?
[FAI]
Pound the meat to tenderize it!
[banging]
As I'm pretty sure
you already know,
Mei's culinary creations
are the best around.
I'm drooling!
[MAO] Yep, my dignity
is in serious danger.
Just like this elf girl who's
taking her long life for granted
and claiming she'll get
serious one day,
when she'll always be
a super-hot mess!
Nope!
Today you four are
guests in my home.
Therefore, it's my honor,
as well as my duty,
to cook for all of you!
--Wow, you're really gonna cook?
--Wow, you're cooking?
[MAO] Time to restore some
of my dignity as a teacher!
[MAO]
Final Dead End!
[GIRLS gasp]
Ka-boom! So, what do you
think of my cooking, now?
It looks incredible, Miss Mao.
You mean it looks
incredibly weird.
I'm confused, it's like we were
watching her start to cook,
but then I can't remember
seeing her do anything.
So, um, you didn't by any
chance use Cartado, did you?
Look, why don't you guys
go ahead and eat up?
And just remember, cooking
is about creativity!
[GIRLS]
Time to dig in! Hah!
What the heck's happening?
[YUSHA]
Is everyone still alive?
I don't get it.
This flavor doesn't even
exist in the natural world.
It's like my mind is
still totally clear,
but only my mouth moves.
[MEI]
It's as if this poison decided
to leave our tongues alone
solely for the purpose of making
us eat this stuff forever.
Oh, goodness, what a shame.
Maybe you should
stay over tonight,
though I'll need to check and
see if I have enough pillows.
It's such a waste
to leave any behind.
[MAO gasps]
[MAO] Come on, monster!
There's still some left for you!
[screams]
[YUSHA]
Chibi?
[FAI]
How inhumane.
[MEI] Guys, what's
going on with Chibi?
[ALL screaming]
[sighs]
[GIRLS groaning]
What in the heck is going on?
You're gonna make
my landlord hate me.
[gasps]
Wait. I know you.
[BOTH]
ENDRO!
Oh! Good morning, Miss Mao!
Also, good morning, Meigo!
Good morning to you,
too, Miss Yusha.
So, I guess her name is
officially settled, then?
Yeah, why not? She's a
maid golem, so "Meigo"!
Very creative there, Yusha.
[sighs]
[MAO]
I don't understand.
Why are complications like
this happening again?
[YUSHA] Ah! You guys,
a maid popped out!
Bad Chibi! That was bad!
When the heck did you
even eat a maid?
I'm not at all comfortable
with that visual.
[SEIRA]
Hold on. This girl isn't human.
She looks like some
kind of golem.
[FAI]
Even though she's so soft?
Would you stop?
Although, I've never seen one
that looked so much
like a human before.
[MAO] What is this?
What is she doing here?
Before I got flung
into the past,
she was an all-purpose
golem that served me.
So how did she
end up in this age?
And why'd she shoot out
of that monster's mouth?
[laughs] I have returned,
unfortunate ones!
And this time, I shall
destroy the world!
Wait, no! Not again!
[CHIBI]
'Lil burp.
[MAO] Crap. More importantly,
if she ever wakes up,
then everyone here will find
out that I'm the Demon Lord!
[MAO yelps]
Oh, good, looks
like she's awake!
[MEIGO]
Um.
Who am I? I seem
to have forgotten.
So weird.
But I guess amnesia is an
actual thing that can happen.
[FAI]
Oh, that reminds me.
Seira's weapon
is a hammer, so--
I'm not doing that!
Are you sure?
Don't be ridiculous!
You guys, I'm pretty
sure she'll be fine
since she'll be living with
Miss Mao for a while.
Looks like you're even bringing
her to school with you now, huh?
Well, I can't just
leave her all alone.
[MAO] I'm even more anxious
when she's not nearby!
She's not bullying you, right?
[MEIGO] No, she's treating
me very well, thank you.
Not that. I meant
with her cooking.
Would you please shut up?
Besides, preparing our meals
became one of her jobs
right off the bat.
Oh, I see.
So what you're saying
is she won you over
through your stomach,
is that the case?
What a totally bizarre
way to put it.
[MAO gasps]
She's the worst.
Nothing but a homewrecker!
Don't you have lesson plans
to prepare or something?
[sighs] Today has
been so exhausting.
You've done a good
job, Miss Mao.
[MAO] Well, let's be real, most
of this stress is from fretting
about what to do whenever
your memories come back.
I think I might have a
drink with my coworker
before I go home.
[gasps]
I understand then.
If you do that, I'll head
back home by myself.
[gasps]
[MAO grumbles]
[MAO]
Does she know?
It feels like she might.
Actually, I think I'll just
lounge around at home instead.
Whatever you prefer. Absolutely.
[whines]
Ugh, no! How many times
must I tell you?
Tell me what?
It's impossible to
eat this in peace
with you looking over
my shoulder like that.
Come on, now, that's an order.
Of course, my apologies.
Please pardon me, ma'am.
[BOTH]
We're grateful for the food.
Oh, this soup's
insanely delicious.
Thank you.
I convinced the
fishmonger to share
some of his secret
broth with us.
Apparently, the product is
labeled "Mackerelman Leftovers."
[MAO] I think I'm
probably better off
not pursuing those
details any further.
Understood.
Oh, and do try some of this
salt-fried tottori , as well.
[MAO]
Wow, this looks incredible, too!
You know...
You wanna join?
Feels silly that you're
just standing there.
A servant is never
permitted to do such things.
[MAO]
This isn't so bad, after all.
Wait, I'm only keeping
this girl close to me
so I can keep an eye on her!
Can't forget about that!
[RONA] Ahem! I have
something to report!
I've reached a stopping point
in organizing the records!
--[FAI] Hey, good job, Rona!
--[MEI] Good job, Rona!
Would you all like to
explain what you're doing
in my house right now?
Simple!
I wanted to experience
being invited over
to a friend's home, as well!
I told you people, I'm not
your friend, I'm your teacher,
and there's a difference!
Why'd you have to pick my
tiny little house, anyway?
How're you, Meigo?
Well, thanks.
I've got a surprise for you.
In anticipation of something
like this happening,
I keep a "Legendary Rare" on
me that restores memories!
And now, I'm so glad I do!
[MAO gasps]
Wait! It restores them
no matter what happened?
That's incredible, Rona!
What great news!
You'll get your memories back!
Oh, my. Do you really think so?
[MAO]
Not good! Not good!
I am in so much trouble
if you use that thing
and she remembers me!
Hold on! Slow down a minute!
Are you positive she wants
this, 'cause she might not!
[RONA]
Sealed door of memories,
open before this
light of blessing!
Now!
[ALL gasp]
Well, do you
remember now, Meigo?
[MEIGO]
Mh-mh.
[RONA]
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Wait, so it didn't
work? What a...
That's so strange.
I wonder if I was
out of magic power.
Mather, what do you think?
[ALL]
Uh...
I just remembered!
[MAO]
Wait, they remember stuff?
[YUSHA] We met at the adventurer
school, and we hit it off fast,
so we formed a party!
[SEIRA] And during our
first quest in class,
Yusha drew the Hero's Sword.
[MEI] And then we set off on a
journey as the Hero's party,
determined to defeat
the Demon Lord.
[FAI] We went on lots and
lots of adventures,
and finally arrived at
the Demon Lord's castle.
[YUSHA]
There, we fought him bravely.
And then,
after we were all thrown
back into the past,
we met up again,
like the first time.
Look at you. Each of you.
You're my fate.
And you're ours.
You sure are.
We're with you.
But! It's on you!
This is all your fault
for flubbing the chant
to that stupid forbidden spell!
I know, I'm so sorry, okay?
Do you realize what
this means, though?
You all have practically
defeated the Demon Lord already!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Yeah, that was no sweat at all.
That's what happens when we
all four decide to get serious.
[MAO]
What do you mean, "serious?"
[RONA] But I'm curious,
how did Meigo end up here?
[YUSHA]
Oh, yeah.
As I recall,
she was the final enemy
protecting the Demon Lord.
She was even stronger
than his Four Generals!
But the thing is,
I couldn't possibly tell you
how she ended up popping
out of Chibi's mouth.
If Meigo is indeed the
Demon Lord's attendant,
then isn't there a chance that
she knows where he is right now?
[MAO]
Gulp!
I don't know. You think
she might tell us?
You seriously think the Demon
Lord's attendant will confess?
Not like there's anything we
can do about it, anyway.
Did you forget her
memories didn't return?
Hey, I've got it, we can
keep her here as a hostage
to draw the Demon Lord out!
What do you think?
[OTHERS]
Okay, elves are scary.
No, that was a joke.
I was totally kidding!
Well, for now,
I say we at least keep her here
in the Lahpanesta Kingdom!
We certainly can't
allow anything
related to the Demon
Lord to run free.
Good idea! I'm on
board with that!
It makes sense,
so I guess you're right.
[MAO] If she truly didn't regain
her memories with that spell,
there's not much chance of her
recalling my real identity.
Which means my peaceful life
will be secure once more!
Try not to hate me for that.
Besides, this is the princess
we're talking about.
She would never hurt you.
[gasps]
[MAO]
Hold on, is she scared?
But golems don't
have any emotions.
Don't worry. You'll be safe.
[MAO gasps]
[MAO] Does that mean her
memories have returned?
[MEIGO] In that case, you
may take me in, Princess.
You will never be mistreated.
Don't be afraid.
[MAO]
Calm down, it's gonna be okay!
She may look like she's human,
but she's just a golem.
[MEIGO] I am a golem and
I was created specifically
to serve the Demon Lord.
[MAO]
She's not a real person.
She's only capable of doing
what she's ordered to do!
She's just...
[YUSHA]
But hey!
If the Demon Lord's
attendant is here,
then that means he must
be out there somewhere!
So we have to defeat him!
Because I'm the Hero!
Victory is mine!
I hope so.
[MAO]
I get it.
Because while she has her
personal pride as the Hero...
...I do, too!
I won't let you!
What did you say?
[MAO]
My pride is as fierce as yours!
What kind of Demon Lord
abandons their loyal servants?
[MAO yells]
What the heck is happening?
[MEI]
Incredible magic power!
Coming from Miss Mao?
[GIRLS groaning]
Hello, Master.
What seems to be the
trouble, Yulia Chardiet?
No, wait, "O Legendary Hero."
Have you not been longing
to defeat the Demon Lord
more than any other wish?
Is that you... Miss Mao?
[DEMON LORD] I'm none other
than the Demon Lord.
The Demon Lord who shall
rule over Naral Island!
You'd do well not to forget.
[ALL gasp]
Ah! No! Rona!
[DEMON LORD laughs]
If you want to save
the princess, Hero,
then come to my castle,
and don't waste time!
I'll be waiting for you there.
And Yulia Chardiet,
I plan to make you taste
true despair once more!
Is this happening?
I can't believe that Teach
is the real the Demon Lord.
It's true.
That form and powerful magic,
they definitely belong to the
Demon Lord that we remember.
Gotta save Rona,
and Meigo, too.
And Miss Mao!
Oh, Miss Mao.
No, you're... the Demon Lord.
I don't understand why
you're doing this.
[laughs]
Would you really like to know?
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[MAO] I'm pretty sure I just
got caught up in the moment,
and so I did it
without thinking.
[GIRLS]
"After the End Roll."