[MAO] In short, it's tempting to
use medicinal herbs in the wild,
but it's unsanitary.
So only in emergencies.
[MAO groans]
I mean, unless it's urgent.
Then you should--
[ALL gasp]
[gasps] Miss Mao!
--[SEIRA] Are you okay?
--[MEI] What's up with Miss Mao?
[YUSHA]
Miss Mao, what's wrong?
Uh! She's got a fever!
Oh my, would you be willing to
leave this one to me, Hero?
Are you sure?
It's important to remain
calm in moments like this.
No panic, no rush.
We're simply going to build the
ultimate hospital right here,
right now!
On the contrary,
you're in full panic mode!
Let's just get her to
the nurse's office, okay?
The way you can make
the right decision
in the middle of a crisis
always amazes me.
[panting]
[NURSE 6A] I have the
results of your exam.
Huh? That look... in your eyes.
It's bad, isn't it?
Yes. I knew it would
come to this one day.
[NURSE 6A] This is terribly
difficult to have to tell you.
I know my body better
than anyone.
I can always feel when
something isn't quite right.
I'm prepared to accept anything.
I've had a long time
to think about it.
So, please, tell me the truth.
[NURSE 6A] Miss Mao, what
you're dealing with is rare,
and it is called the
Demon Lord Fever!
[MAO]
Demon Lord what now?
[MAO panting]
[MAO]
It's called "Demon Lord Fever"
because even Demon
Lords can't escape it.
What a weird way
to name a sickness.
Seems a little harsh
that even I,
who gave up being
the Demon Lord,
should have to deal with this.
But maybe it's my punishment
for tossing my duty aside.
[MAO sighs]
That's some good strawberry
juice. Fill 'er up, please!
Now I'm home and I'm
happy, safe, and sound!
Off. Off. Bed!
[snoring]
[MAO] Well, I have no idea
how I could've caught this,
but there's nothing
to be done.
I guess I just have to accept it
as some kind of karma
being dealt to me.
[stomach growls]
[MAO]
Oh, man.
It's a pain to get up, but I
don't have much of a choice.
They said there's never been any
kind of wonder drug for this,
so the only way to treat it
is to stay warm and
get plenty of rest,
and to make sure I'm eating
loads of "nutritious stuff."
So, I guess it's time to start.
Demon Lord Fever's the worst!
Well, dang.
I know it's my own fault,
but I still can't believe it.
I suppose I should cook
for myself more often.
Huh? What's that?
Oh, right!
It's the drop we got
from the Honey Boo Monster
during that outdoor practical!
This honey is
chock-full of nutrients!
[MAO] Ugh. Shoot, is this
really all I have left?
Well, I guess it's
better than nothing.
[MAO]
Li'l lick.
So sweet!
I've heard it said
that this honey
provides complete nutrition!
I can use it to fight off the
nasty Demon Lord Fever!
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick.
I'm sad.
I mean, what am I doing here
all by myself and super sick,
instead of being the Demon Lord?
No fair.
Why was I unceremoniously
thrown to the past
during that battle
with the Hero?
Ugh!
Although, when
I think about it,
there's really not
much difference
between then and now.
[MEIGO] Have you awakened,
new Demon Lord?
[MAO]
And you are?
[MEIGO]
I am a golem,
and I was created specifically
to serve the Demon Lord.
So, Demon Lord,
have you been able
to finish recovering
all your memories?
Not all. I wish I had,
but I'm not there yet.
Remember, this is 3,000 years of
memories you're talking about.
The details tend to get
a little hazy over time.
[MEIGO] That's to be
expected, of course.
This is your 999th
resurrection, after all.
[MAO] And when the Demon Lord
is resurrected in this land,
a Hero also appears to
take them down, right?
Heh.
So, if the legends are all true,
that means we've now
been defeated 998 times,
which is crazy.
Hmph.
It seems like we're
only being resurrected
for the sole purpose of
being taken down again.
I have full confidence that you
can achieve a victory this time,
for what it's worth.
[MAO]
Very well.
In that case, you may
begin guiding me
toward becoming a
true Demon Lord.
Of course. That's
what I'm here for.
[MAO]
What are those things?
They're glasses.
I will be your teacher.
[MAO]
Wearing those things?
[MEIGO]
Indeed.
What is the major known weakness
of the second tail of
a five-tailed dragon?
[MAO]
Easy-peasy, it's fire.
[MEIGO] That is the weakness
of its fourth tail.
The correct answer is that the
base of the tail is ticklish.
Okay, we're talking about
a different kind of weakness.
Next, if our friend Tom
harvests 300 from his fields,
approximately how much
will he pay in taxes
if it's a rate of 30%?
Well, that's ridiculous.
He would pay 90.
[MEIGO]
Incorrect.
Tom would pay no taxes and would
instead flee into the night,
after the Demon Lord
burns all of his fields.
Wait, am I some kind of tyrant?
You're the Demon Lord.
The Demon Lord's Four
Generals shall humbly serve
as your sparring partners
for combat training.
[BOTH]
Prepare yourself...
...Demon Lord!
[MAO]
Hmph.
[GENERALS scream]
What? Are my generals
all a bunch of wusses?
Wanna join? Feels silly that
you're just standing there.
A servant is never permitted
to do such things.
Oh, I see.
[MAO]
Go forth, my subordinates!
This time, our Demon Lord Army
shall seize Naral Island!
[SUBORDINATES yell]
[MAO] I feel like I'm some kind
of gargoyle in a birdcage.
But one day, I shall take flight
into that pitch-black night
full of miasma.
I am the Demon Lord,
waited upon by everyone,
so why...
...why do I feel so
lost and unhappy?
You say the new
Hero has appeared?
A student at the
Adventurer School.
She pulled the sacred sword
and departed with her friends.
Wonderful. At long last.
And that makes you
smile, Demon Lord?
[gasps]
[MAO] Wait, was I
really smiling just now?
[MAO]
The Hero has arrived!
That's right.
They've successfully
defeated the Four Generals,
and now they're headed
straight for you, Demon Lord.
I'll attempt to intercept them.
[MAO]
Wait.
Yes, Demon Lord?
Nothing. Never mind, forget it.
[MEIGO]
Then please excuse me, my lord.
Even if I wanted to stop
that girl from leaving,
I don't even know
her actual name.
I guess, when it comes
down to it, I'm all alone.
[yells]
[DEMON LORD] I applaud you
for making it this far
and reaching my lair, Heroes.
I was so very close to
conquering Naral Island,
and putting an end to
my sad, pathetic life
in the lonely Demon
Lord's Castle.
Why did the dumb new Hero have
to be someone so clueless?
It's just infuriating!
[knocking]
[MAO] Who could it be at
a time like this? Achoo!
[YUSHA crying]
[YUSHA]
Miss Mao, please, don't die!
Please!
[FAI] Ooo, you've got her
in a nice lock, Yusha!
You should have her
beat in three seconds!
[SEIRA]
Hey, hey, hey, Yusha!
You need to ease up a
little on that grip, okay?
Come on. See? Miss Mao's
trying to tap out!
Let her go and back away slowly.
Now, fight!
Hey, Seira, I don't think
you're helping the situation.
You all really are the
most clueless creatures!
Endro !
Why you litte...
[coughing]
Are you all right, Miss Mao?
Believe it or not, I was
actually doing fairly well
until you crazy weirdos
barged in here.
[MAO coughs]
[FAI] I found some Honey
Boo honey over here!
So sweet!
Wait, that's mine!
Hey! Give that back to me!
That honey is my last
hope for nutrition
before it all
comes crashing down
and I die a sad and lonely death
surrounded by school children!
This is the end...
How could that have
been your last hope?
It seemed like there was
hardly any in there.
Truth.
But if you think it'll help,
then have a lick! Here!
[FAI chuckles]
I won't lie, it kinda tickles
when you lick it like that!
[gasps]
Do you want to taste some, too?
Here ya go, Chibi, open up!
[chirps]
I feel like that
can't be sanitary.
[panting]
She looks really uncomfortable.
When I had Demon Lord Fever
as a kid, it wasn't like this.
I recovered right away.
Hey, I know!
Mei! Why don't we just cure her
Demon Lord Fever with a Cartado?
Because that's impossible.
You can heal wounds
with Cartado,
but you can't cure illnesses.
That's just the nature
of how they work.
Oh, I see.
Guess Cartado has
its limitations
just like everything else.
[MEI grunts]
[SEIRA]
Okay, that's kinda cute.
Hey, Yusha.
I'm sure it's not because
Cartado lack any power,
but more because nothing
can compare to a mother!
You mean as a cure?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[GIRLS]
Aww...
Still here?
Well, thanks for dropping by,
but I'd like to take a nap now.
So, please go.
No, it's settled!
Since you're always
taking care of us,
this time we're gonna
stay and take care of you
the way a mother would!
You're--!
Umm, what did you just say?
[MAO] So, I'm just supposed
to trust these crazies
to look after me?
I'm going to die!
[gasps]
[MAO] Have these girls
somehow managed to discover
my true identity?
Have they actually
come here to end me?
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[YUSHA]
How's that? Feel okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
When you're germy, it's
important to stay clean.
Sure. Prob'ly true.
[door opens]
I'm back!
I brought Teach some good,
restorative fruits and mushrooms
I picked in the forest.
Do you think this
is enough to start?
I'd say so.
I mean, nothing beats
some good healthshrooms
and easilydigestiseeds.
So with that, I now have a plan.
It's time to change!
This is what I call my
"Young Wife Mode."
I'll make some food
that's easy to keep down.
Just realized, Mei's the most
conventionally girly one
of our little group!
Oh my gosh, it's so true!
She can cook, clean, and sew!
[MAO] These girls sure
are full of surprises.
Okay. I'll get started
cleaning up her room--
[YUSHA, FAI]
No, stay right where you are!
Not this again!
[YUSHA]
We'll take care of the cleaning!
[FAI]
Yeah!
[CHIBI 1A grunts]
Chibi. Hey there.
You and I are
friends, aren't we?
[gasps]
[SEIRA]
Chibi? What are you...?
Hey, you okay?
[gasps]
Oh, crap. What did you just eat?
Actually, never mind that.
Why are you coming this way?
Stop right where you are!
Don't you dare open your
mouth and show me!
Go away! I want my mommy!
Doin' okay over here, buddy?
Sure, why?
Well, here's the thing.
Miss Mao's having some
trouble eating on her own,
so I wondered if you might be
willing to come help feed her.
[gasps]
Of course!
Wow, is this really
the same place?
Better believe it!
Looks pretty different, huh?
[SEIRA]
Here you go, Miss Mao.
Let's try some soup, 'kay?
Oh, okay.
Say "ah."
Ahh.
[MAO]
What is this?
I feel oddly warm.
Is it because of the fever?
[MAO]
What the heck is going on?
I was just fighting the Heroes
and now, all of a sudden-- Uh.
Oh, sorry about that,
little lady. Here.
Lemme help. Are you all right?
How dare you!
You shall taste the power
of the Demon Lord! Ha!
Huh?
What is going on?
Where'd my power go?
Oh, I see. So you're
playing "Demon Lord"?
What's so funny to you, human?
My, you're very scary!
I'm in quite a pickle facing off
with the big bad Demon Lord!
What'll I do?
After all, the new Hero
has yet to appear.
You would dare to insult
the Demon--? Wait a minute.
What do you mean
there's no Hero?
Now I get it.
At least, I think I do.
At present, there's no Hero
walking around on Naral Island,
let alone a Demon Lord.
So what does that mean, then?
Only thing I can think,
is that I've been sent
to the past somehow,
and it must have been...
because of her!
But time travel is supposed
to be impossible for everyone
except the Creator-class
god, so just how badly
did that dimwit Hero
have to screw up
in order for this craziness
to happen to me?
[sighs]
Although, I guess it could
be a whole lot worse.
Fortunately, I still possess
my memories of the future.
And if I use those wisely,
I might even be able to prevent
the birth of the new Hero!
Unfortunately, whether it's
because the Hero's magic failed,
or because I've somehow
travelled back in time,
my power has been
drastically weakened.
I need to try and get some rest
so I can recover my power.
To do that...
...I will need to procure
a base and a job!
[MAO laughing]
I am the Demon Lo--I mean, Mao!
Listen well,
foolish little humans
of the Adventurer's Guild.
You will humbly and
obediently find me
a suitable job and residence!
I'm sorry, kid. All outta
good quests right now.
Here, have some candy
and go play outside.
Nice. It's wise and admirable
of you to present a tribute.
I shall return again!
Well, curses!
At this point, I'm going
to have to try everything!
Why is it this difficult
to find a base and a job?
And what possible reason
could everybody have
for continuing to give me candy?
As tasty as it is,
quite frankly,
candy isn't going
to fill my stomach.
[stomach growls]
[MAO groans]
To think that the Demon Lord
could be taken down
by basic hunger.
Ugh...
[groaning]
Well, good morning,
are you awake?
You have no right to ask
me any questions, ma'am.
Would you care to explain
why you're carrying me
under your arm?
When you spot a cute young
girl collapsed on the road,
you take her in!
Look at her.
How can she have such
clear, unwavering eyes?
Anyway, I found you
while I was on a quest,
so I couldn't leave you alone.
[MAO] That may be, but
why do I get the feeling
I would've been safer
if you had left me alone?
[MAO]
Would you just put me down?!
All right. I certainly couldn't
fight while carrying you around.
Huh?
A five-tailed dragon?
So, hey, when you
mentioned a quest...
You sure seem to know a
lot for such a little one.
Here, have some candy.
[MAO]
Not again!
Wait, I don't have
time to eat candy.
Right!
Gaia Gate!
Wow, look at that!
I've recovered quite a bit!
Candy seems to be
surprisingly energizing!
Feeling better, then?
Yep, so let's defeat it already!
I'm afraid I'll
run out of candy.
Wait--I mean, my magic power!
[FEMALE WARRIOR 2A] I don't
know, that's a formidable foe.
Well, yeah, so you just have
to go for its weaknesses.
Go over there and try tickling
the base of its second tail.
If you do that, it'll
calm down right away.
Fine, I'll try it.
Then, we're out of here!
Wait, why are you taking me?!
[FEMALE WARRIOR 2A]
You really saved me today.
It's amazing that you
already have such knowledge
and strength at this age.
[MAO laughs]
Well, but of course I do!
So, considering all of that,
would you ever think
about being a teacher?
A teacher?
That's right, I work
full-time as a teacher
at the Adventurer School.
Would you like to as well?
[MAO] Why should the Demon
Lord train up adventurers
when one of them is for sure
going to become the future Hero?
Sorry, but I don't
think that's really--
Also, the Adventurer School
is run by the kingdom.
Are you serious?!
So, you mean, I would be...
someone with a stable income?
That's right.
Well, you should've said
that in the first place.
I now humbly accept your offer.
[groaning]
Well, hello. May I ask what
you're doing in my bed?
I happen to be looking
after a sick little girl.
How is it this woman keeps
calling me a little girl
with such clear,
unwavering eyes?
Oh, my body feels much lighter.
That's good to hear!
The girls who left when I came
in were worried about you.
They seem like good friends.
They were worried?
She's just like a little baby,
falling asleep when she eats!
It's so cute!
Her complexion is looking
a lot better, as well.
Please take care of
her after we go!
Sure. You can leave
it all to me.
It's my pleasure.
You all really love
Miss Mao, huh?
[GIRLS]
Hm?
[GIRLS giggle]
Interesting.
[FEMALE WARRIOR 2A] That has
to be cold. I should re-heat it.
No thanks.
It's still plenty warm.
[FAI]
"Princess Rona, Fait On!"