[whimpers]
[GIRLS whimpering]
I'm so cold!
And this was supposed
to be a simple quest!
"Just pick a few medicinal
herbs from the mountain."
"Also, there's hardly ever
any snow this time of year,
so it'll be a real easy trip."
What the heck was Teach thinking
when she told us that?!
It's the most snow
I've ever seen!
We're never gonna make it back
home through this blizzard!
At this rate, it's gonna
be our last quest ever!
[ALL whimper]
I'm freezing.
Here's some light, at least.
It's really bright.
Great. Too bad it's not warm.
[ALL]
Yeah.
[gasps] Do you think we
should burn something?
Sure. What can we burn, though?
Uh.
Our clothes?
Hey, Mei? Calm down.
You're right.
We gotta be careful.
When it's this cold,
you can't fall asleep.
You'll die if you do.
Seriously?
If we sleep, we'll die?
Ahh! Wake up, Seira!
Come on, girl!
[gasps] I guess I
nodded off there.
Thank you so much, Yusha!
--[FAI] Wake up, Mei!
--Mei, Don't go to sleep!
[SEIRA]
Open your eyes, Mei!
Don't you dare die!
Whoa!
Man, that was a close one.
You might've just
saved my life, Seira!
What're you doing?!
Wake the heck up,
are you freaking kidding me?
[YUSHA]
I'm awake!
Hey, you guys, stop
falling asleep!
Ow! You don't have to pinch!
Mei, wake up and drink
this tea immediately,
do you understand me?
Blah. Why'm I
drinking bitter tea?
Yusha, no, you have
to open your eyes!
Stop doing that, they're open!
At this rate, we're all
gonna fall asleep!
I know! Hey, everyone!
[GIRLS]
Uh?
Why don't we talk
about something?
If we pick an interesting topic,
that'll help us stay awake!
Oh, I love that!
But, what are we supposed
to talk about?
That's a good question.
Well, how about our
dreams for the future?
Yes! I love that, too!
That sounds fun.
Who should we start with?
Mei! I vote Mei!
Aw, thanks! I'd love to!
[clears throat]
I've had two dreams
for my entire life.
One was going to Tarka Village,
but I already made
that one happen.
Tarka Village was
a blast, wasn't it?
Yeah, and they had some
super yummy food!
The fireworks were pretty, too!
That was the happiest
day I've had
in my entire life
so far, you guys!
Would you like to know what my
second dream has always been?
[ALL]
Yeah. Spill!
I'm glad you asked!
Obviously, it's Cartado.
A complete collection
of every one!
Ancient Cartado
with forbidden spells,
sealed away for centuries
in forgotten ruins!
There's a super rare kind of
Cartado that brings good luck
to its owners. Only one
in every billion monsters
drops it when they're defeated!
Then, of course, there are the
mysterious Cartado that nobody's
ever seen before.
Heirlooms of the royal family!
[MEI]
Guys! There are so many
different kinds of fascinating
Cartado in this world.
Therefore, I want to own
every single one of 'em!
Definitely sounds like you.
Yeah, when I think of
Cartado, I think of Mei.
That sounds like a great goal!
I'd love to see that collection!
[MEI]
And then, once I've gathered
every Cartado in this world,
that's when I'll unleash their
true power for all to see.
At which point, they'll
gain a will of their own.
[ALL]
Huh?
[MEI]
As a result, the Cartado,
with their mind-bogglingly
superior power,
will rule over this realm and
create a brand-new world!
[MEI laughing]
Get ahold of yourself, Mei!
Oh, yeah. The only thing that
matters at all is Cartado.
You don't believe that!
What're you saying?
I don't care how, but wake up!
[MEI gasping]
Can I go next, then?
I want to set out on big
adventures around the world
and try out lots of different
kinds of delicious foods!
For example, did you know
that in the southern seas
there's a certain fish
that's said to contain
seven different flavors?
Then there's the
world's sweetest apple,
the legendary golden apples
of the northern jungle!
And the boar of the eastern
plains that even a thousand
people wouldn't be able
to finish eating!
I wanna snack on
every one of them!
Wow. I've never heard of those.
You have some
impressive knowledge
when it comes to food, Fai.
They all sound so yummy!
--[stomach grumbling]
--[BOTH] Uh?
What? I swear, that wasn't me.
--Then who was it? Huh?
--[stomach grumbling]
[BOTH gasp]
I must eat right now,
or things will get messy.
[YUSHA]
Oh, no, look at Fai!
Let's just feed her
something. Anything!
[FAI growls]
[SEIRA screaming]
You okay, Seira?
I'm used to it.
[laughs] Hey, Seira, what about
your dreams for the future?
Who, me?
Lemme think.
[SEIRA laughing]
[SEIRA]
Wait. I can't say that out loud!
[YUSHA]
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing, I'm totally fine!
[SEIRA] Although... My room is
definitely stressing me out.
Realistically, I'd like
to do something about it
before graduation.
[SEIRA] It started off
so clean and tidy.
How could I ever
let it get this way?
I'll never understand
how it happened.
[SEIRA]
It's a dark mystery.
I think Seira's entered some
intense state of deep thought.
Wonder what her dream is?
That's okay, we can hear
all about Yusha's big dream
while we wait.
[MEI] Hey! You can't fall
asleep, Yusha, remember?
I'm awake, I'm awake.
--I'm awa...
--[MEI] No!
You're obviously
passed out! Come on!
Get up and tell us all
about your big dreams
for the future, Yusha!
Oh, a dream?
I'm pretty sure that's
happening right now.
This is such a
weird dream, you guys!
No! Not that kind of dream,
your future goals!
The future?
I mean, I wanna be
a Hero, of course!
When the Demon Lord
finally revives,
I'll stand up against him all
sassy and without fear!
Then I'll, like, fight them in
all kinds of crazy awesome ways.
But then, once I'm moments
away from defeating them,
my spell will suddenly go
completely out of control.
I bet I'll get blasted off
someplace weird along with
everyone else who happens
to be standing around me.
That really went off the rails
about halfway through.
I guess she's still half-asleep.
Yeah, but it feels disturbingly
realistic, don't you think?
[GIRLS gasp]
[gasps]
[GIRLS yelp]
Um, guys, we'll be crushed!
We need to find a way
to support our shelter!
[SEIRA] I know! I remembered to
bring that long pole this time!
See?
[GIRLS scream]
[SEIRA]
ENDRO!
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmur]
[TOWNSMAN 10A]
Ah! It's the Demon Lord!
[TOWNSWOMAN 10A] Oh, no! The
Demon Lord's finally revived!
The world as we
know it is finished.
[YUSHA yelling]
Uh. Do you think
that could be...?
It is! Oh my gosh, we're saved!
[yells]
Behold our Hero!
The one who drove back
a million of the Demon Lord's
soldiers by herself!
Heralded as the strongest ever
in the history of Heroes!
The Hero among Heroes!
Yulia Chardiet!
Cheese!
That's right! I heard she
defeated a Magic Emperor
sealed in ancient ruins,
right after a magic duel
that lasted seven whole
days and nights!
She's heralded as the strongest
in magic and the sword--
a true Hero among Heroes!
Never forget, you once
saw Yulia Chardiet!
[CHILDREN cheer]
Ta-da!
She looks exactly like my dead
wife did when she was younger!
[YUSHA] Yep! I'm the one
all the fuss is about.
Yulia Chardiet, at your service!
But you can call me Yusha!
[YUSHA]
Pose!
Pose! Pose!
[TOWNSMEN]
We love you! We love Yusha!
We love Yusha!
We love Yusha... Woo!
[YUSHA] Everyone,
thank you for your support!
Gonna go defeat him now!
Wish me luck!
Ha!
[yelling]
Ah! Hey, I caught it!
Yes! I did it! I finally got one
of the rare rainbow coelacanth
that has the seven
distinct flavors!
So, guess what? It's time
to chow down... Forever!
This is the best thing
that's ever happened!
Ah! Shoot!
Oh!
Thank you so much-- Oh, my...
[MEI gasping]
[MEI]
Ba-dump!
[MEI laughs]
[bell tolls]
I just couldn't be happier!
Heh, heh... Here we go,
Demon Lord!
[MEI laughing]
Darling.
Oh gosh, look at that;
it's so nice.
[SEIRA]
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la! ♪
I just love how sparkling
clean my room has been
looking these days!
Although, unfortunately, my
shoulders have been aching
like crazy because of
my big, heavy breasts.
Ahh... Wait.
That'll never happen!
[SEIRA gasps]
Was that a dream?
Uh...
Yeah, it figures.
What about the others?
Uh! A monster?
[gasps]
What is that?
Uh... Yusha! Fai! Mei!
Heh, heh. Prepare yourself,
bad Demon Lord!
Nom, nom, nom...
Everything's so yummy!
I'm so happy right now.
Wake up! All of you! C'mon!
[SEIRA gasping]
Her Monster encyclopedia!
A carta eater.
It sneaks up on adventurers
at night, gives them a dream,
then lulls them into
a deeper sleep.
So, normal methods of waking
someone up won't work here.
What do we have? Anything?
[gasps] Yes!
A Dream Dive Cartado that lets
you enter the dream world!
Lead me into
their heads, please!
Dive!
Everyone, hold on!
Am I inside everyone's
dreams, then?
[gasps] Yusha! Fai! Mei!
[YUSHA]
Prepare yourself! Ha!
[TOWNSMEN]
We love you! We love Yusha!
We love Yusha!
[TOWNSMAN 10D] She looks
exactly like my dead wife did
when she was younger!
[belches] So good! Thank you!
All I want in the world
is a new Cartado!
[GIRLS laughing]
[gasps] Well that was weird,
why was I frozen?
Uh. Everyone!
You have to open your eyes!
You're in the middle of a dream!
This is a problem.
I've gotta stop it, fast!
The thing is, even if it
is a dream, as the Hero,
I can't ignore the Demon Lord!
Listen, I know that
sounds cool and heroic,
but no one is asking you
for that right now!
[SEIRA]
Don't talk with your mouth full!
I know, but it's
so freakin' tasty!
There was no reason to make a
point to brag and tell me that!
[MEI]
Maybe this is a dream.
So? What's the problem?
[SEIRA]
I knew it, Mei!
You understand what's
going on right now, correct?
[MEI] Well, let's
slow down for a minute.
Huh?
I mean, who cares if we
are in the dream world?
Is it really such
a terrible thing?
[gasping]
Look. Just look at those two.
Yusha's fighting the
Demon Lord as we speak.
[YUSHA]
Prepare yourself! Ha!
[TOWNSMEN]
We love you! We love Yusha!
We love Yusha!
[TOWNSMAN 10D] She looks
exactly like my dead wife did
when she was younger!
So, guess what?
It's time to chow down...
[MEI] Of course Fai is overjoyed
to eat her fill.
It's buono !
Those two truly couldn't
be any happier right now.
Have you considered it
might not be our place
to interfere with a
friend's happiness?
I...
I guess not.
There's plenty of room
for you, as well, Seira!
You should come be happy
with the rest of us.
What's that Cartado?
Oh, this one just happens
to make breasts bigger.
[SEIRA growls]
Listen up, that may be,
but even if they're
bigger in my dreams,
I will still be empty inside!
My darling!
Fine then, if you all
just flat refuse to wake up,
then I'm gonna have to
destroy this whole world!
Ah! You just smashed
our dream worlds!
Sei, why the heck
would you do this?!
I am so not ready
to face reality yet!
Would you guys just
wake up already?!
Let's deal with this
by combining
all three of our dreams!
Good call! Then we can
stand against Seira,
with the power of
three people's dreams!
Yeah, I third that!
[YUSHA]
Done!
[FAI]
Yeah!
[MEI]
In!
Here's my dream of
defeating the Demon Lord!
My dream of eating
delicious food!
[MEI]
And my dream of rare Cartado!
[GIRLS yell]
[SEIRA]
This is...
[YUSHA] It's like... the
crystallization of our dreams!
--[FAI] Yummy.
--Demon Lord...
Cartado!
It's "Yummy"? Seriously?
Wow! You're right, it is yummy!
I told you!
Gimme some, too!
Wait, lemme try!
[YUSHA]
It's so good!
[MEI]
I can't stop eating this!
That was perfectly delicious!
Can't believe I'm full!
I can't believe we
ended up eating it all!
We sure did, though.
[YUSHA] Wait! Wasn't that the
crystallization of our dreams?
Seira ate it all right up,
didn't she?
That's a pretty gutsy move,
eating other people's
dreams, you know.
[SEIRA] Stop talking as if I'm
the only one who had some!
[GIRLS laugh]
[SEIRA]
Wait!
Not so fast!
[CARTA EATER 10A screams]
[ALL]
Huh?!
[gasping]
[ALL scream]
[screaming]
[YUSHA]
Huh...?
Where are we?
At least it seems like
we're actually awake now.
Seira, that was
pretty mean of you.
I was hoping to eat so many
more yummy things too.
[MEI] I'll never have another
dream so wonderful again!
Would you shut up? Now, look!
All of it was this
little thing's fault!
A monster, huh?
How'd he get here?
Hold on, isn't that
a carta eater?
[SEIRA]
Yes.
[FAI, YUSHA]
Carta eater?
[SEIRA MEI]
It puts adventurers to sleep,
and then it eats up
all their Cartado.
It's a pretty
terrifying monster.
Wait!
What?!
That thing really got us good!
It sounds to me like Mei
might have found herself
a new "worst enemy."
What's crazy is that if
Seira hadn't woken us up...
Then that stupid little
monster would've eaten
every last one of 'em!
I see.
We owe you one, Seira!
Don't worry, you don't
owe me anything.
After all, isn't it our job to
save our fellow party-members?
[SEIRA grunting]
Seira is the coolest ever.
She's the only one who wasn't
taken in by her own dream!
That can be really
difficult to do, too.
The carta eater makes people
dream of their deepest desires.
So, it's hard to overcome it
unless you happen to have some
rare and formidable willpower.
You truly are incredible, Seira!
Yeah, of course I am.
Now, it stopped snowing.
You all ready to go home?
Heck yeah!
Time to clear the quest!
Let's do it!
[SEIRA]
Still, though...
I really should clean my room.
[MAO]
"Final Dead End!"