Rona, my dear.
Yes, what is it, Father?
[KING 5A] As princess of
Lapanesta Kingdom,
it's important to
remember your duty.
Moreover, do not
forget your dream.
I will never forget. I promise.
You can entrust it
all to me, Father.
[SOLDIER 5A]
Open the gate!
Princess Rona Pricipa
O'Lapanesta is departing!
This journey will
lead me straight to you.
I've waited so long
for this day.
I'm coming for you, Hero!
[YUSHA] And out of nowhere,
the evil god once sealed away
in an underwater temple
was resurrected!
[SEIRA]
When we heard about this,
the Hero's Party set about
to protect the world!
[FAI] We found that wicked
underwater god,
and we started an awesome
battle to teach him a lesson!
[MEI] When it seemed like
we might be losing,
the Hero's Sword began to glow,
and it put a stop to
him once and for all!
[YUSHA] Maintaining world peace
was a complete success!
It was a happy ending!
Let me get this straight.
At the behest of a
mackerel you saved,
you found an evil god
that was sealed away,
then defeated him, thus
saving the world, right?
--[YUSHA] That's right!
--[MEI] You got it!
That so?
Well, that's quite a story.
Stop wasting my time!
[GIRLS]
What?!
Man. Why does Miss Mao
have to be so mean?
I can't believe that
she thinks we're lying.
I'm actually taking
your side on this one.
There's no denying that
we defeated an evil god.
I suppose we need a
witness, or a wet-ness.
I feel a little gill-ty that he
lives far, but we should ask
that Mackerelman to
give his testi-moray.
Yusha, that tale you
told us was interesting!
It reminded me of stories I read
about Heroes when I was a kid.
I look forward to more!
[GIRLS grumble]
Great, so now it's been
downgraded to nothing better
than a fictional picture
book for children.
You know what?
Uh! Yeah?
I'm starting to think nobody
actually recognizes you
as the real Hero.
[YUSHA gasping]
Yusha, keep on living in denial,
but reality will hunt
you down like an animal.
It's just like struggling
to survive in the wild.
But it's not fair because I
actually am the real Hero!
Oh! I can prove it
with the Hero's Sword!
Uh oh.
Look! It's rust!
The legendary Hero's Sword
is in terrible shape!
Yes, that's what happens when
you swing a sword around
at the beach in the salty air.
You've picked up some
barnacle hitch-hikers.
Oh, yeah.
Have you ever heard the creepy
legend about the guy
who had barnacles growing
out of his knees?
[yelps]
It was a spooky night.
There was this adventurer
that fell down a cliff.
--Crusted over by barnacle--
--...I don't want to hear it!
Please stop!
Aww. Do those critters
taste good?
[YUSHA laughs]
She's chowin' down on 'em.
Hey, wait.
Aren't barnacles in the same
family as shrimp and crabs?
I'm droolin'. Huh? Mei,
what is it? You okay?
There's some kind of
commotion out there.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[FEMALE STUDENT 5A]
They're knights!
[MALE STUDENT 5A]
How cool!
Oh, wow!
[FAI] Whoa! What a
magnificent carriage!
[SEIRA] "Magnificent"
doesn't begin to cover it.
That carriage bears the crest
of the Lapanesta Kingdom.
Uh? The Lapanesta Kingdom?
You've never
heard of that, huh?
[MAO] Seriously?
We went over this in class.
The Lapanesta Kingdom is
the oldest kingdom around,
and it's also the only one
here on Naral Island.
The Hero and her party--
Look! Someone's coming!
[gasps] So much fluff!
Fluffy hair, fluffy dress,
fluffy everything! Fluffy!
So cute!
How do you do, everyone?
Greetings from the
Lapanesta Kingdom.
I am the princess,
Rona Pricipa O'Lapanesta.
[STUDENTS murmur]
[gasps]
[MAO]
Move it! A-hem.
You have traveled
a long distance
to grace us with a visit.
We are humbly honored,
Princess. My name is--
Aww, look what a good girl
you are greeting me properly.
That's earned you
a special candy treat!
[MAO]
Uh...?
Here.
[STUDENTS]
Been there.
[MAO grumbling]
I'm deeply grateful...
to receive... this?
Oh. I'm so sorry for that.
I didn't know you were
a teacher here!
Don't worry.
It happens all the time.
But anyway, what business
could you possibly have
that brings you here to our
little adventurer school?
[gasps] I have come here
to meet the Hero.
Huh? To meet the Hero?
Yes! When I heard that
the Hero of this era
had been born. I simply
couldn't wait to come and--
[clears throat]
Actually, I'm here as a
representative of my Kingdom.
Oh, I understand.
This era's Hero.
I guess you could say
that there's a hero,
but there also isn't a hero?
Of course there is one,
except not really.
But if there isn't one,
then shouldn't we
ask ourselves where
a Hero comes from
and what the word "hero"
actually means?
[RONA]
Uhh...
[MAO grumbles]
[YUSHA]
Behold! Your Hero's right here!
[gasps]
[STUDENTS scream]
Whoa, what the heck?!
[gasps]
Bursting with courage,
Yulia Chardiet!
The healing priest,
I'm Ellenoar Seiran!
Stuffed full of food and
dreams, the name's Fai Fai!
Collecting five Cartado
a day, Mather Enderstto!
[GIRLS] Together,
we are the Hero's Party!
[CHIBI 1A]
Ah-ha!
Nice work. That went
much smoother this time.
Ha. It was totally worth using
the Special Effects Cartado
that I've been holding on to
for the right moment.
[footsteps]
[GIRLS]
Uh?
No, please don't hurt us!
[MAO] Well, when you're
exploding things around
a princess, it's no surprise
the national authorities
feel like they need to step in.
[cries] Miss Mao, do something!
Jeez, what an idiotic Hero.
Pardon me, ma'am, but did
you just say "Hero"?
Um. Yep. That's her.
Huh?
I know, what a total
embarrassment, huh?
Oh. But wait. Isn't that a girl?
I don't wanna get skewered!
Princess?
[YUSHA gasps]
I've longed for this moment.
To finally meet my Hero!
Huh?
[RONA] Many, many years ago
on Naral Island,
after the Demon Lord appeared
and the first Hero defeated him,
the Hero's bravery helped
him to found a nation.
And that nation was named
the Lapanesta Kingdom.
For generations, we have aided
and supported the Hero.
It is our duty in the
Lapanesta Kingdom,
which traces its blood
back to the first Hero.
And now, sitting before
us is a new Hero!
And her name is Yulia Chardiet!
[STUDENTS chattering]
This treasure was entrusted
to the royal family.
A gift from the first Hero.
"Dark Purple Fae Truth."
Many believe that it
holds the power
to see the truth of all things.
[MEI gasps] One of the
"Seven Founding Heavens."
One of seven original cards that
form Cartado's very foundation!
Amazing! They're considered
the inspiration for
modern Cartado,
which means what she's holding
isn't just a legendary rare,
it's a mythically rare card I
never thought I'd get to see it!
[FAI]
Whoa there take it easy.
Hero, step forward.
[YUSHA]
Mm?! Okay.
Huh?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[ding]
Wha--?
Good! Herodom confirmed!
[STUDENTS]
That's it?!
Yulia Chardet.
In the name of the
Lapanesta Kingdom,
I hereby recognize you
as the True Hero.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[MALE WARRIOR 1A]
That's amazing!
You are unquestionably
the real Hero of this era.
I knew it! I'm so happy!
Wow. This is awesome.
We can say we're the
Hero's Party with pride.
Now people won't give us those
weird fake smiles anymore!
[FAI] I have a very strong urge
to crack a joke right now.
[MEI] Watching her cry
is making me uncomfortable.
Um, Princess? I promise
you I'll do my very best!
Huh?
Please, from now on
call me Rona.
Sure, you got it, Rona!
Keep it up, kiddo!
[MAO] But I guess this has
nothing to do with me
since I gave up on
being the Demon Lord.
All right! I'm ready to search
high and low
for that Demon Lord
and show 'em what
a real Hero can do!
My, you're fired up!
Although, the Hero
and the Demon Lord
are bound together by
the deepest of ties.
That means... They could be
closer than you think.
Huh?
[RONA] It's great to see
the Hero has close friends...
[MAO]
Wait, is the princess...? No...
Heh. ENDRO!
[FEMALE STUDENT 5B]
Good Morning to you, Hero!
[FEMALE STUDENT 5C] Whoa,
it's the Hero! Good Morning!
Oh, you better hurry up so you
won't be late for class, Hero.
Yeah!
Hey there, Hero, I've been
meaning to thank you
for helping me find my
Lancelot the other day!
I bet finding a cat
was no problem at all
for a Hero like yourself, eh?
[YUSHA laughing]
This's nuts!
For the first time, everyone
is calling me "Hero"!
Heh. I personally enjoy
the sound of their praise.
Yes, I do, too!
I was beginning to lose hope,
but now we're
officially recognized as
the Hero's Party, aren't we?
Right? Right?
Right! Since everyone
recognizes it,
let's be the best heroes
we can be! Yeah!
No. Unacceptable!
Ah! Rona!
Ah, jeez! You startled me!
I had no idea you were
standing there.
[RONA clears throat]
Sometime last night,
while you were all in
the Hero's room talking,
I eavesdropped on you
right around the time
you decided on your
plans for lunch today.
Nice work, that'll save
us time explaining.
[gasps] Hold on!
Are we really overlooking the
fact that she was eavesdropping?
You mustn't settle for
mere compliments.
You are the... Hero!
We must think bigger!
These students
should worship you.
They should show you
how much they love you!
Um. Love me?
They have no idea, do they?
It's awful.
They are so fortunate to live
in the same age as you,
and in the same Kingdom as you!
We really need to get
ahead of this thing
and build up your foundation.
--First...
--Uh. Hey, Rona?
Yes, that's it! Don't you
worry about a thing!
I promise everyone will know
what a great Hero you are!
[RONA laughs]
[ALL gasping]
[YUSHA]
What is all this?
[ALL gasping]
[MAO]
What's gotten into you four?
You look like a wyvern that's
been hit by a fireball.
Oh, Miss Mao.
G'morning! Just curious.
Do you know what
this festival is?
Yes, this is--
[RONA] It's a celebration
that I created.
It's called the "Hero Festival"!
You did all this?
That's right. Everybody
loves going to festivals,
so by throwing one for you
I can make the whole school, and
eventually, all of Naral Island
see how fortunate they are
to have someone like you
as their Hero!
Thank you, Rona.
The princess's knights and we
staff members worked overnight
on her very specific
instructions.
[yawns]
You did all of this
just for Yusha?
That's awfully generous of you.
Yes. But honestly, there
isn't a thing in the world
that I wouldn't do for the Hero!
Really? Thanks so much!
To know that I've pleased
you makes me so happy!
You are most welcome.
I get the feeling the princess
kinda made you do this,
but you've really outdone
yourself with this, Miss Mao.
[MAO] Anything for my
cute-as-a-button students!
And the truth?
[MAO]
The adventurer school?
It's run by the Royal Family.
That takes all
the joy out of it.
[FAI] So even though adventurers
have their freedom,
we're all just
convenient servants
of bureaucratic politicians
in the end.
Now then, it's time for us
to enjoy the festival!
Won't you please join us
Ellenoar, Fai, and Mather?
Let's go!
[CHIBI 1A chirps]
Rona sure is exuberant when you
consider that she's a princess.
I'm a little speechless.
She certainly is impressive.
I'm just amazed that she
remembered everyone's name
because I almost forget
them, like, all the time!
Huh?! That's what you
find amazing?!
Ah! Whatever, let's
catch up to them!
[FAI, MEI]
Yeah!
Uh. Good grief.
They're all acting like a
bunch of little children.
It's kinda funny knowing
that she's the Hero.
[WARRIOR 2A]
There you are, Mao.
Look at what I bought
especially for you.
The cotton candy
pomuroon you wanted!
I bet you're gonna
gobble these up so fast
that they make your
mouth all sticky-icky!
Oh, or maybe, you'd like
to eat these together?
Like this.
Our faces getting
closer and closer
until I feel your
soft, pink cheeks
pressing against mine
as you devour--
Huh? Where'd she go?
[FAI, MEI]
Munch!
[laughs sheepishly]
[ALL]
Yum!
Heh, heh...
[ALL]
Lick. Lick! Lick.
[yelps]
What do you think?
I put together these
stalls to promote you,
so I hope you're
having a good time!
Absolutely! I can feel all
the promotion. I think?
Yes! The Yusha Cakes were great!
The figure is wearing
pink underwear.
I loved it!
[YUSHA grunts]
You guys are so mean!
I'm sorry. But everyone's
having fun!
Just look at our classmates!
[STUDENTS chattering, laughing]
Huh...
Well. I guess it's okay, then!
I'm glad you're feeling
optimistic about this.
That's one of Yusha's
best traits!
[laughs]
And it's exactly how
a Hero should be.
[YUSHA laughing]
Anyway...
It's time for the festival's
main event! Let go, everyone!
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KNIGHT 5A]
Look over there!
It's the Demon Lord's castle!
Seira, Fai, Mei, at long
last we have arrived!
[KNIGHT 5B]
Demon Lord!
I shall smash thee to
smithereens with my hammer!
[KNIGHT 5C]
I'm Fai and I'm always hungry!
[KNIGHT 5D] I bet I can find
some legendary rare Cartado
at the Demon Lord's castle!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[YUSHA, FAI, MEI laughing]
This is how they see me?
A musclebound priest?
I think my hard work paid off,
and that everyone now
sees your true nature.
Wouldn't you agree?
Great job, Rona! Thank you
so much for everything!
I'm so humbled.
Hero? You're so kind!
[YUSHA]
Sip, sip.
So yummy! Heh! I was just
starting to get thirsty.
Thanks for getting us some tea.
I should tell you. I've
always admired the Hero,
I have ever since I
was a little girl.
Huh?
[RONA] My heart would
race thinking about
the Hero's adventures.
It filled me with excitement,
and I would think to myself:
"What if the real Hero
were to suddenly appear?"
And so, I would
dream about becoming
the Hero's bride one day.
It still doesn't feel real to me
that I actually got to
meet the Hero like this!
You have noticed that
we're both women, right?
When it comes to love,
that does not matter.
The law is something
I can deal with.
Ohh...
My Hero, Yusha, please allow
me to be by your side.
[YUSHA]
Mm...
[MAO panting]
Aw... My face is all goopy and
sticky from that dessert.
I gotta hand it to that
princess for keeping up
with a Demon Lord on the run.
Oh! A fancy napkin!
[MAO]
What in the world?!
This is no napkin!
[RED BULLDOZER 5A growls]
I guess the princess is
a big deal if she managed
to get a real monster
for the festival.
I shouldn't be too worried since
red bulldozers are docile
monsters, just so
long as you don't...
...pull... their... tails.
[sighs]
[CROWD screams]
[YUSHA]
Huh? Oh my.
What?
That must be the red bulldozer
I had prepared for
the play later today!
Huh?!
[RED BULLDOZER 5A growls]
[MAO]
Ahh...
I'm sorry, Rona,
but I have to go now.
We can talk later!
Please don't leave me!
My knights are already
guarding the festival,
and the teachers are here, too!
A Hero shouldn't have
to trouble themselves
over little things such as this!
Yeah. But I'm still
gonna go anyway.
And are you're going
because you're the Hero?
That's not the whole reason...
...exactly. Let's see.
It's uh...
I guess it's because I'm me!
[gasps]
[laughs]
All right, wish me luck!
[RONA] It's not just
because you're the Hero.
It's who you are?
[heartbeat]
Oh my. What's this?
I feel...
[CROWD screaming]
[RONA]
What...?
[STUDENTS murmur]
All right. Please welcome Rona,
our new transfer student.
Hi, Rona!
Hi! I'm Rona, and I
belong to the Hero!
[STUDENTS chatter]
Everyone, I hope we
can all get along.
As for you--I hope
we get along, too!
Looking forward to class.
This is but another fate
laid forth by the world.
[MAO gasps]
This is getting weird.
Who is she?
[RONA laughs]
[MAO] "One Room, 100 Square
Feet, Demon Lord Included!"