I don't think I've been this far out before.
Oh, really? You gotta be up early tomorrow?
No I don't.
Good, then let's go a little bit farther.
Th‐there's a spot up ahead with a beautiful view.
I don't care for this thing.
Yeah well, y'know, you might wanna go
ahead and put it on, just to be safe.
Hey, what are you doing?
The vital organs are ruined.
My host body will die soon.
I'll use the man.
I see. The belt does serve a purpose.
My only choice is to relocate to this man's body.
There should be no difference in controlling a male host.
Sever the head...
fuse with the host... and regenerate...
It must all be done in an instant.
It feels strange...
I need to move...
C'mon, move...
Ah! Oh, crap! I'm gonna be late!
Why didn't you wake me up?!
You slept as long as you did
because your body needed the rest.
If I had woken you up, I would
deprive you of energy. It's a good thing.
Yeah, yeah.
And of course, your well‐being is also my well‐being.
Interesting...
it would appear you two are conjoined.
Ah man, what's that even s'pos'ta mean?
I'm not certain, but the reason could lie in
the network of your nerves and bodily fluids
that are linking my body to your brain.
Huh?!
It's possible your brain may be undergoing
some kind of change as well as your body.
Ryoko Tamiya was probably able to sense it, and
noticed something about you that seemed inhuman.
She thinks I'm not a human?
The only thing not human about me's you.
I'm not so sure.
It would not surprise me if you had changed
somehow, particularly at the psychological level.
Going to sleep now...
Hey, wait a second!
We're "conjoined"?
Ever so slightly.
I won't be killing you after all.
No, there's nothing wrong with me.
Something is just... Something is different.
You know, Shinichi, you've changed recently.
I'm not turning into one of them!
I'm not gonna kill and eat people.
Huh?
Hey! I thought I said stand up!
You like that, bitch?! Get some!
Nagai!
Stop it!
You got a problem?
C'mon guys, you need to leave him alone all right.
Shinichi?
And why's that?
Look, I don't know what's going on here,
but I thinks he's had enough.
Heh...
Got anything else you wanna say, Four‐Eyes?
I'm thinkin' the little shit wants another one.
Just forget it. It's kinda pitiful.
Look pal, we've got some business
with your boyfriend here, so get lost.
One thing I don't understand about the
human psyche is the notion of "self‐sacrifice."
Doing something to assist another
being, at a cost to oneself, is unnatural.
I do no see the benefit in this at all.
The human psyche...
C'mon, get up, asshole.
We're just gettin' started.
That's it!
Human beings are different from parasites!
Hey! I said to stop it!
It's not much of a fight when
you have someone outnumbered!
Yo, dude...
You sure you wanna do this? Hmm?
Yeah, I do.
Might've been a bad idea...
This what you wanted?
Don't you think you're overdoing it a little?
Not yet.
You heard the dumbass, he was askin' for it right?
Oh, no, Migi's not gonna know what this is about!
All right that's enough!
It's kinda lame to pick on someone so weak and sad.
Must be your lucky day.
Mind your own business. It's less painful.
Ah!
Wha...
What... What are you?
Come on, let's get outta here.
Hey there, Nagai, you doing okay?
Jesus Christ, man, you crazy?
Maybe... That was probably pretty stupid, huh?
But hey, that's the kinda stuff that
separates us from the animals, right?
Hmm?
Oh, my God, what happened to you?
Don't worry, it's nothing. I'm okay.
I asked him that, too.
And he wouldn't tell me either.
D'you get in a fight, or, uh...
Hey, Shinichi.
Nagai just got through tellin' me.
He said you took on Mitsuo's whole crew.
I wouldn't say I took them on.
They killed me. Look at my face.
Those guys have been doing more
and more crap like that lately.
If they try anything else, you let me know, okay?
Oh, sure.
Uh... It's you!
So I guess you have a girlfriend?
What do you want?
Why didn't you run away earlier?
Huh? I just couldn't...
You barely even know that guy and stood
up for him, and you got your ass kicked.
This guy's not quite right is he?
Do what? What's that supposed to mean?
Let's go.
I can see through you!
You can pretend to be all self‐righteous,
but I know that you're up to something!
What's her deal?
I dunno.
Dammit, Kana...
Stop it!
Shinichi, help!
Murano!
Shinichi!
There you are, you piece‐a‐shit.
Just let her go! Come on!
Nah, I don't think so.
Go on home; we'll take care of her.
What?
Ow, that hurts!
Shinichi, no!
I said go!
Please, stop it!
Y'ain't actin' like a frickin' hero this time!
Face it, you can't do a goddamn thing.
Shinichi...
No not now, Migi.
You can go back to sleep.
Shinichi...
I can take care of this.
For your reference, I will rate each of them by strength.
If your rating is a ten, then he's an 18.
The one to the right is a 13,
and the others are 14 and 12.
Migi, why are you telling me all this?
Even dogs and cats are able to evaluate the
strengths and weaknesses of their opponents.
Animals instinctively avoid fights they cannot win.
Yeah, so what's your point?
Leave him alone!
Well, sometimes a human can't back down from a fight.
There's a difference between humans and animals.
Migi, I don't have much feeling in my hand!
Give me full control!
Sorry, you got something to say, you'll have'ta speak up!
Man, why doesn't he just give up?
You are gonna let her go!
Or else!
Wait! No, Migi, stay outta this!
"Or else," what?
You'll run home and tell your mommy?
I, uh, think that's enough, Mitsuo.
Kana...
Well, well, look what we have here.
Kamijo, Nagai!
Ah, yes, the majority overpowering the minority.
These humans actually make much
more sense than you do, Shinichi.
Looks like it's time for some payback, you son of a bitch.
You think cause you brought
some friends you've got a chance?
You've made a big mistake.
SHUT UP!
Hmm... The male genitalia are
actually quite different from the female.
I can't seem to control them very well.
Something's wrong, I can't move.
Damn! It's rejecting me!
I can no longer merge with a body of the opposite sex.
I must find a woman.
Leaving the urban area was a mistake.
I must find a new host and relocate.
Look, it's not like I can't walk or anything.
I'm fine, really.
Uh, no, you're not.
I'm really sorry.
There's nothing that you need to apologize for.
Oww, ow!
Oh, huh? Your right hand isn't even scratched.
Cause I mean, your left hand
sure got messed up pretty badly.
Ah... How 'bout that?
Tell me... Do you think that I'm weird?
Do I seem normal to you?
Oh, no, you are not normal at all.
I'm not?
Well, you're kinda cool.
You risked yourself to help a friend.
Not many "normal" people out there would do that.
Is that s'posta be a compliment?
Of course.
I've never known anyone who would try
something like that, knowing you couldn't win.
You did a really good thing.
Oh, okay.
My parents are out of town right now...
Do you maybe wanna stay over?
Mmm... No, thanks...
I should go.
Very disappointing.
I'd hoped I'd get the chance to see humans mate.
Oh, go to sleep.
Who are you talking to?
You followed me home?
I just came to apologize.
Oh, uh...
Okay, then.
A truce?
Well, at the very least, WE don't have a problem, do we?
Um...
Yeah...
Sorry, I'm really... tired.
You should be careful when it comes to that female.
It seems she is able to sense, however slightly,
wavelengths that should only be perceptible to parasites.
But she is human, right?
I've noticed Murano's also a very perceptive person.
But THIS girl is on a whole different level.
You should stay away from her.
Yeah...
Wow, this is beautiful!
Yeah, kinda makes all that rushin'
around to get here worthwhile doesn't it?
We should come back here.
And bring Shinichi with us!
He's never far from your mind, is he?
Nobuko!
Your diet appears to be unbalanced.
You don't even know what this tastes like.
Your mother always prepares
nutritionally appropriate meals.
Well, I can eat like that again tomorrow.
It's from a public phone.
Shinichi?
Yeah, Dad?
Y‐your mother...
Uh... what's wrong?
Your... your mom...
I'm going to the police.
I'll get that damned monster if it's the last thing I do!
Wait, Dad?! A monster?!
"A monster"? It can't be...
But... but Mom...
Shinichi, what is it?
Dad! Mom!
What's going on? What is this place?
We're in no rush.
We'll just decide where to stop as we go along.
It'll be nice to just relax and take it easy.
Dad, where's Mom?
That goddamn monster!
She's not a monster, she's... Mom!
Shinichi...
MOM!
Come on, Dad, you gotta call me back.
I gotta figure out a way to find them!
Shinichi, you really need to get some sleep.
"A monster..."
That's exactly what Dad said on the phone.
I know that can only mean one thing.
Hmm... Hold on, Shinichi.
I'm detecting one of my kind nearby.
And it's coming directly toward us.
This is all your fault.
I was against them taking the trip in the first place.
But you said they'd be safe; you said it would be fine!
I never said that it would be "fine."
I merely pointed out that, in terms of probability...
Shut up! I should've told them about what was
really going on when you showed up in the first place!
I understand there's a lot
you'd like to discuss right now,
but I need you to focus on the
battle that's about to commence.
No, you won't need a weapon this time.
I will eliminate it before it's able to
determine whether or not we are friend or foe.
I can't face this thing unarmed.
I'm so full of hate right now, I'm going crazy.
Those damn monsters!
It stopped moving...
It's just outside.
How could it unlock the door?
It's you!
Mom?
So, then the male has not yet returned.
What's that Mom?
That's not your mother.
You know that.
Uh, welcome back!
Mom, are you doing okay?
What's the matter?
This is a unique situation.
A merge with the hand is highly unusual.
One of my kind has taken over
your mother's head, Shinichi.
Huh? My hand?
Yeah, I'm so sorry, Mom.
I mean, I really wanted to tell
you about it earlier, but I...
I just couldn't. I, uh...
I mean, it's kinda crazy, right?
No, Shinichi, she's not...
JUST SHUT UP!!
Am I to assume the male is now dead?
I see. Then I must go back and confirm
whether or not he's actually been eliminated.
The knife, it's in my way. Put it down.
So, yeah, I know, having a
talking right hand is pretty weird.
I mean hard to believe right?
Just the hand? How unlucky.
Without taking the head, you
find yourself under human control.
Stop it, Mom!
I'll tell you everything I've been hiding from you!
Just, please, stop talking like that!
Shinichi, you have to see what's happening.
Your mother is already...
Shut up! Just shut up!
You don't know what you're talking about!
Shinichi!
If you keep talking, I swear I'll cut you off!
Please, Mom!
It's okay...
You remember it right?
The scar on your arm?
Every time I see it, I feel guilty.
And, Mom, I...
I wanna apologize.
Shinichi!
Mom...
Next time: "The Sun Also Rises"