I think I drank too much!
Well, I should probably get going.
Now, hold on!
What's the big rush, huh? Sit down.
Hey, y'know, you're a lot cuter than Shiro said.
You're embarrassing me.
Ha-ha, I mean it, seriously.
Have you heard about that hair thingy?
Hold still...
Sorry about that! I pulled out three by acci...
No...
This is awkward.
It was the hair that gave me away.
I could use some help.
I don't normally eat meat containing alcohol.
I owe you... I owe you my life.
I can't believe he'd do something like that.
How do Shinichi and I seem similar to you?
I mean, whatever it is you think you're sensing,
it could be some kind of "wavelengths"
being broadcast by dangerous jerks like him.
Don't tell me Shinichi...
Huh?
Nobody likes being snuck up on.
Oh, sorry!
Look, if you really want one of
my hairs, you can help yourself.
Oh, uh... Okay, thank you.
You happy now?
Oh...
Wait up!
Hey, I remember you warned me
before about hanging around Shimada.
Does that mean you already knew about
what he was capable of from the start?
No, I... I didn't.
I guess not.
I mean who would be friends with a mass murderer, right?
What's with the serious look?
She has a special gift.
Maybe I could go ahead and tell her everything.
No, I shouldn't, not while Migi's still awake.
Shinichi, I know what you're thinking.
But don't do it.
That female is no ally of mine.
Nor is she an ally of yours.
Your name is Kana, isn't it?
Huh? Yeah, yeah that's right!
You said that you have some strange
telepathic ability to sense my presence,
but even if you feel like I'm close by,
you should not try to approach me.
Why not?
Because you might run into something else instead.
What? Like a monster?
Yeah.
Now why would you say that?
I mean, you're a normal human being, aren't you, Shinichi?
Yeah, of course I'm a normal human.
Hmm... Well, if my senses do happen
to point me in the direction of someone,
I already know what it is I need to do.
I'll pluck out a hair to see if they're safe or not.
No, Kana! You cannot do that!
You okay?
Ah, I'm sorry.
It's just really dangerous, you know.
Does that mean you're worried about me?
That makes me kinda happy.
Shinichi...
I need to talk to you.
Ah, I have to get going! I'm really sorry. See ya.
Huh?
Oh, hello there.
Um, hello.
Shinichi, I don't want you to speak to that person again.
I can't do that.
You know if I just walk away from her,
then eventually she's gonna get into trouble.
Perhaps, but I believe the way you talk to
her has revealed more than enough already.
I'll be careful.
I hope so.
I, um... I know it's strange to
ask you this out of the blue, but...
Ask me what?
Do you... think that Shinichi's
been acting a little different lately?
I've actually only met him a few times.
I'm not so sure if I would really be a fair judge.
I mean when you first met him versus right now.
Did you two have a fight?
You like him, right? I can kinda tell.
Look, he's just different somehow, okay?
Not so much when we're talking, but when...
Mm-hmm...
I... I mean, he did save my life!
He saved your life?! So you mean
you have dreams like that, too?
Huh? Dreams?
Ah! Uh...
I guess I just don't see it.
I get the feeling he's been this way all along, you know?
He's got this kind of intensity about him.
Well, if you don't stop acting so
mopey, then you're gonna lose him for sure.
Looks like I might still have a chance!
I'll be back in ten minutes.
Understood, but, uh...
Couldn't you have worn something
a bit more... normal looking?
It'll just get dirty.
What do you want?
How many are inside?
Are you kidding me? You some kinda moron?
Get outta here before you get hurt.
Ah, of course, you yakuza are quite aggressive.
Okay, Short Shorts,
all these new anti-gang laws are cute and all,
but it won't keep you from getting
your ass beat, you understand?!
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
We got company!
What's wrong? Let's go.
That's one.
Damn you! You're a dead man!
Two...
Heh, gotcha.
That's it asshole.
That makes three.
What?!
Holy shit!
This guy's not dead?!
They managed three hits.
I guess that's about right.
What the hell?!
What's this all about, man?
It's an experiment.
We wanted to determine exactly how successful we
would be against a group heavily armed with weapons.
No, please!
My god what the hell happened over there?
That guy, his head got bashed in!
I'm pretty sure I heard some gunshots.
Yeah, me too!
Hey, he's getting away!
Hey, get back here!
What the...
Where'd he go? He was right in front of us.
Let's get outta here.
I don't want to get in the middle of some damn gang war.
Maybe you're right.
But don't you think we should at
least call the cops or somethin'?
Nah, I'm sure somebody already did.
What is it?
Nothing. It's just, you're quite different from before.
Mass murder at a gang headquarters...
It says 22 people were massacred,
every single yakuza member there.
That's crazy.
It's like it keeps getting
worse out there every single day.
Yeah...
Was that a parasite?
No, they wouldn't kill like
that unless they needed to feed.
The Metropolitan Police Department has
just held an emergency press conference.
They made the announcement that they will
soon be releasing security camera footage of
a male suspect fleeing the scene.
That may have been a bit much.
It was a very successful exercise. Very.
Shinichi, hey!
I'm glad you're here. Thanks for coming.
Um-hmm. Thank you for asking
me to come out today, kind sir.
What d'ya wanna do?
I dunno, wanna go watch a movie or something?
Sure!
I don't know about you,
but I still have nightmares about that day sometimes.
Even after I know I'm awake, I
just can't stop myself from shaking.
Does that ever happen to you, Shinichi?
Yeah, sometimes.
But by the end of the morning, I'm usually okay.
You're lucky.
Unfortunately, my dreams are always so... disturbing
I can't get them out of my head.
Well, actually, a friend told me something one time.
He said it helps to think of people like cows and pigs.
When you look at it that way, you can kinda see
that people are eating chopped-up animals all the time,
So it's natural. There's really
nothing for you to be afraid of.
That's kinda strange...
What kind of person would say that?
Ah... Hmm...
No one like you've ever met.
Well, maybe it's because of this friend...
that you've changed so much.
No, it's not that...
I don't think so.
Look, I'm sorry! I don't mean anything
bad, it's just you're different, that's all.
I never know which Shinichi's gonna show up.
It was that trip.
Ever since he got back, he hasn't been the same.
Um, Shinichi...
When your dad got hurt while on
vacation, and then, you went...
Let's get going.
I guess I shouldn't have asked him about it.
Oh, how cute!
Come here, little guy!
Is that your mama?
Must be.
Maybe they're strays.
Oh, I guess not. She has a collar.
Shinichi?
What a great day.
It's not even that cold out here.
You sound just like an old man!
Old man? Aw, c'mon.
Mommy!
Hey, Mommy, come back!
Wait for me, Mommy!
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Mommy, you're stupid!
You're stupid!
Hey, now...
There's no need to get ugly.
I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
Excuse me? How can you say that to me?
I hope you die, Mommy!
Come on, let's go.
What's wrong?!
A hole... There's a hole!
A hole?
Uh, I, uh...
What's going on? Are you okay?
It was really hard to breathe all of a sudden.
Maybe I am old.
Oh, cut it out! Now you're just being pathetic, grandpa!
Okay...
Sometimes...
it's like my body is being torn apart.
But then, the sensation just goes away.
That's when I feel like a part
of Migi really has merged with me.
But... I really do like Murano.
I care about her more than anything.
And there's one thing that I'm absolutely sure of:
That feeling...
it comes from MY heart.
When I'm with her,
it makes me wish Migi would just...
stay asleep.
Stay asleep... forever.
I'll see ya.
You... you really are Shinichi Izumi, right?
If only we had...
If only we had gotten closer to each other sooner.
If that were the case...
I could truly believe without any doubt in my heart...
that you really are Shinichi.
I'm such an idiot.
I should've known from the beginning.
But!
Why are you making the effort to see her?
She said it's the last favor she'll ever ask.
So how could I ignore her?
I do not really understand that.
Guess I got here a bit too early.
One of my kind is nearby.
Wait, not just one of them, but three. No, five.
Well, are there three or are there five?!
They're over there.
We, each and every one of us,
must alter our way of thinking.
As it now stands, the topic of
global environmental conservation.
They've noticed us. But they still haven't made a move.
Y'know something, Migi?
You and I may be the weirdest crime-fighting duo ever.
Shinichi...
They're currently about sixty meters away.
Eight of them in total.
Two are down low...
And six are elevated...
Still no aggression.
Could you give up your vehicle to
prevent just an ounce of pollution?
Completely reversing the course of
our daily lives is next to impossible.
But if we choose to do nothing, our
entire planet is in eminent danger.
All six up there...
They're all parasites?
And the two below.
At this distance it would be
difficult for them to identify us,
but they might if we make eye contact.
A popular approach is to use scare
tactics to try to elicit results,
offering a terrifying glimpse into of a dismal
future, threatening that we're doomed to fail.
Did he see us?
No, no way, not with this crowd.
He saw us.
Your eyes met.
But they don't seem to be very
interested in us at this time.
Shinichi, now we've seen what's
going on, I say we get out of here.
Yeah...
A parasite running for mayor?
What the hell are they up to?
Hey, Shinichi!
What are you doing here?!
Uh, yeah, well...
I just so happen to live in this neighborhood.
And ya know, I'm the one who asked you here.
Oh, right, of course you did.
But it's right here, in front of you!
It's at the local level and
not with the national bureaucrats
that environmental issues can start to be addressed...
This is bad...
Next time: "Kokoro"