That look on her face...
I hate her.
I hate everything about her!
She doesn't deserve to...
Shinichi, calm down.
We'd be in trouble if we had to fight
while your breathing was this irregular.
I know.
There's so much I'd hoped to discuss with the two of you,
but I can feel a strong sense of imminent threat...
so I'll have to make this a bit shorter than I'd planned.
I've killed at least 38 people so far.
Uh...
Most of which were for food...
But to tell you the truth, I'd say
that figure is quite low among my kind.
I was able to sustain myself with
the same food humans normally eat.
What I've found is that consuming humans is
completely unnecessary in order for my kind to survive.
I've done a fair amount of study on your species...
Searching to find exactly what we parasites are to you...
and, in turn, what you are you to us.
The conclusion I reached is that we are two halves...
of the same whole...
Parasites and humanity are of one family...
We are the children of mankind.
What was that?!
What kind of bullshit are you talking about?
Of course, given your human emotions,
I'm sure this is hard to grasp...
But...
We are actually quite frail.
We're nothing more than a life form
that isn't able to survive on its own.
So, please... Don't be too hard on us.
You've got to be kidding me. Go to Hell.
Interesting...
You two are extremely rare beings...
and that's exactly why I wanted the
chance to share my thoughts with you...
And also to give you an important word of advice.
It's in regards to Goto,
the man who's been pursuing you as of late.
You should avoid doing battle with him.
If you had started facing off
against Goto first rather than Miki,
I'm quite certain you'd be dead already.
Probably so.
Huh?
He is one of the most "frail" among us...
a being I created through experimentation...
But he's invincible.
You do know you just contradicted yourself, right?
Hehe...
Hahaha...
She's laughing.
And then there's the Mayor, Hirokawa...
Shinichi Izumi?
I'm pretty sure that's Detective Hirama...
That means, all these guys... must be cops.
At first glance it all looks so normal -
a mother holding a baby...
and a young high school kid in the park.
But one is a known parasite.
And the other found the body of
his own friend murdered by a parasite.
And here they are, together.
Right after another murder.
What is this?
What in the hell are you two up to?
Shinichi Izumi...
There's a lot more to you than you're letting on.
And there's some blood...
my blood got on the baby's clothes.
Stay back! Hold on. Hold your position!
Now then.
You're Reiko Tamura? Correct?
Excuse me?
And you just killed a man.
His name was Kuramori!
Oh! Uh...
What is this?
Then I'll have to ask the other one.
Ikeda!
What the hell are you doing here?
You and I have met before.
You do remember me, don't you?
So if you're the same person that I met,
then you should be able to say my name.
So tell me, who am I, Ikeda?
Well I uh... It sounds like
you forgot my name, Mr. Hirama.
Hehe...
Okay that one would seem to be human.
Well. You appear to be quite
calm and collected, Ms. Tamura.
I do believe you've mistaken me for someone else.
From this short of a distance...
I feel quite confident that I would not miss.
Is this some sort of sick joke?!
You people are crazy! Leave me alone!
I'd be deeply sorry if I were wrong...
but I'm afraid I'm out of options now...
and I can't risk getting any closer.
Now you listen to me!
I am accountable for whatever happens here...
It's on me!
Don't do this!
I don't know what your talking about!
Hirama wait.
Uh? Huh?
Well done, you were right...
Fire! Fire!
Stop it!
The baby's human!
Shinichi Izumi! Get back!
Shinichi! Stay here!
But Migi...
This can't be happening...
There's no way, right?
You're not involved in this, are you, Shinichi?
No. You wouldn't be caught in this...
No! You can't be!
Shinichi, please!
Uh...
Curious... Why won't she fight back?
She's coming toward us...
She must have something up her sleeve.
Fall back now, Shinichi. Run!
Shinichi...
Wait, Shinichi. Wait.
You can't leave me just yet.
I need to speak to you...
I need to speak to your humanity...
Shinichi.
Mother...
Don't let her fool you!
It's a trap. Remember the hole in your heart!
Please don't.
Whoa. Stop! Hold your fire!
Stop! Don't shoot or you'll hit the boy.
Something's wrong here.
I've been thinking...
for a long time...
About why...
Why was I even brought to this world in the first place?
As soon as I would resolve one question...
another one would inevitably take its place.
I've sought the beginning...
And I've sought the end.
I've walked alone for so long...
always thinking...
wondering...
Perhaps nothing will change no matter how far I go.
So even if I stop,
it will still remain the same.
And if someone were to tell me it was all over,
I wouldn't be fazed.
But today...
today I finally found the answer...
to one of my questions.
Shinichi...
In the end...
I never did anything to harm this child.
This perfectly normal, beautiful child.
Please make sure it's raised in a normal way...
by human hands.
Yes of course. I will.
Hm. Thank you so much.
Uh... "Thank you"?
You know Shinichi...
I recently tried to...
to laugh like a human in front of a mirror.
And I believe...
It felt rather pleasant.
Ahh...
She's dead...
I don't understand.
I'm sure she could have fought well if she'd wanted to.
Or at least run away.
Huh?
I'm so sorry little guy.
I know. I know.
Your mom is gone now, isn't she?
She's gone...
Your mom is...
Mom...
Shinichi.
Are you okay, Shinichi? Did
you get any on you?! Are you hurt?
You have to meet once again
with whomever created this hole...
It's dead.
Its heart stopped.
It was just so embarrassing...
I could never tell...
anyone...
They're dead...
All of them... they're dead... they're dead...
Life...
Life will be absorbed by this tree.
Shinichi!
You... you will... come back, right?
Come back, right?
Uhh...
Oh!
We're back home.
I'm so glad.
Hm...
Hmm...
What's wrong, Shinichi?
I just had a...
a really sad...
a really sad dream...
Uh...
Mm... Uh?
Shinichi?
Shinichi, you're here!
You did come back.
Huh...
Yeah, I did...
Murano.
Huh?
How's Shinichi?
He's fine, and it looks like he'll
be coming back to school pretty soon.
Well that's good.
So, like what happened?
He just left all of a sudden,
and never said where he was going!
Uh-uhh... Mm...
I'm sure she doesn't want to talk about that.
Let's go.
Hmm...
What happened in the park that day...
didn't even make the news.
But still...
Shinichi's back.
He came back.
So, you'll be having lunch in here.
Make yourself comfortable.
So how'd it go?
Man, I'm worn-out.
Well, he looks just a little bit too
calm for someone his age, don'tcha think?
True, he does seem to be surprisingly level-headed, but
well, there are people out there with an easy temperament.
Although, I'm not sure he really has
this ability the detectives are looking for.
Not anywhere in the same league as the other guy, anyway.
Oh, good grief...
So he's really the only candidate?
Yeah, unfortunately so.
Dogs and cats...
And monkeys and birds and bears...
it's all such a waste of time.
I never told anyone that I could talk to animals.
You guys do get that, right?
Just shut up and move it.
So, which little critters will it be today?
Humans.
Hm... Humans?
Hahaha...
Aah, that's just great! Haha!
It means that the true test is finally at hand.
Oh, is that so?
After all this time, now you
wanna hear what I have to say?
Please, sir...
I'm innocent, Mr. Detective!
Believe me.
Hahaha!
Nothing? Come on that was good.
Shut your damn mouth.
Get his cuffs.
Yeah?
Um, Shinichi Izumi...
I need you to come with me, please.
Okay.
No matter what they ask me,
I have to keep Migi's existence a secret...
I should calm myself down, one last time...
This'll be the last thing, 'kay.
Oh, alright.
Okay, Uragami.
This is your chance to prove
your ability to us once and for all.
Alright, please go ahead and have a seat here
and wait to receive your instructions.
Sure.
You're going to be meeting five people...
I want you to find which one of them is like you...
A human that has your same ability...
You did say you could recognize it if you met one, right?
Yeah yeah, that's right, I can tell.
I think I can...
And, let us know if they've been infected.
Wait, what?! So you're bringing one
of those monsters in here with me?!
What the hell are you thinking? Hey, goddammit!
This glass isn't gonna be able to keep me safe!
You can't just leave me in here and
let me get eaten by one of those things!
It's all right. Stop worrying.
That is thick, bullet-proof glass.
And it's also soundproof.
Right, let's begin. Mr. Fukami?
Hmm?
Please come in.
Okay.
Tch!
Hey, Uragami.
Knock it off and look at him!
Yeah, yeah.
What are your thoughts?
Hmm...
Well, I can tell that... this guy's not a parasite.
There is only a minimal response to my telepathy.
He's keeping his thoughts very tightly guarded...
so it's rather difficult for me to
determine if he has the same ability I do.
Well I guess what he's saying at
least sounds plausible, doesn't it?
Hehe... I really should mention this up front...
All of the self-proclaimed "psychics" in
that room... are most likely full of crap.
But if any of them actually had such powers...
or rather, finely honed abilities,
it'd be this guy who has the best chance.
Okay? Whatcha think?
Chubs over there is a total hack...
I want you to tell him something.
"Lying's the first step down the path of wickedness."
Well you'd know!
Yeah, great advice coming from a serial killer...
Okay, next candidate, please.
Huh?
What's the matter, Uragami?
You are screwed up, Detective...
You know what bein' in prison's like, right?
If you put a hottie like this in front of me, then...
Mmph!
Huh?
Ooohh...
Is he... godammit!
So-uh shouldn't we maybe stop him, Inspector?
This is probably affecting his concentration.
Hehehaha...
Oh dear God!
Ah! He's one! He's one of the parasites for sure!
Eww... Disgusting...
Aw don't leave, I'm not done yet! Baby?
Well this has been a waste of time.
Hmmm.
Mr. Izumi, sorry for the wait.
You may go in now.
Right.
You aren't able to hear each other,
so there's no need to hold back, okay?
Now tell me, what do you think of this man?
Well, I... I don't know.
For some reason, you tend to
encounter parasites quite often.
Most recently, you were approached
by the parasite known as Reiko Tamura.
Maybe there's something about you that attracts them...
Or perhaps...
You somehow have a way of
telling them apart from the rest us.
Stay calm.
If I can just be calm, It'll be fine.
No, sir.
I can't help but think...
this is the partner Kuramori
was trying to tell me about...
just before his death...
But mentioning his name...
seems to have no effect on him.
But it's hard to believe a kid could bluff
his way through this without ever cracking.
I think that piece a shit is asleep!
What the hell?!
Dammit, Uragami! Wake your ass up!
Uh... Hehe...
That chick really wore me out...
Heh, heh. Huh?
We're still doing this?
You got a cute face there, boy.
I bet if you put on a skirt or
somethin' I could rub out another one.
Hehehe...
Hm...
Well, well, well, Mr. Detective.
Huh?
I need you to tell this guy...
to look me straight in the eye.
Shinichi.
Yes?
Uh!
Next time: "In Cold Blood"