You're dead!
What the...
Uh...
It's not the one I'm looking for...
But this one IS one of those parasites.
Ah! Hey, wait a second!
What's wrong? Migi?!
I've determined that his human brain is still intact.
It is?!
Whoa! That is crazy!
Just the hand?
How does THAT guy have a human brain?!
No, he's telling the truth!
I really do have a human brain...
It's totally for real!
Can you believe this crap?
Yes, Shinichi, the brain is indeed still intact.
From the lower half of his face to the base of his neck,
perhaps down to his chest, is the parasite.
Yep, that's right.
So, hey guys, that means we're like practically the same!
It was only a year after we got married,
my wife ran off and left me.
She never really said anything about what was wrong.
But my guess was she just got tired of me.
I've never been the most... exciting guy.
In fact, I'm so pathetic...
I didn't even have the guts to
go through with killing myself.
It's really beautiful...
What is that?! Go away! Shoo! Shoo, shoo!
And then, after all that, I...
Oh, my God, he tells the worst stories!
Now, your right hand should be
able to remember some of this stuff.
So, y'see, my very first and only thought
was to take over the brain of a host, right?
So I start zippin' straight for this guy's noggin.
But something's wrong...
What's happening?
It's not breathing.
If that doesn't change, the body will die.
There's no time to take the brain.
Neither one of us will make it.
So since he was about to eat it,
I had to just go for it and
get to merging as fast as I could.
I see, very interesting.
Ya see, that's how we wound up like this.
So, the problem is, whenever I
hand over the talky part to this guy,
he just blathers and yaps and puts everybody to sleep!
Quiet!
Anyway, I sure was surprised to see you!
When this guy suddenly tells me
that one of my kind is coming closer,
I was pretty nervous about what
sort of monster we were gonna run into.
But when you showed up, man, was I relieved.
I mean, wow! There are actually
other people out there who're like me!
So, I am dying to know... Tell me your story.
How'd you get like this?
Yeah, yeah, totally! Tell us!
Sure, but before I do that, do you think
maybe we could go somewhere else, please?
My name's Shinichi Izumi. And this is Migi.
The thing is, we need to stay close to a certain place.
Ah, well, I'm Mamoru Uda.
And this guy, you can just call him "Parasite."
That's right, you can just call me "Parasite".
Wait, where the heck did he go?
It's like he just disappeared.
That's awful! It's just completely awful!
That's why you've stayed so close
to the hospital this whole time?
It must be so hard. I couldn't do it!
Yeah...
I swear ta God, he cries all the freakin' time.
I don't understand how these humans operate at all.
I feel the same way sometimes.
I can't help but notice.
Your Migi speaks quite well.
Huh? Oh, yeah...
Well, that's probably because he
reads whenever he gets the chance.
Well, I learned how to talk
from watchin' a whole lotta TV.
I mean, all this guy does is sit on
the couch, and watch old re-runs and cry.
How about your host? Does he spend all his time crying?
Hey, look, that is just about enough!
Okay, I work at the hotel
that's just in the next town over.
And once he tells me one of those
things is around, I will let you know.
Uh...
Please let us help you out!
I mean...
You're the first person I've met like me and...
This guy really is a crybaby.
But I'm glad I met him.
It feels good to know that
I'm not the only one out there like this.
Shinichi...
Shinichi!
It's really late, Migi. What... what do you want?
This is very important.
I wanted to talk to you earlier today, but in
meeting Uda and his parasite, I missed my chance.
Did you notice, Shinichi?
First, you ran at the speed of a seasoned athlete,
and then you jumped more than three meters high.
What about it?
That doesn't seem odd to you?
Then I'll have to elaborate.
But first, about my own body...
See? Doing this kind of thing takes practice, you know.
If I divide into two parts like this,
each of the halves is still
fully capable of thought and speech.
Wow...
But if I start dividing into parts that are too small,
our intelligence will diminish to where we're
incapable of thought, much less rejoining together,
and those parts would be unable to survive.
Huh... okay...
That's why, whenever I do divide,
a consensus is reached beforehand.
And it acts as a mantra,
an instinct to come back together as one.
Uh, all right then, I think I get it.
Then again, there are places
where even my smallest fragments-.
They are still able to survive.
For example, a place where there
is a constant flow of fresh blood.
In other words, they can survive inside your body.
In my body?
Are you serious?!
Yes, that's right.
In fact, the Migi that's talking to you right now
is actually only about seventy percent of the original.
When I closed the wound in your heart,
I instructed all my parts to return
to your right arm via your bloodstream.
However, once it was restored,
your heart was much stronger than I had expected,
so quite a lot of me was dispersed throughout your body.
They've become so small that I
can no longer communicate with them.
Unbelievable...
Just when I thought you couldn't tell
me anything else that could surprise me.
If there had been no physiological
changes, I was going to keep quiet about it.
Migi...
What is it?
You said throughout my body...
Does that mean even in my brain?
I don't know. But it's not like those
tiny fragments have any consciousness.
I seriously doubt they would try to enter the capillaries.
Is something bothering you?
No, I'm sure it's nothing.
I'm probably just over-thinking things.
Before, I felt like my heart was going
to explode from everything I was feeling,
but I still couldn't cry.
It was the same thing today, too.
I mean, Uda started bawling his eyes out
when he met someone like him for the first time.
But not me...
How about your host?
Does he spend all of his time crying?
A hole in my heart...
Hey, Maki...
Aww, how'd you know I was here?
Tell me somethin'.
Do I seem like a normal person to you?
Huh? Of course you do.
What do you mean?
Oh, come on, what's going on?
You gotta give me something here!
You... You haven't really said anything to me.
Huh?
Back on the boat, and even now, too...
It's like you just sit there with
this terrible look on your face!
It's like...
You're crying inside, but you're holding it all in!
It... it makes me worry.
Sorry.
Just... just forget it, okay?
Oh, it's Uda.
It's here now! A parasite!
And I'm pretty sure it's the one you're looking for!
So, is it headed this way?
No, it seems to have noticed me and is coming closer.
I'm gonna try to stall it
somehow until you can get over here.
No! That's crazy!
If that thing realizes that you still have a human brain,
it's gonna try to kill you!
'Bout another 100 meters!
Get outta there! You need to run away right now!
Uh, o-okay I got it!
I'll make my way around the
cape and be there as soon as I can!
Shinichi, I'm detecting one parasite.
One? It must be Uda.
Come on, it's gonna catch up!
Look, this is the best I can do, okay?!
Well, it looks like that one's learned to
hone its host and maximize its physical potential.
There's no way we can beat it.
We've gotta get outta here!
No, we can't!
Shinichi and Migi will be here soon.
We have to work together to have a chance!
Then you gotta go that way.
It's the only hope we have of not getting destroyed.
Shinichi...
Migi, can you sense the other one yet?
No, I'm tired.
Huh?! No, no, not now!
I need sleep...
Come on, Migi! You can't just
let Uda and his parasite die!
Shinichi, You have to listen to me.
Hey!
If possible, you should run.
Choose your own surviv... al...
Everything will be fine.
I just need to find Uda before it's too late.
Oh, crap!
What do we do? There's nowhere else to go!
This is really bad!
Even if we get cornered here, you
and Shinichi can still combine attacks.
You are the second like this I've met.
The second one whose human brain has remained intact.
As far as I am concerned, you are
nothing more than an unfortunate mistake.
And you must be removed.
Whoa! That's what we're supposed to really look like?
That's freakin' awesome!
Where could they be? Where?
I'm gonna die!
You are clearly outmatched.
I am completely fused with my host.
Your base remains human which
causes you to be much less responsive.
She's right. You are totally slowing me down.
I can feel the effects of your crappy conditioning.
But y'know, her attacks are kinda repeating.
It's just like she's targeting
the same spot over and over.
She may be strong, but she's not very creative.
This battle is all but done.
It is time for you to die now.
In cases when it's difficult to
determine where the parasite ends,
destroying the heart is the best
approach to eradicating one's opponent.
Yes, of course...
the heart...
Another one of us?
Strange... The signal is much too weak.
It's as if... the parasite is asleep.
You're alive. My attack should have terminated you.
Could it be that my targeting was off?
No, that's not possible.
You were punctured through the
heart, yet somehow did not die.
Obviously, I should have cut off your head as well.
Dammit...
Even the voice is still the same.
I am gonna kill you now, and it's gonna be quick.
Yeah, that's it, come on!
Like the disgusting monster that you are!
You are going to die, too. Like your friend.
"My friend"?
What have you done to Uda?!
The signal from his right hand is very weak.
It's almost as if it's hibernating.
This human is all alone.
What? Impossible!
How could normal human agility
be able to evade my attacks?
How is this happening?
I can see it... I can see every move it makes!
It's completely different from when I fought Mr. A!
There it is.
The tentacles move while morphing at the same time!
Unbelievable.
Uda!
He was the only one... The one person in the
world who could understand what I've gone through!
I don't understand.
How is he able to move like this?
The neck...
Aim for the neck up!
I cannot let it live.
I will kill it!
I will kill this goddamn monster!
What is this? He can't be human.
Don't worry, Mom...
I'm gonna hack that demon right out of you!
You fared surprisingly well for a human,
but now it is time...
to die.
Uda!
That... that thing wasn't...
really your mom, of course.
Even so...
I didn't feel like you should be the one to have to do it.
But how? How can you still be alive?
I could see right through your attack pattern.
You aimed in the exact same place, every single time.
So, I just moved the heart and all
the other vital stuff out of the way,
and then let you think you had taken me out.
Mom...
It's over.
It's all over, Mom.
Thank you, for everything. Take care.
Ah! I'll walk with you.
So, then... you're all done here?
Uh... Yeah, I am.
Well, next time you come, we should do some sightseeing.
No, I won't be coming back here again.
You won't?!
Well, maybe someday...
Maybe someday you'll change your mind.
Goodbye...
I wish I could say this better.
How can I put this?
I want you to understand this one important thing, Son.
Right up until the very end...
No, even now, your mother loves you very, very much.
And I love you and your mom, too.
Dad...
I wanna ask you something 'bout what you saw.
Um... The night everything happened...
did... did Mom... Did... she...
Dad, did she suffer at all, do you think?
No...
No, it all happened way too fast.
Oh... okay.
Shinichi?
It's him! He's here.
He's here! He's back!
Shinichi, hey!
Hey.
Next time: "Freezing Point"