Okay... as for the detective himself...
I'll deal with him...
What about the human with the parasite arm?
Of course... Miki is heading that way tomorrow.
Hm?
Ah! Yoko! Yumi!
Oh!
Given your situation...
I would imagine that your
combat style must be truly unique.
Must be how you've dealt with
my kind so easily up until now.
But what I can't understand is how having a human
brain still intact could actually make you stronger.
Judging by the condition of
the body left in our dining area,
it would seem to indicate your
victory did not happen instantly.
Hahaha...
What's wrong? Was that not an appropriate moment to laugh?
So, how do you manage to do it?
I'd love to get a demonstration
of your special fighting techniques.
Man... What's with this guy?
He's creepy as hell and won't shut up.
Stay alert...
He's only attempting to figure us out right now.
And no matter how expressive he may seem to you,
never forget that it's something completely
different from actual human emotions.
Ohh... So you talk to each other while you're fighting.
And that's an effective system?
You certainly have impressive
speed and motion detection...
which means that bringing you back in one
piece could prove to be a rather difficult task.
There are too many blades!
So? Make more!
I'm afraid it doesn't work that way.
There's a certain minimum size requirement.
Ugh!
Hehehe...
That guy sure is pretty slow.
True, you are faster than he is...
but it's not as if you have all that much stamina.
Yeah. I've been running all day!
I'm really tired!
I agree. I am, too.
That fight was short but very intense.
I guess we're pretty pathetic aren't we?
Okay, I think we've put some distance between us.
He's a new type of enemy.
Three-in-one this time.
So what about his legs?
His legs?
Well it's like you told me in our last fight...
that the human part is the weakness.
If we can attack his legs somehow...
Aah...
What's wrong? We can't do it?
I'm worried...
I can't seem to get a feel for
how his parasites are distributed.
But you said there are three of them, didn't you?
So they have to be the head and arms, right?
Logically, yes, but something is wrong...
Uh...
He's here. He caught up to us.
Ah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Oh!
Here we go again.
"Again"?
Ugh!
I swear. You sure do like to run.
And it's getting kind of old.
I guess I'll have to forget
about leaving your body intact.
Okay, it's time to gamble...
Let's aim for the legs, just like you said.
I'll block the next attacks
that come toward your right side.
You'll need to hold your ground
while dodging attacks on the left side.
And how am I supposed to do that?
Huh?
Peculiar.
Haha... Shall we finish?!
Ah!
What the-?
What was that?!
That was a mid-air collision, and
between his own tentacles, no less.
Huh?!
I see his true nature clearer now.
"True nature"?
Indeed... Seeing this new type was quite a shock
at first, but he might turn out to be mostly show.
I sure hope so.
As for the three parasites...
they're distributed through more than his head and arms.
For instance, that leg I was
able to cut earlier wasn't human.
It wasn't?!
Either way, I'm certain that the
head is, in fact, the control center.
And I don't sense independent
thought in his arms' movements.
Look out.
I'll run as many times as it takes!
I've found a good location.
Go into the woods right here.
His control center isn't that competent.
There's no cohesion to his bodily movements,
which is why he falls down and runs into himself.
Most importantly, his head should be parasitic,
so why doesn't it morph and join in the attack?
Good question!
I think the head has a hard enough time just
governing the arms and other parasite areas.
Meaning, the head has to stay intact
or the entire system falls apart.
So, it's actually not at all that difficult.
In the end, he's just a single enemy.
Right... We'll fight here...
Stop running.
Rather than the legs or torso, let's aim for the neck...
Severing the head is the surest way to victory.
Y'think we can get to it?
We can! Whenever I give you the signal,
I want you to run directly toward him...
And at full speed.
What?!
You'll just have to trust me.
I'm getting really tired of this.
Now don't you move!
Use the trees as a shield and maintain your distance.
Dodge his attacks by moving in all directions.
If you avoid him by just using a linear pattern,
he'll be able to learn our
movements and predict our next move...
Until suddenly...
Now!
Huh?
From his perspective,
a prey that has done nothing but
run away now is suddenly coming at him.
Parallel becomes perpendicular,
horizontal becomes vertical...
For someone struggling just to control his tentacles,
he won't be able to track our trajectory.
Haa!
Yeah!
What's wrong?
I didn't know... that was possible!
Now it's my turn.
Uh...
Get over here, Miki.
Yeah, sorry 'bout that.
Irrelevant. As I suspected, you're
better suited to remain a subordinate.
So there weren't really three of them.
What?!
Look. He is now completely one being.
In an instant, he took control of the
entire body and became a single life form.
But just before that happened, his
consciousness split into five separate pieces.
In other words, there are a total
of five parasites in that one body!
Ah-no way!
When the first one was acting as the head,
I felt that there were three because he wasn't
capable of unifying all of them at the same time.
Yes, that's correct.
Only Miki and I can act as the controller.
And only I am able to unify all of us together.
Wow...
Yes.
But now is not the time to be impressed.
It seems we must've come quite
some distance while I was asleep.
We've met before... Yes?
It's that guy!
He moves different from before!
Not even apes can move like that!
Being in the woods is now a disadvantage for us!
Ugh! Ah!
He's quite fast... For a human.
Excuse me!
Uh?! No!
Let's go.
Ah!
Well...
What?!
Very impressive.
Ah!
Hm? What in the...
Aaa... holy... son of ah...!
Uh... What do we do?
Hmm?
I don't know what's going on...
But I'm getting' the hell outta here!
I can't believe that bastard
just drove off! What the hell?!
Are you okay there pal?
My body is feeling weary from the loss of so much blood...
I will need some more.
Blood?
I understand your pain all too well. But, sir...
Is there a detective here named Hirama?
Hirama?
Yes, Chief?
You can go on now.
Kuramori...
I'm going to put aside for the time
being how it is you've even come to know...
Inspector Hirama.
Because I think you know something more important.
About the parasites.
Shinichi, you need some new clothes.
We stand out too much. And we need to eat.
I would. But I don't have any money.
Ah! Migi where did you get that?
From that truck driver earlier.
Before you say it, I am not human,
and I don't want to hear any lectures
about your human laws and morals.
You're my hand, y'know?
I did this out of necessity to preserve my own life.
Listen, even though you and I are
completely different life forms...
we have developed an alliance...
and we must respect one another.
With that in mind,
what do you think is the common purpose that unites us?
To survive.
Yeah, but it's still stealing.
Indeed.
Police have now revealed more information about the
grisly slayings of Mr. Kuramori's wife and daughter,
Hm? What tha? "Kuramori"?
Furthermore, Kuramori's office,
which handled private investigations,
burned to the ground the same night in
what is believed to have been an act of arson.
Police have said that they plan to question Kuramori
about any possible connection between the two incidents.
They must have decided he's
too dangerous to be kept alive.
His family was probably just collateral damage.
Most likely their primary target, the detective, escaped.
I have to get a hold of my Dad!
Shinichi? It's late, where are you?
Everything okay?
Dad, listen to me.
You need to get out of the house... Right now!
Tell me what's going on, Shinichi.
A lot of things...
I can't come home for a while.
Why not?! Talk to me, tell me what's going on!
But Dad...
There's no way I can tell him everything I know!
I have to hurry. I gotta get him outta there!
Okay. Look, Dad...
Haven't I... Haven't I been a good
kid and followed the rules and anything?
And y'know, ever since Mom's been
gone I've tried really hard to help out,
and be someone you can trust...
Dad, I promise, this isn't some kind of stupid prank.
So, Dad, please!
You have to get out of the house right now!
A monster is coming!
And it's the same one that killed Mom alright!
Huh?
Shinichi please tell me that you're safe.
Yes, Dad. I am.
All right then...
I'll leave here for now, son...
Your father believes in you, okay?
That's good... Thanks, Dad.
My name is Hirama.
My sincere condolences for
the loss of your wife and child.
Currently, they're still being
examined for forensic evidence,
but what I've already seen has confirmed my beliefs.
Right now, I'd like to hear what your thoughts are.
You need justice!
Hm?
Justice, huh?
That's right.
Since I was a boy...
I've always admired the great detectives...
Heh... You know, like... like Sherlock Holmes...
but things don't always go as planned,
I managed to become a PI at least...
Okay now listen here...
You could be... a great detective.
Can we... can we avenge their deaths?
Of course we can!
I... I have some information.
Mm-hm.
But I'm afraid I'm a little messed up right now.
Can I have something to write with...
and go somewhere I can calm down first.
Absolutely.
No, this isn't telepathy.
How many times is this now?
It's our sixteenth time to meet in your dreams...
Though I'm sure you'll just forget again.
Yeah but, you don't look anything at
all like the Migi I know in the real world.
You say the same thing every time we do this.
But then, you don't look like the
Shinichi that I know in reality, either.
What, you're already going?
I've now determined that there's simply no way for
me to communicate with the thirty percent of my cells
that still remain scattered throughout your body.
So there's no point in meeting in your dreams anymore..
More importantly, our current situation in the real world
is such that there's no time
to lose on such trivial matters.
I should go.
Is that so?
You'll remember when you wake up.
Migi!
Huh?
What was I...
It's cold...
You mean both of them were failures? Unbelievable.
The real failure was on my part in allowing
the two of you to deal with the investigator.
Killing the family without getting rid of him first
shows your complete ignorance regarding human nature.
The room was dark when we got there...
At any rate, it will be simple
enough just to kill him next, correct?
You underestimate the humans a little too much.
True, individually, they seem like incapable creatures...
But that is not the case.
You need to recognize something that's very important...
The human race is actually a single life form
comprised of billions of separate parts.
In addition to their individual brains,
they possess a single, collective "consciousness."
And when we oppose that...
we are truly defeated.
"Defeated"?
Is she truly one of us?
Something's different...
Something's not right.
Shinichi wasn't at school again today...
And yesterday, he was acting
like something was going on again...
Murano.
Huh?
Got something for ya...
Here... Shinichi forgot it and left it behind.
You should totally go take it back to him.
Wha... But I...
It'll be a chance for you two to patch things up.
If you won't take it back to him, then I will!
Mr. Kuramori?
He duped us.
It's not like he's a suspect,
so why do you think he'd run off?
Huh?
A list of partners...
Reiko Tamura!
Yoko, Yumi...
I will avenge you with my own hands!
Reiko Tamura, you're dead.
Reiko Tamura...
No. She is not one of us.
She's dangerous...
She's a threat...
a threat to our kind.
You are such a mystery...
In a world of so much confusion.
Why was I...
No. Why were we... born?
I didn't think so...
Where are you?
And are you safe, Shinichi?
It was you.
You are the one who dragged me into this hell!
Three of them.
And their intent seems less than peaceful.
Where's she going?
All right...
While I still have the chance...
Good evening, Tamura.
We can try to hide them,
but they can't be suppressed, can they?
The strongest signals that we emit
are those which harbor animosity...
I know of your intentions.
Get on with it.
Next time: "The Adventure of the Dying Detective"