Mitsuo?
What's his problem?
Ah...
Hey, don't!
Shut up!
If I wanna fight this jackass,
it's none of your damn business.
Shimada?
Huh?
I went easy on you this time
because I'd prefer to avoid trouble.
However, if you decide to show up again
and pick a fight with me for no reason...
I'll end you.
Yes!
Shinichi?
You... are Shinichi Izumi, aren't you?
Huh?
I, uh...
Oh, sorry! My mistake, I'm sorry.
Uh! What?! Yeah, that's me!
Who... who're you?
I'm Satomi. Satomi Murano.
We both took our entrance exams in the same room.
Oh, sorry, that's right!
I was so nervous that day I didn't notice anything else.
Well, I'll see you in April then.
Maybe we'll be in the same class!
Yeah, maybe so.
His parasite's "signal" is weak again.
I wonder why? Is it sleeping?
Perhaps if I emit a signal of my own,
it should respond reflexively.
Especially, to murderous intent!
Interesting...
Mm, mm, mm, that Hide. He's kinduv a hottie, huh?
Oh! I, uh, don't really, um...
Oh, c'mon, don't even try to hide it.
I know you drew his face in your sketchbook, Yuko.
Akiho, that is mine!
I mean, he's super cool, isn't he?
I think we have a new hottest guy in school.
I bet he's a model. Do you think he's a model?
S'like he's not real. Like he's fake or something.
Oh, Yuko, do me a favor. Draw
a picture of him for me, too.
Ha! Thanks!
"Fake"?
Why? What do you mean I can't tell anyone?
In this situation, our greatest fear
is that we would cause wide-spread panic
due to a lack of credible information.
When people stop trusting one another,
it inevitably leads to discrimination and fear.
And soon after that... misinformation
and mass hysteria will follow.
That's my son, Shinichi.
Uh, hello there. How are you?
In any case, we still have no
way to distinguish them from us.
And given that, there's simply nothing
to be gained by going public at this time.
We are truly sorry about the loss of your wife.
Nevertheless, to be blunt about
the current state of things,
this is a problematic situation of having a few thousand
violently dangerous killers roaming around the country.
Please, take a look.
Yes... That's exactly what the thing looked like.
So, it's able to morph into just about anything it wants.
It seems the rumors have become widespread.
It appears so.
That outcome could have easily been foreseen.
But if we continue this practice of
preying on them like mindless insects,
we will all eventually be hunted
down and completely wiped out.
Our species is truly weak...
Our imperfections are troubling.
It's hardly surprising that you would have
pondered over and worried about such things.
I only have one question.
I want to find out the real reason.
Why is it we parasites even exist?
The answer to that is quite simple.
The human race has now become toxic to the planet Earth,
which has created a need for balance.
So what you're saying is this thing
I'm currently nurturing within me
is a poison?
So I guess they left, huh, Dad?
"Mass hysteria..."
I need to tell you... the truth.
It's about...
It's about your mother, Son.
I sat there quietly and listened.
I nodded as my father spoke.
And told him nothing about what I knew.
Then, finally...
Dad told me outright for the very first time.
That Mom...
was dead.
We've asked Professor Bigg Mouth for his opinion
on when to brush your teeth. Morning or at night!
Professor Bigg Mouth, please stop that!
Aww, he's asleep again!
Hmm?
What is this? That's just nasty.
Ah! Gimme that!
It's part of an investigation.
Oh, is that what your suspect looks like this time?
How could THIS possibly be a suspect? It's a monster!
Anyway, what's going on, Yuko? Do you need something?
Yeah...
Could you take a look at something for me?
This your friend? That's pretty nice work.
You're getting better and better at this.
So, do you sense anything?
Like, his personality or like his attitude?
Since you draw faces for a living, I just
thought maybe you could tell me about him.
Come on, Yuko.
It doesn't really work like that, y'know.
Oh, 'kay.
He's alone again today. Is he waiting for someone?
Or maybe he's watching someone...
Hey! Look out!
Hey, buddy!
Dude, are you all right?
Yes.
I... I don't believe what I... what I just saw.
Man, I really have to patch things up with Murano today.
Murano!
About the other day,
that was... that was nothing serious.
That girl was just...
she was... making fun of me.
So, I mean...
Shinichi...
Jesus, Migi. Now's not the time! Uh...
I sense Hideo Shimada projecting murderous intent.
I believe I made myself clear, but if you insist.
I'm sure that you'll agree,
we should find somewhere away from prying eyes.
He has four to six targets.
Most likely all human.
The probability that this will
turn into a massacre is quite high.
Shinichi?
If you wish to intervene, I can give you their location.
What would you like to do?
What choice do I have?
Shinichi?!
Man, I don't think I've ever
met a guy so eager to get pounded.
Hmpf! Maybe he doesn't really understand
how much trouble he's actually in here.
Listen up, nobody touches him. I'M takin' him down.
It's okay. You can all attack together.
I'm afraid a distraction is on his way here.
If you want to do this, do it now.
They're right over there.
This guy again?!
He just jumped three meters.
Is his parasite empowering him? That doesn't make sense.
So, Shimada! It looks like you've
finally shown what you really are!
Let me guess...
This means that you want to fight me then.
Look, I didn't ask to be involved with any of this.
Turns out, I'm the victim here.
Aren't I?
You should go.
I'll take care of things around here.
Oh? Well, I'll leave it to you then.
You frickin' serious?
You're just gonna run away?
Well now, aren't you the big hero?
Pretty nice of you to get your ass kicked for you buddy!
My "buddy"?
You idiots have no idea what you're getting into.
So, why don't you just go home?
And don't ever go after that guy again.
I'm talkin' to you.
You are the leader of all these guys, aren't you?
What the... How did he know that?
There's no way he's ever met Yano before.
Heh, what'cha looking at, pretty boy?
Morons without a clue shouldn't be mouthing off like that.
If they won't listen to reason,
then I'll have to try something else.
Let's go!
Uh, Yano? Hey, dude, where ya going?
He'd kill me. If we fought, he'd kill me.
Murano...
Here.
Thank you.
What is it?
I was curious about what happened to those males.
That doesn't concern you anymore.
Did you use your new friend?
I imagine you beat them all senseless, didn't you?
I did no such thing!
Look! Just go!
Ow!
Oh! Sorry!
Um, did something happen between you and Shimada?
Can't stand that smug bastard!
He tries to act like he's all
harmless, but he is full of shit!
Shinichi...
You're acting different again.
And you've never been the type
of person to talk like that.
It's just not right.
"Not right"? What do you mean?
Well, it's like...
The Shinichi I know just isn't this kind of person.
When you act like this, it feels like you're forcing it.
Yeah, well, I'm not, okay?
Either way, you're a completely
different person than the one I knew.
You have changed.
I guess that maybe I have.
But still, I'm not forcing it.
So who is it you're trying to be?
You just snap your fingers and change who you are?!
Are you...
Are you still...
Shinichi?
SHUT UP!
Fine then... I liked you better before.
It's because of the hole in my chest, isn't it?
Or the hole in your back, depending on your perspective.
In my opinion, however, you've
actually grown stronger as a life form,
if not so as a person.
You're able to maintain your composure.
You recover quickly from sways in
mood, and your thoughts are quite logical.
When viewed by others, it's no wonder
they would perceive that you've changed.
Migi, you don't even know what you're talking about.
In any case, this mental
resilience is a definite plus for you.
Is this supposed to be your
attempt at trying to cheer me up?
Perhaps. But if need be, I will consider
alternative ways to improve your psyche.
Well, how very nice of you.
I know what I saw...
It was real.
He changed clothes.
Where's he going?
Oh, my God, his face...
How can he do that?
He can turn into someone else?
That's impossible!
That's like...
No... It can't be!
I'm home.
Oh, hey there, Yuko.
Are you still in your school clothes?
I need to ask you something.
The truth is, we don't have a
clue what these things really are.
Some of the theories are that they could be aliens,
or mutants, or even bio-weapons.
But there's one thing you do know for sure, right?
That they can change their faces.
Yeah, that's what the witnesses all say.
Also, these things can speak our
language, and they kill people for food.
Do me a favor, be extra careful
if you're out walking at night.
Now granted, their numbers are relatively
low compared to the whole human race,
so it's pretty doubtful you'll
even run into one, but, y'know.
Yeah, I guess so.
If only we could just catch one of these things alive.
Killing people for food?
Is that what Shimada's doing?
I should tell my brother.
But what if it turns out I'm wrong about him?
Okay...
I'll just have to ask you myself, Shimada.
Hmm...
These aren't gonna work.
Perfect!
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
I'm not sure if you know who I am,
but I've kinda had my eye on you since you got here.
I watch you all the time.
And that's how, well...
I saw you.
Now I don't wanna believe you're
from another world or anything,
but there are some crazy rumors out there.
If you really, do, um...
kill people... and... and eat them...
Yuko...
If... If you do...
then I'm asking you to go away.
And don't ever...
come back here again.
I... I mean it!
I don't want anyone else to get hurt!
Have you told anyone else about this?
Tell me!
Do you really do all those
horrible things to people, Shimada?
So you see, modern and classical
Japanese are actually quite different.
You have to learn the rhythm of the verbs in order to...
Not good...
Not at all.
No...
Shimada!
That son of a bitch!
Next time: "What Mad Universe"