Hmm...
Huh?
Ah!
One is dead.
Uh...
We got one!
One down.
Retrieve the body... Use a different route.
Yes sir!
Those things aren't really alive...
They're just machines driven by demons...
And all it takes to stop a
machine is to destroy the engine.
To destroy the heart,
destructive spread is more
important than mere penetrating power.
What we need are shotguns loaded with seven-point-six
millimeter, sixteen-pellet number-one Buckshot shells.
What was that? Did you hear that?
I heard gunshots.
Somebody's shooting.
Hey! You know what's goin' on?
Everyone, please remain calm...
The gunman's firing warning shots.
He's only trying to prove a point!
So for now, we're going to wait for a just few minutes.
Then resume evacuations.
Goddamn, humans.
You've fared better than anticipated.
Well now... What is going on here?
Evacuations may now continue.
Nope. All clear...
None here, either.
What's going on?
This can't be right...
Are they onto us?
Captain.
Hm?
The late investigator's notes
mentioned something interesting...
although rather vaguely...
Telepathy?
Yeah yeah, I read about that.
We need to take every precaution.
I'm about to send Uragami in.
Please, don't hesitate to use him.
I don't trust this guy...
Hm?
Hold on for just a second...
Whatcha got?
I have an update on Hirokawa.
So some people still haven't made it down?
That's right.
It looks like a town meeting was scheduled
in the second floor conference room today.
And I doubt the people who're up
there were able to hear the announcement.
Don't worry we'll take care of it.
We'll send some men to check things out.
Yes, well I don't think they're going to react well.
A group of men coming in with guns...
It's likely to cause more panic.
He's right.
We'll go up to the second floor
and bring them back down with us.
Looks like they're making their move.
Don't let them leave...
Try and stall them.
Yes sir!
Okay I'm back...
You can go ahead and bring in your
psycho killer or whatever that nutcase is.
C'mon man.
Ya gotta take these cuffs off.
What'll I do if things get ugly around here?
Look, I'm not gonna run.
I couldn't go anywhere if I
wanted to, there's cops everywhere.
Fine... But stay by me.
Hey Migi...
We should help out, too.
We can at least sense who the enemy is.
That's a bad idea.
Sorry sir... Please just cooperate.
You can't threaten innocent civilians, you hear me!
Hm.
Um, excuse me sir...
I would like to be evacuated now please.
Uh? Uhhh...
I see... So this is it.
Uh... Hold on!
They're all on top of each other.
I can't tell who's who!
Don't break formation.
Please walk single file everyone.
What's wrong?
Ah! Ahh!
Oh God! They're all over the place!
Ahh...
One, two...
Wait! Stop right there!
Ahh...
Not that guy...
That one's human.
Oh, yeah nice shootin' boys!
How could you?
How could you just shoot him down?
Please stand back, sir.
Oh...
Get back in line, now!
No... please wait... I... um...
Now there's one... Kill it now!
Huh?
Our equipment took some hits.
The detection system is down!
Please, everyone, don't panic.
Calm down! Please, calm down!
Waaaahh!
Dammit!
No! Don't shoot!
Ugh!
Uhh...
Wait! Wait... Where are you going?!
Hold it. Nobody leaves.
Forget it. Let 'em go!
Err... Ah!
Everybody down on the ground now!
Put your hands behind your heads.
You've five seconds... Do it now!
Don't stand, no matter what!
If you stand up without permission, you will be shot!
Urrh...
Who the hell are you?!
You can't just come in here and tell us...
Hmph. Guess he was human. Huh...
Uhh... Ooh...
Ah! Dear God!
This building is crawling with parasites...
And we are going to neutralize every last one of them.
So listen very closely.
If you consider yourself to be human...
then you need to do exactly as we say!
There's gotta be something we can do...
Anything...
Let's expand our hunting range.
Kisa-ragi Squad has this zone...
You see anyone suspicious, shoot them.
Sir!
Mutsuki and Satsuki Squad survivors...
You're reassigned to my Shingetsu Squad...
And we'll clean up the rest of the building.
Yes, sir!
Hey. The lunatic's coming with me.
What... me?
Don't go trying anything stupid...
Or I'll make you regret it.
I'm seeing monsters all over the place out here... Haha...
This is all just self-defense...
Or uh... or, or is it...
we have to do our public duty...
It's an emergency, right? It's special... circumstances...
Huh? Whatcha babblin' about?
Hands behind your head!
No! Stop! Now!
So, why aren't you trying to escape?
I think it would be relatively easy
for you to get through the cordon, Mayor.
For you, as well.
Not just yet...
I want to watch a little longer, to
learn more about the enemy's battle tactics.
What are you planning to do now?
I guess...
I feel that it's useless to run
away at this late stage of the game.
Oh? Very well.
Now I can do whatever I wish.
Right, understood... So then, where is Hirokawa right now?
Uzuki Squad encountered his group
while en route to the city council wing.
But unfortunately, we lost contact
with them in the second-floor hallway.
Tch!
We're gonna split up here...
Shingetsu Squad, main wing...
Mutsuki and Satsuki Squads,
you head over to the council wing.
Yes sir!
Hey murderer...
Your assignment's changed,
you're going to be accompanying
the Mutsuki-Satsuki joint team.
The name's Uragami, Captain.
And you're a murderer too, are you not?
But sir... you won't be able to identify the enemy.
Don't worry about me...
it's getting easier now...
I'm starting to get the hang of spotting those things.
Uh?
Uzuki Squad has been located.
It looks like they've engaged Hirokawa's
group and were completely wiped out.
Heh... Just dreadful...
Ah... Hey... I...
It's not what it looks like...
Hmm... Sorry guys...
Those're humans... Fornicatin' humans.
Jesus Christ. Seriously?
At a time like this? Get outta there!
Guess they couldn't wait, huh?
But'cha know... if I hadn't been here,
they'd both be dead now wouldn't they.
Hm.
Oh... thank goodness...
You've got to help me!
Fire.
Huh? Yes, but, sir.
Uh-uh... Ooh...
How could you tell?
He wasn't down on the first floor hall.
Huh?
Listen to me...
just shoot everyone.
The humans had the upper hand right from the start...
But the assault force's objective
was never to protect civilian lives...
It was strictly to eliminate the enemy.
And by making that their priority...
they successfully prevented a panic.
And while it's true that some human
lives were unfortunately sacrificed...
the parasites were effectively wiped out.
We are actually quite frail.
We're nothing more than a life form
that isn't able to survive on its own.
So, please... Don't be too hard on us.
Seriously, man. I'm practically right up in front here.
What's the point of having you at the rear?
Stop right there!
Ah! Please don't shoot me!
I'm not one of them! I swear!
Shoot him.
Huh?
AAHH! No!
What is you damn problem?! Shoot him now!
Aahh!
Tch! The hell were you aiming?
Go! After him!
Urgh! Aah!
So, they're using large shotgun
rounds to destroy the body.
It appears to be a rather effective technique.
Hmm...
What about him?
He sure seems like one.
Yeah, yeah... Fine, go ahead and shoot 'im. Why not?
Just shoot everybody alright. I don't care anymore.
H-huh?
WAAAAAHHH!
Hey! What the hell?! Where do you think you're going?!
AAAHHH!
This way...
There's much more room over here.
Dammit, Uragami!
Ah!
You son of a bitch! This was
your plan all along wasn't it?!
You... You did see that guy back
there, didn't you, are you blind?!
You had to see it, right?! Are you
telling me that freak looked human to you?
What did you say?
What's this? There aren't more of you?
I'll let you have two minutes.
Fire!
Why doesn't he drop?
He-he's not even bleeding!
Uh...
Do you... do you hear that?
What is that?
It's coming from inside him!
Ah...
Well, how kind of you to give me
so much to work with, gentlemen.
Ungh!
What in God's name... How in the hell?
Go for his arm!
Ahh!
Ugh!
Really now...
Some of them are actually still alive.
I see...
They appear to be equipped with body armor.
Uh?
A valiant effort...
Uh...
But I'm sure you're aware... It was all for naught.
You'll be dead in thirty seconds.
Hm? What was that?
It looks as though the Mutsuki-Satsuki team is gone.
They're all gone.
Roger...
Send Yayoi to the council wing.
Hehehe...
Enough! Let's get you back, Uragami.
Are you outta your damn mind?
Ah...
I said that's enough.
Ah... Hello.
Next time: "Sex and Spirit"