Ah, hello.
Yayoi Squad has engaged Hirokawa.
Do not let him get away.
Make sure he's taken out.
Welcome, gentlemen,
so nice of you to come.
It is certainly an honor to have you all here.
When it comes to the art of death,
every species on Earth pales in
comparison to that of the human race.
Yet, as I look at the fine instruments you hold,
I feel they could be put to a FAR greater purpose.
Such implements of force can be
used not for simple eradication,
but rather the protection of
the balance of our very existence.
That's right: To purge those
who offer nothing to our community.
Because when put to task, all
of us must admit an obvious truth:
That not everyone in our vast population
deserves to be part of our family.
Instead, they attack our
values. They attack our ecosystem,
in a crime of arrogant apathy far
greater than that of crude genocide.
Yet, hope is here.
It's staring you in the face.
It may be different and seem frightening,
but you will come to cherish it.
The time has come that we must hold our own
predators in high regard, and in fact protect them.
And the most fascinating thing,
is that these predators will ultimately
allow us to grow stronger and more powerful.
They are our saviors, our masters.
And they will restore the balance that we could not.
Hirokawa...
Not long ago, someone on Earth had a passing thought:
"All life is sacred and must therefore be protected."
Who do you think you are, you monster?!
This is why I cannot abide my own kind.
If defiance is truly your intention,
do not pretend and act otherwise.
Even environmental conservation is
skewed in favor of our own hubris,
a viewpoint most refuse to acknowledge!
We MUST consider all life on Earth, not
just the prosperity of a single species!
That presumes your own rule over creation!
Humans repeatedly claim they're on the side of justice,
and what greater justice is there than natural selection?!
The human race has been inhabited,
and relinquished of the sacred duty
by preserving the balance of life on Earth!
Thus, exposing YOU as nothing
but parasites infesting this planet!
It's you...
You are the infection!
We're the... infection?
Fire!
What's wrong?
The mayor... was a human.
He what?!
Hirokawa, huh?
Right up to the end, I never did quite understand him.
Reiko Tamura was especially intrigued by him,
and had several initiatives underway.
But that's all over now.
This must be rather upsetting...
a human like this among you.
No... no... I don't...
Wh-what the hell is this? What happened here?!
I'm tellin' ya, this was that guy from before.
He's more powerful than the others are.
I mean you can't even shoot him.
Report.
Hirokawa has been neutralized, but...
Well, another parasite has arrived.
We'll meet Minazuki Squad and head over there.
We're on our way now.
U-Uragami...
You bastard!
Oh man, my hand's all numb.
Guess that's why knives've always been my thing.
Say "cheese."
Holy shit!
It blew his whole hand off!
You had to know this would happen,
Detective. I mean, I was already on death row.
I've got nothing to lose.
Now to get outta here.
That big guy is so powerful
he'll break through eventually,
and that's MY chance.
Reiko Tamura would often question our purpose here,
and wonder why we were born.
I guess... none of that matters anymore.
The reason for my existence is to fight.
Shinichi, let's go home.
There's no point in us staying any longer.
After all, our work here is finished now.
How can you be so sure about that?
And besides, we really have to see
if that Goto guy can be taken down.
It doesn't matter.
The humans have already won.
If they really wanted to, they could
use cannons or missiles or even bombs.
They can do whatever they want.
At this stage, we, as individuals,
no longer have any say in what happens.
You're acting strange, Migi.
Fire!
How can he move like that?
You can do better than that.
Humans are supposed to be the most intelligent
life forms on the planet. Isn't that right?
He can dodge gunfire?!
I can do more than that.
I'm improving all the time.
Please, please don't shoot me!
Open fire.
They're beyond our help.
No, don't!
If this monster is able to move like this,
then that drastically limits our firing options indoors.
We're at too great a risk of shooting our own men.
We need a more open area.
Let's fall back!
To the roof. Let's go, now!
One more round.
But shouldn't that have finished him?
Stay vigilant. We need to be twice as
cautious, and engage him on our terms.
This guy's comfortable using
the walls, floor, and ceiling.
Standard indoor combat tactics are useless here.
This place is his lair,
and we're inside it!
It's sad to think we humans lost our advantage
in a structure we created.
All right, split up left and right!
We'll take him out here!
What talk is this?
Son of a bitch...
You're all alone, Captain.
You don't have any more men left to help you out.
Although, I should say...
They wouldn't've helped anyway.
That body of yours seems to be rather special.
It's like it's armored!
That's correct.
But it doesn't protect my entire body, unfortunately.
There are gaps.
Through sheer firepower, you actually
got the better of me to some extent.
Even if I harden my cells,
deflecting gunshots head-on is still a risky proposition,
which is why I deflect them at an angle.
Godammit! Don't toy with me!
Although I am able to dodge gunfire,
it's not that I actually move faster than a bullet.
I just predict its trajectory based
on my opponents' eye and hand movements.
Did you hear that?
I think it came from the roof.
What the hell are you, anyway?
As you can clearly see, I am
simply a pure, feral life form.
You're... an abomination.
And what are humans exactly?
Go to Hell.
Oh a flamethrower, huh?
That might've been a good idea, kid.
See that? Something fell from up there.
Hey, what was that for?
I told you we should leave.
Well, well, it's you.
Ah, Goto!
I see...
So you were involved with this attack, too.
And it was a rather intense battle at that.
In fact, it seems that all
others of my kind were destroyed.
And if you were a part of this operation,
there's still some unfinished business here.
I'm sure killing you will be most satisfying.
And besides, I believe I need to kill you.
And when it's done, I will move forward.
"Move forward"?
Your aim was actually quite accurate,
if you intended to target the heart.
What in the hell?
But this fight must wait.
There are too many others,
and I'm feeling a bit tired today anyway.
He... he just flew!
Shinichi Izumi, what have you done?
Huh?! I didn't do anything!
I didn't! I swear!
Wait right there!
A lot of men died, well trained men...
men under Yamagishi's command.
You saw it. All it took was one monster,
and it was able to overtake us.
You expect me to believe you knew nothing?
You're doing it again.
You're hiding something, dammit!
No, I'm not! I honestly had no idea that just
one of these things could do something like this!
A head!
Someone's head fell off the roof!
Hey, Shinichi.
Shinichi, that was a terrible dream.
Migi, how do you know what I dreamed about?
I just do somehow.
Will Goto be coming after us?
He most definitely will, and it'll be soon.
I could sense how strong his resolve was.
So... We're going to die.
No, we can't give up that easily.
We should try to go get some help.
Like Uda, for example.
Forget it.
We can't drag those two into this.
Well, we can get the humans to help.
They can deploy the military against him again.
How can we do that?!
And even if we did, countless more people will die!
And we'd be responsible for their deaths!
Why should I care?
Migi...
You never really do change, do you?
Dad...
I'm afraid I might be saying goodbye soon.
And Mom...
I might be seeing you again soon.
I got it.
Why don't we just run somewhere far away?
I mean he's not... He can't be so obsessed
he'd track us across the country right?
Hey, Migi, are you asleep?
Ah! I forgot to go to school today.
Hahaha... school...
Are you asleep?!
Migi!
If he shows up now...
If he... if he shows up now...
Hey!
You gonna apologize, asshole.
I... I'm sorry.
He's totally scared, dude!
Get down on your knees.
Please forgive me. I am so sorry.
That's a good boy.
I apologized, didn't I?!
You got what you wanted, huh?!
I said it! I said it!
Are you happy now?!
Shinichi?
Um, hey there.
Ah, so did you really skip school again today?
Uh-huh.
I sure did.
Just the kind of guy I am, ya know?
I'm a scumbag.
Uh, what was that?
You're acting weird.
Wha...
Stop that! It hurts!
Please, let go.
Stop it!
Shinichi?!
Your idea to run far away may not be a bad one, Shinichi.
Oh, hey. Guess you were awake then, huh?
Just run away... Yeah...
And right when I'm finally so close to graduating.
Shinichi...
Your senses seem to be a little dull at the moment.
Well, hello there.
How did you know you could find me here?
You really like this park, don't you?
I kinda like it, too.
I'm sorry about before.
I didn't mean to scare you like that.
You're a pretty mysterious guy, y'know, Shinichi?
Sometimes, I just don't get you at all.
It's cold out here.
You wanna come over to my place?
So we can talk?
There's nobody else home now.
Your true nature shows when your life is on the line.
And it turns out, I'm just pathetic.
All I can think of is that I don't wanna die.
I want to live!
And I wanna keep living.
I've often told Migi he's cold-blooded, but...
but I don't have any right to say that.
When all's said and done,
I've only made it this far by stepping on those around me.
Shinichi...
You're actually a pretty good guy, aren't you?
The two of us have gone through
a lot together, haven't we?
So even if something bad happens, we'll be okay.
We can make it.
Murano...
I think that I might...
love you.
Shinichi, that's a heavy thing to just drop on a girl.
I will live!
I'll do whatever it takes!
Next time: "Repose and Awakening"