Uh? Ah...
I have punctured the boy's heart...
Your human host is now dead.
And you will follow in a matter of minutes.
Now you must accept your fate as one
who was unsuccessful in seizing the head.
There's no time to waste.
A direct hit to the heart is critical
and cannot be repaired very quickly.
At this rate, Shinichi's brain
will soon be rendered inoperable...
My only available option is to merge myself...
with his heart.
As I am sealing the wound,
I must initiate heart function while
also circulating the blood within myself.
The parasite we just encountered seems to have
successfully relocated to another host's head,
but this is a far riskier venture.
Ah...
Good. It seems this might actually work.
But I can't expect an instantaneous recovery.
I'll slowly gather cells from throughout
his body to aid in the healing process.
In the meantime, I will begin to
gradually return to his right hand
through his bloodstream...
Huh? Shinichi's absent again today?
Yeah... I heard the teacher tried calling
his house a few times, but no one answered.
I'm really worried.
Wanna swing by there later?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, but we don't know where he lives...
I do... I sorta went home with
him after school the other day.
Huh?!
Hey, Murano!
I didn't know you and Shinichi were a thing.
Is it serious?
What?! No! I mean we're not a thing.
Oh yeah, excuse me. You just went
home with him "casually"... Hehe...
Akiho, this is none of your business.
Quit being so nosey, get your own life alright.
C'mon, I want all the juicy
details! What'd you do at his house?
So are Shinichi and Murano... Really dating?
I don't know. Who cares!
C'mon, girl spill it! Gimme some dirt!
Could you just drop it?
Seriously.
Sugar.
Uhh...
Hmm...
Huh?!
Hm...
The wound... It's sealed...
But it looks like it's been fused together or something.
Migi?
Did Migi heal me?
Ahh...
It wasn't...
It wasn't a dream?!
Hello?
Ah, I'm glad we finally got you!
I'm calling from Sakurazaki Hospital.
Have I reached Mr. Kazuyuki Izumi's residence?
Yes...
Ah! My Dad! That's my Dad!
Oh, don't worry. He's fine.
He's getting some rest at the moment, but he's
in stable condition, and he's not in any danger.
I just wanted to suggest, when you come to visit,
if you could bring him a change of clothes and maybe some
I'll be right there!
Oh!
Shinichi?
Um... You haven't been to school lately,
so I came to check on you.
You mentioned that your parents were on vacation,
so I was worried that maybe you had gotten sick,
and you were just laid up here all by yourself...
Uh...
Found out my dad was in an accident while they were away.
Oh?!
Wow... your mom must really be struggling right now.
Uhh...
Oh!
Look... I won't be back at school for a while.
Uh...
Shinichi...
Shinichi!
You... you will...
come back, right?
I'll kill it! That thing is dead!
It was able to get away...
but not before Dad had the chance to
see what that monster really looks like...
in its true form.
So then the male...
has not yet returned?
But how did it find our address?
From their luggage... or at their hotel?
I'm sure it won't be long before that
thing figures out which hospital Dad's in.
I don't have much time... I have to hurry!
Um... um, excuse me!
Hm?
Are you doing okay?
You uh, you look like you're kinda worried or
something, so I thought I'd see if you're alright.
Are you from Sakurazaki?
Yeah. I am.
So, do you know Sakurazaki Hospital?
Oh! Yes. I know where that is.
So, Mr. Izumi, it was the night of the 18th, correct?
That's when you say your wife was killed.
Yes.
Has she...
Has my wife's body been found yet, Detective?
Mr. Izumi...
I believe your wife is very much alive.
Huh?
On the 18th...
that's the day on which you reportedly
struck your head and fell into the ocean...
Your wife returned to the hotel alone about 9:00 pm.
That's impossible!
We did confirm...
The staff at hotel's front desk said they spoke with her.
She told them you had to leave on urgent business,
but that she would stay on for one more night.
She then checked out the following morning.
No... That can't be right!
It had to be somebody else!
Um sir, the hotel staff confirmed the burn
mark located on the woman's right forearm.
They've stated that they're certain she
was the same person who arrived with you.
Mr. Izumi...
In my opinion,
I believe that the terrible shock you've suffered
is causing you to confuse reality
from before your traumatic accident
with perhaps a nightmare you had afterwards.
No way... That was not a dream!
I know what I saw!
Ugh... Uh...
This is it.
Thank you so much.
Hehe... See ya!
Yes. He's right down there.
Huh?
Dad, I'm here!
Shinichi.
Dad... I uh...
I'm sorry that I made you worry, Son.
Dad...
But Mom... she's...
Uh, I can't handle this...
It hurts so much I can barely talk...
and... and I can't even cry.
Shinichi, what's wrong?
It's Mom, Dad she's...
Shinichi... About that...
It seems that something has happened to your mother...
and well, we don't know where she is.
Huh?
But, Dad...
You saw it!
Saw what?
What do you mean?
Well... The doctor says that I'm confused... like
looks like I hit my head pretty hard, Son.
But Dad... No...
I've asked the police to keep up their search for her...
The doctor wants me to stay here for a while
longer, but it's nothing serious. So please don't worry.
"Don't worry"?
How can you even say that?!
Shinichi, did something happen back home?
What? Well of course something happened!
Mom has been murdered by some monster!
Dad, you know that!
Is that what I told you?
I told you all that nonsense... on the phone?
Ugh... I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry! I was losing it!
What? Does he really think it's all in his head?
Son, I'm going to recover and be just fine.
I want you to try and take it easy
for a few days, and go back home.
I know it's tough, but hang in
there just a little bit longer.
If you have any problems, then you
can always go to your uncle's house-.
Dad. I need to tell you something.
Hmm?
It's about Mom and the monster-
Shinichi!
Uh...
Please. Not right now...
Dad...
He's crying...
He knows, doesn't he?
He knows that Mom is dead.
I want to tell him the truth
about what that monster really is...
About the creature that killed her.
If only Migi...
If only Migi was actually an ally of humanity.
Here, I brought you some clothes.
So where are you going to stay, Shinichi?
Here with you.
C'mon you know you can't get a good night's rest in here.
They told me about a hotel that's right by the beach.
That's where you should be staying.
I'm at a hospital...
and Migi's asleep...
This could be my chance to get him looked at!
No, now's not the time.
I need his abilities to find the enemy.
And fight them.
I hate to admit it, but...
I have no choice but to trust Migi and rely on him.
Huh?! The Sakurazaki Hotel, is that far away from here?
Um, no, not far at all.
In fact, it's just a few blocks away from here.
A few blocks...
That's at the edge of Migi's
ability to detect our enemies.
If that thing shows up at the hospital,
we might not be able to make it in time.
This is perfect.
Right behind the hospital.
Hello, excuse me.
Uh...
I guess, you'll be needing a room?
It's you!
Hehe...
Hey, Mom! We have a guest checking in!
Dad must've seen it...
He saw Mom get killed.
At some point,
I'm going to have to tell him everything I know.
But for now...
I just have to keep him alive...
and avenge Mom's death.
Excuse me... your dinner's ready for you downstairs.
Get it while it's hot!
Thanks.
Hm-hm.
I could totally tell that she was coming.
Are the walls that thin,
or has my hearing somehow improved?
Shinichi.
I thought I might keep this to myself,
but I've decided to tell you.
It's very important.
The feelings you have for your
family are incredibly strong...
However, your feelings for me
are practically nonexistent...
Actually, I know you think of me
as more of a hinderance at best.
And while we do act as allies, one
could say that we are really enemies
forced into a difficult situation.
Yeah, so what's your point?
You see, during the time that I
was repairing your damaged body,
it would seem that my body underwent a change as well.
A change?
That's correct.
I have now developed a weakness that
others of my kind have never experienced.
Every day now, for about four hours,
I fall completely and totally asleep.
That's it? But you've always gone to sleep.
Not like this...
Previously, even the slightest
disturbance would awaken me immediately.
For instance, if you were surprised,
or if your breathing was uneven.
Or if...
one of my associates approached within 300 meters.
"Associates"?
Correct...
But since this change has occurred,
it appears that while asleep, I am able to detect nothing.
So, if an enemy were to appear
during that four-hour sleep cycle...
it would mean...
the end for both of us.
Oh...
Repairing your heart
meant that I had to spend an extended
period of time detached from your arm.
And as a result, my physiology has been slightly altered.
Why would you wait so long to tell me about this?!
Well, ever since one of my
fellow parasites killed your mother,
you have been harboring a great
deal of hostility toward me.
You must realize that revealing one's
weakness to an enemy is extremely dangerous,
so that's why I said nothing until now.
However, I determined that if you
weren't made aware of this problem...
the situation would become
even more dangerous for us both...
Do you understand?
Yes, I do... But I don't really think of you
as an enemy anymore, Migi.
You did save my life, you know.
That's not entirely accurate, of course...
Since there was my life to consider as well.
Morning!
Oh... good morning.
Oh, hey... There's more color in your cheeks...
Yesterday you were looking kinda ragged, ya' know.
Hmm...
So I guess you slept well, then.
Oh, thanks.
It's been a while since you
were able to read the paper, huh?
It has. When I fell into the water...
my tablet and my cell phone
were both completely destroyed.
Then we'll have to get you new ones when you get home.
Uh-huh... When're you uh?
I'm gonna stay a bit longer and see how things go, okay?
Whenever Migi is in a deep sleep...
I'll have to use my own eyes to keep watch.
I'll try to have Migi sleep
during the day if that's possible,
when people are around and
there's less chance of an attack.
Now, if that thing does show
up here, how would it approach?
Migi told me not to fight unless he was awake...
but I may not be given a choice.
I'll have to defend myself somehow.
Besides, I am not going to run from my mother's killer!
Hello there!
Uh...
Hey, uh...
It's...
It's Makiko, isn't it?
You can call me Maki.
Have you been sitting out here all this time?
I guess you must be really worried about your father, huh?
Um... Well, yeah...
And I don't really have much else to do.
Ah...
Um, do you have a girlfriend?
Huh?
Shinichi. I sense one.
Huh...
It's just about 300 meters away,
in the direction of the beach.
It's here!
Hey Maki, which way is it to get to the beach?
Huh?
If you head straight down the road back to my place and...
Huh...
Wait, hold on!
If you just go straight, you'll hit the seawall!
Stop!
Hold on!
Hey!
He's so fast!
Shinichi. I need to confirm.
Yeah, what?!
Is it all right to kill her?
Yes! Something like that cannot be
allowed to roam free in this world...
I cannot allow it!
Ahh...
You just took off before I got the chance to
finish telling you exactly how to get there.
To get down to the beach, you're gonna
have to circle around the west side... Huh?
Whoa!
Huh? I just saw it down at the far end of the bridge.
This is it!
Shinichi, I have something else I need to tell you.
And it's something about you.
It has finally become clear to me that you have...
Just save it!
You're not getting away!
You will pay...
for what you did to my mother!
You're dead!
Next time: "A Dark Night's Passing"