Good evening, Tamura.
We can try to hide them,
but they can't be suppressed, can they?
The strongest signals that we emit
are those which harbor animosity.
I know of your intentions.
Get on with it.
Why did you not make any attempt to escape?
Because I was intrigued.
I fell prey to my curiosity.
Though I must wonder, are there
any others who support your actions?
No, it's only the three of us.
Hirokawa and Goto know nothing about what we're planning.
I see.
And your reason?
Call it an instinct.
I believe that, going forward, you will prove
to be an extremely dangerous liability for us.
Very well, then.
You remind me a lot of Mr. A.
Mr. A?
We parasites have a tendency to think and operate in a
manner that is normally quite logical and uncomplicated.
I thought that temperament would make
it easy to create a united organization,
but I was mistaken.
Still, for the parasites, myself included,
to have such individual differences...
or rather, such personalities...
makes me very pleased.
I'm actually moved by your decision to eliminate me.
Well then,
shall we get started?
With only three of you, I hope
you have some sort of plan in place.
Stop her! Kill her!
The muscle strength of my host is superior to yours.
Therefore, even in single combat, I would win.
You seem so certain.
Too slow...
Huh?
You can keep that.
What is she thinking, splitting in two?
I'll go after her.
Tamura entered his body.
Are... Are you okay?
Yeah.
Right there, that's her!
Uh, excuse me!
Huh?
Why are you putting rocks in your bag?
It's dangerous out here.
Did you just see...
We saw the weirdest thing back there.
We saw a lady just now who looked like she
only had half her head, and she was, uh...
she was running around laughing and it was crazy.
Just half of her head? Oh dear, how strange..
I still... I still have my
head, but it's empty inside! See?
She's lost her purpose,
and can no longer think rationally.
There's no way half a parasite can
maintain control of the host body.
It's suicide.
Such a waste.
For one so famed for her intellect,
how sad for her to die this way.
My legs... I can't feel my legs!
What is this?!
It's not me! Not ME!
One of us is dead.
Ah, you can survive by burrowing inside.
But now, can you really take over
completely when you're split in two?
Will you be able to defeat me
using a body that's so badly damaged?
Stop it! This is MY body!
Stop it! NO!!
Who am I even talking to now?
Is it Hikawa? Or is it Reiko Tamura?
Please stop! I'm on your side! It's me!
Really, then why are you moving toward me?
Dammit! I can't control anything below my neck!
Just give in.
And die along with that fragment of Reiko Tamura!
But I am on your side!
What have you done?
Is this really your strategy?
The body you attempted to take over now lies in shreds.
Just, come out!
How long do you plan to keep hiding in there?
The human part of our body is our weakness.
You should make your strike without all the grandstanding.
Even if the host body is destroyed,
our parasite cells survive for a short time on their own
and emit brainwaves.
You're obviously experiencing this phenomenon right now.
The strongest wavelengths we parasites
emit are animosity and murderous intent,
as you're well aware.
The ability to detect these is quite important.
It's how we determine whether an individual
who's outside our range of vision is friend or foe.
But you cut your own ally into pieces,
thereby surrounding yourself with fragments of her flesh,
all of which continue to emanate her signal.
That's right.
All those fragments were acting as camouflage,
masking my transmissions as I approached you.
Goddamn you, that's impossible!
Do you know where you came from, and
where it is you're ultimately headed?
Have you ever pondered about such
things, as a human being might do?
Goodbye, Kusano.
Hmm... cannibalism...
Hmm? It's unlocked.
You are more troublesome than I thought, Mr. Detective.
Huh? He left?
Well, when did he leave the hotel?
Dad, what are you doing at home?!
I'm afraid he hasn't been here.
Why the hell are you there?!
Good morning.
I take it you're there to kill him.
As a matter of fact, it's quite the contrary.
I was hoping to contact YOU regarding a personal matter.
You know where Hikari Park Number One is?
It's very important that you meet
me there this afternoon, at 5:20 PM.
What are you talking about?
I need to give you something.
Seeing as how you're something
in-between human and parasite,
it's perfect for you.
A mother...
It's not right! Something's very wrong!
Who are you? Ryoko!
Where is my Ryoko?!
No one's home today, either.
I wonder if something's happened?
Uh, hey! Um, Ms. Izumi?
Where is... Where is Shinichi?
Sorry, he isn't here.
I see...
So, are you, uh, Shinichi's mother?
I'm not.
Do I really look that old to you?
Uh, no.
But please tell me.
Do you know what's going on?
Shinichi...
He's caught up in something bad, isn't he?
What do you mean by bad?
Well, I, uh...
I can tell that something is definitely messed up.
Shinichi would never say anything about it, but still...
You're worried, aren't you?
Worried about him?
I'm quite jealous.
Huh?
Don't trouble yourself.
Shinichi's actually much stronger than he looks.
And he'll be back home very soon, perfectly fine.
But when is "soon"?
Where have I seen her before?
Seriously though, where did Shinichi run off to?
It's just weird.
I swear.
Doesn't he know how worried we are about him?
He'll be back, soon.
It could even be today.
You... you will...
come back, right?
He'll be back.
Hey!
It's okay. You don't have to worry, Murano.
He will...
He has to!
What's wrong?
Where you going?
Sorry! Go ahead without me!
I think this is...
this is where Kana lived.
I wonder if she knew...
the Shinichi that I don't.
No, please wait!
What the...
How is that girl so damn fast?!
Hey!
Goodness, young lady.
A nice, young girl like you shouldn't
resort to using such foul language.
Uh...
Hmm?
What's this?
Ah, there, there, there.
Hey, little fella...
You're good with children.
Well, my wife was the only one
with a job there for quite a while.
So I spent lots of time with my little girl.
Aw, you're okay, you're okay.
I guess I must've gotten here too early.
Then walk around a little bit.
I'd like to get a layout of the terrain.
Sure.
Even a cold-blooded monster still values her child.
I've been doing some extensive research on you humans.
And on some level, I'm able to comprehend your
rather irrational behavior.
Really?
Well, I guess that's good.
But you know, you'll never fully understand, right?
You don't know what it means to be human.
How it really feels to be a parent!
How could you possibly grasp the depth of
the sadness that comes with losing everything?
Everything that's ever mattered
to you in your entire life?!
You can't do it!
Because I could kill this
innocent child right here and now,
and you wouldn't even so much as bat an eye, would you?
You'd just move on like nothing happened!
And you know it!
This baby can't really be yours anyway.
This baby's human.
What is this?
I've never felt this sort of signal from one of my kind.
It's Reiko Tamura's brainwave, but...
What is this emotion?
You could never love it.
You're completely cold and dead inside.
If I could just make you feel even one tiny shred
of the grief I've had to suffer through, then...
I... I wouldn't do it.
I would never...
No human could ever kill a helpless child.
You... you don't...
I didn't think...
I didn't think a monster like you...
Th-that was a sur-surprise.
Yes, I'm rather surprised myself.
Reiko Tamura has started moving.
She's headed for the corner on the opposite side.
So, over this way?
What am I even doing here?
I can't believe I came all this way.
There's a... There's a man! He's over there!
Kuramori!
Are you okay?
Are you able to talk to me?!
Ah, hey there, Detective...
Where are they?!
Are they up on the hill?!
Just go! And if you spot one of them, do not hesitate!
Yes, sir!
Was it Reiko Tamura?!
Did she do this?
Does Hirokawa know what she's up to?!
There's a... a woman...
She's dressed in white... She's holding...
And she's holding a little baby.
And there's some blood...
My... my blood got on the baby's clothes.
Right! We won't let her get away!
There's one more thing I need to know.
You mentioned you had a "partner" in your report.
Is he a human?
What's his name?
Please, you gotta tell me!
He is... human...
Like me, he had a small family, and it was taken from him.
He too...
He also s-suffers...
Talk to me! Tell me who he is!
Yoko... Yumi...
I'm coming home.
I'll see you soon...
Kuramori!
Stay with me, buddy! Come on!
I... I would never...
I wouldn't do it...
The baby...
No! Stay with me!
Kuramori, please!
You were an honorable man...
one of the greatest of heroes.
And I swear you will NOT have died in vain,
Detective!
I understand!
White clothes, holding a baby.
Don't move! What's your name?
Answer me, now!
I just pray that Hirokawa's group
hasn't found out about what we're planning.
We cannot let Reiko Tamura get away.
We have to finish her off.
Now!
Next time: "More Than Human"