I'm sorry but I have some bad news for you, Shinichi.
What is it Migi?
What's going on!
You need to hurry up, right now.
Are you sure it's him?
These signals are very intense and focused.
And given the speed of approach, he must be in a car.
Here. Take a right at the corner.
Great! Now I'm a thief.
Such matters are trivial at this point.
So, uh, Migi...
I have to ask, when did you learn to drive a car?
I did master human language
in a single day, if you recall.
Okay, I need a favor from you.
Please take us out to somewhere less populated.
If we try to fight him in the
city, a lot of people could die.
Very well.
Also, I have an idea that's definitely worth a shot.
Hm?
Well?
It didn't work. He's still alive.
He's extremely resilient.
Let's get out of here.
Where can we go?
Just run.
Okay. Stop here.
Why are we stopping now?
I thought we couldn't afford to waste time, right?!
Take a breath.
Until he catches up, we really should strategize.
"Strategize" now?!
We are about to be chopped into little pieces!
Shinichi, I know what you're feeling.
Anyone would fear being killed.
I'm afraid, too.
But this... this is our moment of truth.
Ah...
Now remember, you have a strength
that other humans don't possess.
And you can be calm, no matter what the circumstances are.
Now, put your hand on your chest
and breathe deeply, like always.
Good. Well done.
Listen.
Yes, Goto's abilities outclass ours in every possible way.
Simple logic says we have almost no chance of winning...
In which case, I say we shift our line of thought.
If it's not possible for us to
win even if we work together...
then maybe we ought to give working separately a try.
Do what?
Sometimes sheer strength can be beaten... by pure chance.
"Chance," huh?
I took a lighter from that car,
and I put it inside your left pocket.
Well now...
They've used the branches to
spread out in all four directions.
How uninspired.
This will be a race against time.
The human body is our lifeline,
but it's also our greatest weakness.
The cells within you that were once
part of me have since been altered..
And are now completely integrated.
Therefore, Goto won't be able to detect you.
He'll come straight toward me
without ever noticing you at all.
If this fight goes on too long, I'll shrivel up and die.
It's indeed a reckless plan...
But that's exactly why Goto
is not likely to see it coming.
What's this? No counterattack at all?
Where is the human boy?
Once I've found and destroyed the host, it's finished.
His body is protected by an armor
of semi-hardened parasitic cells...
but I doubt very much that they cover the entire surface.
That said, there's no time to
search for the gaps in his armor.
But I believe the area least likely to be
protected, and therefore the most optimal target...
would be... his head.
Controlling the multiple parasites throughout his torso
and limbs must require a tremendous amount of energy.
So it must be very difficult for the head already.
That means, if we can remove the head,
he should lose control,
disabling enough protection for
us to be able to destroy the body.
Come on, Migi...
If we don't hurry up, then you're not gonna make it...
We'll have just one chance.
Goto's speed and power are far greater
than mine, so decapitating him won't be easy.
Uh oh. My consciousness is already starting to fade.
I'll have to hurry.
But I still don't have a good angle.
Come out! You cowards!
Am I really that terrible?!
Spreading out in all directions is
nothing but temporary camouflage at best!
You should be using your brains
to fight, not run and hide!
Go now! Do it!
Was that my voice?
There you are.
Hmm?
When exposed directly to fire, Goto's surface
cells will reflexively break away from his control...
And when that happens...
U-ugh...
Damn! Not deep enough!
That's not good.
Migi!
Stay back, Shinichi!
Are you okay?
We have failed.
Well, this is quite a surprise... Well done.
Go, now! Hurry!
But you...
Just go!
Both of us don't have to die!
But still... Migi...
What are you doing?! Get out of here now!
Goodbye, Shinichi.
This is our farewell...
I'm pleased I didn't take over
your brain when we first met...
Because of that, you and I were actually
able to create many fond memories together...
as friends.
I'm... fading...
strangely... sleepy...
and I feel... so very...
alone.
Such... must be...
death...
Who's there?!
Uh...
Uh... I'm sorry.
You a burglar or somethin?!
I'm not!
But, yeah, I guess... Well... Sorry.
Huh?
I sorta did try to take a drink of some of your water.
Ah, did ya now...
I guess that water isn't even free anymore.
Uh, I'm sorry...
Well... Um...
I should be going...
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Okay, wait just a second.
Yes, ma'am?
Looks like you've been hurt, haven't you?
Uh... No, ma'am. This is...
No... On your head...
Guessing ya lost that right arm of yours a long time ago.
No, I'm all right...
And I think the bleeding's already stopped.
Come inside and let's take a look.
But, I...
Well come on...
I don't think any burglar would be this polite.
Besides, you look like you've been crying.
Ah...
Look kid,
I've been livin' on this Earth for a long, long time.
And I can tell if a person's worth a damn or not.
This isn't from a fair fight is it?
Someone bullied you good, didn't they?
Am I right?
Uh-huh...
This cut's pretty deep actually.
Hmph... People out there can do
some awful things to each other.
Uh... Oh...
I never expected such kindness from a stranger.
Thank you so much for everything.
You should probably stay here for the night.
Huh? No, I couldn't possibly.
Where else are you plannin' to go at this hour?
There aren't any hotels around here.
Uh, Ma'am,
do you live out here in the country all by yourself?
Nah, I don't have any more family left.
Oh... I... I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Oh, it's okay, son.
You call me, Mitsuyo.
It's nice to meet you...
My name is... my name's Shinichi Izumi.
Shinichi?
It's nice to meet you, too.
Thanks for this,
I'm sorry to have you help with the shopping.
Oh no, it's no problem.
It's the least I can do.
We should probably tell everybody that you're my nephew.
Nephew?
A lot of strange things have been going on lately.
People really don't like outsiders around.
"Strange things"?
This is what I was talking about.
Some company keeps coming out here and
dumping these huge truckloads of garbage...
One time, it actually caught fire
and nearly burned up the whole mountain.
The big cities are having trouble
finding room for all their crap,
but this is ridiculous.
Yeah...
Everybody around here's been trying to keep watch,
but they still manage to slip in here and dump more.
I don't know how those assholes do it.
Mitsuyo may be a little nuts, but she's got a kind heart.
Still, every time I try to thank her and leave...
she stops me with another barrage of conversation.
With Migi gone, I honestly have no idea what to do next...
so a few hours have turned into several days.
But I can't keep imposing on her forever...
I really must go home and tell Dad what's going on.
About how I lost my arm...
And how I had a friend...
named Migi...
About the day that Migi first showed up...
and all the things we did together...
And about...
about how great Migi was.
He fought for me.
Saved me...
He was intelligent, courageous...
And better than I could ever be.
Because Migi...
is a true hero!
Where am I?
I feel like I've been here before...
What is that?
Uh, who are you?
What's wrong? Did you lose something?
Have I lost...
Oh, that's right. I'm looking for a friend.
Looking for your friend? What do they look like?
Look like?
I can't really remember that.
I'm afraid you're on your own then.
Hey, wait!
I think he looked like you.
That's right! I remember now...
But... He...
He died.
What? Your friend's dead?
Yeah.
No. No he's not.
He's still alive.
What?!
I can tell.
Actually, I know his name, too.
His name...
His name?
Migi!
Ah... Migi!
Some of his cells are still inside me!
Hey, there...! It's me!
Don't you remember?!
Keep it down a little bit...
You're talking in your sleep.
Oh!
It's no good.
There's still some of him in there but...
not enough to do anything.
Migi...
Migi!
I see. Well, I guess it is what it is.
And I suppose I just can't keep you here forever.
I don't know how I'll ever be
able to repay you for your kindness.
Hm...
Hm?
What's your problem?
Don't you know how early it is?
Okay boy, now talk to us!
You really expect us to believe you're her nephew?
Hm? Oh what the hell difference does it make?
Besides, the kid was just about to head out anyway.
Oh, I don't think so!
There's been way too much going on around here lately.
All that illegal trash dumping
and then that crash between
two cars without any drivers...
Uh...
And now, we have a murder on our hands.
Haah?!
Nakano, you said the killer was some outsider, right?
Well take a look at 'im.
I'm tellin' ya, that thing I
saw wasn't just some "outsider"...
This kid has been with me the whole time...
It wasn't no human, ya understand?!
I wasn't just seein' things!
It was three meters tall!
A-and... that thing it had like four front legs!
And a whole bunch of eyes all over the place!
I'm serious!
That's Goto. It's gotta be.
Look, you guys can call me crazy all you want...
But this blood, that's all over my coat is from Kitayama!
And some horrible monster killed and
ate him, he lives right down the road!
You gotta believe me!
So it was around here somewhere?
Yes sir... that's right.
Oh! Uhh...
Ah, that is just horrible.
Wait a second, this is just like
those stories that were in the news.
Uhh... The Mincemeat Murders...
Right.
Understood.
A bunch of local hunters are getting together tomorrow,
and they ought to be able to take
this "monster" of yours down for good.
Hunting rifles... will not destroy him.
Huh? "Destroy him"?
You mean, you know about this monster thing?
Yes, I do...
That's how I wound up here...
He's after me.
Huh?! Oh, quit talking such nonsense.
So this whole thing is my fault!
He followed me here...
And now more people have been killed!
I'm gonna have to keep moving or others will die too.
Come on, son.
All I wanted was to live...
No matter what it took...
Even though some of my friends have already died for me.
But I can't...
I can't keep running away from this forever can I?!
Why can't you?
If it saves you then why not? Just keep on running...
If it can save your life, then you have to do it.
There's no shame in that, son.
Mitsuyo, I can't.
There are things I've avoided that now I must do!
I must sacrifice myself and face that monster...
before any more people out there get slaughtered!
Oh, shut up and cut the crap!
Don't be a jackass!
What is this "sacrifice myself" trash?
How can you talk such bullshit?!
Who the hell do you think you are anyway?!
Sacrifice yourself? What a freakin joke!
What could a snot-nosed brat like you do about it anyway?!
Look, I might not know your whole story...
but I think you need to sit back and
just let the grownups handle this situation.
So, you're determined are ya?
Don't you have someone special out there...
someone you care about?
Someone you know. Someone you wish you knew.
Just someone out there you can't leave behind...
You know...
S-someone that makes you...
human...
Look, I don't know what your plan is or anything...
but you at least owe it to
yourself to give some thought...
to something else... anything else.
Because, son, once you've
thrown it all away, then that's it.
I'm just sayin' don't give up, no matter what,
and remember that there's always an option.
Hold on...
Is there anything I can give you that you can use?
A weapon or whatever?
Uh...
Ah... I'll take this.
Really, you seriously want that old thing?
Well I guess it's better than nothing.
Hm.
Please dear...
Keep that boy safe.
If Goto has changed his appearance...
then there'll be no way to recognize him...
But I guess...
I'll just have to deal with it...
whenever that time comes...
Next time: "Life and Vows"