You. You in the gray coat.
What do you think you're doing?
I think you need to keep your
hands to yourself. That is disgusting.
Ew, that guy's a pervert!
N-no, no! That's not true!
What the hell is your problem! What're you
trying to do? I didn't touch anybody! You're crazy!
Why would you say that?
This year's Kayama Fantasy
Literature Award, the winner is, uh...
It's Dai Yoshimi. "Seventh Transformation," right?
Uh-huh. You read it?
It's about a guy that somehow gains
the ability to communicate with reptiles.
It's completely ridiculous.
Hmm... Huh?
Not this again...
That brings the total to 84.
More Mincemeat Murders?
I hate to say it, but it doesn't even surprise me anymore.
Dinner was great. Thanks.
But, honey, you didn't even eat half of it!
Yeah, sorry.
I may be the only person in the entire world
who actually knows the truth
behind all these horrible killings.
I just don't know what to do about it.
Shinichi!
Morning.
You know, Shinichi, you've changed recently.
Huh? I have?
Yeah.
Really? What're you talking about?
Shinichi...
Huh? I swear I just heard a voice.
Look down here.
Migi? That feels really weird, ya know.
What's wrong Shinichi?
Uh, nothing. I'm fine.
One of my kind is near.
Huh? Again?
It's approaching rapidly.
But there haven't been any Mincemeat Murders around here.
Perhaps the bodies simply haven't been found yet.
It's currently about 70 meters away from us.
Sixty meters...
Not here...
It's inside the building.
Inside the school...
Where is it?
WHO is it?
Is it a guy?
Or a girl?!
It's in here.
Approximately 30 meters away.
Thirty?
Don't make eye contact. It will find us.
It's looking for us as well, but it seems
unable to pinpoint our location in the crowd.
Welcome, good morning, students.
I'd like to introduce our new math
teacher, substituting for Mr. Matsuyama.
HE had to be hospitalized after the
unfortunate traffic accident two days ago.
Now then, I present to you Ms. Tamiya.
I'm Ryoko Tamiya. It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's her.
What?!
And, as of today, Mr. Yamamoto will be
the new homeroom teacher for Class 3-3.
Oh, my God, Murano's class!
Therefore, Ms. Tamiya will act
as assistant homeroom teacher.
No eye contact, Shinichi!
She just looked at me! Do you see that?!
Just look at her... the guys are gonna freak out. Mm-hm!
She found us...
All right, listen up!
Once you do your five laps around the
field, be sure to stretch again to loosen up.
Then split into two groups and set up a match.
You've read up on all the rules.
This surprises me.
After taking over the host, She has managed to
successfully maintain their position in society.
Plus, she functions as a teacher of humans.
She appears to be quite gifted.
What are you praising her for?
We have to do something.
What do you mean?
Well, what if we don't?
She's gonna eat everybody!
No, I highly doubt that.
She wishes to blend in with human society.
I do not believe that she would use anyone
in her immediate social circle as a food supply.
Therefore, I believe they should be safe.
You don't know that.
We should just observe her for now.
With everything that's going on right now,
how can Migi go to sleep?
I mean, what if she suddenly tries to...
All right, class. I want you to use this
formula to solve problems six through twelve.
Mr. Izumi...
Oh, my God!
Is there a problem?
You don't appear to have made any progress.
Huh?! Uh... No, ma'am.
Sorry.
Mr. Izumi, would you please visit
me in the counselor's office later?
Thank you.
Whoa... what'd you do?
Uh...
Dude, how did you do that?
Jesus, what do I have to do to get
myself called to the teacher's office?!
Hellooo? What's wrong with what's sitting right here...
Shinichi knows!
Whatever. You can't teach me all the
things sweet, mature hottie Ms. Tamiya can.
But I don't understand it...
What's she wanna with squirrely ass Shinichi?
Doesn't really make sense.
What's that sposta mean?!
Why you gotta be such a jerk, huh?
Oh, whatever, Shinichi... You
don't know what you're missing.
Shinichi...
She's approximately ten meters away right now.
Oh, so you're awake?
Excuse me.
Please, come on in.
Well then, Mr. Izumi...
You are aware of what I am, yes?
Yeah.
"Yeah"? That's no way to speak to your teacher now, is it?
Oh, there's no need for you to be so anxious.
You should know that I have absolutely
no intentions of killing you right now.
Your right hand should know that.
Besides, if we fought in such close quarters,
we'd both end up being mortally wounded.
I'd like the opportunity to speak with you a bit more.
You think you have time to
meet with me after school today?
Okay.
Huh?!
But what if it's some kind of trap?!
I am totally against this!
How predictable.
Why must humans always be so irrational?
What's that?!
If I wanted to kill you, I already would have.
I am... curious however.
Because I've never seen a case anything like yours before.
I wish to collect more data.
I'd like to exchange information with you...
and discuss our future.
"Future"?
Well, that's all for now.
Hey, Ms. Tamiya!
Yes?
Uh... do you have any plans this afternoon?
I do. I have some student counseling sessions.
Oh, okay.
If you'll excuse me.
Hey I'm going to the bookstore, do you wanna come with me?
Uh-huh.
Huh? Is that...
Shinichi, you should roll up your sleeves.
Why should I do that? We're
not getting into a fight, are we?
Perhaps, something's coming.
Huh?!
Actually, two of my kind are coming.
So it really was a trap?
There's no way to know that for sure yet.
Shinichi, it would be really helpful right now if
you could slow down your heart rate a little bit.
It's making me feel anxious.
I can't do that!
Sorry for the wait.
I'll keep this short...
Meet Mr. A.
Just "A"?
Yes, he has no name.
What is this creature?
Can we even call him one of our kind?
That's enough. There's no merit in killing
one another in a place as public as this.
Interesting... So at this point, you've
only encountered those two types so far.
Yeah.
Now, I'd like to know... In your opinion,
what exactly do you think we are, Mr. Izumi?
Well from everything I've seen...
You're monsters here to feed on the human race.
But you see...
Mr. A and I have experimented,
and had sex with each other.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Please excuse me.
Oh, my God...
And the result might surprise you.
I am now pregnant Mr. Izumi.
So then, here's a question...
This "thing" that I currently
have growing inside my body...
What do you think it might be?
Oh... well, uh...
A human, a normal one.
Good answer. Yes...
The child I am carrying is human, an ordinary human baby.
In which case, what do you think that makes us?
I've no idea.
Nor do I really want to find out.
What I DO know is that you eat humans
in order to keep your human host alive.
And that's what we call cannibalism.
Why would you do something like that?
Have you ever... tried asking
your little friend that question?
I receive nutrients directly through
Shinichi's blood, so I do not experience hunger.
Therefore, I am also at a loss to understand
our own kind's alleged necessity for cannibalism.
Our species cannot reproduce,
and we engage in a sort of pseudo-cannibalism.
I'm not really sure what to call us.
I've given it some thought,
and I consider it strange as well.
Are you actually even life forms? Or what?
Either way, I don't think you're from this planet.
I am leaving now.
Whether or not I find out exactly what I
am, isn't going to change anything for me.
I eat when I feel hungry,
and I get rid of anyone in my way.
And that is it.
That one is dangerous. He must be eliminated.
We didn't merge with our host the same way.
Now...
Humans do sometimes act illogically,
so I will give you a warning.
If you think of me as an enemy,
and decide to make some kind of a
scene, the disadvantage is yours.
You can't change your face.
I've decided it's in my interest
to protect my current human identity,
so I will not behave irrationally.
But if I were provoked, an entire classroom...
Would all be dead in mere seconds.
I believe you have friends in that class, do you not?
Shinichi! Is that you?
She's something else. She was capable of
making you suffer an intense amount of fear.
Shinichi... That's cold.
Huh?
So, uh, yesterday...
you took the bus somewhere.
Where did you go? Murano was worried about you.
Oh... Nowhere.
Shinichi, we are under attack.
I sense nothing but pure killing intent.
Ms. Tamiya? Are you okay?
Idiot.
Somebody help!
Oh, my goodness! Are you all right?
There's an intruder. He went that way.
Okay! Get a hold of the police!
And we must evacuate the students at once!
Time for study hall, class.
Who do you think would try to attack us?
Probably the one from yesterday.
Excuse me, sir.
You are not allowed to be on school property without
a badge from the office! You need to come with me!
Sir, I...
He just neutralized three obstacles.
Are you saying that he killed some people?!
I'm not sure. But he's very forceful.
Dear God! This is terrible!
We need to get the students as
far away from here as possible!
Attention students and faculty! This is an emergency!
There is currently an intruder on campus!
What?
What do you think they want?
Students are to follow their teachers' instructions,
and evacuate the school in groups according to class.
Wait, was there supposed to be a drill today
I repeat: There is an intruder on campus!
Damn! He's doing this in broad daylight.
He has no concern for the consequences of his actions.
He doesn't have the same reasoning as Ryoko Tamiya.
Guess not. Where is she right now anyway?
She is approximately one-hundred fifty meters from here.
It would seem that she intends to
observe our fight from a safe distance.
That's better than fighting both of them.
Make your way to the stairs near Wing C.
Do not approach Wing A under any circumstances.
Ms. Tamiya! She's gone?
Okay, come with me kids! Don't push. Don't push!
I need everybody to stay in line and keep moving.
Just follow me down to the courtyard.
We will have to fight him, Shinichi.
Fight him? But why?
It's daytime in a crowded school.
He walked in here with absolutely
no regard for being seen.
If we run, he's sure to follow us.
It's better to finish him here and now.
Plus, right now, we have the advantage.
And we also have a plan.
Huh, a plan?
Hey, who the heck have you been talking to?
Huh?! I'm just thinking out loud.
Hey, isn't that him there? That's gotta be him.
Huh? He's where?
Over there, that old guy.
Oh, God! What do you think he wants?
Please, stay in line! Keep moving!
He's trying to pinpoint your...
No, he's trying to pinpoint MY location.
However, the size of this crowd
is preventing him from doing that.
And then what? What's gonna happen?
What if he does find us?
Without a doubt, he's going to attack us.
He will come full force, affecting
all those who are around us.
Fortunately, that will give us an opportunity.
Opportunity?
Yes.
While he's busy attacking all the people around you,
I will be able to move in swiftly and surprise him.
It's simple, and it has a high probability of success.
All those people?
That's your plan?
Yes, that's the plan.
Mr. A will be encumbered by a
rather inconvenient obstacle:
A crowd of confused students.
A wall of flesh will protect us.
A "wall of flesh"?
I almost forgot what a sicko you are!
Murano!
Shinichi?
Get outta here!
Did you forget something? I'll come with you...
I said to go! Get away from me!
Uh, I'm really sorry!
Just hurry up and get out of here!
What's wrong, Shinichi?
Do you not like my strategy to fight Mr. A?
Of course I don't!
How many need to die to do it?!
Does it matter?
It's for the sake of self preservation.
Sacrificing others in order to protect oneself...
That's simply the way that all
life forms maintain their existence.
You know, you learned how to speak like us.
But you don't understand who we are at all, do you?
I just remembered...
Humans are very unique animals
that sometimes commit suicide.
It's not like anyone WANTS to die.
What is it you're doing?
I have a better option than a "wall of flesh".
C'mon, Class 3-2, you need to stay in line!
Are you angry, Migi?
Angry? No, of course I'm not.
I have no time for such things.
Shinichi, how do you think we are different from Mr. A?
"Different"?
Well, he's a murderer.
And I'm a decent human being.
He can be someone else. And I can't.
There's one of him.
And there's two of us.
Is that so?
Do you think Mr. A sees us as two separate entities?
I don't understand.
Here, this will be your weapon.
My weapon?
That's right. Mr. A and I are equally matched in combat.
That leaves one obvious factor.
You are going to have to join the fight.
If you allow yourself to become flustered during the
battle, it will only hold me back, and we will lose.
But if you are able to fight effectively, we win.
Got it?
Fight "effectively"? What's that mean?
In other words Shinichi, we delegate our roles.
Do you think that's really going to work?
It's our best option.
All that's left for you to do now is conceal your weapon.
The truth of the matter is,
Migi is way more skilled at combat than I am.
I mean, he's even killed two of his own kind.
I guess my only choice is to trust him.
He's here, Shinichi.
Mr. A is within three meters of us.
Three meters?!
Huh? But that's impossible! He'd be right here!
Directly below us.
Was that meant as some sort of barricade?
The only thing you've accomplished
is to block off your escape.
Next time: "Tangled Hair"