Shinichi, your eyes...
your eyes have no tears.
Goodbye... Murano...
Shinichi, I was unsure earlier about what would happen.
This was for the best, right?
I mean, if that guy had been watching us
again, he'd probably start going after Murano next.
"That guy"?
Yeah...
Y'know the man from before...
He was watching me again this afternoon, too.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
'Cause you would've tried to kill him.
Well, I've changed my thinking on that matter.
His investigation of you would
appear to be ongoing, correct?
If the same person is continuing to
operate despite us having discovered him,
we could actually be facing several enemies.
We may as well track down everyone
involved in this investigation and then...
Kill them all, right?
No...
In fact, I've noticed just how adverse a reaction you
have when it comes to the idea of killing other humans.
And that means,
we will have to work together.
Instead, we should investigate him.
How exactly?
We will call in an ally and ask for help.
An ally, huh...?
But where in the world would we ever find one?
Sorry for making you come here.
And getting you involved in all this, of course.
What are you talking about?
You two can count on us.
You're the only ones in the same boat we are!
We have to help each other out y'know!
I know, but...
but you kinda already helped me out enough already...
You got that right! You totally owe us!
This is a huge pain for us!
That was not me just now.
Right.
Seriously. I get it.
But wouldn't it be better just to kill the guy?
No, we can't. It's not that easy, all right?
Anyway, do you have any idea who might be behind all this?
Actually, I think we do.
Assuming the enemy isn't some
organization... we do have a guess.
Okay, let's say we're gonna just
try to catch him instead of kill him.
You at least know what he looks like, right?
Yes, I remember him well.
Like this.
Okay... I got it.
For now, I think we're going to stay
in the hotel over by the train station.
Right. Okay.
Oh, by the way.
About this guy's name...
we decided "Parasite" was too confusing
because they use that on TV and everywhere...
so I've decided to call him "Joe".
He so desperately needs a friend you guys.
Hehe.
Guh. I do not get it with all the friggin' names.
I agree. Names are totally unimportant.
You look like you're exhausted.
You should really go see a doctor.
Hm. I did go see a doctor... Look!
That's not what I'm talking about.
Yeah, well, they wouldn't believe me anyway.
Someone's hand stretching out and attacking me?
But it did happen, and I did get hurt...
I mean this is real, isn't it?!
Isn't it?
Please calm yourself down.
Believe it or not, I've calmed down quite a bit...
And I've taken time to think
about what happened back there.
As in, what the hell was that... thing?
I haven't come up with anything.
Well nothing that makes any sorta sense at least.
I'll pay you for all the work you've done up until now...
But your job's over.
Over? But we've just barely scratched the surface...?
I mean come on here... How am I
supposed to deal with all this crazy stuff?
I... I at least have to figure out what that thing was!
Asking me to believe your story is far more unreasonable.
I guess I...
Hold on! Wait a second!
You mentioned something to me about
Shinichi Izumi's hand before, didn't you.
Oh?
You did...! You definitely did!
So then you...
You already knew about it! You knew!
That's the whole reason you asked me
to investigate him in the first place!
Do you know what that monster actually is?
Look, you gotta tell me what's going on here lady!
Would you stop this foolishness? We're done.
Hey! I can't just walk away from this... Ah... Ow...
Ugh... Aww..
Hmph.
This would seem to be as far as I can go using the humans.
Ultimately, very little was accomplished.
Perhaps I should get rid of that investigator.
Huh?
Hahaha...
Was I really laughing just now...?
That's the first time I've ever
laughed without making myself do so.
But when I saw how panicked that man looked...
Heh!
I completely forgot about my facial expressions.
Hehehe...
Hahaha...
Already asleep, huh?
Ahh...
Ahh! What a day.
Oh, well, well. Enjoying yourself, I see.
Want some?
No, I'll pass.
You've had it pretty rough lately, haven't you?
What? You've been having bad dreams...
You cry out in your sleep.
And now you've gotten yourself hurt.
Don't worry. It's no big deal.
So... is this job that you've been
working on really just a background check?
Do what? What're you talking about?
I'm just saying that nothing good is
going to come from getting involved in...
in things that you don't belong, that's all.
So now you're thirsty all of a sudden?
If this job gets too dangerous... well
then, isn't that what the cops are for.
I just don't want anything to happen to you.
I don't want you getting in over your head.
Okay?
What you don't think I'm cut out for this, ugh...
No. Maybe not this one.
Jesus hon, thanks for the vote of confidence.
I gotta do this...
I gotta show the whole goddamn world!
The parasites transmit signals...
Those transmissions allow them to sense the
others of their kind that're located nearby.
They can't talk to each other like
they're on the phone or anything,
but if they agree on a kind of "call sign" beforehand,
they're able to exchange simple messages.
Shinichi.
They've found him.
Got it.
We'll meet him at the next corner.
Understood.
Huh?
Huh? Ah!
Glad you came...
I didn't think you'd show up.
Gah!
Please don't say anything.
Now get in.
Who's he? What're you guys planning to do to me?
Look, we don't intend to cause you any harm...
We're just going some place where we can talk in private.
He doesn't need to be so afraid of us...
Honestly, there's so much I want to ask you.
But first... I'd like you to
hear about our side of things.
Fine. Sure I'll hear you out, okay.
But you gotta tell me what's up with this guy.
There is something wrong with his face!
He changed it a bit so you
wouldn't know what he looks like.
Uh, y-yeah...
Right... Please listen closely
to what I have to say to you...
My own life is at stake right now.
O-kay...
And then... I went through everything...
all the way from when Migi dug
into my hand right up to the present.
Naturally, he was pretty shocked at first,
but the more he listened to my story...
the calmer he seemed to become.
But, even though he had begun to relax while I talked...
that skeptical look never left his eyes.
All right. I get the gist of things.
I'm sure you know how crazy this whole thing sounds...
Normally there's no way I'd believe it...
but seeing as how there's a
whatever right here in front of me...
I have to unfortunately believe at least some of it.
So? What do you want me to do?
I'm asking you to keep this quiet.
Can you do that for us?
I understand your point but according to your own
account, there are more of these things out there.
Can we really just stand by and do nothing?
Uh?
If you really do care about humanity...
Then you...
you have an obligation to come forward on this.
Even if they turn you into some kind of experiment...
Even if it means sacrificing yourself,
you have to think of civilization!
You have to think of all of us!
Isn't that what it means to be human?
What'd I say? We should totally take this guy out!
Agreed.
Uh! Ah!
Ahh!
Stop it!
Maybe you should sacrifice yourself.
I want you to listen to me very closely.
If you have a right to live, then we have that same right.
Granted, the concept of "rights" may be uniquely human,
but in any case, you need to understand that
we will do anything to ensure our own survival.
And I will not allow him to come forward
and be turned into some kind of specimen.
If you're saying that will make you our enemy...
I could kill you at a moment's notice.
Take a good look at him.
He's a teenager, still in high school.
From your perspective, he's still a child, correct?
His mother was killed... He's endured a great deal.
He has been forced to step over a pile of corpses,
yet continues to try his best to solve things.
I believe this is when you humans
are supposed to experience compassion.
Would you be able to endure all this?
Migi doesn't really sound like himself at all right now.
I'm sure he's just saying that stuff to
get a reaction out of this guy, but still...
Okay listen...
I honestly do not plan to kill you.
Run for it! Hurry!
Yeah... I know.
I have one more question.
I want to know: Who asked you to investigate Shinichi?
Yeah right... You know I can't say that.
What! Are you serious?
Are you really gonna try and pull
some self righteous bullcrap now?
Well, we do already have a pretty good idea who it is...
And to be perfectly blunt, your
client is actually a parasite.
Wait what?...! That can't be right!
I believe he mentioned her earlier, didn't he?
She was the female teacher who just
disappeared from his high school...
Ryoko Tamiya.
Who... Who's Tamiya?
She's already changed her name, but your
client's name could possibly sound similar.
Ryoko Tamiya... Reiko Tamura...
Look I barely even get the concept of having
stupid names, but I coulda figured that out.
If you decide to continue digging deeper into this,
it will be your client rather than us who kills you.
Son of a bitch...
Shinichi Izumi?
Ah! It's you!
To think, she got in touch with you
right after we suspected something...
She wants to meet on the roof of the university...
What do you think she's up to?
Right now, Ryoko Tamiya is one
hundred thirty meters from us...
Which means she must be somewhere beyond that building.
She went from high-school teacher to college professor...
Very ambitious.
Altruism is action undertaken
for the sole benefit of others.
It's the opposite of self-interest, and
would seem to have no benefit for oneself.
If anything, the action tends help others
while being disadvantageous to the actor.
What a cutie.
Aw, so sweet!
While these actions may not be
surprising amongst our fellow human beings,
what can be interpreted as altruistic behavior
has actually been reported in several animal species.
Honeybees are an excellent example of this,
they sacrifice themselves, one after another,
to protect the hive if a predator should appear.
While this could just be instinct,
some actions would not seem to preserve the species.
The prime illustration of such
a practice could be identified...
as infanticide.
But why kill the offspring of one's own species?
In recent years, what's been discovered is...
something called the "selfish gene" theory...
To put it in simple terms, all animals are
manipulated by their own body's genetic code.
What's important is the self,
and the offspring who inherit that DNA,
rather than the species as a whole.
That being said...
Let's expand a bit further...
We can now justify all altruistic behavior,
such as caring for others in one's "pack,"
familial love, marital love and even maternal love.
This premise would suggest that love
and compassion don't actually exist.
Therefore, all behavior that appears to be love is
really just behavior to aid in transmitting one's own DNA.
To be sure, this theory is not without its problems.
There have been countless examples of animals
helping others completely unrelated to them.
This includes like creatures from unrelated DNA strains,
and even instances of protecting
those of a different species altogether.
Which begs the question,
can a theory like this fully encompass the
complexity or the depth of the human consciousness?
For example, it's interesting to consider
whether human efforts toward such issues
as environmental-and-natural conservation
are altruistic or selfish at their core.
It's almost time.
Who holds a baby like that?
Yeah...
I'm glad you came. You look well.
Why'd you want us to meet here?
I chose this place because
others of my kind rarely come here.
Also, there was a lecture I wanted to attend.
So it's true.
You are quite different from before.
How did the two of you combine?
What really happened?
I find it difficult to believe it occurred without reason.
Uh...
So is that really... your baby?
Yes. It is mine...
I haven't had it long, so I
haven't began working on it yet.
Working on it? How so?
Your right hand... "Migi," wasn't it?
Shall we exchange information again? For both our sakes.
First, I'd like to confirm it was
you who hired the private investigator.
Hm.
Didn't you think that doing so
might put you in great danger as well?
I don't really worry about it...
I know I can simply assume another
identity, if it comes to that.
So what's the deal with this Mayor Hirokawa?
Why would one of your kind want to be mayor anyway?
I'm not entirely sure myself...
And yet... I know that we are still evolving.
We've learned that recklessly slaughtering
human beings for food is not a wise option for us.
Going forward, we're going to have to think about...
how we can coexist with humans.
"Coexist"?
Hideo Shimada said the same thing, you saw what he did.
Couldn't it be said that, in a way,
humans and their livestock coexist?
Now, that's not to say you're equals...
But still, judging from a pig's point of view,
humans are merely predators that feed upon them.
Humans are so fond of grandiose ideals.
You grasp onto the notion that
all life on Earth is sacred,
yet you don't behave in such a way.
I'll admit, there may be a little truth
to some of the things that you're saying.
But that being said...
There are reasons why I will never be able to forgive you!
What happened to you?
You just don't really seem to be
like a normal human being anymore...
I'm not sure how to put it...
A mother and... child...
I heard that your mother went missing.
Uh...
Was she killed?
Ah...
Shinichi, calm down!
Hahaha... I see!
So, one of us ate her.
Huh...
Ohh... Impressive...
It's like the air is trembling around us...
I'm gonna kill you!
I think I'd lose if I fought you now...
So, I'll have to use the child to shield myself.
Ah!
Oh my god! Look?!
It's that lady from class.
It seems human children are more perceptive than adults.
Be quiet.
That bitch...
Move it! Get outta my way!
Goddamn humans...
What's wrong, Shinichi? You must settle yourself.
She will pay... Her day is gonna come!
So, I'll have to use the child to shield myself.
I haven't had it long, so I
haven't began working on it yet.
Hello, young man.
Yes, you!
Huh?
Yes... Come on...
Come here... I do reading.
Yes that's it...
You seem to be full of suffering...
Let me see your hand.
Let's go.
Left hand?
Hmmm...
I see you have a hole in your heart now, don't you?
Huh?! How did you...
It's a very large hole indeed.
So then how can I...
how can I close it?
See the person.
What?
You have to meet once again
with whomever created this hole...
You must meet with them and have talk.
Then you have closure.
Yes... This individual is the
only one who can heal your wounds.
There is no other way.
Huh?
Too late for that, I already killed her.
Next time: "Something Wicked This Way Comes"