As I recall, your host body is
in its late teens, is that right?
Yes, that's correct.
Perfect. I can use you then...
Your assignment is to watch the boy and
observe his movements, but do not kill him.
Is there any point to this?
Yes... While he does pose something of a threat to us...
he is an exceedingly valuable resource in
gauging the future potential of our kind...
Heh!
Shinichi... Izumi...
Got it.
Yo.
Hm? Mitsuo!
Hey, Kana... Ah...
You gonna see your boyfriend again?
Who?
That piece of shit who thinks he's some kinda hero.
Uuh... Just move, I'm going home.
Wh-what's with you, Kana?
That hurts, let me go.
Wait, hold on a minute...
Don't tell me you're actually into that douchebag.
That is really none of your damn business.
Hmph...
Check it out. Look.
Mitsuo?
Hey, loser.
So, didja come by here to kidnap another girl?
Where's your buddy? Who?
That poser-ass "Shinichi" or whatever.
You looking to start some trouble punk?
Huh? Perfect timing.
Hey, Shinichi! Mitsuo wants to talk to you.
Huh?
Tsk...
Oh right. You again, huh?
You n' me. Need t'talk.
This place again?
Can we please keep this short?
There's someone I have to meet.
So, did you and Kana hook up or what?
Huh? Oh, right. Kana's that girl from the other day...
Don't you play dumb with me, you asshole!
Listen, you've got it wrong.
I haven't seen that girl in a long
time, and I was out of town before that.
Out of town?!
Anyway, you got your answer.
Uh... Screw you!
Huh?
Mmph.
Uh...
Don't... It won't go like before.
Eat shit!
Come here!
Uhh...!
Err-ya!
Uhh...
Hey! Ohh...
Hey, man... You okay?
Shinichi!
Oh, hey! I was just at the school
and Kamijo told me that you... Mm...
It's fine...
Nothing to worry about.
Err...
Here. You can have your shoe back.
Hey, wanna go in? I'm pretty hungry.
Uh... Shinichi... did something
happen to you on your trip?
Huh?
It's just that, you seem a little different now.
I was just using my dad's injury as
an excuse to ditch school for a while.
Uhh...
Hey, uh... You are...
Shinichi Izumi...
aren't you?
Well, who's to say?
Ah...
Come on... Who else would I be?
And you're... Satomi Murano... aren't you?
Mm-hm!
Ah! I can sense him. He's getting closer!
I'm not sure how I know it,
but he'll come right up those stairs any second.
There! There he is!
Oh...
I'm home.
Dad...
Ah... Shinichi...
You hungry?
I ate... Did you eat?
No need.
Go easy on the drinking there...
You should probably get some food in your stomach.
Yeah...
So I was looking online...
They recommend hiring a housekeeper for a time like this.
"Time like this"?
Well, I mean...
Cause Mom... or whoever usually cooks the
meals and stuff isn't around to do it anymore.
Look boy...
How can you even...
Never mind... Hire a housekeeper...
I don't really think I care anymore.
I think I have some sorta problem.
What's that?
I don't know what's wrong...
I can't cry...
Okay... Is that all?
I feel like I've lost something...
Like I'm missing an important part... of being human.
Pure foolishness.
Ever since Migi's cells were dispersed
throughout my body, my senses have become heightened.
My hearing. It's stronger.
If I really focus...
Oh, my! You mean Mrs. Hashimoto's son?
That's right. Can you believe it?!
And now an update on traffic.
A collision on Metro Expressway Number Four has...
Filthy pigs! Filthy pigs! Pigs, pigs, pigs, pigs!
Something wrong?
Uh, oh, no, it's nothing...
Uh!
Wait. What was that?
Shinichi?
I'm sorry, you go on ahead.
Uh... Mm...
It's calling out... It's asking for help.
Huh?
Can we save it?
The internal organs have been
crushed, causing irreparable damage.
Death will occur within ten minutes.
Ohh...
I'm sorry...
There's nothing we can do to help you.
Still, this is better than dying
in a dirty, noisy street, right?
Shinichi?
Unfortunately, this guy's not gonna make it.
Shinichi... I've been pretty worried about you.
Why?
'Cause there's something about
you that's really different somehow.
You... you used to be more nervous before, you know?
It was kind of cute in a weird way,
or maybe comforting, I guess.
Mm...
But then, ever since you came back from your trip...
It's like... you've just been cold and distant.
Maybe I've just been imagining things...
You seem like yourself now.
It's dead.
Huh?
Its heart stopped.
Let's go... We're already running late.
Huh! Shinichi?!
Hm?
I don't believe you, how could you do that?!
You just threw it in the trash can!
Oh, do you think the janitor will get mad?
I'm not talking about the stupid janitor!
The puppy... It's cruel to that puppy!
I'm not sure how that can be cruel. The dog's dead.
I know, but Shinichi...
It's already gone... It's not a dog anymore...
It's just a hunk of dog-shaped meat.
Huh?! No!
What's wrong?
I knew you were different!
Before, you never would've done...
Never...
Murano...
Have I... Have I really changed that much?
Migi... Migi!
What is it?
Just then... You heard...
I said something strange to her...
What was it I did wrong?
I don't think you did anything wrong at all...
From my perspective.
But you are very different now from how you were before.
Huh?
The statement you just made about the "dog-shaped meat"...
Was the sort of thing that I would be more likely to say.
Oh...
Hm...
I guess so...
Thank you, Migi.
The dog's carcass will break down and
become nutrients absorbed by this tree.
If I had just done this in the first place,
Murano wouldn't hate me so much right now.
Uh...
Oh, Murano.
Ah...
Hm... I guess today's too soon.
I'll give her some space and try again.
Shinichi.
Hm?
One of my kind is here.
Huh?!
Don't tell me Ryoko Tamiya is back!
No. This seems to be someone different.
It can't be Uda and his Parasite, can it?
So... does that mean this one's here to kill me?
I sense no murderous intent.
What do I do?
For now, I think we should meet them in a public place.
What? Meet them?!
It's possible this is not an enemy.
Uh...
Despite being able to sense our presence,
its rate of approach is calm and measured.
I believe this may be another one similar to Ryoko Tamiya.
In other words, it's the type
that can possibly be reasoned with.
What's that even supposed to mean?!
He's here.
So... You're Shinichi, right?
Yeah who're you?
You're different from how I'd imagined you would be...
You seem quite strong.
Why're you at my school? What do you want?
Yo, Shinichi. This guy bothering you?
Haven't seen you around buddy? Do you just transfer?
Don't interfere.
Hideo Shimada...
That is the name you may use to address me.
Shinichi, I thought that you...
Rather, that the two of you and I could be friends.
Who the hell is this?
Ah... I must go...
Shinichi, would you please show me the way to Class Three?
Class Three? That's Murano's class!
I'm looking forward to Physical Education...
I believe it's a joint session
between our classes today, isn't it?
Hm...
If I go all-out, I'd set a world record.
Mmph!
Ah! Ten point eight seconds?!
It's kinda weird for a transfer
this time of year, isn't it?
I guess so, he said it was because of his dad's job.
Aww...! This is total bullcrap,
I wish I was in Hide's class.
"Hide"?
Hideo Shimada... "Hide"!
Seriously, Akiho? What about Shinichi?
I thought you liked him?
Yeah. I mean, don't you?
Uh-What...?! Come on, gross he's like a brother to me.
Anyway, it doesn't matter because he's with Murano now.
Isn't he?
Uh! Well... I...
Hehehe...
Sports are good training. The more you practice,
the better you become at controlling your body.
Why drag this out? You're planning
to attack me once I let my guard down.
Your assumption is incorrect...
I wonder, if that's what your right hand believes as well.
Just answer me one question...
Did Ryoko Tamiya send you to get rid of me?
Ryoko Tamiya?
Ah... she's going by a different name now.
It's true. She is the one who told me about you...
but she didn't send me here to kill you.
In fact, you'll be pleased to know
that I don't intend to lay a hand on you,
or anyone in your circle while I'm here at this school.
And furthermore...
I haven't harmed any humans for
quite some time, nor do I need to.
Huh?
I've been sustaining myself on the
same sort of food that humans eat.
If parasites could exist without killing
your kind, there'd be no problem, would there?
Like I'd trust you.
The fact is...
we've started to explore ways in which we can
coexist alongside humans, within your society.
Given that you two are a bridge between our two races,
we were hoping that you would
give the idea some consideration.
Fascinating.
Everything you've talked about here
today has served to pique my interest.
It has?
But...
A great deal of it is difficult to believe.
Oh... really?
Whatever the case, I do not wish for conflict either...
So I'd say that's enough for today...
Let's go, Shinichi.
Huh? Why now?
What's the deal?
We weren't even done talking to the guy yet.
Shinichi, I'm going to sleep.
Huh? You're crashing again?
For four hours...
There's no telling what will happen if
Hideo Shimada learns of this weakness.
Ah...
Oh...
Shinichi...
I can't believe he did that.
But then again, most people would've
just ignored the puppy in the first place.
Maybe... I shouldn't have said
that he's gotten cold and distant...
Hm...
What should I do?
If he really is thinking about coexisting with humans,
then maybe there's a way we can come
up with something to make it work...
No! I cannot trust those things. They're merciless!
No matter how intelligent they are, they're
nothing more than compassionless insects!
There's no way I'll ever forget what they've done!
One day, I WILL expose them!
Uh... about the other day...
No, it's fine. Everything's fine.
Uh-um...
Well that was great...
I sure have a knack for screwing things up.
I have... a special power...
it gives me the ability to sense the presence...
of my soul mate.
There he is.
Hello there!
Huh? Can I help you?
Oh. Wrong person.
I'm so sorry... I thought you were Shinichi.
Really? What would make you think that I was Shinichi?
Huh?
When someone mistakes two people...
it's normally because they look
similar in one way or another.
So... How do Shinichi and I seem similar to you?
I told you I was sorry.
Hey! What are you doing?!
I know that voice...
I just want to talk to you for a little bit.
Hey! What're you doing to her?!
Ah! Let go! Shinichi!
I only wanted to discuss some things with her...
It would appear that this
particular female is rather perceptive.
Listen...
If anything happens to anyone close to me...
I will be coming after you.
I swear to God I will take you out.
Hehe. Shinichi.
It's like I keep saying: I don't want to fight you.
What's with him...?
There's something cold in his eyes...
Interesting, his parasite's
signal seemed very weak just then.
Oh, wow!
You're pretty strong, huh?
Uhh...
Uh... Oh, Shinichi!
Walk me to the station!
I'm scared that creepy guy might be there!
Yeah. No problem.
Ah!
Mm...
Not again! What the hell?!
What's wrong?
Telepathy?
Yeah. That's right.
I can tell whenever you're anywhere nearby.
But for some reason, I managed
to get it wrong just then...
But you did finally show up, so
it's not like I was totally off.
Yeah, but...
I'm not so sure that's such a good thing.
Huh?
I mean... whatever it is you think you're sensing...
it could be some kind of "wavelengths"
being broadcast by dangerous jerks like him.
So does that mean you're a dangerous jerk, too?
Uh?!
Uh, well yeah... yeah I am...
So you should probably just stay
away from guys like us, you got that?
Hmm...
Well, I think I'll use this face as bait today.
Hmm... That sow has had a healthy
upbringing, and its skin has a nice sheen.
Hello there, are you lost?
Well, I was just...
I'd be more than happy to show
you around, if you'd like me to.
Dad.
Yeah, I know...
Bed time.
'Night.
Shinichi...
Tell me, Son...
When did you suddenly get to be so strong?
Hm?
It's like you're made of steel.
Like a metal shell with nothing left on the inside.
Uhh...
I'm sorry.
There we go.
Came out even better than I thought it would.
Heh... Hmm...
Next time: "Beyond Good and Evil"