If you want to be free of suffering,
you should believe in God.
Whether or not you believe in
Him, God is always by your side.
On July 4, 1947, a strange craft crashed
in the desert in New Mexico, America.
What it was has yet to be proven.
Conjecture has become fact,
and rumor has become history.
Who's there?
In 1984, a manila envelope arrived at
the home of TV producer Jaime Shandera.
The envelope, from an anonymous source,
contained a roll of undeveloped film.
The film contained what is
called the MJ-12 Document.
Roscoe Hillenkoetter, head of the
CIA at the time of the Roswell Incident,
was at the top of the list of 12 members.
It stated that these men concluded
a secret treaty with extraterrestrials...
...as a special organization
answerable only to the president.
It is now accepted that President
Truman's signature on the document...
...was in fact copied carefully
from another document.
Named as a member of MJ-12 was Vannevar Bush,
head of MIT's Department
of Electrical Engineering.
Connect to Wired.
How could I turn something that
did happen into something that didn't ?
Are you Lain? I see, I see...
I don't know you.
But you know me ...
The flow of information
doesn't always go both ways.
Since the moment of the Wired's
creation, you have always been here.
Here, you are free.
I'm trying to tell you that that's not me!
I suppose.
How long have we been here, then?
At the very least, we cannot have
been here since this world was created.
That has nothing to do with it!
If a being is remembered, that
proves that it's part of a record!
That's preposterous.
How old do you think this
"Lain" girl is? She's still a child!
Let's not worry about me now, okay? I--
The memex memory expansion concept
unveiled by Vannevar Bush in 1945...
...was a system whereby
information recorded on microfilm...
...was projected onto a translucent screen.
What he envisioned was the
compression and rapid access of information.
Even before the advent of computers,
Bush had already created the
basis for our current multimedia...
...while he led the Manhattan
Project atom bomb experiments.
You forgot this.
You forgot this on the floor here yesterday.
If you don't need it, I'll toss it.
I left that here?
That's what I'm sayin'.
Conducting sensory
deprivation experiments using...
...Native American narcotics and isolation
tanks to probe the human unconscious,
John C. Lilly believed his experiments
connected him to cosmic entities...
...by way of a communication network.
Lilly dubbed the beings
that guided him E.C.C.O.,
Earth Coincidence Control Office.
Afterwards, Lilly began work
on communication with dolphins.
Dolphins are creatures
which are able to conduct...
...wide-range networking in
the water via ultrasonic waves.
What?
You promised me earlier.
Promised what?
That you'd go out with me.
You said you'd go out with me!
W-What're you talking about?
Taro, is that true?
Did I?
You didn't! You didn't!
Even if I did, you aren't the you
I want to go out with right now, Lain.
Taro, you moron!
We're the same. I'm me. I'm the only me.
Awesome!
I can't believe you put
together something like this!
Oh, okay...! This syncs
up the parallel processors!
It's not pretty, but you can
keep on expanding it this way.
What're you using as coolant?
Taro...
Is this liquid carbon?
Sit down over there.
Damn...
I think you know what this is.
It's you, isn't it, Taro?
You're with the Knights, aren't you?
You're... the real Lain.
I don't know whether or not
there's another me in the Wired.
But there's definitely no
other me here in the real world.
The other one with a body
has only appeared in the club.
You only need to manipulate the
memories of the people there, right?
I... I can't...
Play track 44.
It's almost over, isn't it?
Finally.
So while we still can, we should...
Roger.
Now communicating.
Stop.
It's not me!
But I knew the data coming into
JJ's place had this kind of effect.
If I had installed this chip,
what would've happened to me?
Would I have killed myself? Gone insane?
I said I don't know!
There's no way a kid like me
could be a formal Knights member!
I'm just a--
I wonder what this will do?
I-It's non-volatile memory!
It'll overwrite existing memories!
What kind of memories?
I-I don't know.
The Knights aren't just
ordinary crackers, Lain.
There's something strange
about you. That's for sure.
That's why the Knights are so interested.
The Knights are users who are fighting...
...to make the one and only
truth there is into a reality.
I don't understand.
What do you mean, "one and only"?
Like I said, I'm not a formal Knights member.
They never explained it to me.
But it's true. The truth has
power because it's the truth.
And because it's the truth, that makes it  just .
It's persuasive, isn't it?
Don't you want truth like that?
I'm going.
Myu-Myu is jealous of you.
Taro...? Thank you.
You...
Hey, this is a date, you know?
I'm a guy. I had to do that.
Ted Nelson, who studied
under the two cult pioneers...
...Vannevar Bush and John C. Lilly,
proposed a giant electronic library
in satellites in stationary orbit...
...which could be used at any
terminal on Earth via radio or phone lines.
He called this concept that
would make this database "Xanadu."
The Mongolian utopia where all
written cultures would never be lost.
This was Xanadu.
It was the concept of
Hypertext that would make it real,
and Ted Nelson's name would
go down in history as its originator.
Hello, Navi.
Click, click... Memory check...
Click, click, click...
That's... That's me ?
Yes. This is me.
Then who are they ?
I'm you, so I wouldn't know.
This is a lie.
It's a lie. It's all a lie.
Why are you doing this?
The Earth has its own
specific electromagnetic waves.
Between the ionosphere and the Earth's surface,
...there is a constant resonance at
a frequency of 8Hz in the ELF band.
This is called the Schumann Resonance.
The extent of the effect on
humans of these "Earth Brain Waves"...
...that the planet constantly
gives off remains unknown.
The Earth's human
population is approaching that of...
...the number of neurons in the brain.
Douglas Rushkoff proposes that
the consciousness of the Earth itself...
...might be awakened when all humans
on Earth become collectively networked.
The network's evolution
would follow a neural model,
and just as neurons within the
human brain are connected by synapses,
the Earth itself would become a neural network.
There is only one truth. God.
Yes. Me.
Masami Eiri, Chief Researcher
at Tachibana General Labs,
further developed the hypothesis
of a worldwide neural network.
His hypothesis proposed a
wireless network whereby all humanity...
...would be plugged in at an unconscious
level without the need for any device.
Furthermore, he encoded the
Schumann Resonance Factor...
...and inserted it into the 7th-gen
Wired Protocol on his own initiative.
Upon discovering this,
Tachibana General Labs dismissed Eiri.
One week later, Masami Eiri's body
was found on the Yamanote train line.
I thought I was innocent,
but I'm being punished.
I didn't start this, but
I have to finish it somehow.
I can't say I didn't know about it,
but I don't remember taking part in it.
I get the feeling my freedom cost me dearly,
but I don't remember selling my soul cheaply.
Hey, hey!
Until I die and say goodbye...
...no one will ever catch me.
You probably don't know the eternal outlaws...
...who wander the distant night.