"No, it's nothing as ambiguous as 'memory.'"
"But you're still there,
too, aren't you, you poor dupe?"
"Am I me?"
"Lain is Lain."
I wish you'd come here...
"I don't need to stay here."
You'll have to excuse me.
All this talking has worn me out.
I've never seen one before!
Lain Iwakura. Are you and the
Lain of the Wired one and the same?
I've seen you before. In the Wired.
"Tachibana General Laboratories'
Biochem Elementary Research Group...
...has announced that they
have mapped the human genome."
"Lain is a Peeping Tom"
"Masami Eiri Commits Suicide on Yamanote Line"
"Come..."
Poor Lain...
Hey, I'm Lain, aren't I?
No!
You're wrong!
That's right, Lain. You're
not needed in the real world.
I'm committing suicide!
Why? Why are you warm?
Why do I have to feel the heat from your body?
Yes. I'm God.
How could you...?
Lain, you'd have more fun if
you were a little more sociable.
She's changed, all right.
Are you okay?
Lately... You've been slipping
back to your old self, Lain.
Are you okay? Lain, I...
Lain, I'm sorry! It's all
our fault! Are you okay, Lain?
Glad to hear it.
"A loving heart is searching for you."
Are you tired?
Yes.
You really are incredible...
So, you've loaded an emulator
of that Navi into your own brain.
It's dangerous to subject yourself
to that much information all at once.
At your current capacity, you'll overflow.
Am I a machine?
Don't talk about me like I'm a machine.
I didn't mean to.
This is basically a software problem.
Lain, you're software.
You're not hardware.
Software...?
Yes. An executable program with a body.
Be quiet...
Be quiet !
Chisa...!
Chisa, we walked home together just once, right?
I understand. I finally
understand what you told me.
Lain...
It's easy to die, Lain.
Right?
There's nothing easy about dying.
Sure it is!
Lain, you already have
a tool that will let you do it.
What do you--
The safety's already off.
The trigger's heavy, so hold it with
both hands and pull it with your thumb.
A girl isn't strong enough.
What, you still want to stay in the real world?
Hey, that's not fair.
You called me here, remember?
I... I never...
Bodies are meaningless.
You're wrong.
Lain.
What is this?
I thought that maybe we could meet
after school and I could introduce you.
This guy's pretty cute!
And then those rumors
about you and that teacher...
I think if you get a boyfriend,
everyone will know they're a lie.
See you tomorrow. We'll talk about it then.
'Bye!
It's not a lie.
W-Who's there?
Who's there?!
Lain...?
W-What?
What's happened to you...? You...
It wasn't me.
I never peeked at your secrets, Arisu,
and I never sent those
secrets out onto the Wired.
It was you, Lain! I saw you!
That isn't me.
It looks like I'm not the
only me. Some other me did it.
What're you talking about?
You might not be the only Arisu, either.
But no matter how often I say
I didn't do it, you'll believe that I  did .
So I'll make it so that it never happened.
I've been working really
hard to be able to do that.
What do you mean?
I don't need devices anymore.
It looks like I've already
destroyed the border...
...between the Wired and the real world.
I can go anyplace I want to now.
So I came here.
I should be able to undo
something that happened!
Lain...
I...
I'm scared...
I'm scared...!
Arisu!
Arisu! Good morning!
Good morning.
What's up, Arisu? Why are you depressed?
Oh, is it that time of the month?
Hey, you ever hear of "delicacy"?
Come on, I was only...
Juri... I don't think I can
go through with it today.
Huh? Go through with what?
What? Didn't you send
me a CU-mail yesterday?
No, I didn't send you anything yesterday...
You're sure acting strange today, Arisu.
Arisu!
Oh, that teacher... He sure is hot!
Yeah! But rumor has it
that he's seeing an 8th-grader!
What, are you serious? That's gross!
Um... Listen, I...
What is it?
A-About that teacher... and me...
Is there something
between that teacher and you?
Do you like him or something?
Sorry, you're too late!
Yeah! He already has a girlfriend.
That's not like you, Arisu.
Yeah, she sure is acting strange today.
Lain! Good morning!
Hurry it up!
Come on, Lain!
Lain!
Lain, you...
Lain, you smiled...
I thought I was innocent,
but I'm being punished.
I didn't start this, but
I have to finish it somehow.
I can't say I didn't know about it,
but I don't remember taking part in it.
I get the feeling my freedom cost me dearly,
but I don't remember selling my soul cheaply.
Hey, hey!
Until I die and say goodbye...
...no one will ever catch me.
You probably don't know the eternal outlaws...
...who wander the distant night.