Why? Why won't you come?
I wish you would come here...
Look! Look at that!
"Why you have to do that...
...is something you
should figure out for yourself."
Gotcha!
Hey, cut it out!
Why?
Don't!
What's the problem? Don't play hard to get!
Come on, let's go someplace happy.
"I...
...don't need to stay in a place like this."
What the hell ?
What happened?!
W-We don't know anything!
W-We've got nothing to do with this!
--She came outta nowhere...
--Oh, no...
Damn it...
"If you stay in a place like this...
...you might not be able to connect."
What a racket...
Can't you be quiet?
"Everybody, hurry..."
Juri, don't make such a big deal about it.
Yeah, it's just some stupid prank.
B-But...
It'll be okay.
Lain?
Did you get one, too?
Get what?
Mail!
Mail?
From Chisa Yomoda!
I... I'm not very good with computers.
You should at least check your mail once a day.
Well, it's up to you, I guess.
Lain's such a baby.
Why is she crying?
Because she got mail from
Chisa Yomoda, that's why!
Chisa? Who's that?
She was in class D.
She killed herself last week by
jumping off a building in Shibuya.
Come on, the teacher told everybody!
It's not just Juri.
Lots of people have
gotten mail from her this week.
But she's...
Right. You shouldn't be
getting mail from a dead girl.
But there it is.
"What's it like when you die?"
"It really hurts! :)"
"Powering up... Working..."
"Just a little longer..."
Log in.
Who are you?
Lain. Please say your name.
La-i-n.
Accepted.
You must be Lain.
Lain has mail.
From who?
Chisa Yomoda.
Do you wish to read your mail?
"Hello, how are you?"
Hello...
...how are you?
Lain, I walked home with you
just once. Do you remember?
I have only given up my body.
By doing this, I can explain
to you that I am still alive.
I wanted to let you know this,
Lain, so I sent this mail to you.
Do you understand?
It's okay if you can't right now.
You will all understand soon. Everyone will.
Why did you die?
Rumor at school has it
that this is prank mail,
but I want you to know that it isn't, Lain.
Why? Why did you die?
"God is here."
God...
...is here.
Huh?
"God..."
I ate lunch late today. I'm done.
Mom?
Yes?
I got mail.
From a girl who killed herself last week.
What is it, Lain?
It's certainly unusual to see you in here.
I...
I was wondering if you
could buy me a new Navi...
Finally caught the bug, huh?
You're in junior high now.
Your friends are leaving you in the dust, right?
I keep telling you that you
should use a better machine.
You know, Lain, in this world,
whether it's here in the
real world or in the Wired,
people connect to each other,
and that's how societies function.
Even a girl like you can make
friends right off the bat, Lain.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I wonder why your mother
can't understand that...?
I'm not scared.
But why bring up your Navi all of a sudden?
There's a friend I want to see.
--What happened?
--Damn it...
We apologize for the
inconvenience, ladies and gentlemen.
The train is currently
stopped due to an accident.
What?
Was someone hit?
I can't believe this...
Miss Iwakura.
Yes, Ma'am.
This will be on the test.
"Come to the Wired as soon as you can."
Chisa...?
Where are you?
Wait!
I thought I was innocent,
but I'm being punished.
I didn't start this, but
I have to finish it somehow.
I can't say I didn't know about it,
but I don't remember taking part in it.
I get the feeling my freedom cost me dearly,
but I don't remember selling my soul cheaply.
Hey, hey!
Until I die and say goodbye...
...no one will ever catch me.
You probably don't know the eternal outlaws...
...who wander the distant night.