God is the one and only truth.
Yes. Me.
Isn't that right, Lain?
You're God?
Yes. I'm God.
Why are you God? I don't understand.
You're dead, aren't you? A dead human .
Somebody like that can't be God, can they?
I realized that I had no need for a body.
To die is merely to abandon the flesh.
That's... That's just what Chisa said.
"I don't need to stay here."
I suppose she did, at that.
I caused the protocol that
governs the Wired to evolve.
Yeah. That's what you did.
But a protocol is just an agreement.
Yes, but I incorporated code
that operates on a higher phase.
So?
There is compressed
information mixed into the protocol.
What kind of information?
Human memories. Mine .
The thoughts, history, memories, and
emotions of the man named Masami Eiri.
What does that mean?
I can live forever as an
anonymous entity in the Wired,
and will be able to rule it with information.
What do you think a being
like that should be called?
A god.
There is no God.
Yes. Even if I were an omnipresent
being and could influence others,
with no one to worship me, I'm no god.
But you had them.
Or made them, I should say.
Knights.
You no longer need a body, Lain.
That's a lie!
Talk about lame !
Some people are like that, I guess.
So I said, go ahead and do it.
Anyway...
--Hey, look at this!
--Isn't it cute ?
It was really cheap!
--At that place next door?
--Yeah, over there!
--Let's go, let's go!
--Today?
Sure, we don't have
anything after school today.
Hey, you're right.
Let's go!
Stand!
Bow!
All right, close your books.
I... I'm real...!
I'm alive...!
I'm here.
Why is this happening?
Was it something I did?
I always tried to keep
something like this from happening.
I always tried not to say anything weird.
Can it be true...?
I'm not supposed to have a body?
That's right, Lain.
You're not needed in the real world.
I'm home.
Dad...?
This is goodbye, Miss Lain.
You must have figured it out
by now. Our work here is finished.
It was only for a short time, but
I know I didn't do enough for you.
You're now free to become anything you want.
No, you were free all along.
I wasn't given permission to
say goodbye, but I loved you.
It's not that I enjoyed playing house...
Maybe I envied a being like you.
Goodbye.
Wait!
Don't leave me alone!
Alone? You're not alone.
If you connect to the Wired,
everyone will welcome you.
That's the sort of being you were.
I'm not alone.
Do you want to do anything, Lain?
This is your world, Lain.
Who are the Knights? They're the
ones who made the fake me, right?
I'm not sure.
No, it's possible.
They say you can trace the origin of the...
...Knights of the Eastern Calculus
back to the Knights Templar.
They've used that invisible human
network, the collective unconscious,
since long before the Wired was born.
What do you want to do, Lain?
Knights...
Who are the Knights?
You really want to know, don't you, Lain?
The Wired's God is a god
because He has worshippers.
Hey, Taro... Let's go someplace else.
This place has gotten boring.
Yeah. Why not come over to my house?
You don't need to come, Masayuki.
What's the big idea?
Taro says he doesn't wanna
hang out with a little kid like you.
Wha--?
You're as much a kid as I am, Myu-Myu!
It's okay for a girl! Everybody
knows that younger is better for girls.
Right, Taro?
What's that?
What's up, Taro? Is there
something on the Net News?
It's a list.
Huh? What kind of list?
What's a list of Knights
members doing on the Net News...?
Y-Yes?
Please remain silent.
W-Who are you?
Time to pay the piper, all right?
W-What do you mean?
Mom, I got killed!
Mom!
It's your turn, Mom! If you don't
hurry up, I'm gonna keep playing!
Okay, Mom?
I'm gonna take 'em out!
A series of suicides occurred
today all over the world,
and each country's
Information Control Ministry...
...and police departments have
begun investigating the cause.
Each victim was involved
in network-related work,
and sources tell us that it
appears that they were all members...
...of a fraternal order known as the "Knights."
Why did you do it?
It was a request from our client.
You hunted down all the Knights in the world.
Our associates are now on
their way to dispose of them.
But why...?
The Wired can't be
allowed to be a special world.
It can only be a field that functions as
a sub-system to reinforce the real world.
But still...
You can't be allowed to
exist in the Wired, either.
But here you are, safe and sound.
Some god or whatever must be protecting you.
Masami Eiri's residual thought program...
...will eventually be
disinfected from the Wired.
Our client is working on a total
rewrite of the Protocol Seven code.
We have no need for gods.
Right. Not in the Wired or in the real world.
We still haven't figured out what you are.
But I love you.
Love certainly is a strange emotion, isn't it?
What will you do?
Well, let me think...
You don't have anyone to pray to you now.
I can't be a god, then.
But I haven't lost all of them.
If only one believer
remains, I can still be a god.
Who?
Come, now... You, Lain.
It's because of me that you can stay yourself.
You were originally born in the Wired.
The legend of the Wired.
The heroine of the Wired's fairy tales.
Liar.
The real world's Lain Iwakura
is merely a hologram of her.
A homunculus of artificial ribosomes.
You never had a body to begin with.
That's a lie.
A fake family. Fake friends.
Yes, it was all a lie.
That's a lie...
That's all a lie...
Poor Lain... She's all alone.
But I'm here. The man
who loves you is here.
You should be able to love me,
the man who sent you to this world...
I am your creator.
Love me.
All right, Lain?
The other...
The other me, she's...
That isn't another you. It's the real you.
Like it matters!
I thought I was innocent,
but I'm being punished.
I didn't start this, but
I have to finish it somehow.
I can't say I didn't know about it,
but I don't remember taking part in it.
I get the feeling my freedom cost me dearly,
but I don't remember selling my soul cheaply.
Hey, hey!
Until I die and say goodbye...
...no one will ever catch me.
You probably don't know the eternal outlaws...
...who wander the distant night.