You've heard of a girl named Lain, right?
Lain of the Wired.
Are your parents away on vacation or something?
I called the number you
gave me, but no one answered.
I'm not lying.
No, I don't think you're lying. I checked.
You're Lain Iwakura, all right.
Your address and phone number check out.
It's late, so I'm going to
have someone take you home.
But next time, I want you to talk to me.
Keeping quiet is a bad idea,
even if you weren't involved.
For crying out loud...
Lain, I'm sorry!
This is all our fault. Are you okay, Lain?
Are you all right, Lain?
A...
What is it, Lain?
A... ri... su.
Arisu! Come on! We're going home.
Lain...
Arisu!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry, Lain...
Tomorrow... Let's talk tomorrow, okay?
I'm sorry!
So do you want to head home, too?
A... risu.
You have a key, right?
Yes.
Message...
There are no messages for Lain.
Good night, Navi.
Good night, Lain.
Don't you think it's embarrassing
for a junior high-schooler...
...to oversleep and be late for school?
Mom... About last night...
Hm? What about it?
Never mind.
Lain.
It's me, Lain. You can hear me, can't you?
Who's there?
You are not alone.
--'Morning!
--Good morning!
Oh, my god!
Was he cute?
Yeah, they wouldn't show his face on TV!
Well...
Oh, you were screaming the
whole time. Did you even see his face?
Well, yeah, but...
I was a little--
You were too scared to look.
Lain!
Lain, did you get in trouble yesterday?
Come on, it wasn't really our fault.
I'm sorry. I'll be right back.
Right, Arisu was closest to the guy!
So, was there blood splattered all over?
Yeah...
Tell them!
--Come on!
--Arisu!
But that's not all.
If you look at the Psyche as a mere
processor, you lose sight of the whole.
As a multi-purpose information terminal,
the Navi has come into wide
use even among grade-schoolers.
However, activity within the
Wired is currently limited by the machine.
The Psyche can dramatically
increase the performance of any Navi.
There was no reason for me to
stay in the real world any longer.
In the real world, it didn't
matter if I was there or not.
When I realized that, I was no
longer afraid of losing my body.
Who is Lain?
Huh?
Who is Lain? Who is Lain?
Who is Lain?
There's something wrong with us!
We saw someone die
right in front of us yesterday,
but we're acting like it's
something we saw in a movie.
I know we were there last
night, but it didn't seem real.
I guess it's like that for me, too.
I don't think you should
take it so seriously, Arisu.
No, that's not what I mean.
I'm saying it's strange
that we can't take it seriously.
Right, Lain?
Huh? What?
What's that, a love letter?
No way !
N-No! I don't think it is, anyway...
Let us see! Let us see!
Come on, don't be stingy! Show us!
Stop that! It's mean!
A brown paper envelope, huh?
What's written on it?
--Huh?
--What the heck is this ?
Talk about boring!
I knew it.
Psyche...
You've got it all wrong!
Somebody peeped at my voice mail!
I can't believe it!
As the relevant clauses were
not in the résumé we received,
we are currently discussing how
to handle it. As for your company...
I love kissing. Just kissing
is enough to make me happy.
You heard about that kid pulling
a stupid stunt on Accela, right?
Looks like the black market
supplier is freaking out.
You can't find it anywhere now.
Rumor has it that the Psyche chip is
mass-produced in factories in Taiwan.
Rumor also says that it was
designed by a group called the Knights.
But I'm not sure if these "Knights" even exist.
In the Wired, there are a
lot of urban legends like that.
Dying feels so good!
I feel accelerated...
What the--? There's someone in my room!
It's a little person like a kid
in a red and green striped shirt!
I can't move in my bed! It's
standing by my door, watching me!
Help me!
I have a picture of you with your secret lover.
I just want to do business. What do you say?
If you don't buy it, I'll leak this
image data to your company's server.
You'll be famous all over the Wired.
Lain, why won't you come here?
Lain has new mail.
Navi--
How's it going, Lain?
Gotten used to your new Navi?
Something wrong?
Do you know what this is?
No.
I thought...
I thought you'd know, Dad.
I said I don't know.
Come on, why not?
No... I can't...
Why not? I love you.
Lain!
Where you been lately?
I haven't seen you around.
I...
What the--? Damn, you're sure
going for the "little girl" look today...
Let's have another rave, okay?
I'll leave the planning to you.
--Why're you trying to act so tough?
--Excuse me.
Look who's talking!
Do you know what this is?
I-Is that a Psyche ?!
Wha--
No way!
I've never seen one before!
W-Where did you buy it?
You know what this is?
What're you saying?
With that installed, I could get full
access to the Wired with even this !
How do you use it?
Talk about lame!
You don't even know that ?
Can I buy it off you? Can I?
Moron! Like you could buy something like that!
What kind of Navi do you have?
I'm not really sure. It's a Tachibana.
Their newest model, I think.
Awesome !
Have you gotten inside it?
You in eighth grade? Ninth?
Eighth.
Then you've taken Basic Information, right?
A Navi's basic motherboard
layout is in the textbook.
You connect it to the board,
opposite the main processor.
It intercepts the original data
and manipulates it on its own.
Using it is easier than building a model kit.
You just need to watch
out for static electricity.
Oh. Thanks.
Hold it!
Information isn't free, not in
the Wired or in the real world.
How much you gonna charge? How much?
Uh...
You're Lain, aren't you?
I saw you once. In the Wired.
You saw me? In the Wired?
You were totally different
then than you are now.
Most people take on a
personality in the Wired...
...that's different than what
they have in the real world,
but yours are total opposites.
No way !
You were here when that idiot
started shooting, too, weren't you?
What are you planning?
What... What should I do for you?
Go out on a date with me!
Moron.
But not like you are now.
I want the wild Lain.
I-I'm just kidding!
But if you feel like it sometime...
What're you talking about?!
Hey...
Forget about it! Let's go!
Sure!
What's so great about you ?
Uh... Excuse me?
Are you here to see someone?
Who are you?
You never saw us.
W-What...? I'll call the police!
We're not here, you see.
H-Hey...
W-What the hell ?
Mom, if they show up again, call the cops!
Are you listening, Mom?
Damn it...
W-What're you doing, Lain?
What are you doing?
Why are you dressed like that?
Well, I heard that you have to
watch out for static electricity.
So I thought it'd probably be
safest if I took off my clothes.
A-Are you kidding?
Welcome home, sis!
I thought I was innocent,
but I'm being punished.
I didn't start this, but
I have to finish it somehow.
I can't say I didn't know about it,
but I don't remember taking part in it.
I get the feeling my freedom cost me dearly,
but I don't remember selling my soul cheaply.
Hey, hey!
Until I die and say goodbye...
...no one will ever catch me.
You probably don't know the eternal outlaws...
...who wander the distant night.