Oh, okay... So that's how it works.
I had no idea the world was this simple.
I always thought the world
was such a big and scary place,
but once you figure it out, it's all so easy.
See? I told you it would be.
That's terrible, Lain!
I can't believe you just said that!
Lain...
I know, but it's true!
--That's the first I've heard of it!
--What does it mean?
--Acting all high and mighty again, huh, Lain?
That reminds me, Juri.
What?
"You should just rewrite bad memories."
But that's...
But that's--
Unbelievable...
Aw, c'mon...!
People only have substance
within the memories of others.
That's why there were all kinds of me's.
There weren't a lot of me's,
I was just inside all
sorts of people, that's all.
Really... No kidding?
Come on, Taro, who are you talking to?
W-What's up?
You know, I...
I kissed an angel.
Taro...
Lain... Lain...
Lain...
Lain... Lain... Lain...
Lain... Lain...
Protocol Seven is expected to allow
the seamless sharing of information...
...between the Wired and the real world.
And now, the following message...
Let's all love Lain! Let's all love Lain!
Let's all love... Let's all...
Let's... Let's... Let's...
All the functions of the
human body, without exception,
can be put into words and
described in materialistic terms.
The body is nothing but a machine.
If the physical limitations of the
body restrict mankind's evolution,
it would be as if the fall of
the species called "man"...
...had already been decided
by a God that doesn't even exist.
The information etched inside
humans isn't only that which...
...they themselves have acquired as individuals.
This species called man is
connected to his predecessors,
and information has accumulated within him.
If that information isn't shared,
it's meaningless. Mere data .
Mankind can evolve. Evolve by their own power.
But to do that, they must
first know what they truly are.
What do you think you are?
Originally, people were connected to each other.
All I've done is to make
things as they once were.
That's what you have done, Lain.
So you can do anything you want.
I thought you quit smoking.
Why is this happening? We did
exactly what we were told to do!
It means that our client wasn't
the only one who thought that...
...those computer geeks playing
"secret society" would be trouble.
What do you mean?
Our client was in contact with Masami Eiri.
No, maybe Eiri was behind it all.
Enough about Eiri, okay?
The guy's dead.
He's not dead.
Whether he had a body or not never mattered.
It never mattered.
Are you serious?
Payment for services rendered, huh?
You've been using us, haven't you?!
Interpret it any way you like.
You want us to leave town, huh? And go   where ?
I suppose a place with no power
lines that isn't covered by a satellite.
There's no place like that
on Earth, and you know it!
If you're going to run, you'll
have to find a place like that.
What's going to happen?
What are you planning to do...
...by connecting the Wired to
the real world without any devices?
Something wonderful is going to happen.
I'm looking forward to it. Aren't  you ?
What the--?
What's wrong?!
What are you seeing?!
Hey!
"Iwakura"
Lain?
No...!
This is Lain's room?
Lain?
L-Lain!
A... risu?
What did you do?
Nothing.
I've just been watching.
Watching what?
I... I thought I had gone crazy.
But I didn't!
Lain! Why did you leave only me?
Why did you only leave my memories alone?
Why do I always have to
remember all those horrible things?!
Do you hate me that much, Lain?
I... I can't take this!
No... You've got it all wrong, Arisu.
I didn't want to hurt you.
Liar! Look at what you've done!
But you're okay, aren't you, Arisu?
You were my friend, even
without connecting with me, Arisu.
What are you saying?
You're my only friend, Arisu.
Even without connecting with me.
"Connecting"? W-What do you mean?
Connecting to me... And everyone...
S-Stop!
I love you, Arisu.
Do you know what you're saying, Lain?
Humans were originally
connected at an unconscious level.
I reconnected them, that's all.
Lain, you...?
I don't do anything.
It doesn't matter which is
real, this side or the other...
I was in both.
I'm a program designed
to destroy the barrier...
...between the Wired and the real world.
You're a program , Lain...?
You and everyone else,
Arisu, you're just applications.
The truth is, you don't need bodies.
You're wrong.
I don't really understand what
you're saying, but I think you're wrong.
Your body's cold, but you're alive, Lain.
Mine, too. See?
See? My heart...
...it's beating.
Beating... Beating...
But why? Why's it beating like that?
Because I'm scared.
It's pounding because I'm scared.
But you're smiling, Arisu.
Yeah, I guess I am. But I'm scared.
I've always been scared. I wonder why?
I wonder why?
Because she's afraid of losing her body.
All sensations are caused
by impulses in the brain.
You just need to block the unpleasant impulses.
Select only the happy, pleasant ones.
Really?
Lain? Who are you talking to?
If you really love her, why
don't you connect with her?
I'm not sure.
Lain? Who are you talking to?
Lain!
You must have a bug.
Very well. I'll take my time and
give you a thorough debugging.
Come, Lain.
What I don't understand is you , God.
Y-You're... talking to God ?
What don't you understand, Lain?
What you did was to
remove devices from the Wired.
Phones... Television... The network...
Without those, you couldn't have done anything.
Yes. Those are things which
accompanied human evolution.
Humans who are further evolved than others...
...have a right to greater abilities.
Who gave you those rights?
The program that inserted
code synched to the Earth's...
...characteristic frequency
into the Protocol Seven code,
which would raise the collective
unconscious to the conscious level.
Did you really come up
with the idea by yourself?
What are you getting at?
No, it can't be... It can't be!
Are you telling me
that there really is a God?!
It doesn't matter.
With no body, you can't understand.
It's a lie! I... I'm omnipotent!
I gave you a body here in the real world!
You were omnipresent, scattered
through the Wired! I gave you an ego!
You mean to say--
If that's true of me, what about you ?
I'm different! I--
The Wired isn't an
upper layer of the real world.
What do you mean?
Inside the Wired, you were God, all right.
But what about before
the Wired was created?
You're just an acting God,
standing in for someone...
...who was waiting for the
Wired to reach its current state.
An "acting" God?!
That can't be!
Arisu!
A body doesn't mean anything to you, right?
No!
I thought I was innocent,
but I'm being punished.
I didn't start this, but
I have to finish it somehow.
I can't say I didn't know about it,
but I don't remember taking part in it.
I get the feeling my freedom cost me dearly,
but I don't remember selling my soul cheaply.
Hey, hey!
Until I die and say goodbye...
...no one will ever catch me.
You probably don't know the eternal outlaws...
...who wander the distant night.