[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands
marked by their
ability to retain
and selectively
manifest the essence
of humanity's
greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of these
specialized strands
use AU spheres to
activate the abilities
lying dormant within themselves,
which then materialize
as physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is
a record of the struggle
between DOGOO,
a supranational organization
comprised of
trained E-Gene Holders,
and mankind's greatest threat,
the Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
Gun Three: "Capa's Island."
[SIO snoring]
[SAINT-GERMAIN] We've begun
our initial descent.
Please place your
seats and tray tables
in their full,
upright position.
Oh, man.
I did not pack for
this kinda humidity.
Holy cow!
After you,
if you would please.
Done!
[COMMANDER} I have
grave reservations
about subjecting
her to his methods.
[DOGOO] Until she can
absorb his methods,
we dare not
subject her to battle.
Proper, if unorthodox
training, is paramount.
Do you disagree?
Not entirely.
[DOGOO] A sniper must be
held to higher standards.
--[DOGOO] For everyone's sake.
--[SIO snoring]
Kindly dismount.
Huh? Yes, sir!
Wait here for
further instruction.
Further instruction?
What does that mean?
Don't leave me here alone!
Catch!
Right.
Let's go!
Come on!
Steady!
Feed 'em some lead!
No points this round.
Okay.
Pretty sure I was just killed.
Pretty damn
persuasive simulations, eh?
Courtesy of my AU weapon.
Welcome to
DOGOO's fancy-schmancy
indoor training facility.
Yo, Saint-Germain.
Yes?
No bullshit:
this gal actually
rack up 200 body
count in Taiwan?
Lest my memory deceives,
you saw the footage yourself.
Everybody's
Michael Bay these days.
If you want cinéma vérité,
you stick with analog.
The Commander expects you
to fully prepare
this young woman,
regardless of your opinion
as to her record's veracity.
Lighten up.
I'm a man who does
the job he is paid to do.
Period.
Hell, I traded my scruples
for a chariot years ago.
You're welcome.
Apologies for the hardship.
Please.
Allow me.
So, who's
the wreck in the chair
trying to squeeze
blood from rock?
I'm Robert Capa,
your hapless instructor.
Huh?
As in Robert Capa
the big-time war photographer?
Tomorrow things get real.
You'll want to hit the hay.
Oh, wait!
Better let mom know
I got here in one piece.
And yeah!
Maybe Asao's
out of the hospital!
What, really?
I'm afraid DOGOO observes
a zero tolerance policy
vis-à-vis personal communiqués
from within the perimeter.
D'Okay, I'm gonna
explain this one more time:
a teenage girl can't survive
without social media--!
What a teenage girl
requires to survive
is no longer your concern.
Life, for you, is now DOGOO.
If you need to make
an emergency call--
Forget it.
Never mind.
Stupid friggin' rules!
You'd think I joined a convent!
Oh. Yeah. Training.
Hooray.
Maybe I'm not cut out for this.
For reals.
Up and at them!
We'd appreciate you
gettin' that ass in gear!
Gimme a break.
Today would be nice!
Sir!
Yes, sir!
Eat it, mutant guppies!
Bull's-eye!
You're joking, right?
Do you not even understand
the concept of sniping?
'Less I say otherwise,
I expect you to hit them
'tween the eyes from last week!
I'm doing the best I can.
Eyes on the target!
Don't even think
of hurling on my floor.
12 laps to go!
Remind me what
the point of this is again?
An E-Gene Holder is
combat-ready at all times!
This is good ol'
fashioned military training.
I'm not runnin' a health spa!
Mustn't be late for class.
On your feet, please.
Just give me a couple minutes.
I'm afraid the Commander has
certain expectations of you.
Yes, sir.
The effects on
the Holder of activating
and engaging his or her
AU weapon are varied.
Determined by the physical
and psychological
constitution of said Holder,
the effects range from
an increase in strength,
to euphoria--
[SAINT-GERMAIN]
--to heightened awareness.
Sufficiently rested?
Yes, sir.
It's Friday, isn't it?
Not gonna lie.
Kinda miss the white noise.
Call me selfish,
but fair is fair.
If I'm expected
to lay down my life
defending Earth from aliens,
I'm owed some
basic human rights.
Jackpot!
Keep me from texting.
Come to mama!
They've totally
got an E-767 AWACS!
And a Self Defense Force US-2?
I gotta get some pics of these!
I am geeking out
so hard right now!
Oh.
I-- uh.
I--I'm sorry.
I got lost!
I shouldn't be here.
I'll go!
Miss Ogura?
Yes?
Wow, it's an
honor to meet you.
Wait.
Seriously?
Footage of you
makin' swiss cheese
outta those bugs in
Taiwan has made the rounds.
You're famous,
and not just here!
In fact, could
I get an autograph
for my mom back home?
Well, I-- S'pose I could--
Not to weird you out,
but I've got some fresh
bananas from back home!
Yeah--we're a
li'l star-struck.
Sorry; apparently
I've forgotten my manners.
Second Lieutenant
Harold S. Conway!
And you're American?
Well, he is;
I'm from Australia, mate!
Canada, born n' raised!
Salutations from the homeland!
S'up from the Philippines!
Hey!
So about that banana.
Dude, give it a rest!
If she wants
anything it's from Japan!
I got a crate of Kiwi!
No thanks!
Please?
Sorry 'bout that.
Meeting the Nobunagun
is kind of big deal,
case you couldn't tell.
So, DOGOO pulled you
guys from all over, huh?
Yep; whole
world's in this fight.
We don't see
much action, though;
mostly oceanography
and vessel maintenance.
When the Alex Rogan needs
refueling, we're the guys.
I'm guessing the
Alex Rogan is a ship?
I'm sure you'll
be introduced before long.
Huh.
This here is the plane
my unit gets to tool around in.
Whoa!
Is that based off a C-130?
Like an HC.
No, SC?
WC-130J, actually.
No friggin' way!
The Hurricane Hunter!
Yeah, you know it?
Duh!
Is that even a question?
You're only the high-flying
weather recon team
who risks life and limb scaling
Category 5s in this beaut!
Well, I don't know if
it's as glamorous as all that.
Although, she does
catch serious wind.
Of all the places for this
glorious piece of
machinery to be hiding.
I know, right?
Who'd a'thunk it?
Backwater outfit like us.
Totally not what I meant!
Just, going off the mess hall,
this place is a ghost town.
Must seem like it, I imagine.
We're not really supposed
to eat with you Holders.
That doesn't seem too nice.
There're ways around it,
if you want.
I mean, if you wander
down to the commons.
Done!
3 more laps!
Try not to keel over!
Gonna die.
No.
Screw that.
Now, a handful
of notable experts
believe it's
theoretically possible
for a Holder
to enable their powers
without the aid
of an AU sphere.
However.
Your training
regimen is intense.
How ya holdin' up?
Well, I am me, so--
Aw, don't talk like that!
The fact they brought
you here in the first place
means you're certifiably a
cut above the average soldier.
You just gotta learn
to have a little confidence!
D'aw, you're so sweet!
I think somebody
needs a second helping.
What?
I've got her covered!
Nobunagun!
Ready to take out the trash!
Tell me.
Why exactly do you insist on
calling yourself "Nobunagun"?
Huh?
Well, a kickass weapon
like this needs a kickass name!
Moving on.
Listen, I notice you're making
friendly with the troops.
Oh.
Yeah!
Kinda hard not to
when they're all so nice--
Well, don't.
They're shields.
Say what?
Ordinary humans,
civilian or otherwise,
stand a snowball's
chance in hell against an EI.
Only use for a non-Holder
in the field is a decoy.
You don't need
to call 'em that.
Sacrificial pawns
have a better ring?
Can't imagine it does,
considering
the military casualties
you could've
prevented in Taiwan
if you'd summoned
the energy to pick off
that last line
of Foot Soldier Types.
If you're looking to bond
with fun new people,
your priorities need an enema.
We're not here to play.
Yeah.
Show me pissed.
Wha--?
Huh?
Like bein' in a funhouse, ja?
Figured you
could use the closure.
You do have only
yourself to be mad at.
Sure, treat 'em like a mirage
if you feel like bein' dead.
What?
Thought you might be pining
for the familiar
comforts of home.
Since you think
I'm so hard on you.
Now make the most of
your home field advantage!
What's taking so long;
they can't be that
much of a challenge.
Come on, I'm hungry!
No, jackass;
you're doing it wrong!
Damn it to hell,
aim before you fire!
Aiming, right.
If I want quantity over quality,
I'll shop wholesale!
You're wasting precious energy!
I got this.
I got this!
Why'm I not hitting 'em?
Because that
thing called recoil
is wreaking havoc with
your center of gravity!
It's about control!
An AU weapon is an expression
of its wielder's
innate capabilities.
Even the bullets depend
on you for their existence.
Great!
That's all well and good, but--!
I just can't!
Chin up, girlie.
This is how we roll.
Give it your all
or I give you mine.
A man has his needs.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Hey.
Lookie there.
You can actually hit
a motionless target.
Too bad the enemy moves.
You gotta cut
'em off at the pass.
Focus your scope on where
the target is moving to.
Aim ahead of your subject.
It's about control.
Aim before you shoot.
No full-auto.
Focus on where
the target's about to be.
Fire!
No!
Miss Ogura!
Um, hey.
Thank you for being so awesome!
Whatever I did,
I'm sure it's nothing.
Sorry, miss, but I don't call
literally taking the shirt
off your back for us "nothing."
What now?
Uh.
Wait.
I--
The hell are those?
First word comes to
my mind is "amazing!"
I'll cherish this
'til the day I die!
Dude.
Capa!
What do you want now?
Some pointers on crowd control?
No!
Explain this!
That?
Nothing.
Li'l something I shot
with your doppelgänger.
You dig the composition?
Give me film over digital
any day of the week.
Certainly brings a smile
to your comrades' faces, ja?
So now they're comrades, not
shields or sacrificial pawns?
That was just
smack-talk to wake you up.
No one says that about
their brothers and means it.
Huh?
You ass!
This crap is unacceptable!
Right, then.
See you later.
Be safe up there, okay?
I'll be rootin' for ya!
So cool.
Speaking of "cool,"
you could stand to take
a page or 2 from those boys.
As things are now,
the Commander's
faith in you is timorous.
Today we stick to fundamentals.
Yes, sir.
This is D-101 reporting.
We're currently passing
through Mexican airspace.
Entering danger zone.
[PILOT 3A]
They call this one Olga.
Dang, been a few since
we had a li'l lady this hot.
Yeah, but only one
li'l lady's got my heart.
[PILOT 3A] All right,
let's catch some wind!
Roger!
Bogies, sir!
They're riding
on the central winds!
[PILOT 3A] What moron'd put
a fleet in the middle of this?
We're blowing at
60 meters a second!
Can't identify as
friendly or hostile!
No metals detected!
Good god.
Don't tell me it's--!
[FEMALE OP 1B] Robert Capa!
Nobunagun!
Suspend training immediately.
What now?
[FEMALE OP 1B]
We have an emergency.
D-101 appears
to have been shot down
over the Gulf of Mexico while
on a hurricane recon mission.
Huh?
[FEMALE OP 1B]
A helicopter is standing by.
Both of you are
to board immediately.
Repeat: board immediately.
But they--
Please no.
Oi, you heard about
the Hurricane, right?
You talkin' about the kaiju that
looks like a giant jellyfish?
Fantastic.
She's an otaku.
What?
Next time.
Gun Four: "Hurricane."
I recommend you watch.