[IYO (13 years old)]
My homeland is destroyed!
Everyone I know is dead!
I failed.
I couldn't be strong
like Queen Himiko.
[DOGOO]
You're alone.
I know that feeling
all too well.
That night, 1,800 years ago,
is when you and I first met.
Gun Ten: "DOGOO."
[DOGOO] Welcome back,
my young friend.
Our next target is
the Frankish Empire.
Its lords,
the Merovingians,
may be of use
to us in our fight.
[IYO (13 years old)]
"The Frankish Empire?"
They rose to prominence
while you were sleeping.
How long did
I sleep, anyhow?
Approximately
300 years.
Oh, I see.
Everyone and
everything I ever knew
are nothing
but dust now.
[IYO (16 years old)]
Who is this man?
[DOGOO] I
thought you might
pine for
companionship,
and this one seemed
suitably interesting,
so I brought
him with me.
A pleasure to meet you.
I am Saint-Germain.
What do you
think you're doing?
I greet you in
the European way.
I meant you
no offense by it.
[DOGOO] At last.
I've finished converting
the DNA samples into E-genes.
Now we must slip them
into various human bloodlines.
Leave that to us.
We shall find
appropriate candidates.
The souls of our
chosen heroes
will pass down from one
generation to the next,
with none of them the wiser.
When the fateful hour
tolls, they will awaken.
We have to seed as many warriors
within your species as we can.
The enemy is already on its way
to Earth, and the hour is late.
Mankind hinges on this mission.
I can hardly wait.
[COMMANDER] I remember
thinking to myself
that when next I awoke,
this strange man
would be long gone.
I'd return to being alone.
A forgotten relic of a lost age.
[SAINT-GERMAIN]
Welcome back, Miss.
[IYO (18 years old)]
Don't look!
How long did I
sleep this time?
200 years, I daresay.
How are you here?
My constitution is strong.
Rest assured.
Do you see
what I mean?
I told you he
was interesting.
So, then, shall we
go find new additions
to our genetic
menagerie?
You can't swing
the proverbial cat
in that fortress
without hitting a hero.
So why this man?
All he has to
commend him is speed.
Yes, I know.
But maybe
it'll come in handy!
Sleeping Beauty
awakens.
[IYO (20 years old)]
Where to, now?
The country of
your birth, Miss.
Oh!
Splendid!
I wonder who
we'll be taking!
Of all people,
you're choosing him?
[DOGOO] He's the sovereign
of your land, Iyo.
He and Queen Himiko
have much in common.
They don't!
Look at him!
This man is a butcher!
I'm not preserving his soul
for its gentle nature.
You want to entrust
my planet's future
to a man who finds
no value in human life?
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
I thought you would have
learned that in 1,200 years.
Dammit, it's
only been 7 for me!
[SAINT-GERMAIN]
Wait!
[Iyo] I'm not your
problem anymore, you know.
[SAINT-GERMAIN] I couldn't
let you go alone.
What sort of fair-weather
companion would that make me?
[COMMANDER] For the
first time in centuries,
I began to live life
as any other human.
A little house,
in a little village.
The pleasures of the harvest.
The changing of the seasons,
which I hadn't
witnessed in so long.
And then...
[IYO (60 years old)]
Look at you,
lodging with a wrinkled
old thing like me.
People will talk,
you know!
Let them.
From where I stand,
you've aged nary
a fortnight, Miss.
[IYO]
It's gone.
All these years later,
I've lost my home again!
We could start
anew elsewhere.
No.
I should have figured
it out centuries ago,
but I've finally
learned my lesson.
There are things in life
that must be protected
by any means necessary--
any people necessary!
Even Nobunaga.
[DOGOO] So, you've had
a change of heart?
[IYO]
I swear to you.
I'll dedicate whatever
time I may have left
to the defense of Earth,
and all life on it.
Good morning to you,
Commander.
Commander?
Our enemy.
Are they here yet?
[DOGOO]
Almost.
Their landfall is imminent.
Which is why you
must take the reins
of the organization
we discussed.
The E-genes have
been disseminated
into the general public.
Please, rethink this!
I'm not qualified!
The millennia have started
to weigh heavily on me.
I am not immune to
the passage of time.
I see.
I'm sorry we only
have my old hand-me-down.
[DOGOO]
Thank you, Iyo.
This task belongs
to your kind now.
I leave the rest to you.
It was only yesterday,
or so it feels.
This moment was
a long time coming.
Yes.
However...
Gandhi to Johnny Rico.
The Battleship Type has pulled
back into the tunnel again.
Johnny Rico to Ellen Ripley.
Prepare for
underwater surveillance.
If it sticks to pattern,
it'll reach your
side in about an hour.
Copy, Johnny Rico.
I'm going below.
Welcome back, Gandhi.
I don't understand it.
All it does is peek out
of the tunnel on this side
and then hurry
back over to the other.
Not that
I'm complaining, mind you.
We can't even scratch that thing
without loads more manpower.
We are well aware
of the manpower shortage.
But even with our
being at a disadvantage,
this will be a decisive
moment in our war against them.
Rest easy, my Queen.
I swear to you, our homeland
will be kept safe this time.
Thank you.
Oh, what do I do now?
We're alone together!
You birds done
chewin' the fat?
Huh?
There's somethin'
we need to talk about.
There's something we
need to talk about?!
Oh God!
We made eye contact!
Huh?
Whoops!
I gotta know--
What?
What do you want?
How come you
were in the middle?
Huh?
When that giant
squid wannabe
took a potshot at
the Clayton Forrester,
you were right
in front of it.
No reason to be there unless
you knew the ship was in danger.
Weren't time to
double back after he surfaced,
you must'a been there
ahead of schedule.
So what was the tip-off?
I'm not sure.
I mean, it just kinda seemed
like the right thing to do.
Like a nudge from
the ol' samurai in yer head?
Huh?
Well, I don't really
get how all this stuff works.
Yeah, I guess so!
So then why'd
you keep mum about it?
Huh?
Wanted ta kill
him yourself
and be
the big hero?
Not in the least!
Ah, don't get your
knickers in a twist.
I been watching ya,
and you're not
that kind of girl.
Clearly.
What?
He's been watching me?
Like, watching watching me?
I kept it to myself
'cause I'm such a noob
and you guys know
what you're doing
and I didn't want to be wrong,
not with so much on the line.
It was just a hunch.
Well I got
a hunch
we're about to
face death again.
What?
I just heard.
The brass decided
to take that tunnel.
And all they're
gonna use
are First and Second
Platoons to do it.
Wait, all by ourselves?
Vidocq and the Commander
are putting together
a plan as we speak.
Whatever it is,
I got a bad
feeling about it.
My gut says
it's too dangerous.
Listen up.
My E-gene says
we need you,
so maybe we do.
Need me?
Yeah.
'Cause your hunches
are spot-on.
I dunno.
This from the bloke
who outwitted every
bobby in London-town.
He's got a real
feel for this stuff.
Think I'd just
take the compliment.
Better not to offend him.
"Fifty years in
the world of the living--"
Asai has betrayed us!
How dare he?
Lord Nobunaga!
We'll be pinned between
Asakura and Asai if we stay!
[HIDEYOSHI]
Lord Nobunaga!
Go now; I shall take
to the rear with my men!
Withdraw while I hold them off!
Hideyoshi!
And at the center of
that nest, the true guardian
of EI evolutionary history:
The Battleship Type.
Here's the latest
interior scan of the tunnel.
We need better intel on
the strength of those tentacles!
We're flying blind!
That's all the data we have!
What if we approach
from this angle?
Hey, guys--listen up!
I didn't even know
you were back.
Go ahead, girl--
speak your piece.
Uh, well.
I guess I sort of
have an opinion
about the plan
to take the tunnel?
Ugh.
Could you piece
your thoughts together
before you open your mouth?
When you don't,
we waste valuable time
while you gather
your wits about you.
This operation
to conquer the tunnel
is our most
important mission thus far.
Simply put,
our success or lack thereof,
will set the tone for
the remainder of this war.
This is a place
for educated opinions!
You do not traipse in here
and start spitballing tactics!
We're trying to save as
many lives as we can here!
Don't you talk to me
like I'm a damn fool!
You have the floor.
The EIs with the base cells
are hiding in the tunnel,
so we're gonna get to 'em
by defeating the big one
who's goaltending
those entrances, right?
It's currently going back and
forth between the two entrances,
which is actually pretty
weird if you think about it.
If it wants to intercept us,
why not wait in the middle?
Yeah.
It's like he's purposely
trying to piss us off.
--That's what I'm saying!
--Huh?
All we're paying attention
to are those entrances.
What's going on elsewhere?
What if the bulk of
the Evolutionary Invaders
are busy digging
an escape tunnel
that empties out
to who-knows-where?
An'--
allowing them all to escape?
That's my theory, at least.
[COMMANDER]
Well, Vidocq?
Yes, Commander!
I'd say that hypothesis
is not without its merits.
Truth be told, she's
probably right on the money.
Damn her eyes!
Why didn't I think of that?
Can you deduce a possible exit
point for this "escape tunnel?"
Of course.
Their previous
failures would tell them
that the nearby coastlines
and the Panama Canal
are heavily guarded.
Lake Nicaragua is their
most likely destination,
given the variables.
Once they've dispersed
into a lake of that size,
finding them will be difficult.
We need to intercept them before
they reach their destination.
That's why beating
the Battleship Type
is our top priority.
Don't you see
that's a waste of time?
All I'm saying is instead
of attacking 'em from behind
and it being super tough,
let's hit the enemy
where they least expect it
and engage 'em head-on.
You little--!
I take it you have a plan?
Yeah!
Cutting them off at
the pass is gonna be too tough
while they're underground,
so forget that.
Instead...
We'll make them change course.
Y'know, draw 'em above-ground!
When they show up,
we'll already be there,
ready to put
the hurt down on 'em!
This is lunacy!
She speaks as though we
can dictate their actions!
'Cause we can!
It's gonna work, but it'll take
all we've got to pull it off.
[CAPA] You pull me
from active duty, and now this?
Guess the girl's
getting her payback.
Must be all the grief
I gave her during basic.
Ain't that a bitch!
When this is all over,
I'm stomping the rookie flat.
My role in this
mission is bollocks!
Hold on!
This isn't gonna work!
Incorrect.
I've factored all variables
in Sio's plan of attack.
Their powers combined
should be enough.
So where do they go,
once Newton and Capa
do their thing?
Filtering the enemy's
route and speed
through the
topographical specifics,
then applying
Newton's and Capa's
strength against that data--
I have it.
This will be our battleground.
Evacuation of
civilians complete.
You are clear to engage.
Yeh, roger that.
[GERONIMO] It's a clever
plan she's thought up.
But will it actually work?
With you helping,
I'm sure it'll be perfect!
Give it your all, Gaudí.
You play an
important part, don'tcha!
Right.
[HUNTER] I can't believe
they're sending me into combat.
Dammit, Jack, I'm a doctor!
Better you try my job
than I try yours.
A blade's a blade,
and we're short on bodies.
The best of British out there,
and remember--I'll be
too busy to save you.
Feels like rush hour
on the 405, man.
Heh, ya think we'll
see any action tonight?
I don't think anything's
gonna pop out of the water
with a target on it,
if that's what you mean.
It's my first time, Cyx.
Be gentle.
Bite me, Mahesh.
No one rides on the back
of my bike except the Princess!
I hear we have your platoon's
rookie to thank for all this?
Yes.
She's getting us through
quite the sticky wicket.
Actually...
She's been doing that
for us all this time.
Ever since we
first met in Taiwan.
[CYX] Whatever.
Can I run her over
when this is all done?
Doesn't that seem
a little much?
The Battleship
Type's the problem!
If it backs up the little ones,
we're done for!
Can't we keep him
busy with a decoy?
We could dangle some Holders
at the tunnel entrances!
Absolutely not!
We're already spreading our
Holders way too thin out there!
One is enough!
You only need one E-gene
holder to take down that squid.
Yours truly!
Here we go!
Oi.
How come you named this
operation "Stone Forest"?
Huh?
No reason!
Totally random!
Yup!
It's "Ishinomori" in Japanese--
ain't he a manga writer?
Next time, Gun Eleven:
"Operation Stone Forest,
Part 1"!
You are such a nerd.