[GERONIMO gasps]
[JACK gasps]
[GERONIMO] It fired?
[NEWTON] It's huge!
[CYX] Is there a warhead?
[JACK] If that goes off!
[GANDHI] It's headed
straight for the Commander!
[SIO grunts]
Ah! What the--?
[SIO] Ahhh!
[gasps]
[SIO] Huh.
Okay...
[monitor beeping]
I'm home.
[knock at the door]
[SIO] Yeah?
Good to have you back with us.
Uh, how long have I been out?
[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands marked
by their ability to retain
and selectively manifest
the essence of
humanity's greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of
these specialized
strands use AU spheres
to activate the
abilities lying dormant
within themselves,
which then materialize as
physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is
a record of the struggle
between DOGOO, a supranational
organization comprised of
trained E-Gene
Holders, and mankind's
greatest threat,
the Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
[SIO]
Gun Nine: "Sio and Kaoru."
[JACK] Japan? Right
bit of overkill, innit?
Not like she's at
death's door or nothin'.
Just a few nicks.
[GANDHI] Strange, I grant you,
but it is the result of
a direct order from
the Commander herself.
[JACK] Eh?
All told, I am thankful
Sio is better off than some.
[BOTH] Hm?
[GANDHI] There is a very
real possibility Galileo will
never see the
front lines again.
[monitor beeping]
[huffs]
So then what's our next move?
That depends on
how Vidocq's meeting
with the brass turns out.
[GANDHI] Which is
unfolding as we speak.
I hate being
mentally outgunned.
Come now, friend.
No one could
foresee the enemy's--
[JACK] She did.
That's what I mean.
Experienced operatives
were bested by a rookie.
[JACK sighs]
[VIDOCQ] Take note,
the prevailing features of
these Engineer
Types are arthropoidal.
We presume the
tunnel's construction
depended largely on them.
[VIDOCQ] Also
resembling arthropods are
the Land Mine Types.
So-called for their ability
to self-destruct on contact.
Size varies; here
you see the larger ones.
Their destructive capacity
is roughly equivalent
to that of a
modest nuclear warhead.
Next we have the Battleship
Type, whose chief function
appears to be
that of patrol guard.
Being a cephalopod, its
body is uniquely suited to
the task of navigating
the maze-like tunnel
it's charged to protect.
No less than seven
E-gene Holders from
First and Second
Platoons were dispatched
to engage the Battleship Type.
It overpowered them
as you or I might a fly.
Injuring two and leaving Clayton
Forrester worse for wear;
though her damage is minor.
And, to be fair, more a
product of Second Platoon's
famed Nobunagun, correct?
The girl's impeccable timing,
as well as her courage,
spared the lives of
every crewmember aboard.
Yes. Kudos to her.
[DOGOO]
The injured you mentioned.
Nobunagun is one of them, yes?
[VIDOCQ] Correct.
But her injuries are minimal.
Thank goodness.
The Commander's all right.
[SAINT-GERMAIN] Your transfer
to a Japanese hospital was
ordered by way of a thank you.
Well, that was nice of her.
Oh. That reminds me.
Fresh change of
clothes and a small
get-well gift
from the Commander.
A box of sugared beans.
Wow, that's really nice.
And a super serious box.
Their quality is most
exceptional, I assure you.
You find the
gift unsatisfactory?
No! I'm sure they're
awesome! I just--
Then enjoy them
at your leisure.
The doctors are hopeful.
I am told your
injuries begin and end
with a bruise
and a sprained ankle.
Tomorrow you'll be
released and taken back
to the Alex Rogan.
Feel free to spend the rest
of the day as you please.
Yes, sir.
[SAINT-GERMAIN] Good afternoon.
Uh!
[sighs]
[grunts]
Oh Japan,
how I've missed you.
[SIO] Your fresh air.
Your attitude.
Oh, I should call Mom!
Hold on. I'm in Japan.
[wails]
My phone should work!
[phone beeps]
Ahhh!
[SIO] Wow.
She really likes to text.
[knock at the door]
Yeah?
Door should be open. C'mon in.
[KAORU] Um, hey there.
Huh?
[KAORU] Long time no see,
Sio. And can I just start
by sayin' you look fabulous?
[titters]
[SIO] Oh, Asao!
[chuckles]
I'll take that as
a sign of progress!
[DOGOO] Is this not
counterintuitive? EIs evolve.
Why then are
these high-profile types
regressing into
invertebrate form?
It is odd, I grant you.
Up to this point,
the enemy has mimicked,
or appropriated,
forms along the food chain
in a direct, unbroken
line of ascent.
[VIDOCQ] Their trajectory
modeled itself on the evolution
of life here on Earth.
Yet the types most recently
encountered betray that model.
Having achieved the
oceanic vertebrate stage,
they've now chosen a form
which reverses that course,
pushing them back to the
middle of the Paleozoic Era.
I believe the adoption
of older forms indicates a
stockpile of base cells
programmed into the DNA
of every EI, regardless
of their evolutionary stage.
In other words, their
genome has immediate access
to each phase of
its development and
can reintroduce
forms previously discarded.
Is there
supporting evidence?
As a matter of
fact, there is.
[VIDOCQ] Here is a 3D
rendering of the tunnel.
Information that
Galileo courageously
risked her life to obtain.
In one of the
tunnel's many chambers,
we detected these base cells
in the belly of an arthropod.
Given that a different EI
Type is guarding this chamber,
we can assume storage and
distribution of these cells
is solely the
domain of said arthropod.
A vitally important,
yet defenseless creature.
[VIDOCQ] Bear in mind, also,
the Musashi Wonder incident,
in which the strict
division of labor between
EI Types became evident.
Not unlike a colony of bees.
[VIDOCQ] Precisely. And this
tunnel is their honeycomb.
Not only a cell storehouse,
but a munitions factory,
if you will. A nest.
[VIDOCQ] And at the
center of that nest,
the true guardian of
EI evolutionary history:
The Battleship Type.
Oh gosh. Is there
something on my cheek?
[SIO] What? Mm-mmm.
Nothing like that,
I'm just thinkin'
how it feels like forever
since I've gotten
to talk to you.
Yeah, guess it takes one
of us being in this place.
I freaked out when
I heard you got injured.
It sounds more serious
than it really is.
Hm. So it seems.
Talk about the shoe
bein' on the other
foot though, right?
Um, okay?
How bad did
you hit your head?
You do remember
coming to see me
at the hospital
after Taiwan?
Oh!
[KAORU]
That was super cool of you.
Hmmm...
[gasps]
Huh?
[SIO] I never
replied to your texts!
Heh. No worries.
I kinda got a little
trigger happy there.
[SIO] Oh, I didn't mind!
DOGOO's just crazy
strict with all that stuff!
I can only use my
phone for emergencies.
In fact, I didn't
even know you'd sent 'em;
I was just now readin'
'em as you walked in.
The thing is, I, uh--
This sounds weird,
but I texted you every day,
even though I
couldn't send 'em.
Like a diary. You know?
Well, that's a relief.
Huh?
Thought you
were avoiding me.
Figured I came
on too strong
for a "lone
wolf" like you.
No! I would
never do that!
Ancient history. So.
Hm?
Now that we're face to face,
let's fill each other in
on everything that's
been going on!
Mmm...
Mm-hmm!
[VIDOCQ] Conquering this tunnel
should be our priority one.
Destroy the enemy's
stockpile of base cells,
and prevent new
warrior classes from
seeing the light of day.
As it stands, they can exploit
their chromosomal
lineage at will.
We must hit them where it hurts!
[ADMIRAL 9A] Which, in
layman's terms, I take it,
means we have to eliminate
the Battleship Type.
Yet we're unable
to do so despite
the combined
efforts of two platoons.
Gentlemen, please; hear me out.
Placing all active Holders
on a single task force.
The Battleship Type is subj--
[DOGOO] Not possible, I fear.
Uh!
And why not?
[DOGOO] There are more pressing
concerns at the moment.
[MALE OP 1B]
Enemy confirmed near Tahiti.
Dai Zong on the
Hawaiian coast reports
[FEMALE OP 1A]
victory near the Big Island.
[DOGOO] The Invaders have
begun landfall operations
at multiple points all across
the Pacific, simultaneously.
Cleary a preemptive
bid to divide and conquer
in anticipation of
your tunnel strategy.
We have no choice but to
answer them and they know this.
[MALE OP 1A] Just reported from
a fishing vessel in Tokyo Bay.
Suspect they've encountered
the wake of a probable EI.
[DOGOO] Your aggregate strike
force will have to wait.
The only forces we
can spare for deployment
on your mission are
First and Second Platoons.
[DOGOO] Adjust your
tactics accordingly.
We will have to make do.
[DOGOO] Admirals, I expect
full consent for
Vidocq's revised gambit.
[ADMIRALS 9B, C, and D] Sir.
Merde!
[SAILOR 9A]
You're absolutely sure?
Look, dammit,
I know what I saw!
Fine. Then where'd it go?
Ugh. How the hell
should I know?
[SAILOR 9A] I'm telling ya,
it was algae or somethin'.
Think about it, man:
this is Tokyo Bay!
Ain't no Invaders gonna
have the balls to come here!
[SAILOR 9B] Meh...
Yeah, you're probably right.
[underwater boom]
[SIO] Don't get me wrong;
most of 'em are fine.
I mean, they have their issues,
sure, but they're nice to me.
Adam, though--the one
they call Jack the Ripper?
Ugh! Guy picks apart
every little thing I do
like I'm some kinda spaz!
Yeesh. Doesn't sound fun.
And seriously, what kind
of psychopath is proud
to identify with a guy known
for chopping up innocent women?
Okay, be honest
with me, though.
If he gave you the time
of day, you'd totally melt.
Hu--! Aaah!
[KAORU] Don't freak out,
I'm just sayin'.
You've met some
pretty interesting people,
but of everyone,
you talk about him the most.
Yeah, 'cause he's disgusting!
Gimme a break!
[laughs]
I wish I'd gotten to
know you before all this.
All what?
The Invader scare has
the whole country on edge.
[KAORU] Everybody's pickin'
up and moving their families
deeper inland to get
clear of the line of fire.
Buying food and stuff like
it's the end of the world.
I had no idea.
The hospitals are
filling up with refugees.
See? Over there.
[KAORU]
Japan hasn't been hit yet,
so the countries
that've taken the brunt
are shipping the
survivors over here.
Mostly kids.
[KAORU] Reminds me of
what you're doin' out there:
putting yourself in harm's
way to keep the world safe.
You're amazing, Sio.
Don't put it like that!
You'll make me feel guilty
for talking smack
about DOGOO!
I don't feel amazing.
I mean, not even a little.
More like the opposite.
Still wonder if I
made the right choice.
We really gotta work
on your confidence.
It never ceases to
amaze me the excuses
you dig up to be
hard on yourself.
[KAORU] Change of subject.
[SIO] Nursing?
I'm already enrolled
in a volunteer program
at the hospital; I give
'em a hand on my days off.
You're gonna laugh,
but I'm doing it 'cause
a certain someone inspires me
to make the world
a better place.
Wow, that's seriously
awesome! Good for you!
I'm gonna start calling
you Florence Nightingale!
[chuckles]
No pressure, huh?
[KAORU'S phone beeping]
It's the Evolutionary
Invader warning system!
[gasps]
[EI TYPES chatter]
[helicopter overhead]
[PILOT 9A]
This is the view over Odaiba.
Single Landing Type confirmed,
with multiple Foot
Soldier Types in tow.
[EI TYPES chatter]
[NURSE 9A] Your
attention, please:
everyone in the Tokyo Bay area
has been ordered to evacuate!
We need all of you to stay calm
and follow staff instructions!
Stay here and help
'em get out, I gotta go!
Huh?
[SIO] Ow.
I really think you
should stay here with me.
It's not that bad!
Trust me, I know what I--
[SIO] Oh, right. No AU sphere.
It's all right.
Jus' lean on me.
♪
[EI TYPES chatter]
[NURSE 9A] Everything's
going to be fine, children.
Let's just get on
the bus, single-file.
--[GIRL 9A sobbing]
--[NURSE 9A] Got 'im?
Wait here a sec. I think
just had a brilliant idea.
Huh?
I'm gonna help you
get where you need to.
But you gotta promise
not to budge from this spot.
[SIO] Eh...
[KAORU] You guys look
like you can use a hand.
[NURSE 9A]
Oh my gosh, thank you!
[phone beeping]
Top Secret Emergency Call!
Agent One-Two-Four-Eight-
Seven-Five-One reporting.
Code name: Nobunagun!
Put me through to the
Alex Rogan immediately!
[EI TYPES chatter]
[COP] Damn it,
patch me through to DOGOO,
who do you think?
I need backup here!
[COP yells]
[EI TYPES chatter]
[SIO] Correct! Send a
descent pod for an emergency
AU Sphere drop! A-SAP!
[SIO] The shoe really
is on the other foot.
[SIO] Can't believe
I'm so helpless without
my stupid sphere.
[distant rumble]
[gasps]
[chatters]
They're coming, Asao!
Get outta here!
[KAORU] This li'l
fella's the last of 'em.
You're an angel.
[SIO] Asao!
[BOTH] Hm?
Start the bus!
[whimpers]
[groans]
[tires screech]
♪
It's Mr. Saint-Germain.
Oh, silly me. DOGOO
capped its petty cash fund
as a result of our
buying this conveyance,
and now I've carelessly
plowed it into the enemy.
[car excelerates]
[SAINT-GERMAIN] Huh?
[grunts]
♪
[SIO] No. No.
Mr. Saint-Germain.
[EI TYPE chatters]
Quick, make a run for it.
[NURSE 9A] What?
Now!
But we--
[KAORU] Just do it!
Hey, sushi-face!
[gasps]
That's right!
Easy target right here!
[KAORU] Or are you scared?
What are you doing?
Don't provoke it! Please!
Whatever you're
thinking about doing--!
Aah... That's it, come to mama!
[KAORU] What are
you waiting for, Sio?
Run away while I
got him distracted!
Like hell I will!
[yelps]
Uh-huh. That's a good boy.
Let's see what you're made of!
[SIO] Okay, then. Waiting for
an AU sphere isn't gonna cut it.
My friend's in danger.
And I will protect her!
[SIO] Oda Nobunaga.
If you are in there somewhere,
if your soul and mine
really do share the same body,
give me everything you've got!
[NOBUNAGA grunts]
Hrm!
[yells]
[BOTH] My hand has been forced!
♪
[KAORU shrieks]
That was... unexpected.
[KAORU] Sio!
Huh?
You're incredible!
How'd you do that?
Hm? Um. I'll tell you
when I figure it out.
Wha'd I tell you
about being amazing?
[laughs nervously]
Well, that's it for me.
Fresh out of ammo.
[KAORU] Sio!
[EI TYPE chatters]
[EI TYPES chatter]
[SIO] Oh, sure.
Figures now the
rest of 'em show up.
Sio!
[EI TYPES chatter]
♪
Oh god. What now?
No. S'okay, it's
one of our pods.
♪
[JACK] 'allo 'allo.
Textbook example of an
"Hail Mary" here, innit?
[JACK] Oi! What's the trouble?
Uh! Wha--Jack!
Where have you been?
[JACK] Typical. Ol' Jack to the
rescue and you give 'im the biz.
Whatever. Sit this one
out if you like, luv.
[yells]
My goodness. Someone
ain't half as tough as they
make themselves out
to be. Sashimi anyone?
He's got this.
Uh! Sio!
[sirens]
[FEMALE REPORTER 9A]
Thankfully members of DOGOO's
Fourth Platoon were on hand
to push the Invaders back
before the surge could
make it further inland.
You back among the living?
Mmm. Mhmm.
Oh. Good.
You do realize the
life-debt you think
you owe me's now
paid in full.
[KAORU] No! You saved me. Again.
[SIO] Whatever. I only pulled
off that shot 'cause of you.
[KAORU] Guess we should
just call us even.
I save you, you save me;
world keeps right on spinnin'.
[SIO] Yeah, but--
Shush. Friends help each other.
Hm. Mhmmm!
[SAINT-GERMAIN] Hmph. Friendship
is a beautiful thing, is it not?
Yeah! Right? Seriously,
lone-wolves don't know
what they're missi--
[screams]
[SIO] But, I--I saw you--
You couldn't possibly--
Ah. Rest assured, miss,
I have a singularly
strong constitution.
You--You survived
an exploding car!
We still have a
schedule to satisfy.
This changes nothing; our
mission is on for tomorrow.
Huh? What kind of mission?
[SAINT-GERMAIN]
All in good time.
[SIO] Uh...
[KAORU] Hey, Sio.
Uh?
[KAORU] That's the "illustrious
Jack" over there, right?
Huh?
[SIO] Oh. Uh. Yeah.
[KAORU] You two would
be a total power couple.
[whimpers]
[KAORU] Alright, I gotta jet.
Oh. You goin' home?
Mhmm. Seriously; get some
rest. See you when I see ya.
Mmm.
[JACK] You birds
done chewin' the fat?
Huh? Ah-ah-ah-ah! Y-Y-Y-Yeah.
[JACK] Right then.
'Cause now it's my turn.
Huh?
There's somethin'
we need to talk about.
Huh?
[SIO snoring]
[SAINT-GERMAIN] Rise and
shine, poppet. Quickly now.
[SIO] What? "Poppet"? When
d'you start calling me that?
[SAINT-GERMAIN] Apologies.
An outmoded term of endearment.
[SIO] Where'd you pick it up?
[SAINT-GERMAIN]
Next time, Gun Ten: "DOGOO."
[SIO] Hey!
Don't change the subject!