What remains is solely
the province of our sniper.
Hopefully her aim is
as good as her strategy.
Keep the path to
Ol' Squidbutt clear
[TANK COMMANDER 11A]
'til our gal gets a clean shot!
[grunts]
[yells]
♪
Heh.
[SIO] Poor baby,
your grabby-grabs are gone!
Time to get Sengoku on your ass!
[BOTH] "Our hand
has been forced!" Ha!
♪
[chuckles intensely]
Nobunagun here!
Battleship Type sunk!
Yeah, that's our girl!
[chuckles]
♪
[grunts]
[SIO struggling]
Ahhh!
Ah! Cut it out!
This is so not cool!
[SIO struggling]
Rise and shine,
you alien sons of bitches!
[GANDHI grunts]
[GANDHI] Hang in there, Cyx!
Just a little more!
[CYX] With pleasure!
Kick-ass! That
was the last of 'em!
Gaudí--now!
Roger! [grunts]
[yells]
♪
[gunfire]
[helicopter overhead]
[PILOT 12A] The EIs
have been isolated, ma'am.
[PILOT 12A] Up to them now.
[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands marked
by their ability to retain
and selectively manifest
the essence of
humanity's greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of
these specialized
strands use AU spheres to
activate the abilities lying
dormant within themselves,
which then materialize
as physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is a record of
the struggle between DOGOO,
a supranational
organization comprised of
trained E-Gene Holders,
and mankind's greatest threat,
the Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
[SIO] Gun Twelve: "Operation
Stone Forest, Part 2."
[panting breaths]
[GERONIMO]
How 'bout a friendly wager?
Whoever slaughters
the most of these things
gets to order the loser
to do whatever they want.
Count me in.
But'cher gonna feel
right foolish when
this goes south for ya.
You'll eat those words.
Feeling obedient?
[HUNTER] Right, so. You're not
includin' me on this are ya?
May the best man win.
I will.
Wait. I'm not quite--
I wasn't ready!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[JACK grunts]
Yer losin'!
[grunts]
[CYX] Up top, Princess!
[GERONIMO] Finally!
[CYX] Better late than never!
[GERONIMO] Floor it, Cyx!
Heh.
Hold on!
Two against one? Cheater!
Ha-ha! I'm not
killing 'em, so whatevs!
[GERONIMO] Cyx!
Let's play our trump card.
'Bout time!
[GERONIMO] Hmph.
Geronimo. Changing mode.
♪
Engage Ghost Protocol.
[yells]
Now, Cyx!
Give 'em hell! Yeah?
[grunts]
[yells]
[HUNTER gasps nervously]
Leave me alone!
[EI TYPE chatters]
[HUNTER] Gandhi!
Listen up.
I'll pin him to the wall,
[GANDHI] and you
skewer him. Sound good?
Aye. Sounds great.
[EI TYPE chatters]
There. Dead.
[grunting]
[HUNTER] How is it still alive?
Jack and Geronimo
killed them so easily!
[GANDHI] Stand down!
[HUNTER panting]
[GANDHI] You killed
it, see? Try to calm down.
Hold it together.
We need to move out.
[HUNTER] I--I canna--
[sobs]
Forensic pathology
is all I'm good at.
I've never cut up
a living EI before.
I'm sorry.
What the hell good am
I in a battle like this?
I'm gonna die
out there, Gandhi!
[HUNTER sobbing]
[GANDHI]
Geronimo is ferocious--
[GANDHI] --but she cannot
stoke that flame for long.
Jack is a consummate killer,
but sooner or later,
his blades will lose their edge.
Look around us.
[GANDHI] We are surrounded
by thousands of those things!
Cyx and Gaudí are both
pulling their weight.
It's high time
you found your spine!
Y' think so?
Maybe it's high time you
did the maths and
figured out this is suicide!
This plan is the stupidest
thing I've ever heard!
[huffs]
She didn't have to come
out here and deal with it--
[GANDHI] How dare you?
She's engaging
the Battleship Type!
And she's doing it alone!
[struggling]
[FEMALE OP 1B] Nobunagun
is caught in the tentacles!
I thought the giant
squid had been defeated.
Perhaps another one
was lying in ambush.
None of the data backs
that up! But if he's right--
And what about air support?
[MALE OP 1A] Negative,
ma'am! Not while that thing
is using her as a shield!
[grunts]
Dammit!
Hang in there,
girl--you got this!
[groans]
[SIO] Okay. Can't move my arms.
Legs are no good, either.
[SIO] But maybe
they're perfect as-is.
[FEMALE OP 1A] Commander!
Sphere 25 has gone inactive!
[FEMALE OP 1B] Nobunagun
disengaged her AU Weapon!
[COMMANDER]
Unarmed? Is she mad?
Hmm!
They told me, your weak spot--
[SIO]
--is right between the eyes!
Attagirl!
Ngh!
[COMMANDER] No damage?
[MALE OP 1A] It has the same
hard scales as the Armored Type!
It appeared out of nowhere!
But that's impossible!
It seems not. I think
you will find your answers
in the Battleship
Type's remains.
[VIDOCQ] You see that
hollow portion of the torso?
I believe it was carrying eggs.
This one was born
on the battlefield.
[VIDOCQ] We have the
Messenger Types to thank.
The eggs hatched
inside the giant squid,
at which point messengers
brought the hatchlings
a constant stream of data
from the fight with Nobunagun.
Metagenesis occurred
who knows how many times
within the squid,
until only one
sublimely-evolved
specimen remained!
This creature that now holds
the girl in its clutches!
Remarkable that it
could adapt so quickly.
[yelling]
[COMMANDER]
Hold your fire, girl!
You need to save your strength!
[VIDOCQ] Just stay alive!
I'll think of something!
[SIO] If I can get one
to ricochet just right!
[SIO] Triple Volley!
[SIO] I know where
you don't have armor!
[SIO] Take out the eyes first,
then move in for the kill!
[gasps]
[SIO] Land Mine Types?
Get out of there, Sio!
The Munroe effect!
--[TANK COMMANDER 11A grunts]
--[VIDOCQ gasps]
[heavy exhale]
A number of battles with
the Evolutionary Invaders
are being fought along
the entire Pacific Rim,
all of them major.
[FEMALE ANCHOR 12A] However,
the most recent encounter
broke out near Costa
Rica just before daybreak
this morning,
putting it around 3p.m.
Japan Standard Time.
We'll come back with
updates from the field
as we get them.
Train's pretty empty, huh.
It's no real surprise.
People are scared.
Barely half our class
even shows up anymore.
I just want poor Suguri
to start feeling better.
[SUGURI breathes shakily]
It's a long-shot after
what she saw in Taiwan.
That girl Sio, who
used to be in our class?
Like, while we
sit on this train,
she's probably off somewhere
fighting those nasty things.
I wonder if she's okay.
Those creatures
are hardcore.
How long's a schoolgirl
gonna last out there,
even with her power?
But--!
[BOTH gasp]
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER 12A]
Sorry about the sudden stop.
They're having a
power issue down the line,
so we'll have
to wait here a bit.
We appreciate your patience,
and we'll get moving
again as soon as we can.
Heh.
[yells]
Fast little blighter!
Son-of-a--!
[JACK] Don't tell me the
new model's got proper legs!
Gandhi! Hunter!
Look alive in there!
You got incoming!
[HUNTER] Uh!
[GANDHI] Hunter!
[yells]
[grunts]
[GANDHI] Great--it wants me!
[EI TYPES chatter]
[GANDHI groans]
Wha--? They just--
[gasps]
[HUNTER] Could it be--?
What the crap?
When are we going
to start moving already?
[crying]
It's okay.
We're almost home, Miki.
You're all right.
Uh. Calm your kid down, lady.
I'm so sorry.
Please, honey, that's enough.
[KAORU] Hey, don't be scared.
I promise, there's absolutely
nothing to worry about.
A friend of mine's beating
up the monsters for us.
We have to be tough,
just like her!
[MALE OP 1A] Vancouver
reports casualties!
[FEMALE OP 1A] Sixth
Platoon requesting backup!
[MALE OP 1B] Third Platoon
losing ground in Tahiti!
[FEMALE OP 1B]
Dai Zong is injured!
He can't combine
with Hackenschmidt!
Rasputin has taken
a lot of damage too!
[FEMALE OP 1A] Report from
Fourth Platoon in Sydney.
Van Gogh is injured.
Mozart and Borgia have
lost their camouflage.
[MALE OP 1B] The Gunboat
Types have opened fire!
[FEMALE OP 1A] Mozart's
vitals are dropping!
[DOGOO] What's our
progress in Costa Rica?
And what of Nobunagun?
[FEMALE OP 1B] We still
can't find her signal!
[HUNTER panting]
Dammit! Hunter, get over here!
I can't hold it off!
[HUNTER gasps]
Jackpot!
Your friend who's out there,
she's gonna beat up
the bad guys? You promise?
Yeah! Cross my heart.
She's saved me lots of times,
so I know she's good for it!
[KAORU]
We're gonna be just fine.
You wanna help me cheer her on?
I bet she'd really like that.
Say "We believe in you!"
Mhmmm.
We believe!
[BOTH] We believe, too.
♪
Good luck, Sio. You can do it.
You can do it, Sio.
[FEMALE OP 1B]
Nobunagun's signal is back!
[MALE OP 1A]
Video feed on-screen!
Nobunagun!
Listen to me.
Disengage your
AU weapon at once.
You're taking damage
from the feedback!
But, Commander! If she
disarms right in front of it,
she'll be a sitting duck!
[COMMANDER]
Then bring her back in now!
Hell no, ma'am!
[SIO] If I back down,
this thing'll head
straight for Upala.
I'm stayin' 'til the
pre-evolved base cells
are neutralized!
Upala team: sit-rep!
[PILOT 12A] Gaudí sealed off
the hot zone completely, sir.
We can't contact anyone inside.
I repeat, no contact.
Status unknown.
[panting]
[JACK] Tired, Geronimo?
'Cause you look tired.
Your lead's shrinkin' fast.
Yeah? I'm not worried;
your knife's getting
as dull as your wit.
[JACK] Piss off!
[GERONIMO] Save it for
the rest of 'em, limey.
[JACK chuckles]
Back at ya, Tonto.
[EI TYPES chatter]
[yells]
[BOTH panting]
[GANDHI groans]
Hunter! I am at my limit!
You have got to help me!
Carpenteric Sulfide is
at seventy-two percent.
[HUNTER] Another
twenty-three's Burtonium.
Which means if I
add Juran Radicals--!
[HUNTER gasps]
Yes! It's perfect!
Finally!
It tastes so bitter!
What on Earth is it?
Observe.
They're slaughtering
each other.
That aerosol.
What is it?
Eugh.
[HUNTER] This is one of
their eyes. What do you see?
Their habitat has
been the ocean so far.
So it's no surprise
that their ocular organs
are suited to that setting.
And?
Use your damn head! The
refractive indexes of water
and air couldn't
be any more different!
[HUNTER] Using an
eye meant for the water,
you'd be practically
blind on land!
Not thinkin'.
Only attacking anythin' that
gets in their way.
So why aren't they
killing each other
all the time, eh?
Clearly, they have a way
of telling friend from foe
that doesn't depend on
their mediocre eyesight.
See this? It emits
pheromones that signify
a creature should
not be targeted.
[HUNTER] That's why
they ignored me after
I got covered in EI guts.
Chemically speaking, they
thought I was one of them.
If we can spray them
with more of this negating
compound I made on the fly.
[gasps] Brilliant!
Let's take it to Cyx.
[JACK] Heh!
[GERONIMO grunts]
Going for the tie--!
Uh!
[JACK] Wha--? There?
[JACK] But that's just...
the rookie.
You're telling me to go to her?
[REAL JACK] Yes. It is essential
that she not perish now.
[REAL JACK] Defend her.
Bollocks.
That's a change of plans.
[laughs]
Suck on my science, bitches!
Son-of-a-bitch! When did
I become a damn taxicab?
Congratulations.
I guess you win the bet.
What?
[JACK] Looks like I got
somewhere else to be.
[GERONIMO] Excuse me? We're
in the middle of a battle!
Don't be cross. When
my E-Gene points the way,
all I can do is take wing.
Huh?
[GERONIMO] Jack?
[grunts]
How do the tentacles
have armor, too?
Ahhh!
[grunts]
[yells]
♪
Feathers?
[JACK] Close call, yeh?
Are you all right?
Jack? What're you doing up here?
Hmmm.
Well, it's simple. I flew.
[JACK] Never thought you'd
catch me "in the altogether,"
so to speak.
I call it... Nightingale Mode.
Heh.
[JACK] S'like two sides of the
same coin, or light and dark.
With the world circling
the drain in a major way,
another me awoke!
[SIO] Next time, for the last
time, Gun Thirteen: "Nobunagun!"
Wait, it's almost over?
I'm still such a noob!