Sonar and MAD systems are down!
Atmospheric methane
levels rising, sir!
What the hell
are we dealing with?
It's right under
the Halsey, Captain!
Dammit!
Jesus, Mary, an' Joseph!
Is that a--?
[COMMANDER] This EI has
assumed a curious form.
[MALE OP A] At its
current speed and heading,
ETA to Panama Canal
roughly 19 hours.
[MALE OP B] The US Navy
is taking heavy losses,
but they do not want
E-Gene Holders deployed, ma'am.
Why is that, I wonder?
[rapid gunfire]
[explosion]
It's right in front of me,
but I don't believe it!
[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands
marked by their ability to
retain and selectively manifest
the essence of
humanity's greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of
these specialized strands
use AU spheres to
activate the abilities
lying dormant within themselves,
which then materialize
as physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is a record
of the struggle between DOGOO,
a supranational organization
comprised of
trained E-Gene Holders,
and mankind's greatest threat,
the Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
Gun Seven: "Musashi Wonder"!
You guys!
That's totally
the Battleship Yamato!
But how come the EIs
hauled it back up like that?
Oh, y'know what, though?
The Yamato sank way
closer to Japan than here.
C'mon, self!
She's what they
call an "otaku," yes?
No freakin' way!
Huh?
This one is the Musashi,
not the Yamato!
The Yamato had
more anti-aircraft guns,
and the plating
on her hull was....
So, yeah. I guess
it's the Musashi?
Unless it's not!
1940s warships have
never really been my thing.
So, maybe it is the Yamat--
You don't know!
We get it!
Just stop!
Huh?
I'm gonna shut up now.
[COMMANDER]
The EI apparently intends
to leave the Pacific Ocean
for the waters of the Atlantic,
via the Panama Canal.
The US Navy is
thinking with its ego.
They'll sink it or die trying.
Why do they care
who sinks it?
It's a point of
professional honor.
To have an Imperial Navy
battleship en route
to the Panama Canal
is still a slap in the face.
Oh, that's right.
In World War Two,
Japan was planning to
try and destroy the canal.
Hang out!
But the Musashi's way too big
to sail through
the canal, isn't it?
They designed it
to be larger than
the U.S. warships
going through Panama, so--
You're partially
correct.
But history has
passed you by.
The canal can handle even
Yamato-class battleships now.
Wha--? When did that happen?
That aside, the Navy
can't have forgotten
their conventional
weaponry doesn't do anything
to an EI but
thoroughly piss it off.
If nothing else kills it,
they've warned that a nuclear
attack is not off the table.
They'd actually nuke it?
My god.
[DOGOO] A swarm of Invaders
tied the remains of
that ship back together,
for a purpose at
which we can only surmise.
There's no reason
to think a nuclear blast
would destroy the EIs,
but that won't stop
the U.S. from trying.
But that's barbaric!
I quite agree!
What if the blast
causes them
to mutate in
unexpected ways?
Listen to me!
Musashi deserves better!
Right then.
Sentiment aside, we cannot
allow them the nuclear option.
We prevent that by
sinking the ship ourselves.
That is not what I had in mind.
Message from HQ: "For
the duration of the mission,
the target's call sign
will be 'Musashi Wonder.'"
So, "Musashi Wonder."
Time to hatch
a plan that will let
our American friends save
face on the world stage.
Galileo.
Give me something to work with.
Don't fret, Signore Vidocq--
I'm on the case!
All right!
Io!
Europa!
Ganymede!
Callisto!
Off you go, little moons!
The U.S. Navy is gearing up
for a nuclear strike.
Second Platoon is onboard
the Clayton Forrester.
Special Ops team,
report to the briefing room.
Look what I found!
A buncha eggs!
Ew, that's disgusting!
Lemme guess,
we gotta break those,
before we deep-six the ship.
No room for negotiation
on that, I fear.
We can't allow
the eggs to be scattered.
I'll stomp 'em
all flat, don't worry.
But what's the plan for the MW?
The small Colony Types
iverse tasks.
Not only have they
mastered the onboard guns,
they propel the ship
in lieu of a working engine,
and do reconnaissance.
Man, when did they get so smart?
If you want smarts,
go up the chain-of-command.
Huh?
I get it.
They're the hoi polloi,
just bending their
knee to the ol' monarch.
So to speak.
Wait.
What?
There's a smart one, okay?
It's the brains
of the operation;
all the others are just gofers.
The EIs aboard that
ship are like stem cells,
vast potential
without any inherent goal.
Somewhere within
the Musashi Wonder,
there lurks a self-aware core,
which dictates its actions.
Put that core to the sword, and
the whole colony will collapse.
Thus the Musashi will return
to her status as
a somber war grave.
At which point, of course,
a nuclear attack on America's
part becomes unnecessary.
Another platoon can come in
and destroy
the rest at their leisure.
So, Vidocq's saying the Brain-EI
brought the Musashi
back to life, right?
Okay, but why?
So this "core" thing,
what's it look like?
Show the man.
Aye, sir!
This is it.
That thing rebuilt
a whole warship?
That is definitely
the Musashi in there.
What's this all about then?
I had to show her
the observation data.
She wouldn't shut up about it!
If it were a person,
this Brain-EI would be the best
model ship-builder in history!
Oh, wow.
That's nice.
It's perfect! And sending it
to the Panama Canal?
The core is such a nerd!
Does it make me
a big ol' traitor
that I kinda wanna see
it go through the canal?
I mean, that'd be cool, right?
Hey, how does the head honcho EI
know so much about the Musashi?
It's not really like they
can read our history books.
Look alive, Sio-taku!
Huh?
Where're ya going?
The Yanks just
came to their senses.
Time for us to save the day!
So... So we can go?
Does this mean
what I think it means?
CVN-74!
The USS John C. Stennis!
Ready, set, go!
Signore Vidocq
convinced the Navy
to lend us this ship
because he's so dreamy!
He swore he'd take
down the Musashi Wonder
come hell or high water.
Guess it struck a chord.
But we're the ones
stuck doing the dirty work.
You know it.
And if we don't take her down
before she reaches the canal,
t'll go from dirty
to radioactive!
Quite!
So failure is not
an option, my dear.
332.8meters was way
too far to run!
Dying!
'Suppose you could use a hand.
Too late!
Mind's made up!
Oh?
About what?
I'm gonna sink that ship.
And I'm gonna do it by myself!
Musashi Wonder has entered
the theater of operations.
Roger that, Vidocq.
Come in, 2nd Platoon.
Are you ready to engage?
This is the strike
team up on the Alex Rogan.
We're all good to go, Commander.
Ditto! We're in
place on the John C. Stennis!
Ready on your word, ma'am!
These dots are the egg
cluster and the core.
First, you'll destroy
the top of the conning tower
and storm the ship via your pod.
Having done that,
you'll then eliminate the eggs.
Finally, you'll strike the core,
leading to
the dissolution of the ship.
Jack and Newton,
you're on point.
Nobunagun, you'll blast
open an entrance for the pod.
Gandhi, you cover our sniper.
Hey, hold on a sec!
I thought AU Weapons only worked
on the creatures themselves!
So won't my bullets
just bounce off,
no matter how
many I shoot at it?
Correct.
And, adding to our dilemma,
there's a layer
of EIs along the top
that are impervious to
all conventional weaponry.
Really?
Then how do we break through?
Think about it.
In that case!
I'll start us off!
Nobunagun has opened fire, sir.
Good.
Galileo, observe
the point of impact.
Yes!
Of course!
Reconfirm our data link
with the US fleet, A-SAP.
Yes, sir.
That conning tower's armor
is 500-millimeters thick!
The density of EIs at our
target point is dropping, Sio!
Shoot that tower to
your heart's content!
Incoming!
EI concentration
dropping rapidly!
Almost-- almost!
We did it!
The tower's clear!
You're free to fire at will.
Booyah!
Sorry 'bout that, Musashi.
Strike team, go!
Going down.
Strike team is on the ship.
Follow my probe to the eggs!
Getting warmer.
Nothing's gonna
hug my face, right?
Whoa!
At sea, "no one
can hear you scream."
When'd you grow
a sense of humour?
Vidocq!
Come in!
I wanna go on the ship, too!
They're onboard
so I'm done out here, right?
I suppose.
I should be the Holder
to sink the Musashi!
Here I go.
If you wanna play,
who am I to turn you down?
Don't tell me you
really meant all that!
Hold down the fort.
Orders, sir?
Can't turn tail or we'll be
the laughingstock of the world!
Take us right up to her!
Paint to paint, dammit!
Nobunagun just jumped
onto the target, sir!
I'll guide her to the EI core!
Don't let me down, Galileo.
So, how many eggs left?
Zero, love.
No hatchlings, either.
Give Nobunagun some
back-up, would you?
She's headed to the core alone.
That dummy needs a babysitter!
Or a leash.
Wait. Is that it?
Musashi.
You were resting in peace,
until they hauled you back up.
I've spotted the core,
deep within the hold!
I'm taking it down!
Are those the Musashi's crew?
Why's the EI all
tangled up in 'em?
These memories.
They're not from
the ship itself.
Yes, of course.
They're from the crew!
The EI must've
used those feelings
to resurrect the Musashi!
Listen to me!
You don't belong here!
Stop the ship!
'Cause if you don't...!
The Navy'll vaporize
it with a tactical nuke.
Don't let Musashi
go out like that.
She deserves better.
The hell's wrong with you?
Shoot the damn thing!
Oh, right!
Rest in peace... Musashi!
Musashi Wonder's
hull is breaking up, sir!
Where's 2nd Platoon?
All members safely evacuated!
I'm glad I got to meet you.
And to your crew-- At ease, men.
Musashi Wonder has sunk
5,000 meters and still dropping!
How deep does
the Middle America Trench run?
Ah.
Just shy of 6,700 meters.
Give or take.
Our enemy is resilient.
But can they survive
at such a depth?
It's difficult to say.
But at the very least,
it will be a struggle for
them to return from the abyss.
Let me get this straight.
The Evolutionary Invaders
encountered the drowned crewmen
of the Musashi sometime
after it sank in 1944.
The EI absorbed the dead
men's resentment at their fate,
and the ship in order
to play out the crew's
original goal of
invading the U.S. mainland?
Really.
That's quite the ghost story.
Don't you "quite
the ghost story" me!
I was there!
I know what I saw, okay?
Galileo!
What's the big idea?
That is the most tragic
bathing suit I 'ave ever seen.
But this is the only
one my mom packed for me!
I didn't know we'd
be going to the beach!
An authentic Japanese
schoolgirl swimsuit!
Hey!
I am gonna kill you!
Shio's wearing a one-piece!
C'mon! Give it back!
Look at 'em getting along.
Today we gonna find out
who the real gopher is!
[GAUDÍ] Wait, why am I here?
We gotta make sure
it's a fair fight!
Shut your traps already!
All three of you
buy the damn bread!
Aye, sir!
Next time, Gun Eight: "Tunnel."
These three are
a pain in the arse.