I believe this
calls for a toast.
Welcome to north-northwest
o' no-man's land, friend.
[GONDA chuckles]
Hear-hear.
[RESEARCHERS] Hm!
Welp. Better let you
in on the lay o' things.
As of that swig,
you've got clearance
to know the lab's
dirty li'l secret.
[GONDA] Oh yeah?
Sounds fun.
[RESEARCHER 6A]
That's the spirit!
[RESEARCHER 6A] Yeah.
In all seriousness, though.
You can't tell
another living soul.
Ever.
[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands
marked by their ability to
retain and selectively manifest
the essence of humanity's
greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of these
specialized strands
use AU spheres
to activate the abilities lying
dormant within themselves,
which then materialize
as physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is a record of
the struggle between DOGOO,
a supranational organization
comprised of trained
E-Gene Holders,
and mankind's greatest threat,
the Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
[SIO]
Gun Six: "Monster Meat"?
[PILOT 6A]
Tiger to Alex Rogan.
We are currently passing
through Alaskan airspace.
[MALE OP 6A]
Copy, Tiger.
This is the Alex Rogan.
Any problems with the sample?
None to speak of.
Appreciate the caution,
but our security detail
is bored to tears.
[MALE OP 6A]
Roger that. Safe travels.
Hm. It's like we're inside
a freakin' snow globe.
That a fact?
[GAUDÍ] Oh, sí.
She's been assigned
to Second Platoon.
Her AU Weapon's a giant
sniper rifle or something;
plays into her name.
Nobunagun.
Yes, I heard.
A Japanese girl if
I'm not mistaken.
Well, good for her.
'Sides, Second Platoon can't
really afford to be choosey.
Let's hope the gal
lives up to her namesake.
Maybe she'll give 'em
a much-needed edge.
Small chance o' that.
Poor dear can't seem to
hit the side of a ship.
At least according to
the info I have, princess.
Oh my. I'll bet Jacky-boy's
not too happy about
having to share the
limelight with her.
There's more to
it than that!
I mean, sure,
she had a rocky start,
but she and Jack won
a huge air battle!
They even took out
an Armored Type!
Doesn't seem to
me like someone
who can't hit the
side of a barn.
Well...
You've certainly done your
homework on the new girl, Gaudí.
Fascinating. Is this
turning into an obsession?
Ah!
No! I'm just
interested is all!
Aren't you a li'l young to
think of girls in that way?
[GAUDÍ] Uhh...
[CYX laughs]
[GERONIMO laughs]
Stop it!
It's not funny!
[crashing sound]
[GAUDÍ gasps]
[CYX]
What's goin' on?
It's this
damn blizzard!
Losing altitude!
Visibility's practically
zero out there.
[rumbling]
[GAUDÍ whimpers]
[CYX] Princess!
What's the play?
[GERONIMO]
No freakin' clue.
But I'll tell you this:
Dying with that thing
is not an option!
Brace yourselves!
We're going down!
[CYX] Gaudí!
For heaven's sake, stop cowering
and activate your power
before it's too late!
[GAUDÍ]
Sí, no problem!
Easy-peazy!
Oh, wait!
[GAUDÍ yells]
[GAUDÍ grunts]
Yay. We didn't die.
[GAUDÍ]
Containment unit secure.
[CYX]
Any luck with the radio?
[PILOT 6B]
Total whiteout.
We're gonna have to wait 'til
this blizzard calms down.
Achoo!
[GAUDÍ] Miss Geronimo,
we need to get you out--
[CYX] I'd thought you've
have learned by now
not to approach the
princess when she's cold.
Sí. My mistake.
[PILOT 6A] Good news:
we're only a short hike from
a civilian research lab.
About three klicks
up the mountain.
[thud]
Ah!
They should have comm.
equipment, right?
We could send a
distress call to HQ!
So, Three K hike?
[GERONIMO] Stay here;
we'll come back for you.
[CYX] Guard the prisoner
with your life!
Aw! Come on.
Seriously?
Why I gotta be the one
to freeze his butt off?
[GAUDÍ yells]
[CYX] Hm? What?
[GERONIMO] Nothing.
Just a shadow.
[MAN] It would seem
we have houseguests.
In the middle of this storm?
So much the better.
We will show them
every hospitality.
[CYX]
Too quiet for my tastes.
Not as if these people can
be out running errands.
[GERONIMO] Hm.
[MAN] Had a spot of
trouble, I take it?
[CYX and GERONIMO gasp]
[CYX] Our plane was forced to
make an emergency landing.
[MAN] That's terrible.
[CYX] May we use
your radio, please?
[MAN] Absolutely.
Forgive the question.
But uh, you're
both military, yes?
We're DOGOO.
Princess!
I see.
[CYX] Thank you, but--We don't
really have time for food.
Our companions
expect us back A-SAP.
[GERONIMO] Maybe just
a quick bite or two.
Princess.
What'd you say your
name was again?
Mister...?
Gonda; my apologies.
Is anybody else
stationed here?
No.
You're all alone, this
deep in the mountains?
The economy
being what it is,
this industry's
had to cut corners.
So, as DOGO operatives,
I imagine you ladies have to go
toe-to-toe with those kaiju.
Sorry, what?
You're talkin' about
the Evolutionary Invaders?
[GONDA] Yes.
[CYX] Hm?
Oh my.
What a grand name.
[GERONIMO] Huh.
[GONDA] Your plane had to make
an emergency landing, you said?
By chance, were you
transporting--Kaiju?
Heh. Apologies, I mean
"Evolutionary Invaders."
Love to tell ya, but
we'd have to kill ya.
She kids, of course,
but only slightly.
[GONDA]
You're right.
A fabulous stroke of luck.
Yes. Neither one of them
seem any the wiser.
[static]
[CYX]
Damn. Nothing.
I can't get through.
I wish I could tell you
this was unusual.
Blizzard like this interferes
with almost everything.
Your companions will be
popsicles before long.
Don't know that I
appreciate the joke.
Forgive me.
That was in poor taste.
Only thing the princess
hates more than the cold,
is the thought of our friends
gettin' left out in it.
The whiteout ought
to let up by morning,
if we're lucky.
You should retrieve
your companions
and bring them back
here for the night.
I may not be the ideal host,
but surely I make
for better company
than whatever you're carrying.
[GERONIMO] Ahh!
This is heaven!
So this guy.
While I'm inclined to
chalk his awkwardness
down to prolonged isolation.
Do we dare take
him up on his offer?
Not that it appears
we have a choice.
We certainly can't leave
Gaudí and the others
out there to freeze.
We'll try HQ again tomorrow,
once this blows over.
Don't really
see the point.
That comm'd be useless
in the tropics.
What on earth
do you mean?
Their equipment's dead.
It's been sabotaged.
[CYX gasps]
[GERONIMO]
You didn't notice?
The wires were cut.
Sabotage?
So what's going on here?
H-Hmm?
Are those bloodstains?
We beat a path
right to its door.
Wait, what?
To whose door?
The kaiju.
Whatever's going on,
it's certainly a first!
No self respecting EI
has ever set up camp
in a snow-encrusted
backwater like this!
I don't disagree,
but... those eyes.
Prolonged isolation my ass!
[GERONIMO and CYX] Huh?
[GONDA laughs]
Called that.
Princess!
[GERONIMO grunts]
[GERONIMO yells]
[CYX grunts]
[tires screech]
E-Gene Holders.
Delivered right to my doorstep.
[CYX]
Son of a bitch!
Cyx!
Sorry?
We can't use
our powers.
He's a human being.
He's a maniac!
That man just tried
to run you over!
Not the issue!
Drop it!
Mm?
Where's he off to now?
Running away?
[GERONIMO] Huh?
[beep]
Hello.
[RESEARCHER 6D yells]
[gasps]
He's mad!
[GONDA] Oh, yes!
It's fate!
We have been gifted with
a pair of E-gene Holders!
[GONDA chuckles]
[GAUDÍ] Hold up!
You've actually met Nobunagun?
Yeah. They had us
on the Alex Rogan
before we came to
pick you guys up.
Sweet a gal as
you'll ever meet.
Sweet and totally
smokin', amirite?
Details! Please!
Um. Not that I'm
obsessed or anything;
just y'know, mildly curious.
[PILOT 6A]
Well, take a look at this.
At what?
¡Díos mio!
[GAUDÍ exclaims]
Yeah. Uh. Wow.
Curiosity has been sated.
[PILOT 6A] Keep it.
Don't mess with me.
[PILOT 6B] We're in good
with the photographer.
You magnificent man, you!
Ahh! Just look at 'er.
Classic beach-body curves.
She's perfect.
Wish I was in Second Platoon.
I getcha.
The grass is
always greener.
And hell it'd be better'n
gettin' chewed out
by Ms. Bossy-Bitch
every day.
Hey! Watch your
tongue, soldier!
"Chewed up."
Gaudí shall never be any
woman's little chew toy!
[horn honks]
Ah! Cyx's back!
[horn blares]
Is that them?
So why are they going so fast?
[GAUDÍ gasps]
Aah! Pilots take cover!
[GAUDÍ yells]
[crashing sound]
Princess!
Exactly as I thought.
Step on it!
[RESEARCHER 6A
breathes raggedly]
They-- They're dead.
I'm the only one left
he hasn't massacred!
Son of a bitch is insane.
If I die, I want this
video used as evidence.
[clattering]
It's Gonda!
The man believes
he's been possessed!
He just-- He keeps ranting!
He says an Evolutionary Invader
has taken control of his mind!
[RESEARCHER 6A] You seem like
a fella who knows the score.
We scrape by out here
like a bunch o' hermits.
Only fun we get is
treatin' ourselves
to the occasional gourmet meal.
Y'understand?
Sure.
So if we buy stuff that
ain't strictly legal--
Black market beluga caviar
n' Cuban cigars,
little treats like that?
[GONDA]
I'm sorry, sir.
Where is this going?
Well, buddy.
Whad'ja think of that
prime cut y'had tonight?
Ever taste anything
quite like it?
Fifty bones says you can't
guess what it was a cut of.
[GONDA] Uh...
[RESEARCHER 6A]
"Pacific Rim" give you a hint?
[GONDA] Huh?
[RESEARCHER 6A]
C'mon, you watch TV don'tcha?
"Evolutionary Invaders,"
the media calls 'em.
[GONDA] Aahh.
[RESEARCHERS laugh]
[GONDA] Aaaaahhh...
Is he still in there?
He couldn't've--?
[gasps]
No, that smell.
Explosives!
[GONDA chuckles]
Aaahh!
[GONDA laughs]
[GONDA] You have to get up
real early in the morning
to fool me, boy.
I knew you had one of
my brethren in custody!
[GONDA laughs]
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
Look out!
It's breaking free!
There's a deadly
creature in there!
[GONDA] Look out?
I think you'll find
this "creature"
and I have an understanding.
[GONDA] It's over.
I won't be trussed up and
corralled like so much chattel.
Not by DOGOO.
Not by anyone!
No more shall my brothers
be subject to your butchery!
We shall be free!
[RESEARCHER 6A]
It was all a gag.
We were yanking
the idiot's chain.
Hell, even if you could get
something like that on the DL,
we'd never actually
feed it to anyone!
We tried to tell him, but he--
he just got it into his head,
and that was it.
[GERONIMO gasps]
[GERONIMO] Gaudí!
Miss Geronimo.
[CYX gasps]
Gaudí!
Use your power!
Sí! On it!
[GAUDÍ yells]
Aahh!
Faster, Cyx!
[CYX] You got it!
I can't get that
close to him!
Then just get me as
close as you can!
Let's fly!
Roger!
[GAUDÍ yells]
[GERONIMO] Aaaaahh!
[GERONIMO yells]
Yah!
[CYX] I did everything
I could for him.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
What sort of mind gets taken
in by a belief like that?
The guy was destined
to become homicidal.
He should've been
locked away years ago!
It's not fair to make
that assumption.
We can't know what living
in this place does to a man.
Seclusion can play cruel tricks
on a person's sense of self.
That's no excuse!
There but for the
grace of god go us.
How well would our minds
hold up, I wonder?
The poor bastard.
[GERONIMO sighs]
Ah-ha!
Found you!
What are you fussing
over now, Gaudí?
Nothing! Just something
I worried I lost!
Must be pretty
valuable, huh?
Uh, well, it sure
is valuable to me.
Hm... Ah!
Is this
pornography?
She has clothes on!
It's not even mine.
Ah. So I can
throw it out?
[GAUDÍ] No!
Okay, I'll level with you.
It is mine.
Please let me have it back!
[GAUDÍ whimpers]
[CYX] Hmph.
[GERONIMO chuckles]
[GAUDÍ] I know.
I fibbed. I'm sorry.
[GERONIMO] Honesty's
always the best policy.
[GAUDÍ whimpers]
[GALILEO]
Welcome to Cooking 101!
Today, we make the sauce!
My secret ingredient to make
it molto gustoso is vinegar!
You like, Signore Vidocq?
[VIDOCQ]
I'm going to be sick.
[GALILEO] Oh, no!
Next time! Gun Seven:
"Musashi Wonder"!
Sorry, sir!
Practice makes perfect!