[COMMANDER] Good to have you
back and fully recovered,
Adam Muirhead.
[SIO] Adam?
His name is "Adam?"
Honestly, I was a bit
surprised it took me
this long to get
back on the horse.
Watchin' her fight
must'a set me back.
Huh?!
That's enough.
You are hereby reinstated.
Second Platoon will surely
rally to dear Jack's return.
Aye-aye.
[COMMANDER]
Sio Ogura.
Uh--Ma'am.
[COMMANDER] You also are now
assigned to Second Platoon.
Ma'am!
[gasps]
Which means she is
in your care, Jack.
Aye-aye.
[JACK] Tch.
[SIO grunts]
[COMMANDER]
You surprise me.
I felt confident you'd object.
[CAPA] Under normal
circumstances I would.
"Sniper's" the last thing
you could call that girl.
Far as I'm concerned,
my training gave her just
enough rope to hang herself.
Then, why agree to this?
Because, hopeless as
she is in the role
you people've
pigeonholed her into,
her instincts are uncanny.
[COMMANDER]
I suspected as much.
It appears you and I
are of the same mind.
[CAPA] Frightening.
[whirring blades]
[CAPA] As a special ops sniper,
Ogura's a joke.
But throw 'er in a battle
squadron and something tells me
she'd give us all
a run for our money.
[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands
marked by their ability to
retain and selectively manifest
the essence of humanity's
greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of these
specialized strands
use AU spheres
to activate the abilities lying
dormant within themselves,
which then materialize
as physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is a record of
the struggle between DOGOO,
a supranational organization
comprised of trained
E-Gene Holders,
and mankind's greatest threat,
the Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
[SIO] Gun Five:
"The 2nd Platoon"!
[CREWMAN 5A] It's coming
into view, Miss Ogura.
[SIO] Huh? Ahh!
[CREWMAN 5A]
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Yep, that's Second
Platoon's headquarters.
The big, bad Alex Rogan.
[SIO] It's the size
of a small country!
Hashtag "epic!"
I might take you more serious
if you weren't such a spaz.
[SIO grunts]
Aw, what's the matter, love?
I hit a nerve?
What I ever do to you?
Lotsa people freak out
their first time. S'cool.
[SIO whimpers]
[inaudible]
Stop it now, Sio!
For the love of all
that's holy, don't go there!
[JACK] Snap to.
[SIO] Huh?
[JACK] Get it in gear
or you're on your own.
Wait!
Don't leave me here!
[SIO] Aaahhh...
We had this conversation.
[GANDHI] Welcome back, Jack!
[SIO] Hm?
[JACK]
Gandhi. Newton.
And Nobunagun.
Wonderful.
Welcome aboard the Alex Rogan;
glad to have you
as part of the team.
Yeah! Part of
the team! Thank you!
We have not yet
been introduced.
I was born Mahesh Mirza.
My E-Gene name is Gandhi.
Oh. Force fields, right?
I, uh, prefer we
not call it that.
This, if you'll recall--
Huh?!
[NEWTON moans]
[SIO] S-Seriously?
As I was saying,
this is Isaac Newton.
Real name: Jess Beckham.
[SIO] I-I'm good!
Perfectly fine, in fact!
He's-- He's a grown man!
He can kiss whoever he wants!
Besides, she's European
or something, right?
This is probably just
a greeting thing.
Yeah, um. Or, not.
But you know what?
Who cares?
It's none of my business.
End of story.
[SIO] Huh?
It's been too long.
[SIO] O-- Okay!
Definitely European!
And very soft.
No, no, no!
Don't get all worked up!
This is just hello!
With tongue.
Really intense tongue.
And nice teeth.
Somebody make her stop!
[HUNTER] Damn it.
Nice going, Jack.
What m'I supposed
to do with this?
Is it too much to ask
that you give a thought
to the guy doing the autopsy on
what's left of your handiwork?
Fat lot of good four
wrecked organs'll do me!
[VIDOCQ] Now, now,
Monsieur Hunter.
The heat of battle leaves room
for naught but survival.
[HUNTER]
Perhaps, Vidocq.
But for all his
alpha-male gloating
y'think he'd show
a wee more skill.
Always with the complaint.
And at least the brain
is fully intact, non?
I assume you don't object
to my having a peek?
I don't see why not.
Anythin' specific you're after?
Let's say my delicate
instruments have been
all a-tingle since Saipan.
I've ignored them in
the past at my peril.
Right. Let's slice
the bastard open, then.
You take the
deductive reasoning;
I'll take the cuttin'.
The Doctor's in.
We employ three
floating fortresses.
The Alex Rogan, of course,
Second Platoon's home.
Plus the Joji Atsumi.
And the Steven Hiller.
Our auxiliary battleship,
the Clayton Forrester,
ties all three together.
There are two Holder platoons
stationed on each craft.
We circle above the Pacific
Ocean so that when reports
of an Evolutionary Invader
come across the airwaves,
the platoons nearest
the sighting can descend
and engage the enemy with
a minimum of lead time.
In addition--
Ah, sorry, I seem to
have overwhelmed you.
[GANDHI]
Still with us?
[SIO] Yes!
[chuckles]
[GALILEO]
What's up, doc?
[HUNTER]
Ah. Gali-gal.
Just who I'm after.
Ah! It's Galileo!
Can it, rookie.
That's what I'm callin' you 'til
I think you've earned otherwise.
[GALILEO] Hmph.
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
Baked noodles on the bread.
I love Japanese food.
[GALILEO groans]
Somethin' on your
mind, Gali-gal?
[GALILEO]
Don't worry about it.
Well. This is fascinating.
And rather bizarre.
Galileo!
Yes, Vidocq, sir!
From your particuliar
vantage point,
you had a good view of
the Taiwan incident.
The EI that blew
itself to pieces,
would you be so kind as to
share any data you have,
as well as Sükhe's footage?
Yes, sir! Absolutely!
My pleasure!
Right.
On to the tour of the
Alex Rogan's facilities.
Cool. Let's do it.
Fully equipped
conference room.
Our twenty-four seven gym.
Train as hard as you
fancy at all hours.
The records archives.
E-Gene information
and what have you.
[SIO weakly]
Impressive...
[GANDHI] Here we have
the private quarters
for Holders only.
When you need a break.
Like, now perhaps?
[SIO] Uh-huh.
My door's always open to
a fine thing such as you.
Ah! Thank you, but no!
I mean in another life,
maybe, it's just!
[GANDHI] You are
spoken for then?
Not exactly!
Just sort "off the
market" for now!
[GANDHI laughs]
Apologies, but you're just too
adorable to resist teasing.
[SIO whimpers]
[GANDHI] I imagine Jess was
quite a shock to your system.
Uh. Kinda.
[GANDHI]
"Gropey" is her default setting,
as opposed to her
conduct in battle.
[SIO] That's a little
hard to swallow.
[GANDHI] It's a
byproduct of our gift.
Holders act on very different
impulses outside of the fray.
Newton, for example,
is a cruel sadist.
While Jess is anything but.
She engages in lip-lock
with all and sundry.
I almost think she views
it as philanthropic.
The tongue can be
a bit much, however.
You're saying she slips
everyone the tongue?
So she and Jack aren't an item?
[GANDHI] By "item,"
you mean--
Ah. Yes.
You like Adam.
Oh, please! Gross!
Boo! Whatever!
Then I misspoke?
Uh. Li'l bit, yeah!
[GANDHI] Splendid.
Then I have no competition.
Whoa.
You--You're not seriously--?
You see, my demeanor changes
outside of battle as well.
Sometimes I like to
play the aggressor.
[SIO]
What is happening?
[GANDHI] Oh God.
Seems I've overdone it.
[DOGOO] I trust you gleaned
something useful?
Indeed.
I may have uncovered
a valid empirical basis
for your conjecture,
vis-à-vis the enemy's
uncanny aptitude
for relaying information.
[DOGOO]
You're certain of this?
M'sieur Hunter
dissected what was left
of the Florida carcass to
my exact specifications.
The cranial cavity displayed
a number of discreet chambers.
Combined with what
may be safely presumed
from close examination of
Sixth Platoon's Taiwan footage,
a hypothesis begins to form.
Observe.
These scattered fragments
give identical readings
to that of an EI.
Given they're
fragments of an EI,
I hardly find this surprising.
Quite.
My thoughts exactly.
Until I discovered
that each fragment
is teeming with
distinct vital signs.
[DOGOO]
What are you suggesting?
As I said, it is
a mere hypothesis.
But the burden of proof
is easily satisfied.
[SIO groans]
[SIO] Throwing a girl
into a circus is no way
to teach her how to socialize.
[SIO]
Miss you, Asao.
[SIO] You'd want me to do
my best here, wouldn't you?
[SIO groans]
[SIO] No internet.
Of course.
Atsumori. Atsumori.
Ah.
Here we go.
Found ya!
Oh man, it's the same
song, all right.
[SIO]
Something is up with me.
Just wish I knew what.
[NEWTON]
Well, hello there.
[SIO gasps]
Burning the midnight oil?
[SIO]
Not really.
[NEWTON]
Relax, pumpkin.
Fellow platoon members
are virtually family.
No secrets between us.
Well, um, actually--
Whatever it is,
I'm certain I can help!
Uh. It's cool;
I'm good, I promise!
Darling, what will it take for
to see me as your go-to girl?
[SIO]
Boundaries would
--[NEWTON] I'll do anything!
--[SIO] be a good start.
Yes. Anything.
[SIO] I can't
deal with this!
Sorry, didn't see you there!
So the hunter
becomes the hunted?
I think I prefer when
you act dominant.
Not interested!
Heh. A tragedy; truly.
[SIO groans]
Listen.
Can we be serious for a second?
[GANDHI] Hm?
[GANDHI] What about
E-Gene influence?
[SIO] Well, like,
what's it done to you?
Ah. I see.
Well, sharing my personality
with a pacifist martyr
has mellowed me out a bit.
What were you like before
you became Gandhi?
Care to see?
Uh. No!
That's okay.
Thank you, though!
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE OP 1A]
All Second Platoon Holders:
report to the Clayton
Forrester immediately.
Repeat: all Second
Platoon Holders
to the Clayton Forrester.
Another time perhaps.
[SIO whimper]
[SIO] Dumb question,
but the Clayton Forrester?
[JACK] Is the ship we
were on this morning, yeh.
Vidocq's timing's
absolute bollocks.
Holy crap, I'm looking at
an Aquitaine-class frigate!
And an Independence-class?
This is the greatest
day of my life!
[GALILEO]
Signore Dai Zong, hello!
[DAI ZONG]
Ni hao.
[SIO] Huh.
Didn't realize there were
Holders younger than me.
Oh! Greetings,
Miss Nobunagun!
Excellent work the other day!
[SIO]
And you are?
So I flatter you and you
don't even remember me?
[SIO] Sorry.
Recognize me now,
Miss Thing?
Oh! You're her.
"Her," huh? You can't
even manage a name?
Oh, don't be like that.
DOGOO wouldn'ta recruited
someone your age
unless they knew--
My age is not of
any consequence!
Ah! I'm sorry!
Take-backs!
Sorry if it hurts your
tender little ego,
but I have seniority over you.
[SIO] What?
Which makes it my job
to whip you into shape.
Ten-hup!
Go buy me some
yakisoba bread, rookie!
Oh. Well, if you
really need some.
[GALILEO] Si!
I've finally moved up
in the pecking order!
No longer am I the low
man on this totem pole!
[JACK] Heh. Congrats,
Miss Leanin' Tower.
[SIO gasps]
[GALILEO] Please, Jack.
Just let me have this.
Namaste!
What's John gonna do now
his lackey's been promoted?
Look! First,
I'm not his lackey!
Second, I only bring him lunch
when I'm already getting
some for myself!
Does he pay you back
for the trouble?
[GALILEO gasps]
Hate to say this, that's
kinda what a lackey is.
[GALILEO] No one
asked you, rookie!
Sorry!
My mistake!
Looks like
Galileo's in denial.
Ugh.
The both of you are grunts,
so quit fighting and accept it.
[GALILEO] Did you
just call me a runt?
Did I just hear what
I think I heard?
[GALILEO and SIO gasp]
[GALILEO and SIO]
Miss N-N-N-N-Newton.
Oh Galileo, my dear;
how have you been?
[GALILEO whimpers]
I've been violated
by her mouth.
[SIO] Are, uh,
you gonna be okay?
[VIDOCQ] Having a
little tête-à-tête?
[GALILEO]
S-Signore Vidocq!
Ah, the famed
Nobunagun, I presume?
[SIO] Yes!
Yes, sir!
Word of your Florida exploits
have been making the rounds.
You will be vital to this
operation's success.
Sir!
[GALILEO ] Nobunagun!
This betrayal will
not be forgotten!
[SIO] There some special reason
she's staring daggers at me?
[VIDOCQ] This operation
bears a twofold objective.
Of chief importance is
terminating the Easter Armored
Type Sixth Platoon let slip
through their fingers.
Obtaining brain tissue
samples in the process
is our secondary goal.
Hang on. Sounds like
we're on damage control
for someone
else's screw-up.
No.
It's more about solidarity;
there are only so many Holders.
We must look out for
one another, yes?
Ha! Solidarity my eye.
Vidocq wants to secure his
precious tissue sample.
[VIDOCQ chuckles]
M'sieur Dai Zong graciously
joins us from Third Platoon;
securing the sample will
be his responsibility.
With pleasure.
As for the Armored
Type's termination.
Nobunagun, you seem
more than capable.
Yessir!
Wait, you want me to
kill it by myself?
Oi, all due respect.
Why assign it to someone
so green when you got me?
You gone daft or what?
[SIO grunts]
This mission's
division of labor
was chosen by the
Commander herself.
Yer havin' me on!
Your attention,
please, Jack.
This iteration of the enemy
is plated in armor
that AU weapons cannot breech.
The only method for securing
the aforementioned brain tissue
is to exploit the small
gap above its neck.
Ergo, a precision sniper
would be more efficient
than a hack-and-slash
man like you.
Fine. Move on,
I'm over it.
[SIO]
The Commander picked me.
Feel up to it, Nobunagun?
Yes, sir!
Yes, I do.
[CREWMAN 5B]
Sonar to Control Room.
Target sighted.
We've got one Armored Type.
And five Gunboat Types.
[GALILEO] Those goggles
communicate directly with mine.
What I see, you'll see.
Follow the signals
and it'll put you
right where you need
to be, okey-doke?
Okey-doke.
[MALE OP 1A]
Confirmation from the Pickett:
the Easter Armored Type has
entered the operational radius,
flanked by five Gunboat Types,
assumed to be its
security detail.
You have the green
light to engage.
[MALE OP 1B]
Saturation attack commencing.
Steady!
Fire at will!
[JACK chuckles]
[JACK yells]
Oh, did I do that?
Now that I've got
your attention.
Report.
[GALILEO] Problem.
I'm not getting a reading
consistent with Gunboat Types.
[VIDOCQ] Then they
are flagship-class.
[roaring]
Think she can handle
herself alone?
[JACK] Dunno.
We'll find out.
[SIO]
Think precision.
Stay calm.
Focus on the gap above its neck.
[gunshot]
[SIO gasps]
[SIO yells]
[JACK]
I'll clean house.
You two get over
there and cover her!
[NEWTON whines]
Let no one say
you don't care.
[JACK]
Shut up and go!
[GANDHI and NEWTON]
Aye-aye, captain!
[JACK]
Bleedin' hell.
Are reasonably
competent associates
as hard to come by as all that?
[roaring]
[GANDHI]
Holding up out here?
[SIO] Gandhi!
Why're you--?
I was ordered to by your
worrywart of a mentor.
Huh?
[NEWTON]
Fire in the hole!
[SIO] Ah!
Gravity's a bitch.
You're clear!
Take the shot!
Right!
Aaaahhhh!
Eat it!
Fragments in sight!
I count--three-hundred twelve.
Bearing, speed-- Bingo!
This one!
Center screen!
Making run.
[DAI ZONG grunts]
[DAI ZONG] Gotcha!
Report!
In hand!
Mission accomplished!
[JACK] Heh.
Yeah!
[DOGOO]
You were correct.
Exactly per my hypothesis,
this iteration of EI parasitizes
the brains of its fellows.
Put it into layman's
terms for me.
Oui, Ma'am.
I will certainly try.
These EIs retain the memories
of the brains they've eaten.
When their host dies,
they disperse into the sea
in search of another.
The digestive systems
of terrestrial organisms
cannot break them down,
so when they're eaten by say,
a fish, they simply live
on within the fish.
Allowing them to travel up the
food chain perfectly intact.
Records of previous failures
travel the chain with them.
Ergo, a new type is born
which builds on the memory
of its predecessor.
[COMMANDER] So, this EI
is a messenger of sorts?
They speed up natural
selection geometrically.
These "messengers" are to thank
for their breakneck evolution.
This is chilling
news, Vidocq.
[VIDOCQ] Indeed.
If the Invaders continue to
evolve at this pace, Ma'am--
--they will surpass
humankind in a matter of weeks.
[CYX] Princess!
Your lovely clothes!
[GERONIMO] Don't make
such a fuss, Cyx!
[GAUDÍ] She's right,
Miss Geronimo!
You're too reckless!
[CYX] You dare
criticize the princess?
[GERONIMO] Someone thinks
a lot of themselves!
[GAUDÍ squeals]
[GERONIMO] Next time,
Gun Six: "Monster Meat."
[GAUDÍ] I'm sorry!
Forgive me!