[bubbles gurgling]
[horses neighing]
[people fighting]
[MITSUHIDE] Tonight the
sun shall set on Honnoji!
[RANMARU] My lord!
Rebellion is upon us!
The fiend's shadow
engulfs all!
Their ranks crowd
shoulder-to-shoulder!
[NOBUNAGA] What crest
does the enemy bear?
My lord, their sign
is the bellflower.
Keep vigil.
With respect!
Our hand has been forced!
Boldness must be
met in kind!
[WARRIOR roars]
[blood splattering]
[NOBUNAGA yells]
Mitsuhide!
[NOBUNAGA is impaled]
[NOBUNAGA's skin rips open]
[NOBUNAGA grunting]
[DOGOO] I require
a warrior's blood.
Forgive me, Oda Nobunaga.
[SIO yelps]
[SIO panting]
No moustache.
Please, no moustache.
[SIO sighs relief]
Man, these dreams.
What's with the HD quality?
And why do I always gotta
be some derpy old geezer?
[SIO groans]
[beeping]
[SIO whipmers]
[SIO yelling]
C'mon, mom!
You're killin' me!
Why didn't you wake me up?
[MOM] Don't put
this on me!
I tried!
I don't believe this!
Backpack!
Got it! Laters!
Be safe!
This is "teh suck."
Stupid nightmare!
[TEACHER] Okay,
we're ready to push off!
Load up, please.
Single file.
[SIO] Wait!
Wait don't leave without me!
[SIO gasping for breath]
I know. I'm late. I'm sorry.
Um, and you are?
Ah-ha.
Sio Ogura.
Well, get on the bus.
We've got a plane to catch.
[classmates laughing]
Right.
[SAILOR 1A]
Okay!
Bring 'er up!
[SAILOR 2B]
You got it.
Nice and quiet out
here this mornin'.
Yup.
Bettin' we'll see
a fine haul today.
Heh, I'll hold
you to that.
Huh?
What in the...?
[SAILORS yelling]
[MALE OP 1a] I'm getting a hit
from Surveillance Satellite D.
Target has emerged
in the Bashi Channel,
just off the coast of Taiwan.
[MALE OP 1b]
Moving West at 25 knots.
[FEMALE OP 1a]
Level 3 alert.
[FEMALE OP 1b] All Holders,
prepare to engage.
[St. GERMAINE] Interesting
choice of venue.
Though, 'tis the nature
of uninvited guests
to be obtrusive.
[FEMALE OP 1a]
Battlefield map coming onscreen.
[SIO yawns]
[students chatting]
[Watanabe] Think about
all the food there.
I'm gonna stuff myself.
[YAGINUMA]
Whoa! Almost there!
I can see the coast!
[SIO gasps]
Uh...
[SIO giggles uncomfortably]
[CUSTOMS AGENT growls]
Uh, I promise not to
do anything illegal?
Ogura!
Right here!
Now, we are guests
in this country,
so I expect you all
to behave yourselves.
[camera clicks photograph]
Selfie with the
rockstar Buddha!
[SCHOOLGIRLS giggling]
Come on!
Whoa!
Shut up!
[WATANABE] I say we
check out the temple!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Ermergerd totes!
[YAGINUMA]
You coming, Kaoru?
[KAORU] Huh?
Yeah, sure.
[TEACHER] Check your watches
and meet back here in two hours.
Stay inside the park.
I vote we cruise
the riverbank!
They're supposed to have
a tiger over there somewhere.
How cool are you?
155 millimeter Ogura Gun.
Lock on!
Bam!
[SCHOOLGIRLS laughing]
[SIO] Uh, just kidding.
[YAGINUMA] She's doing
that thing again.
[SUGURI]
What a train wreck.
[SIO]
Way to freak 'em out again.
So what next?
Nature trail?
Hey, what do you think
about asking Ogura to come with?
We s'posed to
know who that is?
Oh.
Her?
[SIO] Sorry!
I'm a klutz!
She smells
like a dude.
She's kind of
a loner, right?
I mean, look.
[SIO]
Um, excuse me?
Can I have one
of these thingies?
Oh--wait!
They speak Taiwanese
here. Dang it.
[VENDOR] One "thingy,"
comin' right up.
Uh, wait. You understood me?
Meet enough tourists,
you pick up on their
gibberish 'fore long.
[VENDOR giggles]
Enjoy.
No, uh! One!
I only wanted one!
I-- Me no afford?
We've been through this, kid.
I understand you jus' fine.
Second one's on the house.
Duoxiè!
Whew. That was an ordeal.
Yummers!
Somebody looks content.
Oh. Hey, Asao.
Not that it's any
of my business,
but you're not gonna
waste the trip eating?
Oh.
Well, I was...
you know, just...
I mean it's so cool we get
to come to places like this.
I dunno 'bout you,
but I'd hate to
miss out on stuff
by parking my rump
on a bench all afternoon.
Are you asking me
to hang out?
Surprised?
Listen, why don'tcha come
sightseeing with
me and the gang?
Uhhh... I-I'd love to.
I guess I'm just whatcha
call a "lone wolf."
So join our wolfpack.
[YAGINUMA]
Hey, Kaoru!
Turns out Ol' Beardy's hollow
inside and open for business!
Let's go!
Yeah, okay!
We'll be there in a sec.
[SIO] I'm good. No worries.
We both know
a popular gal like you's
got way too many
plates spinnin'
to worry about
some weirdo like me.
Have it your way, then.
[KAORU]
Little advice?
Don't think bein' weird means
you got nothin' to contribute.
Seriously. Come see
the big guy with us.
It won't kill ya.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Maybe some other time?
But, yeah.
It's cool you asked.
I tried.
Still, I choose to view this as
a step in the right direction.
Give me your info
at the hotel later.
Might be creepy to keep
this pic all to myself.
[SIO giggles]
Talk about worlds colliding.
Still... at least she's nice.
You gotta be kidding: a F-CK1?
Wow! Go Taiwanese Air Force!
What the heck?
Wha-What on Earth is happening?
It's raining M-60 A3s?
No, wait.
Those are CM-11s!
Known as Brave Tigers!
Run for your lives!
Huh.
Okay, that one
I don't recognize!
Someone please tell
me what's going on.
Hold up!
You can't just fire one
of those at point blank range!
Whoa!
It shrugged off a
105 millimeter round!
IED?
[EVERYONE screaming]
You okay, sir?
He ran for cover.
Had to 'ave.
[SIO crying]
[SIO gasps]
The old man from--
[memory of KAORU]
Seriously.
Come see the big guy with us.
It won't kill ya.
Asao!
An Evolutionary Invader
has infiltrated Kaohsiung!
Taiwanese forces are engaged,
but they're out of their depth.
[ST. GERMAIN]
So they've slopped ashore.
[COMMANDER]]
An altogether troubling notion;
they're no longer being
restricted to the seas.
Contact the Taiwanese
government immediately,
and order them to desist.
The weapons required
to combat these creatures
are laughably beyond the scope
of conventional warfare.
Yes, Ma'am.
E-Gene Holder status.
Second Platoon's Jack the Ripper
is in a pod as we speak.
ETA to battlefield,
approximately one minute.
And his backup
is where, precisely?
Gandhi and Newton are still
readying themselves for descent.
Jack the overachiever.
We can hardly blame the others
for keeping their distance.
He was the scourge
of Whitechapel once upon a time.
I question our use of him.
And I question
your unsolicited comment.
Forgive my speaking out of turn.
[SIO panting]
A BGM 109?
No wait-- that's--!
[JACK] Oi, oi.
Big bloke, aren't ya?
You know what they say.
Just mean there's
more of you to love.
'Kay. Who the heck is he?
Aw.
Havin' some trouble there?
Land-lubbin' ain't all
it's cracked up
to be, is it, big stuff?
The key is practice.
[Gandhi]
Jack, do you read me?
Loud and clear, Gandhi.
If you chaps wanna
stay put, 's grand by me.
He's the size of a small
continent, but stupid-slow.
I can take him alone.
I'm fancyin'
a tryst in the park.
Evacuation is
still ongoing.
Proceed with caution.
Yeh, now he tells me.
Wow.
Okay then.
He sliced that
thing like a cucumber.
Hey, hold on a sec!
Where's Asao?
You were with her,
weren't you?
There was this big explosion.
She was with us,
but when I looked back--
Yeah, she won't answer her
phone, so maybe she got away?
Idiot!
There's only one path!
You'd have seen her run!
Then she's still in there!
[JACK] You break
you buy, gov'na.
Ta-ta.
[JACK stabbed]
Right.
So uh, Gandhi?
On second thought, maybe...
Maybe a spot o' backup
would come in handy after all.
Status report!
Jack!
Seems the big
one's just a ruse.
He's, uh...
actually a transport ship.
Assuming I can
eviscerate 5 with each blow.
Carry the one.
And we got ourselves
quite the soiree.
Asao?
Can you hear me?
Asao!
[ASAO cell phone ringing]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
You're alive!
Bloody hell.
I'm try'nna work
here, d'ya mind?
Piss off!
I-I just... I'm trying
to help my friend.
What?
Ah.
Well, help her
and be done with it already.
I'm not a nanny!
Every second I--!
[SIO whimpering]
Wait your turn, jackarse.
's plenty of me to go 'round.
Cheers, mate.
How many of you
bastards are left?
Damn.
Well, ain't this a bitch.
Too much blood loss
to maintain my form.
Jack the Ripper's E-Gene
signal has gone offline.
Sphere 13 is
confirmed inactive.
[SIO] Hey.
Are you dead?
Huh.
's weird.
I feel like
I've seen you before.
A long time ago.
Asao!
Don't do it.
Only thing you'll accomplish is
gettin' yourself Mary Kelly-ed.
I can't leave 'er.
Sorry.
She needs my phone number.
Stand back!
[FEMALE OP 1b] Reading an energy
influx to Sphere 13.
It's rebooting!
[COMMANDER] I take it Jack's
reentered the fight?
[FEMALE OP 1a] No, Ma'am.
There's an E-Gene signal, but
it appears to be unregistered.
Are you telling me
there's an unknown Holder
in the thick
of it out there?
Details.
Now.
[FEMALE OP 1a]
Pinging genetic epoch.
I've got a hit.
Source gene from 1582!
Sphere 13 at 90 percent.
95 percent.
105.
110!
It's off the charts!
Well, what do you know?
She's one of us.
I remember.
All of it.
[DOGOO]
Rest assured, Nobunaga.
Your essence
shall be nobly used.
My purpose holds
to create warriors
fit to embody the
inimitable Nobunaga legacy.
This orb shall
respond only to them,
forming the substance
of whatever improbable weapon
lay closest to
their hearts.
Such are the
lengths I must go
to protect your world
from its enemies.
What manner of weapon
will your inheritor choose
when the time comes?
Hah! Is it not
perfectly obvious?
A gun!
Nobunaga?
Is that you?
All right, girl.
So who are you now?
Nobunagun.
[JACK]
'Kay.
That's a new one.
[NOBUNAGA} Hear me,
heir to my immortal soul.
When the fateful day comes,
let no enemy escape
the fires of your wrath!
Gandhi to HQ.
ETA in Kaohsiung
approximately sixty seconds.
Sounds like Jack
is in bad shape,
so I will pull out
all the stops.
Over.
Copy that.
Be advised an
unregistered E-Gene Holder
has just come into play.
Code name: Nobunagun.
A mysterious outside party's
joining us in the fray, Newton.
Care to bet on
whether it's a hot girl?
[NEWTON] Damn it, Gandhi.
Focus on the task at hand
or so help me I will
crush your balls into pulp!
I love your style...
so visceral!