[COMMANDER] You have
new intel, Vidocq?
[VIDOCQ]
After having applied my
not inconsiderable mind to it,
I have a theory which
explains pretty conclusively
how EIs made it
to the Atlantic Ocean.
[DOGOO] Go on, then.
As we have already
successfully deduced,
their Florida gambit was
based on their Taiwan defeat.
They relay such information
via the Messenger Type
we discovered the other day.
[VIDOCQ] These are all the
sea creatures capable of
being parasitized
by a Messenger type,
rendered as visual data.
Then I compiled that data
back into my "easy chair."
[VIDOCQ] The next step was
to push said data through a
food-chain filter and
a rate-of-speed filter,
narrowing down
the possibilities.
It's child's play, really.
Here's every conceivable
ocean transmission route.
However, even the
shortest sea-route available
would not allow for the info
to reach Florida so quickly.
[COMMANDER] Which means--
[VIDOCQ] You were correct.
There must be a shortcut
that's escaped our notice.
The presence of such a
thing explains quite a bit.
How better to dodge
our dragnet, en route to
the Atlantic, than
to skip it altogether?
Hmmm.
You're saying there's--
An undersea tunnel--indeed.
West of the canal,
they've found a passage.
And thanks to that,
they can reach the Atlantic
without going
around South America.
Do you know where it is?
Suffice it to say I
have a few spots in mind.
[COMMANDER]
I'll send you a team A-SAP.
♪
[NARRATOR] "E-genes":
recombinant DNA strands
marked by their ability to
retain and selectively manifest
the essence of humanity's
greatest figures.
Known as E-Gene Holders,
the inheritors of
these specialized
strands use AU spheres to
activate the abilities lying
dormant within themselves,
which then materialize as
physical weapons
of varying types.
What follows is a
record of the struggle
between DOGOO, a supranational
organization comprised
of trained E-Gene
Holders, and mankind's
greatest threat, the
Evolutionary Invaders.
Make no mistake:
the battle is on!
[SIO] Gun Eight: "Tunnel."
[beeping]
[beeping increases]
Bingo, sir! There's
a tunnel dead ahead!
Hm. What a surprise.
[COMMANDER] Careful,
Holders. The one who dug
that tunnel may still be there.
[GERONIMO] Roger!
[GAUDÍ] Miss Geronimo?
[GERONIMO] Ma'am,
allow me to correct you.
Whatever dug this, it's here.
And I don't mean "it" singular!
There're tons of 'em down here!
Ahhh!
[SIO] Where am I?
Hmmm... What mission
was I here for, again?
[KAORU] Heya, Sio.
[SIO] Huh? Uh--Wha--Asao?
In the flesh.
[SIO] Flesh, yeah. Heh, heh.
Don'tcha think maybe that
bikini's a bit much for uh--
whatever we're doing here?
Is it? But yours
is pretty skimpy, too!
What the hell? A two-piece?
Wha--uh--
[JACK] Oh, shut it, wouldja?
[SIO] Wasn't I just--? Huh?
It's always a
crisis for this one, innit?
[SIO] Wait--Jack?
When did you get here?
Lemme guess, you and
Jack are an item, huh?
[SIO] An item?
Us? That's crazy-talk!
[KAORU] Are you sure?
[JACK] Sio's outta
luck, I'm afraid.
Already got me a steady snog.
[BOTH] Huh?
Huh?!
Tell 'em, lover boy.
All's fair in
love and war.
Aaahhh...
[NEWTON] Stop teasing me, Sio.
When it comes to warming
your bed, I'm your bird.
Oh, hell no!
Goodness, Sio. It looks like
you're already spoken for.
Please, Asao--
you've got it all wrong!
It's okay! We can still
be friends at least, right?
C'mon, give
Mumsy some sugar.
[whimpers]
[NEWTON moans]
[screams]
Ahhh!
[SIO] Just a dream.
Thanks for nothin', brain.
[sighs]
[NEWTON] Pucker up.
[SIO screams]
You--! How--?
Newton, what the hell
were you doing in my bed?
I was told to come wake
you up, you silly goose.
Huh?
It's a working breakfast.
We chat about our
next mission over food.
Oh. Sure.
[SIO] Jeez, she couldn't just
knock like a normal person?
Princess, are you all right?
They're nothing to
worry about one-on-one.
But they do outnumber us.
[GERONIMO] I'll be fine.
Guard the Europa probe!
Roger!
[GALILEO] Too many legs!
Too many eyes!
They're like giant bugs! Ew!
Like bugs. I wonder.
[GERONIMO] They retreated
into the tunnel.
Fine. Return topside for now.
It's enough for the moment that
we confirmed their shortcut.
[VIDOCQ] Let's take
a look inside first.
Huh?
Sorry ma'am, there's
something else we must
confirm without delay.
Roger that.
Cyx and I will check it out
with the probe in-tow.
[GAUDÍ] But I'm supposed
to defend you two.
Should I come with?
No, you wait for us out
here. Secure our retreat.
Lead line released.
I'll keep at it as
long as I've got air.
Thank you. Carry on.
[JACK] Why are we arse-in-chair
while First Platoon
gets to hog all the glory, huh?
Wait, I'm confused.
Does Jack not get along
with those guys or what?
No. You should hear
the way they carry on.
He and Geronimo
especially.
Bugger off! If First Platoon's
all they're cracked up to be,
they shouldn't need
our help to begin with!
That logic doesn't
necessarily hold true.
Think of it this way.
That tunnel is important,
and the EIs will
defend it accordingly.
You don't suppose there
are unknown types down there?
Most likely.
So, uh, we've
fought a lot of EIs now.
Where do you think
they come from?
We've seen the eggs.
[SIO] Talking about this tunnel,
I just--I thought it might
hold something really
important to 'em.
[JACK] "Something" like what?
[SIO] Dunno. I didn't think
it through that far yet.
Yeah, thanks so much
for your dazzling
grasp of the obvious,
Sherlock Homely.
How's about you stop
running your grey matter
through the wringer already,
and start focusing on
hitting your
targets more often?
Well, maybe we'd be
better off letting Vidocq
do the heavy lifting,
so to speak.
No. Kicking arse?
That's the job our E-Genes
are best suited for.
Hrm...
Break's over! Second
Platoon! On your feet!
♪
[FEMALE OP 1A] Starting
descent pod ejection sequence.
Destination:
Costa Rican waters.
[FEMALE OP 1A] Descent pod:
ready to deploy!
Pod away!
Tunnel like this is
for more than transport.
Look at all these
caves on the side.
They're not just simple caves.
These're rooms.
[VIDOCQ] Care to
take a peek for me?
[GALILEO] Aye-aye, sir!
[GALILEO shrieks]
They're everywhere!
Huh? Actually,
it kinda looks like
they're guarding
something, in the back.
Huh? What're you?
I'll run a scan--Uh! Geronimo?
Yeah sorry, HQ.
We're turning back.
--[VIDOCQ] What's wrong?
--[CYX] Princess?
[GERONIMO] I've got a
bad feeling about this.
Something's coming!
Cyx, topside now!
[CYX] Roger that!
Dammit! Gaudí!
[GAUDÍ] Sí?
We'll be there
in thirty seconds!
[GERONIMO] Seal off the
exit the moment we're through
and then build us a ramp
to the surface! Understood?
[GAUDÍ] Roger! Here goes!
[GAUDÍ yells]
♪
[gasps]
[HUNTER] It's huge!
[GALILEO, CYX,
GERONIMO, and GAUDÍ yell]
[FEMALE OP 1A]
Second Platoon, inbound!
[shrieks]
Gali-gal!
[screams]
Deactivate
her AU weapon--now!
If it takes any more
damage, the feedback--
[VIDOCQ] Negative!
If we un-summon it
before the Europa probe
has a chance to
dock with Galileo,
we'll lose all the data
it's collected. Unacceptable.
I know it's painful,
but I need you to hold out
[VIDOCQ] just a little
while longer, my dear.
You son of a bitch!
This intel is priceless to me.
All right. I'll do it for you.
[screams]
Damn it all! I'll get it--!
Better late than never!
[HUNTER] Second Platoon!
[GANDHI] Heads up,
Hunter--coming at you!
[HUNTER] Come on.
The intel has
been saved, signore.
Oui. And it is
all thanks to you.
[GANDHI] It's retreating?
[whimpers]
Oi! Gali-gal!
[HUNTER] She's out cold!
We need a med-evac
team here, STAT!
[CREWMAN 8A] Yes, sir!
Take this sphere below.
I need the data
pulled off of it.
[CREWMAN 8C] Sir!
You little shit!
She gonna be okay?
Wait a sec.
Was it spying on us?
[MALE OP 1A] Battleship Type
has retreated to the tunnel.
[VIDOCQ] Keep monitoring
its status for me.
[MALE OP 1A] Sir!
[whimpers]
Stay with us, Gali-gal!
Just hold on!
Sorry, you'll have
to wait back here.
[HUNTER] Thank you
for seeing her off.
No. We're on the
same team, right?
It was the least I
could do. Hope she's okay.
Would've been nice if
Vidocq had cared a little!
He's so hung up
on his damn data,
he forgets how to act
like a human being!
[sighs]
I don't know why the
Commander sent you in.
First Platoon had the situation
totally under control.
Huh. I seem to
remember you three
getting flogged into next week.
Are y'sure we're talking
about the same fight?
Bite your tongue, Jack!
All you did was swoop in
at the end and hog the glory.
[JACK] The hell I did!
Hey guys, I'm back.
[SIO] Uh! Okay...
Tension's kinda thick in here.
Don't worry about it.
You still haven't met
First Platoon, have you?
[SIO] Oh uh--no!
[GANDHI] The one in
the middle is Geronimo.
The one in fancy eyewear is Cyx.
And the little chap
on the left is Gaudí.
Glad to make your acquaintance!
Hi. Sio Ogur--uh!
Nobunagun here!
I'm pleased as hell to meetcha!
Great.
Long as you don't
get in our way and
mess things up for us,
we'll get along just fine.
Uh! I'll do my best!
[GAUDÍ] I don't get it.
Whatcha looking at, Gaudí?
[SIO]He's really focused
on it, whatever it is.
Ah! It's nothing!
Cross my heart!
[GAUDÍ]
My buxom beauty is a lie!
Oh. Señor Vidocq.
[SIO] Can I talk
to you real quick?
As long as you
keep it "real quick."
Would you do me a
favor? Maybe check in on
Galileo when you
have a bit o' downtime?
What for?
Because she--she really
respects what you do for us.
Figuring all
this stuff out.
Even if you just
swing by for a second.
[VIDOCQ] Ridiculous.
Huh?
That sounds like an
utter waste of time.
You jerk! Don't you
care that she's hurt?
EIs will not magically
vanish because I visit her.
Have you forgotten the
gravity of the situation?
Earth is under attack!
I need to parse the data!
[HUNTER] You can spare
two lousy minutes.
Hunter!
Don't tell me
you agree with her.
Maybe you've
conveniently forgotten,
but she let herself
get hurt because of you.
She was doing her job,
as were we all.
If we're quite finished
here, I have work to do.
[HUNTER] Classy!
Tch!
Bloke's a cold fish,
but he ain't wrong, you know.
--[SIO] Huh?
--[HUNTER] What?
We're fighting a war.
You take to the battlefield,
an' eventually you get hurt.
If you really roll snake-eyes,
maybe you give up the ghost.
Ain't rocket-science.
Just 'cause it
happens doesn't mean--!
[JACK] Doesn't mean
what? Go on, rookie!
Tell us how it works!
Hrmmm.
Now, now--
let's keep it civil.
Save that piss and
vinegar for the real enemy.
I don't like Jack,
but at least he knows
what he's talking
about, new kid.
Just worry about yourself.
What she said.
Do us all a favor and
stay out of our
way, Second Platoon.
I hear mediocrity's
contagious.
Piss off!
Ough! Not a shred of empathy
in the whole lot of 'em!
Don't be mean!
It's noble to worry about
a hurt teammate, right?
Oh, look who grew
a pair all at once.
Yeah, shoulda
seen that comin'.
Throw a new
girl into the mix
and the niño
gets a mouth on him!
What? No, wait!
[ALL gasp]
[SIO] Commander?
[JACK] Wha--?
During your next mission,
you'll be getting your
orders directly from me.
As I hope you know,
the commander
doesn't take to
the field on a whim.
You'd be wise to grasp
the implications of this.
It means that our next
encounter's a really big deal.
You're going to
be working together,
so set aside your feud.
Engage that infernal creature.
Show it just who it's
dealing with and send it...
straight to hell.
♪
Well, least finding it
won't be much of a bother.
Uh-oh. Someone
gettin' cold feet?
Ha! Dream on, Ger-wrong-imo.
[SIO] You did good,
Galileo! This one's for you!
♪
[FEMALE OP 1A] Full-body
sonar scan is now complete!
[FEMALE OP 1B] It resembles
a giant cephalopod,
with two limbs
capable of attack.
Before anyone attacks its body,
we need to neutralize
the tentacles.
First Platoon, you take
the arm to your left.
[COMMANDER] Second Platoon,
the arm to your right.
Holders, attack!
[yells]
--[GERONIMO] Gaudí!
--[GAUDÍ] Roger!
Geronimo!
[CYX] I see what
you did there!
[GERONIMO] On your left!
[SIO shrieks]
[GAUDÍ] C'mon,
you two! Slow down!
[JACK] What's
the hold-up, rookie--
waiting for a bloody invite?
Hey! Nobody told
me we had a boat!
Take us up!
[CYX] With pleasure!
[GERONIMO] First blood
goes to First Platoon!
[NEWTON] Can't let you get
a big head about yourself...
can we?
[JACK grunts]
Spineless and boneless.
Perfect timing!
[GERONIMO] No it wasn't!
Sorry, I tried!
--[SIO] You're welcome!
--[GANDHI] Look out!
[SIO] Huh?
[JACK] Dammit! I betcha he's
stuffed to the gills with 'em!
[GANDHI] Every one of them
was bred to explode on impact!
Newton, I need you
to stomp that tentacle!
Nobunagun and I will
attack from behind
Gandhi's finger-fence!
[JACK]
The arm's our main objective,
but we get ta kill a
lotta bugs on the way!
Who died an'
made you king?
[GANDHI] And don't
call it a "finger-fence!"
Hop to, wankers!
[SIO] They're
all so good at this!
I have to bring my A-game!
[SIO] Man, First Platoon
is pretty far out there.
We must be kicking the EI's ass
for it to pull
its arms that wide.
[SIO] Unless, the arms are
that far off to the sides,
because it wants to lure
the E-Gene Holders away--
--and bum-rush
the Clayton Forrester!
[SIO]
They don't see it, do they?
Just me. What do I do?
[SIO] Newton!
Ease up your G-force!
Change the angle of fire!
What? Kinda busy here!
Uh, never mind. Gandhi!
[SIO] Put your barrier
right in front of its head!
My hands are kind of
full up here! Spit it!
I--It's--Just forget it!
[SIO] They all know
what they're doing.
So why do I feel like they're
all in the dark right now?
I mean, it's just a hunch!
I'm probably wrong!
And even if I'm right, there's
no time to convince them!
What do I do?
Our hand is forced!
[gasps]
[FEMALE OP 1A]
The target's surfacing!
[GERONIMO] It fired?
[NEWTON] It's huge!
[CYX] Is there a warhead?
[JACK] If that goes off--!
[GANDHI] Not good! It's headed
straight for the Commander!
Hard to stern!
[CREWMAN 8C] We can't!
There isn't time!
[SIO grunts]
How the hell'd
she get back there?
Clever girl--
now shoot it down!
She can't!
[GANDHI] At that
range, the blast will
kill everyone aboard!
♪
Heh.
Augh!
If that had...
hit the Forrester--!
Who knew its head could do that?
New girl's pretty good.
Whad'ya know.
[huffs]
[COMMANDER]
Give me a damage report.
[CREWMAN 8D] Ma'am!
The engine was untouched.
We're still mobile.
[COMMANDER]
Attention all Holders:
Cease hostilities and return
to the Clayton Forrester.
We'll pull out for the
time being and regroup.
I repeat:
Back to the ship at once!
[KAORU] Hey,
I watched some Gamera!
[SIO] Wha'dja think?
[KAORU] Oh man, the
monster with the knife-head!
And the alien one that
looked like a squid! So fun!
[SIO] Yeah, "fun."
That's the ticket.
[SIO] Next time,
Gun Nine: "Sio and Kaoru."
[KAORU] I'll protect Sio,
no matter what!