[BARDOCK] Frieza!
I'm coming for you,
you murderous self-serving
traitor! It's over!
[SOLDIERS]
Long live, Lord Frieza!
[BARDOCK LAUGHS]
No way Frieza!
[BARDOCK]
You've lived long enough!
[BARDOCK] Actually,
it's been too long for my taste!
[BARDOCK] Frieza!
Listen up! We quit! All of us!
[BARDOCK] Got it! We don't
work for you anymore...!
We're free!
[BARDOCK] You can find someone
else to do your dirty work!
Oh, yeah!
There's one last thing!
[NARRATOR] Deployed
on a routine military operation,
the Saiyan baby,
Kakarot, flies toward Earth,
missing the deadly surprise
attack on his home planet!
His father, Bardock,
confronts the assailants,
Frieza and his
entire army, alone!
[BARDOCK] This is for all the
people we killed in your name!
Here! Have it!
[FRIEZA LAUGHS]
No way!
[DOORE] That's the guy,
right there! Bardock!
[SALZA] He doesn't look
so threatening to me...!
Anyway, he's space-dust now...!
And there goes the
whole monkey farm!
Now this is live entertainment!
What's this?
Someone's getting away!
Magnify that image!
Right! I'm on it, Salza!
[SALZA] I want an
interior view as well!
[NEIZ]
That's it! Got it!
[SALZA] Where does
he think he's going?
[NEIZ] It looks
like he's heading
toward a planet called Earth!
Intercept course?
Yes!
[COOLER]
Belay that order!
--[DOORE] Sire!
--[NEIZ] Yes, Sire!
[SALZA] But someone
is escaping!
[COOLER] Frieza's the one in
charge of this quadrant....
Let him clean up his own mess!
[COOLER] I've got seven planets
to destroy by
the end of the day!
[COOLER] Why
should I allow myself
to get behind schedule
just to cover his mistake!
[COOLER] Besides,
it's just a Saiyan child...!
He's no threat to us!
[COOLER] Ah, look at him!
What foolishness!
He's so pleased with himself
that he's blinded by
his arrogant pride!
[COOLER] That could
be King Vegeta
on that space pod
for all he knows!
You've got a
lot to learn! Brother!
Let's get out of here!
♪ OPENING SONG ♪
[ROSHI]
Look at that!
I can see clear to the mainland,
Goku! That's amazing!
Awesome, huh? Watch this!
I can make the walls go higher!
[ROSHI THINKS]
Remarkable!
He's never trained harder,
but he's so relaxed
and confident about it!
Beating Frieza changed him.
There, divide that by ten!
Hi! I thought my little
scholar might be thirsty!
Here's some tea! Hm?
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
[CHI-CHI] I know
what you're up to,
now you get out of here, huh?
[GOKU] Icarus!
Leave Gohan alone...!
He's trying to
finish his homework!
What? Did you hear what
your Father just said?
He told Icarus to
leave you alone
because you were
doing your homework?
Goku, are you
feeling okay, honey?
[GOKU] Oh, yeah!
I'm feeling just fine!
[CHI-CHI] Are you sure you
don't have a fever Goku...?
You sound a little strange!
[GOKU] No, I feel great...!
I just want Gohan to
finish his homework!
Yep! I knew it!
I knew it!
Goku has never cared if
you finished your homework!
[CHI-CHI] Gohan, I'm
afraid there's something
seriously wrong
with your father!
I wonder if all this fighting
has finally knocked a few
screws loose in Goku's head!
That's it, he must've
bruised his brain.
Nope! Not here!
Oh, no! My poor husband!
[GOKU HUMS TO HIMSELF]
He's a vegetable!
All right! This oughta
be enough for a few days!
Oh no! I need to get him in
bed before he hurts himself!
[CHI-CHI YELPS
AND FALLS INTO TABLE]
[GOKU] Hey Gohan,
hurry up and finish,
so we can go camping!
ChiChi, whatcha
doin' down there?
Um, dear! You never
mentioned this camping trip!
That's why you wanted
Gohan to finish his homework?!
[GOKU] Come on!
Finish that later...!
We're all waiting
for you, little man!
Who's all?
[OOLONG AND KRILLIN LAUGH]
Uh... We're all!
Oh, I see! You had
it all planned out!
Well, what's more important,
camping or homework?
ChiChi, I'm not an idiot!
[GOKU] Every parent knows
the answer to that!
Camping! Of course!
Huh? Oh!
What? My brother killed
by a Saiyan? That's absurd!
How could a Saiyan generate
enough power to destroy Frieza?
[NEIZ] It happened, my lord...!
[NEIZ] This Saiyan has
been living on Earth...!
He left Vegeta right
before Lord Frieza blew it up!
Mmm! I never did like him!
And now he goes and
disgraces my father and I
by getting killed by a Saiyan!
[COOLER THINKS] Father
always spoiled you rotten,
you little brat!
Salza!
Sir!
Prepare the ship
for departure!
I don't know who
this Saiyan thinks he is,
but no one attacks our
family and lives! No one!
Plot a course for Earth!
[KRILLIN] Well, the rice
is almost done...!
And the stew looks good!
[KRILLIN] Now we just
need Goku to bring the fish,
and we'll be ready!
I don't know what
it is about camping,
but the food
always tastes great!
I think we're gonna
need a little more wood
if we wanna keep this fire hot.
Well, what d'ya say, Gohan?
Right!
[GOHAN] Let's see here!
This one oughta do!
That's that!
Well, you're a little
on the small side,
but just right for
making Sushi! Hmm?
[GOHAN CHUCKLING]
I got it, Krillin!
Great! Bring it on over, Gohan!
Hmm? Huh?
[ICARUS SQUAWKS]
[OOLONG] Hey, what's all
the squawking about...?
I'm trying to relax over here!
[KRILLIN] Sshhh!
[OOLONG] Don't shush me...!
Icarus was the one
making all the noise!
[KRILLIN] Guys, guys!
Be quiet!
Behind you!
Krilli--
[DOORE]
Nighty-night!
This monkey destroyed Frieza?
[NEIZ] Give me a break! His
fighting power is only fifty!
A pitiful level even if you
do have him by the tail!
Hey, these guys can cook!
[GOHAN]
Stop it!  You big freak!
We should get the heck
out of here, buddy!
Easy, boy! Whoa! Back off!
[GOKU]
Hey!
Hmm? Mm!
[DOORE] Well...
what do we have here?
My name is Goku!
These are my friends!
Goku! This is the Saiyan
that destroyed Frieza!
You don't say!
Let's kill him!
Yeah! I wanna kill the
guy that killed Frieza!
[SALZA] Destroying Frieza was a
feat that few could pull off!
You will be a
prestigious kill for us!
So who are you guys, anyway?
[NEIZ, SALZA AND DOORE] We are,
Cooler's Armored Squadron!
Great! There goes
our camping trip!
Look out, Dad!
Come on, Krillin!
You've got to get up!
So! We've found one
that knows how to fight!
Hold him still, Doore!
[DOORE] You moron!
What'd you do that for?
It's not my fault!
You should have
held him tigh-- huh?
Thank goodness
for retractable heads!
[DOORE GASPS]
Sir! We didn't expect you.
[GOKU SHOCKED]
[GOKU THINKS]
Frieza...!
But how?
[GOHAN]
I'm coming, Dad!
Huh? Gohan! Turn back!
[GOKU] This isn't the best
place for you right now!
This isn't the best
place for anyone now!
Dad! You've been hit!
[NEIZ LAUGHS]
[NEIZ] Smoked meat!
[COOLER THINKS] I can
see how Frieza might have
underestimated this one.
He's somehow
different from the rest.
Could he be a Super Saiyan?
[SALZA] Nice work, my lord!
[DOORE] Yeah! Two Saiyans dead!
The universe is a better place!
[COOLER]
They're not dead!
[COOLER] Anyone who can
counter an attack like that
after taking the full
force of my Death Beam,
can certainly survive
a little swim!
[SALZA]
You think he's alive?
He's alive all right!
Find him! And kill him!
[NEIZ, SALZA AND DOORE] Sir!
[GOHAN] Dad! Are you okay?
Wake up! Dad!
Bah! I don't get it!
The Scouter's not picking up
anything! It must be broken!
[DOORE] Hmm!
He's probably dead...!
No one's ever gotten hit
by Cooler's Death Beam
and lived to tell about it!
Er, as far as I know.
Yaye! He's waking up!
Keep licking, Icarus!
[KRILLIN] Huh? No, no, no, no!
I'm fine! Where's Goku?
Wake up! Wake up! Please, Dad!
Gohan!
Hey, Dad!
My body's fried!
What was that?!
Attention to detail!
That's why we're the best!
We're so darn thorough!
[SALZA] Yeah! We always
get the monkey!
[MULTIPLE BLASTS]
Huh? Uh, no! Daddy!
Gohan!
Boys, turn up the heat.
This is the grand finale!
[DOORE] Oops! Do you think
we over did it a little bit?
[SALZA] No, but we may have a
hard time finding their bodies.
'Cause they're probably
in a million pieces!
[GROUP LAUGHS]
[NEIZ] We put 'em
through the shredder...!
No one could
have survived that!
[COOLER] Oh, no?
[DOORE] Lord Cooler!
[COOLER] Weak minds are
easily deceived! He's alive...!
And I want you to comb
every inch of this place
until you find him!
Yes, Sire!
They can't hide forever! They'll
come out sooner or later!
I don't like these games
any more than you do!
I would just rather blow
up this wretched planet!
But I'd rather see him die
with my own eyes! And I will!
Now!
Wait up!
[KRILLIN]
Come on!
[ICARUS SQUAWKS]
[OOLONG]
Don't leave me!
[KRILLIN] Icarus, what are you
trying to tell us? Is it Gohan?
Down here?
Gohan, Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Who's there?
Hey! Are you guys okay!
[GOHAN] I'm fine, but my
Dad's hurt pretty bad!
Is he down there with you?
[GOHAN] Yeah!
He's right next to me!
Hold on! I'm coming!
[GOHAN] Krillin! My Dad's
sensing some trapped animals...!
He's worried about them!
Gotcha! You heard him!
Give those animals a hand!
We're on it!
[KRILLIN] Just a second, guys!
Ah, fresh air...
thank you, Krillin.
Are those, animals doing okay?
Oh, yeah! I've got a
search and rescue team on it!
[KRILLIN]
They'll be fine!
[OOLONG STRUGGLES THEN LAUGHS]
[OOLONG]
Krillin!
Huh? Whoa!
[OOLONG]
Thanks.
Oh NO!
Bingo!
[NEIZ] What the? That thing
nearly took my head off!
[NEIZ] Darn lizard must be
what set off my scouter.
[KRILLIN] All right, you guys!
We need to move fast...!
Gohan, you and
Icarus head to Korin's
to see if he has
any Senzu Beans!
[KRILLIN] I'll stay here!
I'm going to hide with your Dad,
but we're sitting
ducks until you get back,
so don't waste any time!
Right!
[KRILLIN] And don't forget what
we said about flying, Gohan!
Right! No flying! That's okay.
I've got the Icarus Express!
Right, boy?
Best of luck you
guys! Stay safe.
[GOHAN] Thanks!
Don't worry! We'll be fine!
[KRILLIN] Oh, yeah! Remember to
stay at higher altitudes
so they don't spot you...!
We're counting on you guys!
Right!
It's too dark. I can't
see anything down there!
Good. I don't think he saw us.
Right! Yeah! Let's go, boy!
[GOHAN]
Whoo! Awesome, Icarus...!
I didn't know you
could fly this fast!
[KRILLIN THINKS] Please
don't get caught, Gohan...!
We need those Senzu Beans!
Good job, Icarus! Almost there!
[GOHAN[ Look!
There it is! The tower!
[GOHAN]
Cool! We made it!
[GOHAN] You go down
and get some rest...!
I'll meet you in a just a bit!
[GOHAN]
All right! Here goes!
[GOHAN THINKS] Hang in there,
Dad! I'll be back soon!
Hey! I can see the top! Wow!
[GOHAN] Hello! Master
Korin? Is anybody home?
Well, if it isn't
the son of Goku!
Yeah! I came for some
Senzu Beans, Master Korin!
Can I have some?
Oh you just come barging
in here unannounced, huh?
And now you want
some Senzu Beans?
[KORIN] Well, what exactly
did you bring me?
[GOHAN] But Sir! You have to
give me the Senzu Beans!
They're for my Dad!
[GOHAN] I'm being rude,
aren't I? You're right!
I should have brought a gift!
I'll be right back, Sir!
[YAJIROBE] Hey! Wait up!
Don't leave without these!
What's this?
A bag of Senzu Beans, what else?
Hey, what the...?
I'm the bean daddy
this time! Bean Daddy!
Is that so? Well, who put you
in charge? They're my beans!
[YAJIROBE]
I watered 'em!
Here, Master Korin!
These are yours!
Huh? Oh, well, I guess you
do have pretty good manners.
I guess you can keep them!
[YAJIROBE]
Stop messin' with him...!
You were going to give
him the beans anyway!
Would you shut up!
Thank you!
I really appreciate it, Sir!
It was great seeing both
of you again! Take care!
[KORIN]
See ya later, kid!
[GOHAN]
Bye, bye! Thanks!
Hmm!
Hey, Gohan, catch!
What's this?
Ahh! Another bean! Thanks!
Why on Earth do I let
you live up here?
I dunno. Beats
the heck out of me.
See ya later!
[GOHAN] Icarus!
I'm ready, boy!
We did it!
Now, let's get these Senzu Beans
back to my Dad, on the double!
Mmm! Pretty nice kid. Oh, and
by the way, what's a bean daddy?
Uh, I don't know, but ah,
anyway speaking of
beans let's make some chili.
Keep it up, Icarus!
You're doing great!
Huh? Wow! I can't believe
it's already morning!
How are you doing Goku?
Goku, wake up!
Goku!
Hey! What's all the
racket? I'm alive, okay?
Oh, don't mind me!
Just checking!
After all, there's no sense
in guarding a dead guy, right?
That's right!
Mmm! Man!
[KRILLIN THINKS] Your Dad
needs you, Gohan! Hurry!
[DOORE] This is ridiculous!
I think they're dead!
[NEIZ] As if it
matters what he thinks...!
What matters is
what Lord Cooler thinks!
Come on, boy! Almost there!
Oh, you've really
got it bad, don't you?
Hey, I know! Here!
Take this, boy!
Whoa!
[GOHAN CHUCKLES]
That did the trick!
Good as new!
Got 'em!
Betcha never thought you
could fly this fast, did you?
[GOHAN LAUGHS]
[SALZA] So! Going
somewhere, monkey-boy?
Uh, oh! Icarus! Let's
get out of here, quick!
[DOORE] Let
him have it, Salza!
[DOORE LAUGHS]
[GOHAN YELLS]
[GOHAN] It's okay!
I've got you!
Icarus!
Hey... whatchya got in the
bag there monkey boy?
There... give it here.
Give it!
Alright... that's it.
You're going bye bye kid!
I call this my
can opener attack.
Doore!
Who did that?
[PICCOLO]
That would be me!
A Namek? Out here?
[DOORE] Why isn't that toad on
his own world where he belongs?
[NEIZ]
Frieza blew it up!
[DOORE]
Oh, yeah! Yeah.
Ah, yeah! Piccolo!
[DOORE] It's all over for you,
Namek! You're going to die!
[PICCOLO] Not likely!
I've seen you fight!
I'm going to rip you apart!
[DOORE]
Where'd he go? Huh?
[PICCOLO] Gohan,
what are you doing?
Get those beans
to your dad! And hurry!
[GOHAN] Right!
We'll be right back!
Oh yeah! That's
what you think!
Gohan!
Ha! You missed me!
[SALZA] He was aiming for
Doore, you idiot!
[DOORE]
Move it.
Darn it! I can't...
[DOORE SCREAMS]
Doore!
You're dead!
Have it!
[SALZA]
Excellent, Neiz!
[SALZA] Finish him off!
I'm going after the kid!
Right!
And Neiz make it hurt.
Yes! I'll bet you're feeling
pretty stupid right about now!
Deep fried Namek!
How yummy!
[NEIZ SCREAMS]
[SALZA]
What the?
Neiz! I thought you--
[SALZA]
No way!
[SALZA LAUGHS]
[SALZA]
What the heck is that?
[SALZA LAUGHS]
[SALZA] The Party's
over, Namek!
[SALZA]
Who are you?
My name is Piccolo! You should
never have come to this planet!
[COOLER] Salza!
Leave him to me!
[COOLER] Salza, what are you
waiting for? Go get the kid!
[SALZA]
Yes, my lord!
[PICCOLO] You're
supposed to be dead!
[KRILLIN] Gohan should've
been back by now!
Darn it!
Goku! You've got to hang on!
[GOHAN] Krillin!
Where are you?
[KRILLIN]
In here!
What in the world took so long?
[GOHAN] We got shot down
by those three goons...!
If it wasn't for Piccolo,
we wouldn't even have these...!
There's enough for an army here!
[OOLONG LAUGHS]
Awesome, Gohan!
Looks like we're having
beans for breakfast!
Where's Icarus?
He's not hurt, is he?
[GOHAN] I almost forgot! Icarus!
I need to go find him!
[KRILLIN] Here! Give those to
me! I'll take care of your Dad!
Now, now! Did you really
think you'd gotten away?
Oh, no! What do we do?
We had them! They were
right in our hands! You!
[KRILLIN]
You ruined everything!
I don't believe it!
[OOLONG] Oh, no! Goku? Goku!
Hey, Gohan, catch!
[GOHAN] Thank goodness!
It's still here!
[GOHAN] Here Dad!
Take this! Quick!
A bean! But how?
[GOHAN] There's no time
to explain! Just eat!
Krillin, no!
You jerk!
Kids! They never
know their own limits!
[SALZA] Now it's time to take
care of the sick and wounded!
It must have been a fluke!
[SALZA] I don't see
how a guy like this
could have possibly
killed Frieza!
Huh? What's this?
Impossible...!
I'm picking up a power level
that's going off the scale!
[SALZA] But the
Saiyan was barely alive...!
And the only other
one in there was that pig!
[SALZA] It couldn't be
the pig, could it?
[SALZA] What
the heck's going on?
[SALZA]
It's you!
Goku!
Hang in there! You did
great! I'm proud of you!
Gohan!
[GOKU]
Rest easy, son!
[GOKU] Hurting innocent people
is something I don't tolerate!
[SALZA STAMMERS]
He's healed! But how?
If I were you, I'd get off
of this planet! Trust me!
You don't want any of this!
[COOLER] Oh,
but I do, Saiyan! I do!
[COOLER]
Salza.
Yes! Lord Cooler!
[COOLER] Perhaps you
could do me a little favor.
Tell me, what should
I do with this Namek?
[GOKU GASPS]
Put him down, Frieza!
[SALZA LAUGHS]
This is Frieza's brother
you imbecile! Wake up!
[SALZA]
This is Lord Cooler,
the most illustrious
fighter in the Universe...!
Soon you will be at his mercy!
What mercy?
[EXPLOSION]
[GOKU THINKS]
Piccolo! No!
[COOLER LAUGHS]
[GOKU] You're as twisted
inside as your brother!
Full of hatered! Well, no more!
You've dug your own grave!
Really! Because,
after I kill you,
I'm going to turn this planet
and everyone on it into dust!
No way! Not on my watch!
[GOKU POWERS UP]
Well! Now it's
getting interesting!
I'm glad you're amused!
I am! But I would
like to see the power
you used to destroy my brother!
Then I won't disappoint you!
No one disgraces our family
and lives to tell about it!
Well, well not bad!
Rather impressive, actually!
Frieza! Yes! I can see how he
would have trouble with you!
My brother was a pest!
I would have killed him
myself sooner or later!
He was alway
trying to beat me!
[COOLER] Trying to prove
that he was the best...!
And he definitely had the edge!
But then it happened!
As you know, I'm in the
third transformed state,
but I found a fourth beyond it!
What?
You should feel privileged.
You will be the first
one to witness this form.
First you will see,
then you will die!
[COOLER BEGINS TO POWER UP]
Whoa, man!
He's huge!
[COOLER CHUCKLES]
Yes! Time to die!
[COOLER]
You're mine!
[GOKU BELLOWS]
[COOLER GIVES AN EVIL CHUCKLE]
[COOLER]
I love doing that!
Well, back for more, I see.
Hello!
So this is what the legendary
Super Saiyan is supposed to be?
What a laugh!
[COOLER]
Look at you!
[COOLER LAUGHS]
You couldn't even
detect my movements.
[COOLER] What are
you going to do huh?
No way!
So this is the mighty Super
Saiyan that defeated my brother!
How ridiculous!
Frieza deserved to die if he
got beat by a weakling like you!
I am the supreme
master of this Universe!
I am the great destroyer!
The taker of life!
[COOLER] It is my
will that this planet
and everyone on it
be annihilated!
[OOLONG] What's going on?
The whole planet's shaking...!
We're all going to die!
Goku!
No! Krillin! Gohan!
No! They didn't do
anything wrong! I can't...
[COOLER LAUGHS]
[GOKU BELLOWS]
What's this?
What? What's going on?
He's different! He's changed!
[COOLER] Saiyan insect!
Prepare to be squashed!
Why don't you wake up!
You're hurting people!
What have they done to you?
I can't let you take
your unhappiness
out on other
people anymore!
[COOLER] What are you talking
about? I kill when I want!
[COOLER] The weak die
and the strong survive!
All right, then! We'll
play by your rules, Cooler!
Let's go!
[COOLER LAUGHS]
Now I know why
my brother was killed!
I love it! You're too much!
[COOLER] Sleeping on the
job, Super Saiyan...?
I can gather energy a
lot faster than my brother!
You shouldn't have
taken your eyes off me!
Now die with this planet!
[GOKU ROARS]
[GOKU STRUGGLES]
[COOLER LAUGHS]
[COOLER] Struggle all
you want! It's over...!
That's what you get for
disgracing my family!
You've murdered
millions of innocent people!
[GOKU] Can't let it go on!
[COOLER LAUGHS]
[COOLER] Yes! It is I who
decides who lives and who dies!
[COOLER] All living beings are
mere playthings to me...!
No one can comprehend
my power and cunning!
[COOLER] What?
[GOKU BELLOWS]
[COOLER]
No! It can't be!
Curse you!
[COOLER] Blast that Saiyan!
This beam can't hold me forever!
[COOLER] I'm going to
get off, and when I do,
I'm going to rip
him to pieces! Huh?
[COOLER] It's the star
for this solar system...!
Maybe I'll just
blow that up instead
and let them all freeze
to death in the darkness!
[COOLER] Wait a second...!
I'm heading right for it!
[COOLER] Curse
that Saiyan monkey...!
Why wasn't he destroyed
with the rest of them?
[COOLER] Wait! I remember
now! I remember!
[COOLER] Belay that order...
Frieza's the one in
charge of this quadrant.
Let him clean up his own
mess! He's no threat to us!
[COOLER] I don't believe it!
I could have killed him...!
I let him go!
[COOLER SCREAMS]
[MASSIVE EXPLOSION]
Yes! I did it! With a little
help from the Sun!
[KRILLIN] How ya
feelin' there, champ?
Way to go, Dad!
Well, we all helped!
Even Icarus leant a hand!
Good boy, Icarus!
[OOLONG] So where
in the world is Piccolo?
That's a good question! Huh!
You know Piccolo! He'll show
up when we least expect it!
Yeah, but he was injured!
Hey! That must be him now!
All right! Piccolo!
[SALZA]
Ha! Hello!
[SALZA LAUGHS]
[SALZA] You look like a bunch of
deer caught in the headlights!
[SALZA LAUGHS]
[SALZA]
You lose, suckers!
Now! Die!
I don't see him!
[SLOW LAUGH FROM GOHAN]
[GOHAN] Piccolo! I know you're
there! Come out! Piccolo?
♪ CLOSING SONG ♪