[YOGI] Poor Gareki. He's still
in a foul mood. More than usual.
[TSUKUMO] It doesn't surprise
me. It's only been a week
since he lost the only
family he'd ever known.
[YOGI] I've got it!
Circus is putting on a show.
You and Gareki
should join in!
[NAI] Huh?
[YOGI] See, it takes time to
work your way through the grief.
And what better distraction than
a production? Bye bye, sorrow!
[NAI] Yeah! I'm in!
[NAI] Wow!
[NAI] Gareki. You look
completely different!
[GAREKI] Huh? I guess so.
New suit and all.
[YOGI] What Nai is saying--
at least, what I
think he's saying--
is that you look royally cool!
[GAREKI] Pain in my ass.
Dressing up. Why bother?
No investigation
was conducted.
So why go through
all the trouble?
[YOGI] We're here to support
Team One this time.
Since we happened to be
in the same town anyway,
they asked us to help
out with the show!
[YOGI] Face painting
and sweet treats!
So much awesome!
Right? Back me up here!
[YOGI] By the way,
Tsukumo dear...
Why on Earth did you
agree to wearing that?
[TSUKUMO] I... don't
understand the question.
♪
[NAI] So, Gareki.
Y'having fun?
[GAREKI] Eh? Sure.
[NAI] Gareki is sad because he
lost the people most important
to him. I think you call
people like that... "family"?
I wonder how you become
important to someone else?
[GAREKI] Watch where
you're going, huh?
[GAREKI] Hmm?
[NAI] Somehow, Gareki feeling
sad makes me feel sad.
I guess that makes
Gareki important to me.
How do I become
important to him?
He saved me, which made
me happy--very happy.
And Tsubaki.
She rescued him as well,
and her kindness and
warmth made them family.
[NAI] So does the warmth
come from being kind?
I think it must. Have I been
nice to everyone, every time?
How do I make Gareki
feel warm when he's sad?
[NAI] I remember Karoku
was nice. Was warm. But...
[KAROKU] Best to send the new
guy packin'. You know this.
[NAI] Karoku's words scared me.
Why would he say that?
[NAI] I wonder where Karoku is.
And when I do find him...
What then?
[NAI] Hmm?
[BOY A] Circus is wicked sweet!
[BOY B] Oh man, that's cool!
--He has horns!
--Kid. Tone it down.
[BOY A] Hey, mister.
Do you have horns for real?
[BOY B] Let us touch them!
[BOY A] Yeah, let us touch!
[Yogi laughs]
[YOGI] You're a big hit with
the kids, Gareki! Well done!
[GAREKI] Whatever.
Just get 'em outta my way!
[YOGI] Hey, kids!
I've got candy bars!
Okay, everyone
get in line!
[KIICHI] We don't have the time!
[YOGI] Whoa! Uh...
Kiichi! What's up?
[KIICHI] One of our
high-performance rabbits
malfunctioned and
escaped into the crowd.
I shall allow you
to help search for it.
[YOGI] Sorry. Kinda busy.
And a candy bar for you...
[KIICHI] Listen to me!
This is an emergency!
Its defense protocols
are on the fritz.
It could misread children's
mischief and attack!
[YOGI] Look, now's
really not a good time.
[KIICHI] The security
force cannot keep pace
with the rabbit's capabilities.
And yours truly is the only
member of Team One available.
[TSUKUMO] I'll go.
[YOGI]
What? Uh...
But you're supposed to be
on stage in a little while.
Fine, then. I'll go.
[YOGI] Hey, big sis. I've got
to step away for a bit.
Could you keep an eye
on Nai and Gareki for me?
[IVA] O-lé!
[YOGI] I'm not sure
she was listening.
Uh, well then.
Bye bye, perona!
[BOY A] What's that
a'posed to mean?
[YOGI] Uh, bye bye, perona.
[BOY A] Y'can't leave until
you do that thing for us!
[GIRL A] Why're you leaving?
[BOY B] Do you hate us now?
[YOGI] Of course not! I've got
an important mission is all.
[children start crying]
[NAI] I'll help! I can
hand out the sugar!
[YOGI] Well, the thing is...
I appreciate you wanting
to help, but our difference
in size is rather... Huh?
Gareki, my pal!
[KIICHI] You're late!
[YOGI] Sorry, so sorry.
[KIICHI] What's with all
those marks on your face?
[YOGI] Yeah, that...
took some convincing.
[NAI] Gareki?
He's... gone.
[NAI] Oh. Yogi.
I can't find Gareki.
[NAI] Um. Yogi?
Is something wrong?
[GIRL A] Nyan-perowna's back!
[BOY B] Nyanta!
Wait, are you shorter now?
[BOY A] Your legs
are all saggy.
[GIRL A] Up high!
I'm up high!
[BOY A] Gimme a candy bar!
[BOY B] Candy, please!
[IVA] This is my favorite
part of the show!
[NAI] Miss Iva!
Gareki's missing!
[IVA] Don't you worry.
Gareki's nearby.
Handing out sweet dreams
to all the children in town.
It's one of our
most important jobs.
[DIRECTOR] Finale time.
Let's take another crack
at the love
declaration scene.
Now give us some unbridled
passion. From the top!
[JIKI] My darling!
My manly heart swells
to espy your tender beauty.
Please open the gates to
your heart and let me, uh...
Wait. Wait a second. Sorry.
[DIRECTOR] Ugh! What?
[TSUKUMO] It's unusual for
you to flub a scene, Jiki.
[JIKI] No. I... It's,
uh... Your costume is...
[TSUKUMO] I'll put on my proper
costume before the show.
[JIKI] Yeah. That'd be great.
[Tsukumo winces]
[JIKI] Uh--what's wrong?
[TSUKUMO] It's nothing
to worry about. I think.
[KIICHI] Oh, come on. Where'd
you run off to? Dumb rabbit!
[YOGI] No sign anywhere.
[KIICHI] How hard is it
to find one stupid robot?
Are you even looking
with your eyes?
[YOGI] Yes, Kiichi,
I'm looking.
[KIICHI] You and I took the
same test to make our rank.
Yet you screw up
on a daily basis!
I'd say my doubts are valid.
[YOGI] You keep
bringing up our rank.
Maybe you just suck at
standardized testing.
It doesn't really matter now.
[KIICHI] Yes, it does!
It means that you,
who scored the same on the test
as me, will be seen as my equal!
[YOGI] Kiichi,
stop with the flailing!
[KIICHI] What's
with you, anyway?
Showing sympathy and
hesitating in the field?
Mishandling your power--
[KIICHI] That's exactly the kind
of behavior I'm talking about!
You see one person in trouble
and you turn into a kitten!
And that blinds you to
the needs of the masses!
[YOGI] Yeah, maybe.
I do get sidetracked.
"The masses," huh?
Of course! The bunny-bot!
Its defense parameters are
in total overdrive, right?
That means it'll
try to be on guard
at a place with a
bunch of people.
--The plaza theater!
[TSUKUMO] I hope they've
tracked down the rabbit.
[TSUKUMO] Come in.
[JIKI] Showtime.
You about ready?
[JIKI] On behalf of Team One,
allow me to extend my thanks!
We'll stage the most romantic
play this town has seen!
[TSUKUMO] My analysis of
the text differs from yours.
Let me break it down.
A petulant, overcompensating
General finds his desire
for a beautiful young
Mermaid unreciprocated.
In a fit of inadequacy,
he bottles her up.
signifying his impotence.
[JIKI] Uhh! Wow.
I didn't think o'that!
Tough crowd...
[JIKI] We should go over the
workings of the contraption.
[JIKI] Now, when I
sit down on the bed,
the bottom of the jar
you're in will open.
Bubbles will surge up,
masking your flush to safety.
The mermaid's escape
knocks the socks
off the audience every time.
You'll do fine. So get out
there and break a fin.
What do you say?
[TSUKUMO] Sure.
[KIDS] Shing! Ba-zing! Behold
the manliness! The epic-ness!
You've rubbed this
kitty the wrong way!
[JIKI] Soon, my dear, the
drug I secretly administered
will take effect,
turning you human.
[JIKI] I shant present
you to the king.
Soon enough you'll
be a proper woman.
And then I shall make you
mine on this very bed!
[MAN A] Man, what a lech!
[MAN B] Cold-blooded snake!
[WOMAN A] Poor Mermaid.
Hang in there!
[JIKI] Now seal her in!
Soon you will transform.
And you won't survive
submerged for long.
[JIKI] Do you hear me?
Joining me is the only
chance you have left.
[JIKI] I think I'll wait
for you on the bed.
[RABBIT] The bottom
is about to open, hop.
It's broken, hop?
Time to weld, hop-hop.
[IVA] You did great out there.
[GAREKI] Ah, that bastard!
[NAI] Wait. Gareki?
Not Yogi?
[GAREKI] I'm 'onna kill him.
Tsukumo's play should be drawing
to a close any minute now.
Why don'tcha kick back,
take a load off?
[NAI] I hear... Tsukumo?
[GAREKI] Huh?
[NAI] She's saying something.
But it's so faint.
[GAREKI] What is it?
Your super-hearing pick
something up again?
[NAI] "I can't breathe.
Trap door... won't open."
[TSUKUMO]
What should I do?
I can't just break
through the glass.
The people in the front
rows will be cut to ribbons.
[JIKI] Is she stuck?
[TSUKUMO] Jiki.
[JIKI] I grow tired
of all this waiting.
I'll drag you out
of there if I must!
[JIKI] What the...
A rabbit?
[RABBIT] Attempted vandalism,
hop. Neutralize target, hop.
[MAN A] What is that
rabbit doing here?
[MAN B] Must be a
friend of the Mermaid.
[JIKI] That is a Team One
rabbit. Must be the one
reported malfunctioning.
Stupid heap of junk!
[JIKI] This is bad.
Time is running out!
[KIICHI] Last place to check
is inside the theater!
[YOGI] Was that Iva?
[DIRECTOR] There's got to
be a way to open that thing!
[STAGEHAND] The trapdoor
is welded shut;
it'll take more time to cut
open than she has left!
[DIRECTOR] Miss Iva!
Poor Miss Tsukumo is trapped
inside of the Mermaid tank!
Master Jiki nobly tried
to break her out of it,
only to be stopped by
a Team One Rabbit!
[IVA] Very well, then.
[IVA] All of you: listen up.
You will play your parts
exactly as instructed.
[ALL] What?
But we haven't seen a script
or rehearsed or anything.
[YOGI]
That's gonna leave a mark.
[TSUKUMO] Everyone.
[IVA] It serves you right,
General Jiki!
Surprised? We joined forces
to punish you. I've partnered
with the rabbit and the
Mermaid's brothers three.
[JIKI] Iva?
[GAREKI] Tch.
[YOGI] Ah. Thank the waves,
you're safe! Oh darling sister.
[GAREKI] We became
human for you
and have come to,
uh, rescue you.
[NAI] Hail, little sister!
[YOGI] You accursed scoundrel!
Keep thine distance!
[RABBIT] Hop!
[GAREKI] Now,
return to the castle
with your caring brothers.
[NAI] Hail, little sister!
[RABBIT] Are they helping, hop?
Must be good guys, hop.
[RABBIT] Hop hop!
hop hop! Hop hop...
[KIICHI] And now
the time comes
to wake from your dreams
and thus journey home.
[JIKI] I'll admit, I was
worried there for a moment.
[IVA] But the curtain has
yet to fall, "General."
This is what you get
for abandoning me
to chase floozy Mermaid tail!
[JIKI] Wha? Ah...
[MAN A] That two-timer!
[WOMAN A] Enemy of women!
[IVA] Moron. What
were you thinking,
endangering
Tsukumo like that?
[JIKI] What? Iva, I...
[IVA] And now you'll pay!
Taste my boot, disgusting cur!
[JIKI] No. Iva, wai--!
[IVA] You address me
as "Your Majesty"!
[YOGI] Tsukumo?
Guys? Everyone ok?
[TSUKUMO] Yes, thank you.
I'll be fine.
[YOGI] Well, that's a relief,
huh? With enough time,
even things like this can
be fondly remembered--
[GAREKI] Sorry, Goldilocks.
Won't happen.
Now lemme smack you
around a little bit.
[YOGI] Huh?
Wait, why? Remember?
You already punched me earlier.
Right? Gareki? Ow!
[GAREKI] Whine like a bitch
and I slap you like a bitch.
Be glad I went so easy!
[YOGI] Yeah.
I actually am grateful.
[GAREKI] Huh?
Whaddaya mean?
[YOGI] Well, y'know. You've
been acting so down lately.
I'm glad you're feeling
energetic enough
to bonk my noggin again!
And also, I'm glad we
did the parade together!
[GAREKI] Idiot.
What are you talking about?
[YOGI] It was your first one
ever, right? How did it go?
Did you have fun?
[GAREKI] Are you kidding
me, dude? Never again!
And what the hell's that
"epic manliness" thing
they kept askin' me to do?
[YOGI] The night is still
young, cats and kitten.
I vote that we go out.
And party hearty!
[NURSE A] No fair!
We should be down there,
front and center,
having an awesome time.
[NURSE B] Yeah, and there's
only one doctor to blame for it.
Even though I dare
not speak his name!
[NURSE C] Shhh!
Girls, Formation Alpha!
[BUSINESSMAN A] Goodness,
you are very dedicated
to your work, Dr. Akari.
But there is a show
tonight, isn't there?
You must've received more
than a few invitations!
I would imagine
you're rather popular!
[AKARI] Ah, with the ladies?
When I find the time.
[BUSINESSMAN A] Yes, of course!
[AKARI] Please excuse me, sir.
[NURSE A] You're not popular
with this lady, buster.
Because of you, I missed
the whole production!
[NURSE B] Not all women
are swept off their feet
by money, looks and status,
Mr. Doctor-man!
[NURSE C] Someone oughtta
"find the time" for Dr. Akari,
then humiliate the jerk.
Make him suffer for once.
[AZANA] Ah, Dr. Akari.
[AKARI] Azana. What
happened to your face?
[AZANA] Oh, the patient.
It thinks my bedside manner
could stand to improve.
[AZANA] But the lil' guy seems
to be quite fond of you, Doctor.
[AKARI] That's strange.
I've never shown
the beast an
ounce of kindness.
[AZANA] Oh, right.
Here's the report, sir.
[AKARI] There are no
issues with its feed.
And the condition
of the air is nominal.
However, a greater
variety of fresh plants
will further simulate
its natural habitat.
[AZANA] Doctor?
The, uh, report?
[AKARI] How odd.
Mental note: Further study
may require vivisection.
[AKARI] What is
that horrid stench?
[TSUKITACHI] Smoked Tarunero.
[AKARI] Don't eat it here!
You're stinking up
the entire room!
Just so you're aware:
My tolerance threshold
for your antics can be
measured in microns!
[AKARI] Face-time with you
causes my cells to rupture
and die from stress!
Your existence alone
hinders my vital functions!
[AKARI] Is it too much to ask?
A little peace and quiet?
[AKARI] Go away! Or have I
been speaking too delicately?
[TSUKITACHI] You know,
Doctor, if you took a break
every once in a while, you
wouldn't be so unbearable.
[AKARI] What?
[HIRATO] Standing
can't be comfortable.
I'm sorry, please have a seat.
[AKARI] I'll sit when
I'm damn good and ready!
[TSUKITACHI] Right, right.
Let's just raise
our glasses
and say cheers!
[AKARI] I'm in no
mood for cheers!
[TSUKITACHI]
Down the hatch, then!
[TSUKITACHI] I didn't
mean to get him wasted.
[HIRATO] Yet you kept
filling his glass.
[TSUKITACHI] Yeah, but you
egged him on too, man.
[HIRATO] So?
How did it go then?
[TSUKITACHI] Well. We
managed to shut down
an entire supply route,
which by my count's not too bad.
But that was it. The trail
of clues disappeared.
So yeah. How'd Team Two
like to go to Rinole?
[TSUKITACHI] Come on.
Don't look at me like that.
Just look at it as a chance
to play around in the snow.
It'll be an easy investigation;
just checking on some stuff.
I mean, it's kinda
cold there. But, uhhh...
[TSUKITACHI] Ah,
who am I kidding?
It's arctic,
ball-shriveling cold there.
[TSUKITACHI] But hey, for
the lucky bastards you send,
you could spin this as a
holiday destination experience!
[KIHARU] Whoa. It's freezing,
bro! Let's get this finished up
so we can make a beeline
for somewhere warm!
[KAGIRI] Wait.
Hold on a sec. Yes!
Triggered a ping in an
unexpected location!
[IVA] What's with
all of these photos
of Tsukumo in her
mermaid costume?
[JIKI] Those are
for, uh, publicity!
[IVA] It seems you still need
more lessons beaten into you.
[JIKI] The play is
already over, Iva.
[IVA] Excuse me?
[JIKI] I mean...
Your Majesty.