[HIRATO]
A poison aping death.
[TSUKUMO] Captain...
[HIRATO] My sincerest apologies
for the unseasonable shock.
[HIRATO] She'll be fine.
I am Airship Two Captain Hirato.
National Defense Agency, Circus.
I shall return
shortly to tender
a more formal act
of contrition.
[OLD WOMAN A] Circus.
[YUKKIN] Yukkin?
Yukkin! Yukkin!
[YUKKIN] Yukkin,
yukkin, yukkin.
[KIICHI] Kindly let these
impossible creatures
log your voice print.
Whatever comes to mind.
[NAI] Oh. Um...
Hello there?
[GAREKI] Rabbit stew.
[GAREKI] So I can say
whatever I--? I hate you, Yogi.
[RABBIT] Voiceprint
registered, hop.
[JIKI] Okay, then. Allow me to
welcome you both to Airship One.
[KIICHI] First order
of business.
Making sense of this mess. Feel
free to dive in, mops-first.
[KIICHI] I want this place
looking ship-shape again
before the captain returns.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you expect us
to dust off the good
china for you?
Blame the dolts with
Airship Two. They're hardly
a fair representation
of Circus hospitality.
[NAI] Okay?
[GAREKI] We'll have it
done before you can blink.
[KIICHI] I'll be
pleased to see it done
before I develop
crow's feet.
[JIKI] Where does
she get the energy?
There's no reason we
need to taunt them.
[JIKI] So, Nai I have my
head fairly wrapped around.
[JIKI] Gareki, on the other
hand... No family records.
No paper trail leading
to his stint in Karasuna.
[JIKI] Wait, a human
trafficking ring?
Could... Could that be
the same freighter
Hirato and Tsukitachi
ran aground?
[GAREKI] Next time,
I'm keeping my mouth shut.
[RABBIT] Hop. Hop. Hop.
Hop. Hop. Hop. Hop. Hop.
[NAI] What's the matter?
[RABBIT] My fur is all matted
from working outdoors, hop.
[GAREKI] What? Thought
you were state-of-the-art.
They couldn't design ya to
keep from gettin' fuzzballs?
[NAI] I'll brush 'em out!
[RABBIT] Thank you so much, hop.
That feels wonderful, hop.
[GAREKI] Things you just
don't think you're gonna see
when you wake up
in the morning.
[GAREKI] Fine.
I give up.
We couldn't have this place
clean if we had a week.
[GAREKI] Yo. Who else
needs a brushing?
[RABBITS] Hop!
Hop, hop, hop, hop, hop!
[KIICHI] What?
[NAI] Oh, Kiichi.
Look, we're almost finished.
[KIICHI] These creatures are
not your personal maid service!
[GAREKI] Maybe not. But no
harm lettin' 'em help, right?
[TSUKITACHI]
Hello, all. Miss me?
[NAI] I heard they
found Tsukumo!
[TSUKITACHI]
Yes, she's fine.
[NAI] Hurray!
Woo-hoo!
[TSUKITACHI] But Yogi's still
catching up on his rest,
so I think it's for the best
if you boys stay with us
a little longer. If you
like, though, I'm happy
to answer any questions
you might have.
[GAREKI] Yeah I got one for ya.
How's Tsubame doing?
She's hangin' in
there like a trouper.
Asks about you constantly too.
[GAREKI] Yeah, well.
That's good news.
'Course, under our protection,
she's not exactly free as air.
There's a whole slew of
restrictions. For her trouble,
though, Circus shoulders the
burden of her grandpa's bills.
[GAREKI] What?
[TSUKITACHI] Oh, she was
all about that detail.
Said in so many words it freed
his mysterious benefactor
from having to
shell out more cash.
[GAREKI] Yeah. That's good.
Real good. For everyone.
[NAI] Are you...?
Moving on, then. Exactly how
tricked out is this ship?
[TSUKITACHI] Ooh, a
weapons enthusiast!
Hey, let me give you the grand
tour tomorrow and you'll see.
[JIKI] Uh, hello! Very
unqualified civilian, sir!
[TSUKITACHI] How else is he
going to get qualified?
The mission I have in mind
happens to play up the origin
of our bracelets, so these two
have a vested interest.
[JIKI] We don't even
have a clear idea
of our target yet, sir!
Worst case scenari--
[TSUKITACHI] If we can't protect
them, what the hell good are we?
Kiichi agrees.
[KIICHI] Well, naturally,
sir. If Airship Two
can keep them alive,
this'll be a walk in the park.
[TSUKITACHI] Dig in, boys!
Tomorrow's field trip
will be epic!
[JIKI] Okay, see, Captain?
If you call it that,
it sounds like we
don't have work to do!
[JIKI] This is
just a formality.
Since it's our first
mission together and all,
I need to see how
the two of you move.
[JIKI] Let's start
with running away
and I'll do my
best to catch you.
[GAREKI] No prob.
[GAREKI]
How hard can it be?
Guy got his ass handed
to him by a rabbit.
[JIKI] Great.
Ready when you are.
[JIKI] Let me explain
something to you, my friends.
[JIKI] So far the enemy's
been holding back.
At full bore, you won't
stand a chance.
Only naïve idiots rely
on luck. Understand?
[JIKI] Let's be real
about your function here.
You're a scapegoat--a pawn
in the game for Nai's fate.
[JIKI] If you care
about staying alive,
you might want to take stock.
Maybe go back home,
wherever that is.
[JIKI] If not...
Enjoy the field trip.
[JIKI] Enjoy the field trip.
[RABBIT] Where are
you going, hop?
[RABBITS]
Hop! Hop! Hop! Hop!...
[TSUKITACHI] Why do you want
to talk to Jiki? What happened?
[NAI] I just, uh...
I... I don't want
Gareki to die!
[TSUKITACHI] Uh...
Slow down there, champ.
Back up to the beginning.
[NAI] Okay. It's just, this
seems like it's all about me.
And he...
[TSUKITACHI] You feel
guilty that everyone's
getting caught up in trying
to protect you, yeah?
Mm hmm.
[TSUKITACHI] It's the price
we pay for the benefits
you give, kiddo. Think how many
varugas you've reeled in for us.
That amounts to a
lot of lives saved.
[TSUKITACHI] So if you start
to feel bad about using us
to find Karoku, don't.
We do things for each other
and sometimes a little
ugliness goes down.
Doesn't mean it's your fault.
[NAI] Well, yeah. Except that I
actually asked Gareki about it.
He's only here because of me.
It feels like if something
happens to him, it is my fault.
[TSUKITACHI] Where would you
go right now, if you could?
Where do you think Gareki
would go, if he could?
[TSUKITACHI] It's a hard
world to make a home in.
Moreso after seeing the things
you've seen. But listen.
It doesn't mean you don't
deserve happiness.
Just that it'll be a
bit harder to come by.
[NAI] Would be nice
to be home. To be happy.
An admirable goal to have.
And maybe in some bizarre way,
this is how it has
to happen for you.
You feel guilty
because you care.
And if you care,
chances are, you need him.
[NURSE C] No, stop!
Please, sir! It isn't worth it!
[YOGI] Let go, I've got
somewhere to be!
Just make up an excuse
for me or somethi--!
[AKARI] Back in bed, damn you!
[NURSE C] Oh, thank goodness!
[YOGI] Come on! Gareki
and Nai have been taken in
by the crazies on Airship One.
You have any idea
how they'll be treated?
[AKARI] Airship One
deployed yesterday.
You won't be able to catch up.
[YOGI] Deployed where? Vint?
Your new friends have been
declared essential. I take that
as a sign that your colleagues
are warming up to them.
[YOGI] No!!
[JIKI] Vint is home to a high
concentration of rare
and endangered species. The
government cordoned it off
as a wildlife reserve. But in
spite of the sanctions, a lot
of critters are still
getting poached.
Trouble is, so are
the poachers.
[KIICHI] Their eyes are
glazing over, Jiki.
You lost them at "endangered."
Essentially, boys: looky, no
touchy; stay out of the way.
[GAREKI] Oh, hey.
[AZANA] Never introduced
myself back in Rinole.
Hi, my name is Azana.
[NAI] Your face.
What's wrong with it?
[AZANA] These?
Oh, they're nothing.
Our lab animals tend
to get a little frisky;
they think of me as
their scratching post.
[KIICHI] Stifle the
small talk, gentlemen.
I believe we still have an
investigation to get started.
[JIKI] I recommend we
split into two groups.
Each group takes one of you Room
of Life folks as its guide.
[TSUKITACHI] Good.
Gareki, you're with me.
We can chat about
artillery and whatnot.
[GAREKI] Cool.
[NAI] Yeah!
[JIKI] Sorry, Nai.
You're mine.
[Nai yells]
[KIICHI] Jiki! You forgot
your guide, you moron!
[JIKI] I have no problem writing
someone off who isn't worth
my time, but I'll be damned
if they'll do that to me.
[TAMON] There's definitely a
correlation between the number
of poachers found murdered and
the decrease in animal deaths.
[AZANA] Hello there!
[TAMON] Cute, huh?
He got that wound
from someone trying
to take his pelt.
[TSUKITACHI] How'd he escape?
[AZANA] The poacher got killed.
[TSUKITACHI] Who found him?
[TAMON] Me. Well,
me and Murano did.
Interesting. It's good to see
the little fella's okay, though.
[TSUKITACHI]
What's the haps?
Get any sleep last night?
[GAREKI] Not really.
[TSUKITACHI] So.
About our bracelets.
They incorporate living cells
from the creatures indigenous
to this place. Vint has a most
unforgiving environment.
Short on food,
sunlight, fresh water.
The various animals that call
this little slice o' heaven home
had a rough job
adapting for survival.
Over time, they learned to
metabolize energy sources
in the most efficient
way imaginable.
They evolved a rate
of cellular regeneration
unknown anywhere else.
[TSUKITACHI] This produces
what we call Incuna.
A cell that's
nearly omnipotent.
Which Circus uses to
rather dazzling effect.
Observe.
[GAREKI] All that
from a single cell.
[TSUKITACHI] Yep. But its powers
don't come without a price.
[GAREKI] Huh?
[TSUKITACHI] An Incuna's power
is far from straightforward.
Handled inexpertly, it can,
among other things,
knock you on your ass.
See, Circus cherry-picks its
operatives from those in the
general populace genetically
inclined to wield such power.
Even then, years of
training are required.
[ISOSA] The poachers' remains
were found right around here.
[KIICHI] Judging from
the circumstances,
I think it's safe to say
these were varuga attacks.
[ISOSA] A frightening
possibility.
[KIICHI] Strange they
should target poachers
specifically, though. They're
not usually so discriminating.
[NAI] Jiki.
Something's nearby.
[JIKI] Aw.
It's only a moss lizard.
[NAI] That's not what I heard.
[ISOSA] Murano, don't!
[MURANO] Kiri, please! They're
not poachers! They're with me!
[NAI] Yeah, that would be it.
[ISOSA] It's very
skittish around people.
Poor thing was almost
killed by poachers.
[MURANO] Aw, son of a--!
Kiri! Calm down!
[ISOSA] Kiri!
[MURANO] Damn it, come on!
Why do you have to
be so predictable?
[KIICHI] Please.
Spare me the show.
You've known how this would
end for a long time now.
[KIICHI] And I'm sorry.
But it's in our job description
to be "predictable."
We're here for a reason and
that's all there is to it.
[MURANO]
Kiri! Run away!!
[TSUKITACHI] Huh. Guess
the gang's hit pay dirt.
[GAREKI] What does that mean?
Don't worry, son. Nai is being
very well taken care of.
[MURANO] Kiri!
[JIKI] Nai! Move!
[NAI] Yogi?
[YOGI] Einsam Zelle!
[MURANO] Kiri!
[YOGI] Close, huh?
You alright?
[NAI] Mm hmm.
[MURANO] What was
I supposed to do?
[MURANO] She was dying.
The drug was her only hope.
I had no choice.
[MURANO] Yes, the
price was high.
But I'm sworn to
protect these creatures.
[MURANO] Not just Kiri.
All of them.
I wanted the power
to save lives!
[JIKI] I want details as to
how you obtained the drug.
[MURANO] My contact was
anonymous. But he...
He supposedly worked under
Akari, so I trusted him.
[JIKI] How conveniently vague.
But that's all right.
Perhaps an interrogation
will bring things into focus.
[ISOSA] No, please! It's not
like he's a bad person!
He only wanted to help!
[YOGI] This sucks.
[NAI] Yogi?
[KIICHI] I shall be swift
in ending your misery.
[KIICHI] This sacrifice
will not be in vain.
The Scythe of Castigation
will vanquish
the evil which
plagues your soul.
[YOGI] Yeah. Sucks.
[GAREKI] Wha--Yogi?
[YOGI] Gareki!
That's, like, the very first
time you've ever used my name!
[GAREKI] Huh?
[YOGI] So you really do care?
Gah! I thought you hated me!
But it turns out
you've just been
playing it close
to the vest!
[GAREKI] Wait, wait, wait.
You're nuts; this wasn't
the first time.
What the hell are you on?
[YOGI] Uh huh! Was too!
[GAREKI] Knock it off! I've
used your name lots of times!
Like back in Rinole, when you
went all berserker on me--
[YOGI] I never properly
apologized for that, did I?
Oh, god, I'm so sorry.
[GAREKI] Look, whatever.
The important thing's you're
okay now. You are okay, right?
[YOGI] Never better!
Which means you guys
can come back home to
cozy ol' Airship Two!
[YOGI] Good to be back!
[SHEEP] Baa!
Welcome home.
[SHEEP] Baa.
[NAI] Good to be back.
Come on, man. Say it.
The super secret password.
[GAREKI] Good to be back.
[SHEEP] Welcome home.
[NAI] Tsukumo!
[YOGI] Jiki, hey.
What're you--?
[JIKI] I've been
given orders to stay
with Nai and Gareki
for a while.
[JIKI] Good to be here.
[KAROKU] How do you suppose
he's getting on out there?
[SERVANT A]
Uh... Well, I'd say...
[KAROKU] That's good.
Thank you.
[SERVANT A] This sucks.
I can feel Lady Luck
giving me the stink eye
every time I'm near him.
[SERVANT B] His
condition's actually been
pretty stable lately,
hasn't it?
[SERVANT A] For now, yeah,
but it's only a matter of time.
Waste of resources
if you ask me.
[NAI] Can I ask you a question?
Like a... kind of personal one?
[GAREKI] What?
[NAI] Where would
you go if you could?
[NAI] Come on. Where?
Where? Where? I wanna know!
[GAREKI] Shut up! Damn!
[GAREKI] Okay. Weird.
For a second there, it was like
he could see right through me.
[GAREKI] Yeah, well, screw that!
I'm a useless piece of crap.
No point in broadcasting it.
A piece of crap that,
every now and then,
stupidly feels like he
can make a difference.
"Where would I go if I could?"
It's not about "could,"
it's about should, in which
case the answer is nowhere.
[YOGI] Come on,
man. Say it.
[GAREKI] "Home." What
does that even mean?
[NAI] Know where'd
I'd go, Gareki?
Somewhere we could
all live together.
And if we find Karoku,
he could come too! You'll see.
[NAI] I'm gonna make it happen.
It'll be awesome!
[GAREKI] Will you please stop
flappin' your gums?
[AKARI] Well, nurse.
It seems our patient is looking
a bit pale, wouldn't you say?
[TSUKITACHI] What do you care?
The room's clean, isn't it?
[KIICHI] The rabbits
were not theirs to use.
[TSUKITACHI] Yeah, yeah.
Here, have an éclair.
[KIICHI] You're amazing!
[TSUKITACHI]
Jiki! Snack time!
[KIICHI] Oh, these
are wasted on him.
I'll take his share,
thank you very much.