[YOGI] Gareki!
[YOGI] I'll be
right back! Watch Nai!
[NAI] Wha... I...
[YOGI] Please.
Don't be dead!
[YOGI] Ga...
[YOGI] Gareki, no...
[IVA] Krone Saphir.
[IVA] These stones
shine at my behest,
banishing evil to oblivion.
I am known as
Queen of the Crown.
National Defense
Agency Operative.
Iva: Circus Airship Two.
And those who turn
away from my love
rush to their own fall.
[YOGI] Thanks, big sis!
Uh--
[IVA] Nice going!
[IVA] Slowpoke!
Damn right "thanks, big sis!"
[IVA] You cool to get up, kid?
[YOGI] No! Don't push
yourself! Take it slow.
Just tell me where
it hurts worst.
Feel wonky? Like you might
blow chunks or something?
Oh, man. Oh, man. You must've
been scared out of your mind!
It's all my fault; I should've
been on top of things!
Please find it in your
heart to forgive me!
[GAREKI] Will you get
the hell off me, please?
I'm trying to wrap my head
around what just happened!
And stop snotting on me!
[IVA] Give him some air, spaz.
[YOGI] What are you
even doing here, Iva?
[IVA] Meh. I was chasing
a varuga from Gaven, but...
He got away.
The slippery little bastard.
So. I thought "home,"
but whatevs.
The possesor showed up en
route and I couldn't resist.
I had a bit of extra
steam to blow off.
[GAREKI] The possessor?
[IVA] A varuga in beast form.
[GAREKI] I see.
[IVA] Ah. Men's faces wearing
that look do nothing for me.
I need to ogle
something adorable.
Tskumo's here with
you guys, right?
[AKARI] He'll be okay.
Just a minor contusion.
[NAI] Contu... what?
[AKARI] It's a bruise.
Nothing to worry about.
[NAI] I hope Gareki
and Yogi are all right.
I shouldn't have
wandered off on my own.
[AKARI] Correct,
but this isn't your fault.
We were attacked, plainly.
This would've
happened either way.
[AKARI] Why did it target
Gareki and not Nai, I wonder.
Neither of them
have varuga blood
in their systems,
according to our tests.
[YOGI] Doctor Akari,
I presume?
[NAI] Oh, no! Gareki!
[IVA] Not what it looks like.
He was too slow on his feet.
So I helped.
[AKARI] Marvelous.
She's here.
[IVA] Start giving me lip,
doc, and I'll "help" you.
[YOGI] Tried to tell
her Gareki'd prefer
me giving him a
piggyback, but...
[GAREKI] Somebody,
please, kill me.
[AKARI] Well,
I don't see anything
that would make me
suspicious. But...
It's probably best we let Iva
take you back to the ship.
[NAI] Gareki.
I'm sorry...
[GAREKI]
Huh? Why's that?
[NAI] 'Cause I...
[GAREKI] S'alright.
You still in one piece?
[NAI] Uh-huh.
[AKARI] Let's get this
assignment back on track
and hope for no further
interruptions, shall we?
[AKARI] There must
be something here
to shed a little
light on Karoku.
[NAI] Ka...
Karoku?
[YOGI] Oh, wow.
I'm guessing this
is where the two of
you used to live?
[AKARI] Leave no
stone unturned. Yogi?
[YOGI] Right.
[KAROKU] Hey.
Look in my eyes.
We good?
[NAI] Good, yes!
[KAROKU] Atta boy.
[NAI] He's warm.
Like the sun.
[KAROKU] Look at you.
[UNDERLING A] Master Karoku,
sir, you're needed below.
[KAROKU] If I touch
this light...
Would its warmth help
me find my tears?
[KAROKU] Coming!
[ELESKA] Unacceptable!
[URO] A valid observation,
but please understand.
Circus is protecting him.
[ELESKA] My Karoku is all
about this little Nai nobody.
I wanted him brought
here as a surprise!
You don't understand what
it's like with him, Uro.
All he does is stare at
me with that blank look.
[URO] My lady, do not
doubt that he cares.
[URO] Look at you;
in the bloom of youth.
What man isn't all desire
for you? He's simply nervous.
[ELESKA] Sycophant! You say
what you're paid to say!
You have no idea!
I need him to yearn for me!
I want him to lose all control!
[ELESKA] Talk to me, please!
What makes a man tick?
[URO] Every man is different.
I can't really say.
[AKARI] Not a scrap
of anything useful.
[YOGI] According to Nai,
their living situation
was pretty
straightforward.
That fair to say?
[NAI] Hey. There's a bug.
[YOGI] Oh, yeah?
[YOGI] Is that important?
[AKARI] Perhaps.
Move this rock.
[YOGI] Okay...
Jeepers. Good call.
[IVA] Hooray!
Tsukumo!
[YOGI] Hooray!
Lunch!
[YOGI] Ho, ho! Are you
yankin' my chain with this?
Talk about a feast
fit for a king!
[IVA] This is just...
lovely, dear.
[YOGI] Tsukumo, you
have outdone yourself!
[AKARI] This isn't a picnic.
We need to move along.
Wolf it down, folks.
[IVA] Oh, c'mon!
It's somethin' we call
stopping to smell the roses!
This li'l vixen works hard
to tempt our palates!
Isn't that right, Tsuku-Tsuku?
[TSUKUMO] Iva.
[NAI] Gareki. Has the
pain gotten better?
[GAREKI] Less talking.
More eating.
[GAREKI] You guys
dig up anything?
[YOGI] Matter of fact,
we did: a notebook.
Couldn't really
make heads or tails
of what's inside it, though.
Looked like a bunch
of crazy-person math--you know,
just weird, squiggly symbols.
Then again, numbers
aren't really my thing.
[YOGI] But hey.
Dr. Akari seemed captivated.
[GAREKI] Great.
[GAREKI] Hey.
I need a favor.
[SHEEP A] Baa. Welcome home.
[SHEEP B] Baa. Welcome home.
[HIRATO] Good to be back.
[NAI] No way!
I'm coming, too!
[YOGI] Ah. Capitán.
[GAREKI] Like hell
you are, dude...
[YOGI] Thanks for
pickig' up.
[NAI] Don't go!
[YOGI] So, yeah. We're just
about to leave Rainbow Forest.
Thing is, we're
not all that far
from Karasuna,
where Gareki's from.
He's asking us to drop
by a place he knows.
[GAREKI] Damn it all.
[YOGI] So that's okay?
[IVA] He's not on the phone!
Stop faking me out!
You're cool with this?
[IVA] Hello? Possessor
attack? Like, minutes ago?
[HIRATO] Precisely
why Yogi's in tow.
[HIRATO] He stays with them,
you and Tsukumo escort
the research team back to
base. Akari's there, yes?
Put him on.
[YOGI] 'Scuse me, Doctor.
Captain Hirato wants a word.
He'd like to say thanks.
[AKARI] All part of the job.
He can save his breath.
[HIRATO]
How extraordinarily mature.
[YOGI] Huh? I know
he's blunt;
I'm not gonna say
that to his face.
And no, sir, I'm not telling
him he's adorable either!
Don't you pull the "direct
order" card on me, sir!
Oh, no! If you
want to pick a fight
between you and the doc,
I am not playing referee!
[HIRATO] So, that's that.
[TSUKITACHI] Well, this
sucks. I'm not a fan
of being in your debt.
[YOGI] Good news, Nai. The Boss
said you can come with us!
[GAREKI] He's just
gonna get under our feet!
[YOGI] He's got separation
anxiety; take it easy on him.
[GAREKI] Huh?
[GAREKI] Fine. Whatever.
[NAI] Yay!
[YOGI] And there
was much rejoicing!
[YOGI] This is awesome;
it's not every day
I get to be a tourist, you know.
[GAREKI] Man, don't announce it.
Unless you wanna get mugged.
[NAI] That looks fun!
[YOGI] Check it out!
Me and that leather bracelet
were made for each other!
I'm gonna play.
[GAREKI] Really?
[YOGI] What the--?
Come on!
Aw, seriously?
[GAREKI] Give it here.
Check it.
[YOGI] Whoa!
You are a god!
[sound of three
more shots fired]
[YOGI] Wha--?
So are we leavin' or...?
[NAI] Gareki?
[YOGI] Hey!
Where's the fire?
[WOMAN'S VOICE] Gareki!
[GAREKI] Tsu... Tsubame.
[TSUBAME] You're back.
After all this time.
[GAREKI] What's up?
Why the tears?
[TSUBAME] I...
think I... probably...
killed someone.
A lot of someones.
[TSUBAME] I didn't really
think you'd left. I couldn't.
Figured you were just
out and about, y'know?
[TSUBAME] You realize
it's been over two years
since we've seen you.
Why? I mean...
[YOGI] So. You guys
go back quite a ways.
What, were you,
like, classmates, or...?
'Cause you don't
really look alike.
Sort of, uh, you know, rules
out sister, so... Girlfriend?
[TSUBAME] Ew, grody, no!
I've been saving myself
for a doll-eyed,
chubby-cheeked man of steel!
[YOGI] Okay...
So. Not Gareki.
[GAREKI] How's Yotaka?
[TSUBAME] He, uh...
doesn't know about my thing.
Blackouts. He's not stupid.
He knows something's not right.
[GAREKI] Well.
You guys are twins.
Might as well have a direct
link into each other's cortex.
[NAI] Why do you
think you killed them?
[YOGI] Nai!
[TSUBAME] I don't know.
I've been having
these blackout episodes
more and more lately, but...
The more they happen,
the less any of it makes sense.
[TSUBAME] I wake up
in strange places.
Sometimes there's blood on
my clothes, or my hands.
I never remember
anything, though. Ever.
[TSUBAME] But yesterday
was different.
[YOTAKA] Party's over!
What the hell are you people
doing with my sister?
[TSUBAME] Yotaka, no!
Stop! It's Gareki!
[YOTAKA] You're kiddin' me.
[YOTAKA] Well, damn.
Glad you're still alive, man.
[YOGI] Not to be that guy,
but should we really
be sleeping here?
[GAREKI] She said the dude
who lived here took off.
He's not coming back.
[YOGI] Yeah, uh... That's
kind of what bothers me.
Think about it, Gareki.
This village is
practically deserted.
Can't have always
been that way.
[GAREKI] Yeah, well,
whaddya gonna do?
[YOGI] So no one actually
answered my question...
What's the story
with you three?
[YOGI] I'm just... curious.
[GAREKI] Lemme think.
I was about eight, I guess.
My folks sold me off.
[GAREKI] I got grouped
with some other kids.
We were all
auctioned off as a lot.
[GAREKI] There was this cargo
ship we all got stowed on.
I wasn't very popular.
Guess I instinctively rub
some people the wrong way.
I was the runt, you see;
so that more or less
singled me out for the bullies.
They used to tie me up,
make off with my rations,
pretty much every day.
Good thing, too.
Turns out there was something
mixed into the food.
Everyone started
acting like animals.
[GAREKI] I was weak,
but I was alive.
Then a woman named
Tsubaki saved me.
[GAREKI] She pitied me.
Took me in without a thought.
Tsubame and Yotaka were her
siblings. Younger, of course.
Long story short, she
loved the wrong person.
Wound up getting killed.
I never met the guy.
But trust me.
He's a dead man when I do.
[GAREKI] What?
[YOGI] You need a hug.
[GAREKI]
'Scuse me?
[YOGI] I'm all that
stands between
you and a heart of stone.
I need to show you there's
still a chance for love--
[GAREKI] And I need to
show you some boundaries!
[NAI] Stop fighting!
I don't like it when you fight!
[YOGI] Hug it out, bro!
[GAREKI] Both of you.
Shut the hell up!
[TSUBAKI]
You'll fit right in.
My brother and sister
are just about your age.
[TSUBAKI] You
remind me of them.
That's why I couldn't
leave you there.
[TSUBAKI] Don't worry,
it's from him.
Free medicine is
free medicine, right?
We needed this.
[GAREKI] Why do you
trust this guy?
You barely know him!
[TSUBAKI] He took me out of that
horrible sweatshop, remember?
And he's taking care of
grandpa's medical bills.
[TSUBAKI] Besides, it's just
a dietary supplement.
All he wants in exchange is
routine data on the twins.
[GAREKI] You don't
trust him, do you?
I can hear it in your voice.
Something's not right
about this and you know it.
[TSUBAKI] Look, I don't earn
enough to make ends meet, okay?
We have to eat
one way or another.
They're my responsibility.
You all are.
I'm trying my best,
Gareki. Please.
[GAREKI] Whatever.
Nobody asked you to try.
Stop acting like you're
in this by yourself.
I can earn, too! Just stop
seeing him! He's no good!
[GAREKI] I know a crooked son
of a bitch when I see one.
[YOGI] Shh. Outside.
It's Tsubame.
[GAREKI] So, what, you've been
keeping watch or something?
[YOGI] Um. Well.
[GAREKI] You've been on
high alert since she told us
about her blackouts,
haven't you?
[YOGI] Sorry. I...
[GAREKI] Don't. I get it.
[GAREKI] How the hell did this
happen to her? Why? When?
What am I talking about?
It's the medicine. Has to be.
[GAREKI] Which means the man who
killed Tsubaki is still around.
[GAREKI] Hey.
Is there a cure?
That's what I thought.
[NAI] He's been...
drawn on.
[GAREKI] No he hasn't,
he's been... Oh, crap.
These marks.
I know these marks.
They're exactly like the ones
we found on Tsubaki's body.
[GAREKI] I knew it.
The son of a bitch is back.
[GAREKI'S VOICE]
I never met the guy.
But trust me.
He's a dead man when I do.
A dead man when I do...
[GAREKI] Yotaka!
[TSUKITACHI] Welcome back, doc.
Bring us any tacky souvenirs?
[AKARI] I was there
for work, not pleasure.
[TSUKITACHI] That a fact? What's
in your breast pocket, then?
[AKARI] It's called
a Flower Rabbit.
[TSUKITACHI]
Aw, c'mon! No fair!
[AKARI] Life isn't fair!