[MAN] I'll have
to admit, I'm surprised.
I'd never expected the
much vaunted Circus
to be staffed with
such young agents.
[HIRATO] Not quite the attitude
I'd expect from the man
who became CEO of the
Lindain Group by age 42.
Seems rather counter-intuitive
in my opinion.
[MAN] Ha!
You're a smart one, aren't you?
[HIRATO] Indeed. Now what is the
business you wish to discuss?
Yes, well. It seems the
Gald Company has a secret.
They're making things
that go bump in the night.
[YOGI] Behold, the Floating
Iron Castle. Vantnum!
We almost never
get a day off.
So let's make this
one count, huh?
[YOGI] Hey, Nai!
You pick the first stop.
[NAI] Oh, umm... Hmm...
[JIKI] So, you guys...
[YOGI] Did you have
a suggestion, Jiki?
[JIKI] Actually,
I'm going off on my own.
[YOGI] What?
But, "Boys' Day Out."
[JIKI] I'm hitting up a few
hobby shops. Gonna be a while.
[YOGI] Jiki!
[YOGI] Prepare yourselves
for the piece de resistance!
[YOGI] The promised land!
[GAREKI] No way in hell.
[YOGI] Wha? Huh?
Nai's having a great time!
[GAREKI] Quit it.
[YOGI] Take a page
from his book!
[GAREKI] Dude, I'm serious!
Would you just shut up?
[YOGI] I-I can't breathe!
[GAREKI] Get
off'a me. Damn it!
Screw you! And Nyanperona! You
need to grow up and recognize
that this "cat" chump is just
a grown man in a fur suit!
[YOGI] Quiet. None o' that!
You lying liar from Liartown!
Nyanperowna is a
real living creature!
And not just some
guy in a fur suit!
[YOGI] Well, that
was a nightmare!
[YANARI] Hey.
[YOGI] Oh, hi there young one!
We were just discussing how
Nyanperowna is totally real.
[YOGI] Uh...?
[YANARI] You left behind
your credit card receipt. ZZA.
These digits are
exclusively used
by the National Defense Agency.
And after hearing your
outburst in the store,
I have deduced that you, sir,
are the one inside Nyanperowna!
[YOGI] Ah! From the
mouths of babes..
[GAREKI] So what's
your angle? Snotty brat.
[YANARI] Takes one to
know one. I'm Yanari.
[NAI] Yanari? Hi.
[YANARI] I'm trying
to find a pasta place.
Blue roof, black gate?
If you want Nyanperona's
"secret identity"
to remain a secret, you'll
help me find that place.
[JIKI] To the untrained eye,
there are no subtleties in soil.
But I know otherwise. There is
more than enough to admire here.
And I'm not just
talking about dirt!
[AZANA] Pardon me, Doctor.
[AKARI] Azana.
It seems like you have
more injuries
every time we meet.
[AZANA] Maybe, I've got
some good news though.
Things in Vint are
nice and quiet again.
[AKARI] Good. And I hear the
poachers have been apprehended.
[AZANA] That's...
That's really great! So...
Did you hear anything
from Hirato?
[AKARI] What about Hirato?
[AZANA] Uh... I forgot. He gets
on your nerves. So... yeah.
I was just wondering if he
mentioned finding some leads?
[AKARI] I understand
your suspicions, I do.
But there are no traitors
in the Research Tower!
[HIRATO] The Vint situation
proved otherwise.
We've not yet determined
the identity of the man
who claimed to work
for you, Doctor.
However... Someone is
leaking intel, without a doubt.
[AKARI] Not yet. He hasn't
found a single thing.
[MAN] Admittedly,
I have no proof.
But they have an uncommonly
high employee turnover rate.
There's more. When
those employees leave,
they tend to die from odd
accidents. Illnesses.
Or they just disappear entirely.
And this part doesn't leave
the room, understand?
They're bad news.
Just the other day,
Palnedo hosted a party at
a Gald Company facility.
A friend of mine was
invited to the event,
and now he's gone missing.
[HIRATO] I understand.
And shall see to it.
We'll make sure each and every
rat goes down with the ship.
[YOGI] Shing! Behold the
epic manliness! Ba-zing!
You've rubbed this
kitty the wrong way!
[YOGI] National
Defense Agency, Circus.
Airship Two,
Combat Personnel, Yo--
Nyanperowna!
[YOGI] Mee-yow!
[YANARI] Yeah, no.
It's only half as cool without
the Nyanperowna outfit.
But I did it special
just for you.
[NAI] There's somebody
looking at us.
[GAREKI] All right.
You got a problem, chief?
Now take your head off
so we can see you.
[RISSUN] Uh, I, uh...
[YOGI] Gareki, stop!
How could you?
And in front of the children!
Their hopes! Their dreams!
[RISSUN] Hi! I'm Rissun!
[YOGI] You're the city of
Vantnum's adorable mascot!
[RISSUN] And official
guide to our lovely town!
[NAI] Hi there! Is there
a pasta shop that has
a blue roof and, uh, black gate?
My friend wants to find it!
[YOGI] We couldn't even
track it down online.
[RISSUN] Oh, that sounds like
the place over in District E-22!
[YANARI] Really?
[RISSUN] The city of Vantnum
thanks you for coming,
and hopes you have
a memorable stay!
[NAI] Thanks again,
Mr. Squirrel guy!
[YANARI] Nai. So, uh,
earlier with the rodent.
You referred to me
as your friend.
But, uh... What did we
do to become friends?
[NAI] I don't know.
Ice cream?
[YANARI] No!
Not ice cream!
How do you make a person
be your friend? Officially?
[NAI] I'm not so sure.
[YANARI] Really?
[NAI] Well, I mean,
it's like... Hmm.
There's warmth!
You can feel it!
Morons! Your one job
is to watch him!
What if they attempt
to take him again?
[HIRATO] Can we
be of assistance?
Oh, uh... My son has
apparently snuck away.
[HIRATO] We currently
have operatives in town.
I'll send them, just to be safe.
[JIKI] Emergency orders. Secure
and protect a 9-year-old boy.
Son of the CEO of the Lindain
Group. Indigo-black hair.
[YOGI] Wearing shorts and a
blazer. And his name is Yanari.
[YOGI] Wha--? Hang on.
[NAI] Hmm? It's Rissun!
[YANARI] Oh, wow!
So you came with us, huh?
[RISSUN?]
Huh? Uh, yeah.
[NAI] Hey. Your voice
changed. You're not...
[FAKE RISSUN] Nobody move!
[YOGI] How dare you, sir?
Sullying this fine suit.
[UNDERLING A] Don't move!
[UNDERLING B] Master Yanari,
we've been looking for you!
[UNDERLING A]
Are you all right?
[UNDERLING B]
Quick, come with us!
[YANARI] No! No way! I'm not
going! I've got to find it!
[NAI] Yanari wants
to find a pasta shop.
[HIRATO] Please
leave it to us.
We in Circus know how
to deal with such rabble.
[YOGI] Wait.
What'd he just say?
[GAREKI] Huh?
[HIRATO] It seems
the blonde is trying
to escape with
the child. Now go.
[YOGI] Oh... Oh!!
[YOGI] Hirato actually let us
get away! What a swell guy!
[NAI] This house
is a pasta shop?
[YANARI] No. But this
is the right place.
[YANARI] I'll see her soon.
See my mother.
[NAI] Mother?
[YANARI] Mother!
Mom!
[YANARI] Mom?
[GIRL B] Are you... Yanari?
[GIRL B] She was in an
accident. About a month ago.
I'm so sorry. We didn't have
any way to get a hold of you.
So we weren't able to tell
you about the funeral.
[YANARI] I see. I'm too
late. Now she's gone.
Thank you for your time.
[NAI] Yogi.
Yanari's drowning.
I can hear it. Hear
his heart breaking.
[NAI] My heart hurts too.
[YANARI]
Nai. What is it?
[NAI] Yanari.
[YANARI] Why're you
looking at me like that?
[GAREKI] What's the big idea,
leaving me tied up?
You carelessly
damaged the hopes
and dreams of the
town's children.
You have also exposed
my children to danger.
[GAREKI] No biggie.
Yogi's got this handled.
[HIRATO] Not just
Nai and the boy.
I was also referring to you.
[GAREKI] Wait. What?!
I'm not a kid, pal, and I
sure as hell ain't yours!
[GAREKI] What's so damn funny?
[HIRATO] You are.
Very well. Gareki...
Would you like to be
a child of Airship Two?
[GAREKI] Huh?
[YANARI] My father's work
drove my mother away.
One day she just
left the house.
I felt like she
was abandoning me.
It hurt; I missed
her so much.
But the last time
I saw her, I...
[YANARI] I... just ignored her.
What a terrible thing to do.
I'm the worst person alive!
[YOGI] No, Yanari.
You're wrong.
[YANARI] I'm not wrong!
That's why I never
have any friends either!
[YANARI] My father and the
terrible things he works on.
So many people hate him!
And the worst part is, I'll
grow up to be just like him!
[YANARI] Unless... I already am!
It's awful. I'm worthless!
Terrible! A coward!
Worthless, you hear?
[slapping sound]
[YOGI] You should never talk
about yourself that way.
Not with those words.
[YOGI] You hurt
your mother, yes.
But you can't keep taking
it out on yourself, Yanari.
You're not the same
person you once were.
[YANARI] Huh?
[YOGI] You don't have
to be like your father.
If you promise to stand strong,
on your own two feet,
you'll grow into
a fine young man.
[YOGI] And those times
when you feel like
you don't have any
friends.. you have us!
[NAI] Yeah!
[YOGI] And you have Gareki,
who's not here.
And Tsukumo, waiting outside.
We're all your friends!
[GIRL B] Um...
[YANARI] I... I made that.
Just for mom.
[YANARI'S MOM] Yanari. You're my
pride and joy. Happy Birthday!
[YANARI'S MOM]
I hope you're happy.
And growing tall and strong.
Oh, Yanari. I'm sorry.
[YANARI'S MOM] I want
you to know I love you, son.
[YOGI] Being Nyanperowna, I've
noticed something. It's crazy.
For the kids who need him
the most. He finds a way.
He makes their day brighter.
Like it's his destiny.
[NAI] Really?
[YOGI] Yanari needed friends.
Then destiny brought us to him.
[YANARI]
Nai! Thank you!
When you grabbed
my hand earlier, I...
stopped feeling alone for
the first time. I owe you.
[NAI] Nah, my pleasure. Gareki
and Yogi did the same for me.
And... And so did Karoku.
[YANARI] Karoku?
[NAI] Yeah.
That's who I'm looking for.
[YANARI] Hmm. I've heard
that name. But where?
[JIKI] Yanari!
We need to get in the air!
[YANARI] Yogi.
Nyanperowna is awesome
'cause you put your
heart into it!
[Yogi bawls]
[YANARI] Gareki.
You were really brave
when you took on that
fake squirrel guy for me!
[GAREKI] Anytime.
[YANARI] Nai!
I bought this for my mother.
But I want you to have it.
[NAI] But...
[YANARI] Thank you for
being my first friend!
[NAI] Sure!
[YANARI] Goodbye,
new friends.
Thank you for the
memorable adventure!
[HIRATO] Would you like to
be a child of Airship Two?
[GAREKI] What's that even
mean? Cryptic four-eyed jerk.
I've made it this
long on my own.
[YOGI] Nai!
[NAI] Huh?
[YOGI] Phone call!
Nai speaking!
[YANARI] Hello? Nai?
[NAI] Oh. Yanari!
[YANARI] Wasn't Karoku the guy
you've been searching for?
[NAI] Yeah?
[YANARI] There was a girl I
went to Selection School with
who mentioned him.
Her name was... Eleska.
[YOGI] Eleska?
[GAREKI] Does he mean
working on the Airship?
My plan was to make
some extra cash
sticking with an
easy mark like Nai.
Just planned to use him.
Never thought I'd end up here.
Staying here... It's just...
When did by-the-numbers
business become so complicated?
When did I start caring?
[GAREKI] Huh?
[NAI] Gareki. I brought
some juice for you.
[GAREKI] Oh, thank you.
[GAREKI] I can't stay.
Not with the way I am now.
Never measuring up.
Always the weak link.
[KAROKU] Time for a chat, Nai.
Come. Sink down with me.
[GAREKI] Nai!
[KAROKU] You sure are
taking your time, Nai.
[NAI] Karoku!
Where are you?
[KAROKU] Are you reluctant to
part ways with your friends?
Lucky them. I don't
even get to see you.
[NAI] But why did you go?
[KAROKU] I never chose to.
I was taken against my will.
[NAI] Karoku! Where did
they take you? Tell me!
I promise I'll come for you!
[KAROKU] Hurry.
Come right away.
[KAROKU] Or else.
They plan to kill me.
[KAROKU] You'll find me.
[TSUKUMO] Nai!
What's wrong?
[NAI] He's there.
He's at the Misty Mansion.
[TSUKUMO] The Misty Mansion?
[NAI] Karoku's there.
Tsukumo! I've...
I've got to go
get him! Or else...
Or else they're
going to kill Karoku.
[HEALER] That'll be a rather
difficult place to infiltrate.
The Misty Mansion
is apparently
one of Kafka's top
research facilities.
Trouble is, we still have
insufficient evidence.
Which has proved to be quite a
hurdle to our investigation.
[JIKI] If we go after
them half-cocked.
everything we've
accomplished will be undone.
Unless we have
some concrete proof,
the Command Tower will
never allow our mission.
[TSUKUMO] But how's Palnedo's
granddaughter Eleska
connected to Nai's
friend Karoku?
With just Yanari's memory to
go on, the info's not reliable.
[NAI] Well, I'm going.
That's that.
[JIKI] And what do you plan
to do when you get there?
[NAI] Something! I dunno!
But I've got to try, for Karoku!
[YOGI] I'm sorry, Nai.
[NAI] But now he's...
He's running out of time.
So I'm going.
Alone, if I have to.
[GAREKI] Well, count me in.
I don't work for Circus.
I'm just a dumb cat burglar.
But if we find proof, you can
do something with it?
[YOGI] No way.
Not alone. I'm coming with.
I'll leave my Circus ID here!
[TSUKUMO] I'm going too!
[YOGI] Captain Hirato!
[NAI] I--I have to--
[HIRATO] No one leaves.
Without me.
[HIRATO] I'll take
responsibility.
We'll raid the Mansion under
the pretext of rescuing Karoku.
[HIRATO] Time for Circus
to save the day.
[RABBIT] Each of us is unique
like a snowflake, hop.
[JIKI] Long ears, same
eye color, same voice,
same traits and attire.
You're all identical!
[RABBIT] Look closer, hop.
Maybe then you'll see
the differences, hop.
[JIKI] Silly rabbit.
I'd put money
that everyone agrees
with me on this.