[NAI] Karoku.
[KAROKU] Hey, Nai. C'mere.
[NAI] Yeah?
[KAROKU] You'll be
all right. I promise.
[NAI] No, wait.
Tell me where you're going.
Cat got your tongue, love?
You're on my tummy.
Please--it hurts.
I can't breathe.
I hope you are not
implying I'm overweight!
Please, ma'am. It's not mine.
Fantastic; a Circus ID.
Damn it. Am I busted?
[GAREKI] Crap.
[SECURITY] We've got an
intruder! Everyone stay calm!
[GAREKI] Seriously?
Nothing worth a damn?
[NAI] Uhh, 'scuse me.
[GAREKI] What?
Um... Are you...
gonna go outside?
[GAREKI] Come again?
[NAI] I wanna go outside.
Except I...
Ah... Nice bit o'
bling you got there.
I'll break you outta
here, if you want.
Really?
Thing is...
I ain't cheap.
If you want out...
Give me the bracelet.
Sure thing! It's not mine
to give away, though.
We'll have to get Karoku's
permission first.
You got a deal.
Ugh. This is the
last thing I need.
Are you with Circus?
No. Stupid question.
You're too disheveled.
Fledgling cat burglar,
I presume?
Looks can be deceiving.
Oh, indeed.
Yes, they can.
What?
How about a nice game of tag?
Let's see... how far you can
make it before I devour you!
The hell?
Haul ass! Follow me!
[HIRATO] Forgive me, Tsukumo.
I had my tea without you.
[TSUKUMO] Sir, please!
We're out in the open!
Yes, darling, I noticed.
Camouflage is second nature.
You remained unseen though?
Of course.
Excellent. And your report?
Concerning Miné?
It's as we suspected.
Then we'd best make haste.
Damn! Give it up, punk!
[MINÉ] Clip, clop, plip, plop,
your knees give way.
Chip, chop, slip, slop,
your intestines splay.
Your Ladyship!
Everything's under control;
the intruder has been cornered!
[MINÉ] No need for watercress;
no need for brie.
You'll be eaten...
Uh, Lady Miné.
[MINÉ] ...'ere the
clock strikes three.
That's better. Always play...
with just enough
in your belly to give the
ol' legs a kick start, eh?
[GAREKI] What the hell is she?
We're not sure yet, sir.
[MINÉ] Come, don't be dull;
this is tag, not hide-and-seek.
The whole point,
darlings... is to run.
[NAI] Um, 'scuse me.
That woman...
Where did she go?
[GAREKI] Life always boils it
down to one of three choices.
Enemy. Obstacle.
Or easy mark.
Mostly.
The name's Gareki.
What do I call you?
Oh, Nai!
How do ya like
steerage, Palnedo?
Not exactly first class,
but we do our best.
There's no open bar.
But hey, it is cozy.
What do you intend
to do with us?
That's gonna leave a mark.
Damn teenagers.
Oh, my.
Hellooo!
Fancy meeting you here!
Just look at me!
No makeup, house in shambles.
[WHISPERY VOICE] If you had
simply done things more quietly,
we would've let you
live indefinitely.
Get the lead out, kid!
[TSUKUMO] Not good.
This is grand. We have
been beaten to the punch.
Another lead;
another blind alley.
At least we know
she was involved, but...
that only makes the whole
scenario more... regrettable.
Talk to me. Yes, but someone
else had the same idea.
A hijacking?
Right under their noses?
Don't worry. We're on it.
[GAREKI] Give me a break.
Bastards don't waste
any time, huh?
[POLICE] We clear on that end?
Guess that clinches it.
Son of a...
We've gotta get outta town.
'Course, I say that...
Every way in or out
of this hellhole is probably
crawlin' with fuzz.
Moment of truth. Be ready to
jump when I give the word, okay?
O-Okay.
Let's go!
Karoku.
Should've been easy pickins.
Didn't plan on the
crazy bitch bein' a...
whatever the hell that was.
'Scuse me.
Thank you for getting
me out of there.
So what, you were like her
prisoner or something?
Maybe. I was looking for Karoku.
Oh yeah? Suppose you tell me a
lil' something about this guy.
He'd been around as long as
I can remember. But then...
He went away, and didn't
come back. I got lonely.
He left this weird kind
of trail in the sand.
Little red splashes in a row,
all the way to the ocean.
I followed them and found this.
What's with you?
Just say puddles of blood.
Look, I hate to tell you this.
But the dude's probably
not comin' back.
Sounds like he got in a scuffle.
His attackers got
the drop on him
and dragged his body out to sea;
let the tide clean
up their mess.
Lady Miné recognized
the bracelet, right?
Said it was from Circus.
Not to say this guy's pal
was with them or anything,
but still... Might
be a connection.
That trinket's gotta be worth
something, even if it's bunk.
Either way, I'm in the market
for new stomping grounds.
Can't help feelin'
like I'm owed.
[NAI] How long has it been since
the last time I saw Karoku?
What am I supposed to do
about food without him?
My insides are burning.
Karoku...
What are you doing? Hey.
There's a sound
that doesn't belong.
What sound?
I don't hear anything.
But suddenly...
I'm weirded out.
Gareki.
Where are you going?
Something's up with this train.
I'm gonna go nose around...
You just stay put,
I don't need you--
♪
Gareki!
What next, toddlers as lookouts?
[HIJACKER C] Just be cool
and watch my back.
[HIJACKER D] What the...?
[HIJACKER C] Sorry, fellas.
Shoulda caught the next one!
Oh, I see. You might've
done me the courtesy
of saying you weren't involved.
[HIJACKER C] Hands up!
Really?
Fine.
[HIRATO] Well done.
You're with me.
[TSUKUMO] Yes, sir.
Ow...
You all right?
It's official. This is not
shaping up to be my day.
Seriously, though:
Who dresses like that?
That noise again.
[GAREKI] What?
It's in front.
Hey. Damn it!
Don't move! You so much
as twitch an eyelash,
and I'll kill 'em both.
Why not just subdue them, sir?
Note their mannerisms.
We are dealing with
ordinary citizens.
They're outside
of our jurisdiction.
Damn you, old man.
This is your doing!
You've driven us to this!
[PALNEDO]
Basic economics, son.
For the company to stay afloat,
massive layoffs were inevitable.
Call that heartless if you must,
but I will point out that in
your boundless compassion,
you are holding my
granddaughter hostage.
Congratulations.
You shut your friggin' mouth!
This way!
[HIJACKER A] Son of a bitch.
[HIJACKER B]
Who the hell is this?
Hit the deck!
[HIJACKER A] Come out,
you little bastards!
[HIRATO] That's quite
enough. Stop this.
You wish only to
satisfy your anger.
Vain grasping, in the end.
Put that down!
[HIJACKER A] Screw you.
There are bombs in every car.
Set to detonate back to front.
Unless you hit the brakes,
In which case...
they'll all go off at once.
You're kidding me.
[HIJACKER A] We knew Palnedo
couldn't be reasoned with.
We just want him to burn.
So what if we burn, too?
It's poetic justice.
[HIRATO] Tsukumo,
see to their safety.
I'll handle the explosives.
Yes, sir.
Pardon me.
Who are you people?
We're employed by Circus.
I am Hirato. Captain of
Airship Two. A pleasure.
Tsukumo. Special combat
personnel. Nice to meet you.
Circus has girls our
age working for them?
I had no idea.
That's awesome.
Yes.
Whoa, what--?
[GAREKI] Wait, is he
actually hearing
the radio signal setting
these things off?
'Nother one.
The noise?
Too much radio interference.
Tsukumo. It appears
as though our best option
is to evacuate and
derail the train...
[GAREKI] Is he on something?
What, we're supposed to jump?
No. No, we've got
a better option.
[HIRATO] ...from slowing
down until we've dismounted.
[GAREKI] Hey! Four-eyes!
Beg your pardon?
We don't have to jump.
I've got this. You in?
[GAREKI] 'K, Nai. Where's
the sound coming from?
Down there.
Step back, please.
[GAREKI] Jackpot!
Heads up. This puppy's
a signal device.
Check out the circuit board.
Your top-of-the-line ST Corp
radio wave controller.
I'd know one of these
babies anywhere.
No mad bomber would
leave home without one.
Alrighty. This here's
the sensor. Good.
And this is the transmitter.
Son of a bitch.
There's no indication of what
kind of signal range there is.
We're gonna have to
disconnect the rear car.
Pray we get enough distance
before the next signal.
[HIRATO] That can be arranged.
Step aside, if you would.
In vacuo.
[NAI] So, where
are we going now?
[GAREKI] Don' know yet.
Somewhere the cops can't get us.
[NAI] Gareki?
[GAREKI] Yeah?
[NAI] Thank you.
[GAREKI] What?
This makes twice
you've saved me.
But, sir...
You're sure about this?
You saw his bracelet.
Naturally.
For now, let it go.
[HIRATO] Mr. Palnedo.
Pardon me. Might I have
a moment of your time?
You must forgive me, good sir.
I don't mean to appear
uncooperative.
But I'm experiencing
mild chest pains.
Nothing serious, I'm sure.
Oh, dear.
One has to watch the ol'
ticker at my age. I'll be fine.
Luckily my personal
physician is on hand.
Now if you'll excuse me.
[HIRATO] Let us know if
there's anything you need, sir.
[URO] The Karasuna issue
has been put to bed.
You haven't been
getting enough rest.
Imagine a hostage not
being able to sleep.
Even if he did arrange
his own capture.
Worth it, though:
to see Circus in action.
Everything in moderation, yes?
Time is on our side.
We're at leisure to strike
whenever necessary.
[PALNEDO] Incidentally,
a certain young man
has caught my eye.
An independent concern,
so to speak.
He reminds me of you-know-who.
And I'm not the only
one who thinks so;
Circus appears to have taken
an interest in the lad as well.
I'd like him brought in.
Finished!
[HIRATO] Tsukumo.
[TSUKUMO] Are those baked goods?
[HIRATO] Fresh from a
cafe in Karasuna, in fact.
[TSUKUMO] Muffins, scones,
shortbread cookies.
I don't know where to start.
[HIRATO]
These are for Yogi.
[TSUKUMO]
Of course they are.