[GAREKI] Yotaka.
[GAREKI] Holy crap.
[YOTAKA] I'm just
so... So hungry.
[YOGI] Get out of here. Just go.
Take Nai and run for it.
[GAREKI] Oh, yeah, right!
How 'bout you run?
[YOGI] He's beyond listening
to reason, I'm sorry.
[YOGI] If you don't
wanna die, clear out now.
[YOGI] He's on the move.
[YOGI] Meet'cha
back in Karasuna!
Don't worry,
I'm a professional!
[YOGI] I'll see
you there soon.
[GAREKI] Bastard!
He expect me to turn tail
and run from my
friends? Screw that!
[GAREKI] I owe them.
[TSUBAKI] We need
to give you a name.
How 'bout the characters
for "flower pebble"?
"Gareki." You like?
Work with me here.
We're family now.
Still sounds lame.
Fine, whatever.
[YOUNG YOTAKA] Here.
Why'd gramps make
me bag up the scraps
from the factory floor
to give to you?
What's up? Are you
like some kind of genius?
Come on. What's the
hold-up, Gareki?
We're waiting on you so
we can sit down and eat.
[YOUNG GAREKI] What?
Why not just eat without me?
[YOUNG TSUBAME]
Ah! There's Mr. Fix-it!
What? I'm busy.
Oh, um, well. We, uh...
Nothin' major, really.
Just kinda, sorta.
I dunno. We were...
Trying to track ya down.
Jeez, she wouldn't
shut up about it.
[YOTAKA] Gareki.
[GAREKI] Oh, great.
Why're you here?
[YOTAKA] Making sure my
sister didn't follow you.
Because I worry about her!
[YOTAKA] And I can
see I was right to.
Guns and crap. Why you think
you need that is beyond me.
Why'd you even
come back, anyway?
[GAREKI] Hey,
this ain't about me.
[YOTAKA] The hell
it's not, you son--
[GAREKI] Shut your trap.
You don't talk to
me like that. Ever.
You're not my brother
and you never will be.
Hell, you think I wanna live in
that sinkhole with you guys?
[GAREKI] You wanna
know why I'm here?
'Cause I'm knee deep
in the kind of crazy
that'd get hicks like you
and Tsubame eaten alive.
[GAREKI] Get out of here.
Now. This ain't for you.
[YOTAKA] You can go to hell!
[GAREKI] I'm not someone you get
close to. That's just how it is.
Life always boils it down to
one of three choices, right?
Enemy. Obstacle.
Or easy mark.
[GAREKI] She out
of her mind? Idiot.
[GAREKI] Nai. You can make it
to Karasuna by yourself, right?
[GAREKI] Just follow
the road we came in on.
Go straight and it's a day's
walk from here at most.
No problem.
Look, I'll even give you
my jacket. You'll be fine.
[NAI] No way!
[NAI] I don't wanna;
you can't make me!
[GAREKI] Whoa.
Ease up, hoss.
[NAI] That thing'll get me!
[GAREKI] Grow up already.
It's got a hood.
You can wear it
like a disguise.
[NAI] It's not just that.
I don't want to leave
you by yourself.
You'll break into a
million pieces if I do!
I'm not going!
Seriously, dude.
C'mon. That's crazy talk.
Don't worry. Least not about me.
Where was this with Yogi?
He's the wuss.
[NAI] Nuh-uh.
He's strong.
[GAREKI] Wha-- Wait.
If you're trying
to say I'm weak,
I'll kick your ass from
here to tomorrow!
Think you can protect me,
huh, big shot?
[GAREKI] Damn it, Nai.
Just listen, okay?
You wanna see
Karoku again, right?
That's your thing.
Take it from a pro:
Don't let yourself
get blown off course.
Play the game; use Circus.
I hate to admit this,
'cause it's lame, but...
Thing is, I don't know
which way is up anymore.
Not since seein' poor Tsubame
with that look in her eyes.
Seein' Yotaka
worried about her.
Yogi's gonna try and kill them.
I know he is. He's gotta.
But I just can't
stand by and watch.
They're still my friends.
I left them, yeah.
But I wanted them to
be okay, you know? Safe.
[NAI] Gareki.
[GAREKI] Find that warehouse
we were in. Lay low there.
And don't lose any sleep
over me, all right?
[GAREKI] Snap out of it.
It's not about you,
it's about your promise.
The bastard who
destroyed your family
is about to get some payback!
[NAI] What does he mean don't
let myself get blown off course?
Like, by friends?
[NAI] So if things aren't
my problem, I should just...
[NAI] Yeah, no. If he
really believed that,
he wouldn't've gone back. He's
only trying to keep me safe.
Ah... Huh?
[TSUBAME] Oh, god.
Please, no; not again.
I... How did I get here?
[TSUBAME] What's wrong
with me? What have I done?
I can't be sick, please.
If something happened
to me, Yotaka would be...
What do I do?
[MEIGA] Hey there.
Are you all right?
[MEIGA] It's okay,
don't be frightened.
[TSUBAME] You...
You shouldn't.
[NAI] Tsubame.
[TSUBAME] No.
♪
[YOGI] He's not
at full bore yet.
There's still hope.
Dorn Kiste!
Einsam Zelle!
[YOGI] Yotaka, listen to me.
I don't want to hurt
you if I don't have to.
[YOGI] Please. Think about
your friend Gareki. Just try.
[YOTAKA] Gareki.
[YOTAKA] Gare... ki.
[TSUBAME] Why did you--?
[NAI] I don't...
I don't know.
Something was...
wrong about him.
[TSUBAME] I'm so sorry.
I... Your hand.
There's something
wrong about me, too.
[NAI] Huh?
[TSUBAME] I'm a monster.
[NAI] Nuh-uh.
You're too warm.
Exactly like him. Karoku.
[NAI] You feel warm
and comforting.
That's why Gareki...
[NAI] Yeah. You mean the
world to him, so he came back.
[TSUBAME] Oh, please.
I'm the reason
he left in the first place.
[NAI] That isn't true! Gareki...
He said... Well, uh...
[TSUBAME] You're sweet.
Thanks for trying, Nai.
[MEIGA] How romantic.
[MEIGA] You peppy young things
are just so full of life.
[YOTAKA] Why is he here?
What's his game?
He's not trying to kill me.
I don't get it.
[YOTAKA]
Yogi... That right?
[TSUBAME] Yotaka!
[TSUBAME]
Don't do it. Please.
[TSUBAME] Whatever
this is... Just...
[MEIGA] The more, the
merrier, right, gang?
This is what we call efficiency.
Makes research a breeze.
[NAI] Yogi.
[MEIGA] You know
what this calls for?
I mean, we're all
friends here, aren't we?
Why not make it a party?
We've already got a
first-class spread. Chow down!
[GAREKI] Yotaka.
[YOTAKA] Gareki.
[GAREKI] What the
hell's gotten into you?
You look like a goth.
[YOTAKA] So suddenly
you care. Awesome.
[YOTAKA] We're not brothers.
Never will be.
[GAREKI] You selfish prick.
Think about what
you're putting your sister
through--and the old man.
[YOTAKA] Shut your trap!
You left! You ran out!
And now you're gonna die!
[Meiga laughs]
[MEIGA] That's the stuff. Gimme
teen angst at a boil any day.
[GAREKI 'Scuse me?
Who're you?
[MEIGA] Loaded
question there, champ.
Let's go with
"an interested party."
Suffice it to say I've got
an appetite for games.
[Meiga laughs]
[MEIGA] The more twists and
turns, the better my data.
[MEIGA] Your pal got
wise to my prescription,
started wolfing down
Tsubame's share.
His transformation
escalated, of course,
but what's fascinating is
the girl's change is
fully psychosomatic.
[MEIGA] Even once he knew
what was in store for him,
Yotaka stuck to the regimen to
keep his family in the black.
There's a lesson in
that for all of us.
[TSUBAME] Yotaka, no!
[GAREKI] You bastard.
It was you. Wasn't it?
[GAREKI] You're a murderer.
[MEIGA] Hm?
Ah, the older one
who tried to get
'em off the meds.
[MEIGA] Yeah, no,
see, when his powers
first got its hooks into 'im,
Yotaka lost control.
Big sis roared, thinkin'
she could rein him in.
Man, quite a sight.
What'd I tell ya?
The more twists
and turns, the better.
[MEIGA] Why would I kill a
fine piece of ass like that?
[GAREKI] You're a liar!
You did it!
I'm not gonna believe
a word of your crap!
[MEIGA] Yes, yes, I remember
you; the one who left.
[MEIGA] Too bad you
didn't stick around, eh?
But it's never too late to earn
your wings. Isn't that right?
[GAREKI] Varuga!
[MEIGA] There's always
room for one more.
[MEIGA] Son of a bitch;
thought you were dead.
Aw, kids today.
[MEIGA] Front and
center, Yotaka.
Kill 'em all.
That's an order.
[TSUBAME] Yotaka!
Don't listen to him! Please!
That's not who you are!
You're not a killer like him!
[YOTAKA] No, I'm not.
[MEIGA] Hm.
[YOTAKA] Sorry, sir.
[YOTAKA] Piss off.
[MEIGA] Hmph. Hey, what do
you know? Fascinating stuff.
Apparently love is
psychosomatic as well.
Of course.
I wondered why
you could never fully
shed your humanity.
Tsubame's influence
kept pulling you back
from your new state. As twins,
you share a unique bond.
One I should have taken
into consideration.
And here you've led
such a hard-scrabble life
up to this point.
What on earth is the appeal
in being human
when that's your lot?
[YOTAKA] You'll never know.
Few people ever really do.
[YOTAKA] When you're down
and out, you take meaning
where you can. In a smile, a
tear--whatever. It's beautiful.
[YOTAKA] You know,
I pity you.
[MEIGA] Is that right?
Well, I've lost interest.
[MEIGA] You'd do well to
bear this in mind, buck-o.
Like it or not, you're your
own thing from here on out.
Those warm fuzzies are just
an echo of your past life.
[Yotaka winces,
screams in pain]
[TSUBAME] No!
What's happening?
[MEIGA] Evolution, sweetheart.
There's no denying progress.
[MEIGA] Do me a favor,
stay out of my way.
But watch, 'cause this
is where it gets good!
[TSUBAME] Stop this!
[YOTAKA] Gareki.
Kill me now. I...
I can't... hold out.
[YOTAKA] I don't want
to do this anymore.
I'm tired of hurting
people. Please!
[YOTAKA] Don't think
about it! Make it stop!
Just kill me, damn you!
[YOTAKA] Now!
[YOTAKA] Tsubame.
[TSUBAME] Yotaka.
[YOTAKA] Fly away from here.
You're free. So go.
Yotaka!!
[NAI] What smells so nice?
[KAROKU] We call it a flower.
They give off a fragrance.
[NAI] Can you eat it?
[KAROKU] No. Best to
just sit back and admire.
[NAI] Oh. Like your fragrance!
[KAROKU] What?
[NAI] You smell like sunshine!