[TSUBAME] Yotaka!
[TSUBAME] Don't goooo!
[HIRATO]
Stand down, Yogi. Now.
♪
[KIICHI] Is a
little self-respect
too much to ask for?
Heaven's sake, you look
like a furrier's apprentice.
Circus requires better
of us, Lieutenant!
[YOGI] Gee, thanks.
Add insult to injury.
[KIICHI] I realize the situation
was an emotionally delicate one.
But there's no excuse for
softness in someone who purports
to be a warrior. Your
hesitation could've cost lives.
[YOGI] You, uh,
saw all that, huh?
[KIICHI] Yes, and it chaffs me
to no end that you and I hold
the same rank. An insult to
combatants across the globe.
[KIICHI] Although...
You were delectable bait!
[Tsubame weeps]
[TSUBAME] He's gone.
He's really gone.
[NAI] Everyone
is so... sad.
[NAI] I don't
like this at all.
[YOGI] Forgive me.
I tried.
[GAREKI] Oh, man.
Look at yourself.
You gonna be okay?
[YOGI] Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
[NAI] Gareki's so calm about
all this. How does he do it?
[NAI] Or is he faking?
[NAI] I'm not wounded like Yogi,
or crying the way Tsubame is.
But I still feel
something in my chest.
[NAI] And thinking
of that terrible man
makes my insides twist.
Where's the warmth?
I don't understand.
It's like all that's
left is cold and hurt.
♪
[HIRATO] "Spineless.
Makes sport of the weak
under cover of darkness.
A reveler in shadow.
In a word, craven."
That's how Team One's
report describes you.
Your pet broke its leash
and very nearly killed
one of my best operatives.
Fortunately for us all,
you got so swept up in the
moment, you flubbed your exit.
So. Are the weak
really your only prey?
[HIRATO] Aller.
[TSUKITACHI] I see the little
ladies are field-tested now.
Good on you.
[TSUKITACHI] I'll take it
from here, if you please.
Thank you kindly for
reeling the bastard in.
You are a credit to
your title, good sir.
[HIRATO] Your irony is
not lost on me. Retour.
[TSUKITACHI] Just take the
compliment. The irony's mine.
[TSUBAME] You're with them.
[TSUBAME] The people who killed
Yotaka. You're one of them.
[YOGI] Yeah.
[GAREKI] It's not
like that, Tsubame.
That man did all this.
Not Circus.
[TSUBAME] Sure, yeah.
[GAREKI] These people
are the good guys.
They're about law and
order; about justice.
Yotaka was twisted
into something bad.
He got made into a monster
against his will.
There's nothing anyone
could've done. I'm sorry.
He turned into what
these guys call a varuga.
It's okay. Let me.
[YOGI] A shadow organization
known as "Kafka" is responsible.
They use people; trick them
into accepting their terms.
Without getting too technical,
there are two ways
to make a varuga.
[YOGI] There's lab-monitored
cell fusion, and there's
accidental transmission through
contact with tainted blood.
A lot of times,
Kafka administers
a special drug to
unwitting subjects.
Your brother was
given such a drug.
His transformation was the
result of a years-long regimen.
[TSUBAME] Wait, a drug?
[YOGI] Varuga cell regeneration
is exponentially faster
than a human's.
Devastating injuries
often heal within
a couple of days.
[YOGI] Their metabolism
comes with a price, though.
The only way to
compensate for it
is to feed on other
complex organisms.
That's where
Circus comes in.
We track these creatures down.
And you've seen the rest.
The hope is to finally
make Kafka accountable
to the law, make them answer
for what they've done.
In the meantime, all we can
do is set their victims free.
[YOGI] But that's...
That's just...
"Setting them free" means
nothing. Another stupid spin.
Truth is, all we've set free
are our consciences.
What we do is kill.
[TSUBAME] Good. I won't
have to do it myself.
[GAREKI] The hell do you mean?
[TSUBAME] Put me
down like I deserve!
[GAREKI] No!
You don't mean that!
You're not a varuga! Get that
idea out of your head!
[TSUBAME] Yes! I am!
I took the drugs, too.
For a while, at least. Before
Yotaka kept them from me.
[TSUBAME] One day...
I'll change like he did.
[NAI] Tsubame, no.
[TSUBAME] Besides...
What's the point anyway?
Look at me. I'm alone!
[TSUBAME] I can't do this.
I hate it here. I've got no one.
Tsubaki's gone.
Yotaka's gone.
Grandpa's in the hospital
with Alzheimer's.
I don't... I don't want
to live like this!
[GAREKI] Listen to you!
The old man's still alive!
And he needs you!
Who the hell's gonna
pay his bills if you
decide to off yourself?
[TSUBAME] You think I've
been paying for all that?
We've never had
that kind of money.
[TSUBAME] Some friend from his
past has been footing the bill.
No idea who. One of the
nurses told me in private.
Point is, he doesn't need me.
He hasn't for a while now.
[TSUBAME]
Please. Set me free.
[GAREKI] Tsubame.
[NAI] It's so sad,
the way she cries.
It's like... Like rain.
Like she's drowning.
[JIKI] Well, no luck here. Find
anything useful on your end?
[KIICHI] The bastard kept
copious notes on his
test subjects. However, there's
no paper trail back to Kafka.
Not so much as a scrap.
[JIKI] Like they walk
between the raindrops, huh?
You'd think there'd at
least be a payment record
or second set of books.
You've gotta respect
the lengths their Damage
Control department
must go to to keep
the trail cold.
[JIKI] A worthy adversary
if there ever was one.
[KIICHI] Ugh. Please. There's no
value in admiring the enemy.
[JIKI] S'pose all we can do now
is interrogate our new friend.
Whaddya say?
[HIRATO] Just rewards.
[TSUKITACHI] Nice, you're
quoting Akari now?
[HIRATO] The man has a
Ph.D. in molecular biology.
Would it kill you to
refer to him as "Doctor"?
[TSUKITACHI] It might.
Oh, speaking of which:
At some point, the three of us
should pick each other's brains
about the notebook he
found in Rainbow Forest.
Nothing fancy, just a
little tea between friends.
[HIRATO] By "tea,"
I assume you mean booze.
[TSUKITACHI] Like you
even have to ask.
[HIRATO] Best of luck.
Akari detests me.
[TSUKITACHI] Ah! Explain
why I have to gild his name
with "Doctor" and you don't?
[HIRATO] He's quite
rude to me. I'm exempt.
[TSUKITACHI]
That's the criteria?
[JIKI] Not to overstep,
but we have work to do, sirs.
[KIICHI] Apparently that
only applies to us.
[TSUKITACHI] Yeah, whatever.
You guys dig up anything?
[KIICHI] As usual,
Kafka covered their tracks.
[JIKI] I vote we
get what we need
straight from the horse's
mouth, so to speak.
[KIICHI] Something tells me this
is going to be a very hard sell.
[TSUKITACHI] No harm
in trying, I suppose.
[HIRATO] Interested in
atoning for your sins?
Give us something
we can use. Legally.
Details about your connection
with Kafka, for example.
Do they provide you
with drugs, or vice versa?
Don't you sons of bitches
know who you're talking to?
[TSUKITACHI]
Hm. Guess not.
[MEIGA] You think I'd
sell out my own kind?
[HIRATO] What is your
relationship to Palnedo?
Last chance.
[YOGI] Captain Hirato's
performing a burial.
[YOGI] It's over.
[GAREKI] He's dead.
[GAREKI] The man who
destroyed the lives
of the people I
cared about most.
[GAREKI] So why don't I
feel any better about this?
What's wrong with me?
[NAI] Gareki's feeling the same
sting in his heart that I am.
The same ache.
[GAREKI] It's like
nothing's changed.
I should've gotten
to kill him myself.
[URO] Meiga's been terminated.
[PALNEDO] Who is that?
[PALNEDO] First I've
heard the name.
[TSUKITACHI]
So, yeah. That kid.
[HIRATO] You mean Nai?
[TSUKITACHI] No, the
one with the attitude.
If memory serves,
he was on that ship.
[TSUKITACHI] The one that we
took it upon ourselves to sink?
[TSUKITACHI] You think
it means anything,
or is it simply
another coincidence?
[HIRATO] Excellent question.
[YOGI] Captain, I...
[HIRATO] It can wait, Yogi.
[HIRATO] You understand
we had no choice
but to use you as bait?
Such is the fog of war.
The possessors inexplicably
left you unharmed.
We had to utilize that.
[HIRATO] Why do you
think I authorized
your stop-off in Karasuna?
We've suspected for some time
that Kafka had sunk its
talons into this place.
When I realized you would
visit come hell or high water,
my path was clear: draw the
enemy--both their operations
here and their intentions
with you--into the open.
[YOGI] I'm sorry,
Gareki. I really am.
[GAREKI] It's all right.
I knew what I was signing
up for with you guys.
[GAREKI] Damn it.
[TSUKITACHI] Let's not
stand on ceremony.
If you'd come with
us please, young lady.
[GAREKI] No way!
To hell with tha--!
What are you doing?
[GAREKI] It doesn't
have to be this way.
You're not as alone as
you think. There's gramps.
And us--and people you
haven't even met yet!
[TSUBAME] You left.
[GAREKI] What?
That was no one's
choice but yours.
[TSUBAME] And this.
This is my choice.
We tried. We wanted you to
feel like part of the family.
[TSUBAME] You don't
have the first clue what
your skipping out on us
really did. We deserved better.
[TSUKITACHI] Take all the
time you need. I'll wait.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
Thank you. I really appreciate
you doing this for me.
[NURSE C] He has to be Circus;
look at that sexy hat!
[NURSE A] Who d'ya
think he's here for?
[TSUBAME]
Hey, Grampa. It's me.
[TSUBAME] I've done
a lot of thinking,
and I've decided it's best
if I leave the village.
That means this may be the last
time I can come see you.
But don't worry.
[TSUBAME] I've made
some new friends,
and they're going to make
sure you're taken care of.
They said you'll
want for nothing.
[TSUBAME] So see?
Everything'll be fine.
[NURSE A] They came here
for an old man? Circus?
[NURSE B] He's the one that
boy's been paying for, right?
[NURSE C]
Wait. What boy?
[NURSE B] You know...
he was here yesterday.
Still in his teens. Kinda
lanky. Black hair. Attitude.
[NURSE C] Ohh.
Yeah, right, him.
[TSUBAME] S'cuse me!
What's the name of the
boy you're talking about?
[TSUBAME] Please!
It's important!
[NURSE B]
Hmm. Lemme think.
On one of your
grandpa's good days,
he had a conversation
with him. Gareki, or...?
♪
[TSUBAME] Hey.
Where's Gareki?
[YOTAKA] Sorry, there's
no easy way to say this:
I think he's fallen in
with a bad crowd.
He's gone. Just put
him out of your mind.
[TSUBAME] Gareki!
[HIRATO] Ready to
move on, I presume?
We could've renewed the land
title. Why do it by yourself?
Hiding a family
secret, perhaps?
[GAREKI] I told you:
I don't have a family.
[HIRATO] You've done
a very noble thing.
Do not think it's lost on me.
[HIRATO] Heh. Such a softie.
[GAREKI] Up yours.
[TSUBAME] Everyone was
looking out for me.
[TSUBAME] I wasn't
alone after all.
[TSUKITACHI]
Well, come along then.
I need one more favor.
[TSUBAME] Not a
bad way to go out.
[TSUBAME] I don't
care if it hurts,
or if I'm dissected or whatever.
Just learn from me.
Use me to bring Kafka down!
[TSUBAME] I owe a
lot of good people.
[TSUBAME]
Bring them to justice!
Oh, we will.
[TSUBAME] Let my last
breath mean something.
You're very brave.
My respect.
[TSUBAME] I've got this, Yotaka.
Let me show you what
real wings can do.
[HIRATO] Your profession
being what it is,
I assume you know a foul
mood is counter-productive.
[AKARI] All the more
reason for you to go.
[HIRATO] You cut me to
the quick, my good man!
Am I not always a
balm for what ails you?
[AKARI] Get. Out. Now.