[NAI] Jiki.
[NAI] Over there.
The rainbow.
That's where we should be.
[NAI] It's him! Please!
[JIKI] Is that right?
[JIKI] We'd be fools not
to assume it's a trap.
[JIKI] What the hell?
[JIKI] Ah, the cavalry.
At least now I know
we're on to something.
[YOGI] Gareki!
[YOGI] Dorn Kiste!
[YOGI] This is
too much for you.
[YOGI] The sooner I get you
back to the ship, the better.
[GAREKI] Level with me.
You going in?
[YOGI] Yeah.
The rainbow's our--
[GAREKI] Look, I know
I'm out of my depth.
I mean, you people.
Your skills are...
It's like... It's like I'm...
Like I'm nothin'.
[GAREKI] Still.
I wanna help. Just to...
[YOGI] What?
Hey--wait!
You're telling me--?
Oh, dear.
Look at you.
I would be honored.
Hey, we need all the
help we can get, right?
Come on, buckaroo!
Let's kick some tail!
[AKARI] Damn you,
Azana! Snap out of it!
Listen to yourself; you're
rambling like a madman!
[AZANA] Oh, it makes perfect
sense. Look at Murano:
His whole life was about
protecting lesser creatures.
And even he had to make
a deal with the devil.
[AKARI] It was you, wasn't it?
The one who's been using my good
name to peddle the varuga drug.
[AZANA] It was the best
way to operate, doc.
Your name's got a lot
of weight behind it.
Please understand,
I don't want to hurt you.
Just come with me and
everything'll work out.
[AKARI] Hirato?
[AZANA] Dammit.
You'll never know, Doc.
How much I've looked up
to you and respected you.
Always so good. So honest.
So... So everything I'm not!
I hate crawling in
your stupid shadow!
I could never measure up;
never even approach
how perfect you are!
I hate you!
[HIRATO] Treason is
very serious, young man.
The position you're in is dire.
More than I think you know.
By law, I'm authorized to
execute you on the spot.
[AKARI]
No, Hirato! Don't!
[AKARI] Azana! Wait!
[HIRATO] We've known about him
for some time. My apologies.
[HIRATO] Now that
he's exposed himself,
he'll have Ikami to deal with.
[AKARI] That poor kid.
[KAGIRI] Hey, hey!
Final Dungeon. Boss Fight!
[KIICHI] Come on! I was holding
my own, sir. Thanks a lot!
[TSUKITACHI] Nicely done,
sweetheart. I'm proud of you.
[Uro laughs]
[URO] Ill-advised.
[URO] Keeping the powers of your
banshees in check in an attempt
to preserve your target opens
a window of opportunity.
They're holding back.
Which is fortunate;
their full strength wouldn't
leave sufficient room
for a loop hole.
Not by a long shot.
But because of the restraint--
the delicate balance
they have to maintain
not to kill me--
luck was on my side, you see.
I had just enough space
to call up an old friend.
[IVA] Bear down!
[URO] Too late!
[URO] The balance
has now shifted!
You really ought to have known
better than to come at me
with these pale imps. Either
your captain is an imbecile,
or you're being used
as sacrificial pawns.
"Somewhere over the
rainbow," eh, ladies?
Circus is drawn to it
like moths to a flame.
Fathoms easier than
divide and conquer.
Nice chatting with you.
[IVA] Don't count
your chickens yet.
[JIKI] Stupid things!
[JIKI] Yogi. What the
hell was that about?
[YOGI] Didn't you just hear
that? That snap? Oh, man.
[NAI] Yes!
You're both alive!
[GAREKI] Sup.
[YOGI] Aw, little buddy.
I bet you were scared
out of your mind.
[JIKI] Reunion's over guys.
Stay on your guard.
Rainbow. Dead ahead.
[NAI] It's Karoku.
You look tired, darlings.
Let mother sing you a lullaby.
The light behind the
door's not for your kind.
Oh, no; you, my tragic
poppets, are for the dark.
[JIKI] We're running
out of time.
[YOGI] No! Wait!
[JIKI] Go, I'll stay
and hold her off!
[YOGI] Yeah, good plan!
[YOGI] Almost there.
[NAI] Yogi!
[YOGI] Dorn Kiste!
[YOGI] Iva!
[NAI] Tsukumo!
[GAREKI] Stop draggin'
your feet, dumbass!
[GAREKI] We can make it.
We can make it!
[KAROKU] Follow the sound
of the gently whispering air.
Find the source. The center
of the maze is waiting.
Like a seashell, from whence the
breath of the ocean sings.
Find the empty heart. Embrace
it. Be ready for miracles.
[YOGI] Give me the key!
This is no joke! Do it now!
Or I'll lop your damn head off!
[URO] Oh, the
naivety of youth.
As if all the answers lay in
wait behind a single door.
It's not so simple.
The door's a mystery to us all.
You're stalling!
[KAROKU] Welcome.
[NAI] Ka... Karoku.
[NAI] Karoku!
[KAROKU] Hey.
[NAI] You're... You're alive!
Oh, no. You're hurt.
[GAREKI] Huh.
So that's him.
[GAREKI]
Wait. Where are we?
[GAREKI] Nai, wake up.
The hell's that by your feet?
Stop ignoring it!
[GAREKI] I'm frozen
to the spot!
[NAI] So. Question. Can
Gareki have your bracelet?
[GAREKI] Can't speak.
Gotta try. Come on!
[GAREKI] Nai! Snap out of it!
Look at the ground!
[NAI] Wha--?
[NAI] Karoku? Karoku!
[GAREKI]
What? But how?
[NAI] He's...
He's covered with red.
[KAROKU] I was trying to let
the poor guy have one last look
at you. I'm afraid it's
me you've been hearing
in your head these past few
weeks. I was using his voice.
He was overjoyed to know you
were coming. Believe me.
Thing is, he was
actually meant to end up
somewhere a lot emptier--
a lot less warm--than here.
He spoke of his little Nai
all the time. I can't tell you
how glad I am to put a
face with all the stories.
I know. It's difficult to
accept me as anyone but him.
He is a part of
me now, though.
In a way, I'm more
him than he is.
We get rid of clothes
we've outgrown, right?
No big deal. It's much
the same principle.
Don't be scared, Nai.
Take my hand. Please.
I'm so proud of you
for making it here.
It's important you understand:
This side is where you belong.
[GAREKI] Damn it!
Move your hand!
[KAROKU] Time to say
goodbye to Gareki.
It's a shame we can't keep
them forever, isn't it?
[NAI] Uh-uh. It's wrong.
[KAROKU] Come on.
Don't be so stubborn.
If it'll help you let go,
I can always shatter him.
[NAI] No, don't!
[GAREKI] Hey, psycho!
[GAREKI] His pulse is weak.
[KAROKU] You leave
me no choice.
If you're not quite done
having fun, I can always wait.
Patience is one of my
virtues. Be seeing you.
[KAROKU] Play as long as
you like, Nai. I'll be here.
[MAKUNOBE] You launched a
raid without authorization?
Do you realize how much
trouble you've caused?
This infantile stunt has set us
back months--possibly years!
[HIRATO] I understand, sir.
And I take full responsibility.
My humblest apologies.
[TSUKITACHI]
Don't buy his baloney;
he couldn't have
pulled this off alone
if he'd wanted to. I share
as much of the blame.
Before you dish out punishment,
though, look at what we've done.
[MAKUNOBE] You stand there
with a straight face and argue
the ends justify the means?
The primary target
eluded you completely!
Not only is Palnedo free,
he's now claiming that Uro
acted without his knowledge!
So in the court of public
opinion, the old man's
the victim! Somehow Uro
slipped through your fingers!
And if that weren't bad enough,
Azana, the mole,
is also now at large!
[ISHLAR] And what
of the rescue?
Has this Karoku fellow shed
any light on the situation?
[HIRATO] He is
receiving treatment,
but is still unconscious.
Dr. Akari can offer no prognosis
as yet. He suspects, however,
that it will be some time
before the boy can speak.
[NAI] Karoku.
[TSUKUMO] C'mon, Nai.
We should be getting back
to the ship. He'll understand.
[GAREKI] Son of a...!
Look, I know there's a test,
that you gotta come
from good stock.
Not what I'm askin'.
There has to be some
kind of exception!
[HIRATO] Well,
there is the academy.
Bear in mind, we're
talking years of study.
[GAREKI] Listen. I despise
varugas. An' Kafka can suck it.
If it weren't for them, my
friends would still be alive.
I'd have something
resembling a family.
I won't sit back and let that
happen to someone else.
It eats away at me; it burns.
[GAREKI] Ah, whatever. I guess
I just got used to being here.
Being a part of something
bigger than myself.
Course, I say that,
but the truth is I've felt
like a third wheel
from day one. I hate it.
I just... I just wanted to
earn my stripes with you guys.
It's the least I
could do, right?
I mean, I dunno. You guys...
You guys are like...
Oh, to hell with it! Find a way
for me to join Circus, please!
That's what I thought. I've
been listening very intently.
I've been through all the books
'n crap. But there's nothin'
in there 'bout how to join if
you're not on the register.
[HIRATO] It's all right.
Sneaking your name on there
is easy enough. I'd be happy to.
I'm the one who got you
into this; it's only fair
I take it one step further.
That's as far as I'll go.
Beyond that, it's on you.
Best of luck.
[HIRATO] I'll be
waiting eagerly to see
if you conquer the Academy
in season to rejoin us.
[GAREKI] No worries.
I got this!
[GAREKI] The hell'd he go?
[YOGI] He had a heart-to-heart
with the captain.
That night, before the big raid.
[YUKKIN] Yukkin.
[NAI] Not gonna lie.
I don't like this one bit.
I want things to
stay as they are.
[TSUKUMO] Oh, Nai. Yogi?
[YOGI] I know he chose
this path for himself,
so I should support him,
but... It's just...
The whole idea of him being
a child of Airship Two...
I dunno. Bothers me.
We don't exist. I mean,
we do technically,
but as far as the rest of
the world's concerned.
You join Circus and that's it.
They edit your records so it's
like you never drew breath.
In theory, it's to
protect your family--
keep them from being something
the enemy can use against you.
An Airship's the only home
we ever know after that.
Sure, we meet
tons of nice people
when we're doing shows
and all. But it's so brief.
When you and Gareki came to
stay with us, I was so happy.
For once it felt like we
actually got to make friends.
It was awesome.
Like a breath of fresh air;
like a mountain sunrise.
It was just so...
I dunno. I'm just conflicted.
There's so much for
Gareki on the outside.
All sorts of people for him
to meet and make friends with.
Tons.
[NAI &amp; YOGI] Gareki!
[GAREKI] Oh, hey.
[YOGI] We're just
here... uh... to say.
[NAI] Gareki.
[TSUKUMO] Come on, guys.
He needs you both to be strong.
[YOGI] Gareki.
Promise you'll cry
on Nyanperowna's shoulder
whenever you get lonely!
[GAREKI] When are you gonna get
that I'm not five years old?
[TSUKUMO] I'd like
to say something.
[GAREKI] Yeah?
[TSUKUMO] Forgive me. I'm rather
bad at this kind of thing.
And I'm not much better
as a seamstress.
But Nai and I wanted you
to have this. We made it.
[GAREKI] Jeez.
This is a train wreck.
[GAREKI] Cool, thanks.
[NAI] Here. This, too.
[GAREKI] So, your guy's still
sleeping or whatever, right?
[NAI] Mm hmm.
[GAREKI] Best wait, then.
Not really yours to
give till he says.
Ask him when he comes out of it.
[NAI] Yeah. All right. I'll keep
trying to get through to him.
[NAI &amp; YOGI] Gareki!
[YOGI] This sucks!
I don't wanna say goodbye!
What if this is the last
time we see each other?
[TSUKUMO] Both of you; stop!
[YOGI] I can't help it! We've
been through so much together!
[GAREKI] Hey.
Gimme some credit.
You act like I'm gonna
flunk out of the Academy.
Where do you think I'm putting
in for once I ace it? Dumbasses.
Or do you not want
me coming back?
[YOGI] Wait... You think
we think... I'm lost.
[GAREKI] Does Four Eyes not
tell you people anything?
[TSUKUMO] Hirato.
He knew all along.
[NAI &amp; YOGI] What?
You do know what a manipulative
fink you are, right?
[Hirato laughs]
[JIKI] It's because he survived
that shipwreck, isn't it?
That's what this whole
thing has been about.
[KIICHI] What do you mean?
[JIKI] Kafka's
experimental freighter.
[KIICHI] Oh, yeah.
[HIRATO] Everything happens
for a reason, my friends.
The shipwreck.
Nai and Gareki's paths crossing
and intersecting with our own.
[TSUKITACHI] Does seem
rather miraculous. I guess.
[HIRATO] Ha. Lives dovetail
in mysterious ways.
[HIRATO] Take Nai,
for example.
Who'd believe he's the glue that
holds all of this together?
[GAREKI] See ya.
[GAREKI] Now what?
[NAI] You're warm.
I just had to check.
[GAREKI] What?
[GAREKI] Knock. It. Off!!