[AZANA] Well, first off, a thank
you's in order for putting up
with such a long flight.
Secondly, I'm sad to say
the place we're looking
for is a bit of a hike--
[YOGI] But.. We...
Damn you, Captain Hirato!
[HIRATO] Let's talk about
the last show for a moment.
From what I understand, you
rather had your hands full.
[HIRATO "The play's ending
didn't make much sense."
"Nyanperowna was
not very friendly."
These are direct quotes
from a public survey.
[HIRATO] I have
literally dozens.
Don't look so grim.
You kept the show going and
no one was gravely injured.
Far as I'm concerned, that's
a gold star for you both.
[HIRATO] Next up is
Rinole. City of Ice.
I know it sounds bleak.
But it's not a mission.
It's a vacation.
[YOGI] What kind of
cynical, sadistic overlord
calls this a vacation?
[AZANA] Your attention
please, everyone.
I have something for you,
care of Captain Hirato.
[YOGI] Great.
Is it a severed head?
[YOGI] Whatever.
[YOGI] Hang on.
What the...?
[YOGI] Is that a snowman?
[NAI] Snow man?
[TSUKUMO] The Research
Tower engineering team
put him together. He's designed
to keep us warm. Called Yukkin.
[YOGI] Yukkin?
[NAI] Yukkin!
[YUKKIN] Yukkin.
[YOGI] H... He's adorable.
[YOGI] And toasty!
I take it back, capt'n.
You're not sadistic.
An overlord, yes,
but not sadistic.
One day I'll wrap my
head around you!
[GAREKI] Yeah, whatever.
Why do I get the feeling we're
being used as bait again?
[GAREKI] I'm good for more than
dangling on a hook, dammit.
Put me in the game.
I'm the one with the legitimate
vendetta here; I need closure.
You sons of bitches owe me.
[YOGI] Where are my manners?
[YOGI] I'm hogging
all the warmth.
[NAI] He is cold.
He's been blowing his hands.
[GAREKI] Gimme a
break, dude; I'm not five.
Besides, chicks
and kids first.
[TSUKUMO] I'm a year
older than you Gareki,
not some pathetic child.
Please help yourself.
[GAREKI] Look, just give
the damn thing to Nai!
[YOGI] Gareki!
[YOGI] That's not how he's
s'posed to be used...
Alrighty. So. If you need me,
I'll be staying at the inn.
[NAI] Um, Gareki.
[MAKUNOBE] I am in firm
disagreement as to your letting
this potentially dangerous
creature roam free.
[AKARI] I urge you to keep in
mind that Niji, the species
from which Nai was fashioned,
are unimaginably rare.
Their natural habitat is
complex; too complex to recreate
under lab conditions. None
have survived captivity long.
[AKARI] They appear to thrive
on the abundant aural stimuli
of their native eco-system.
The absence of these sounds,
along with the stress of
prolonged confinement,
overwhelms their immune
systems. I hypothesize
the best course is to
classify Nai as "free-range."
[MAKUNOBE] Kafka nearly
abducted him once;
why make their job easier?
[HIRATO] With all due respect,
the Research Tower
and Circus have very
different plans for Nai.
To them, he is an
irresistible puzzle box
from which technological
riches are to be pried.
To us, though,
he is simply a lure.
A tool for bringing varugas
out of the woodwork.
Unfortunate, but factual.
[HIRATO] What I hope all of
you can understand is that
the risk of capture is a basic
function of this important role.
I appreciate your
concern lest the enemy
get their hooks into him,
but should that occur...
I will kill Nai personally.
[AKARI] You cold son of a bitch!
You're not wide of the mark.
I may view Nai only
as a specimen. But unlike
you, who he depends on
to protect him, I don't presume
the right to take his life!
[HIRATO] How noble of you.
[AKARI] Excuse me?
[HIRATO] You stand as a beacon
to life as its own virtue.
And I as the dark inverse
of that sentiment.
We are the mirror
image of one another.
[AKARI] Insolent bastard!
That smirk is just
begging for a fist!
[TSUKITACHI] Please. C'mon,
girls, you're both pretty.
[AKARI] Nobody asked
you for your two cents!
At least Hirato
tries to be polite!
You're just a
self-satisfied punk!
[TSUKITACHI] Pull in your claws
there, doc, it was a joke.
[HIRATO] If you'll
excuse me, Mister Akari.
[TSUKITACHI] Despite
appearances, there's more
humanitarian in him
than you think.
He doesn't want
to take Nai out.
Least not if he
can help it--really.
Think about it.
Read between the lines.
He was just trying to get
the brass off your back
about letting
Nai run around.
You persuaded them
dissecting the little guy
was a bad idea, right?
He's with you:
He wants him alive as much
as you do, if not moreso.
Believe me, he knows how
to deal with these people.
It's a gift.
Hey. You're birds of a feather.
You gotta love how long
it's taking to decrypt that
notebook. Not to mention
how often a certain someone--
you--lays into 'em.
If it comes to it, we've got a
tracking device in his bracelet.
You can rest easy, doc:
Nai's in good hands.
[GAREKI] Let's go.
[YOGI] Yukkin!
Come here, boy!
[YUKKIN] Yuuu!
Yu-kkin! Yu-kkin! Yuuu!
[YOGI] So awesome!
[GAREKI] So ridiculous.
[YOGI] Is it just me, or is
the air creepy thick in here?
[YOGI] All better. I think.
Team One's already been here.
Used to be the country estate
of some Kafka mucky muck.
[GAREKI] What do
they expect us to find?
[TSUKUMO] We're
conducting a finer sweep.
Making sure nothing was
missed the first time around.
Standard procedure.
Keep an eye out
for any documentation
that ties back to Kafka.
[YOGI] Hey, Nai.
You warmed up yet?
[YOGI] Oh, of course you have.
Make you a deal, my friend.
When the blizzard
dies down a little,
you can go play in the snow.
How's that sound?
[NAI] Okay!
Snow is fun!
It's all powdery and
squeaks under your feet!
[YOGI] Cool.
[GAREKI] Yeah, uh, I gotta
admit, it was really...
Really kinda neat, I guess.
[YOGI] It never
occurred to me...
Was this Gareki's first
time seeing snow too?
Must've really liked it to let
that comment slip. Adorbs.
[YOGI] Okey-doke!
No stone unturned!
Then our last day here,
we'll play like we mean it!
[NAI] Hooray!
[GAREKI] Well, that was a
complete and utter waste
of company time.
[YOGI] Not really.
We did our job.
If nothing's there,
nothing's there.
[NAI] Where'd Yukkin go?
[YOGI] Huh?
[YUKKIN] Yukkin.
Yukkin. Yukkin. Yu?
[KIHARU] See, what'd I
tell ya? Ace in the hole.
[KAGIRI] Yeah, but...
what is it, exactly?
[YUKKIN]
Yu. Yu. Yukkin.
[YOGI] 'Kay, look. I'll go
back and retrace our steps.
You all get to the inn.
[GAREKI] Nai. See if you can
pick up the thing's voice.
All this damn snow's
gonna make it hard for us.
It basically muffles everything.
[NAI] Right. Listening!
[TSUKUMO] Come on,
time's running short.
[YOGI] 'Kay.
Right behind you.
[KIHARU] Bro! Check it out!
He's super warm!
I could seriously play
with you for hours!
...yu, yu, yu, yu!
Yu? Yu!
[KAGIRI] Dude. This thing's
from Circus Airship Two.
First I've ever seen one,
so it's gotta be rare.
[KIHARU] Aha.
So they are here.
Woo hoo! Talk about
timing, right?
Another hour and the jig
would've been up!
[KAGIRI] You realize if
we leave anything behind,
Mr. Uro will redecorate that
creepy old mansion's foyer
with our insides.
[KIHARU] What? Then let's
earn those bonuses
and take Circus out ourselves!
[KAGIRI] Lay off the caffeine.
You're a pain in the ass.
But y'know, if it means
I can line my pockets
with a few more Circus
artifacts, maybe we should.
Worth a shot.
[NAI] What's that?
[YOGI] Hope the poor
guy didn't fall in.
I should go take a look.
[NAI] Then let me go
down there with you!
[YOGI] Sure, why not?
I can use those ears of yours.
[TSUKUMO] Just be careful.
[YOGI] Granted,
it's dark, but I swear
this place looks manmade.
[YOGI] Yukkin! Hello?
[NAI] I hear
something that way.
[TSUKUMO] Gareki, what--?
[clang]
[Yogi moans]
[YOGI] Sorry. My bad.
Hey, Tsukumo?
You mind keeping watch up there
in case something happens?
[GAREKI] Totally manmade.
Last I checked,
lanterns don't
form by themselves.
[YOGI] Hello.
[GAREKI] I'd say there's
a pretty good chance
we're under the
mansion right now.
[YOGI] Of course.
[YOGI] I think it's
best if you stay here.
No tellin'
what's behind this.
[YOGI] It's a ghost!
Run for your lives!
[GAREKI] Damn it, what
the hell is your problem?
Calm down!
It's a friggin' doll!
[YOGI] Nai! What are
you doing? Get back!
Nooo!
[YOGI] Um, okay.
A nervous box.
[YUKKIN] Yukkin.
[TSUKUMO] Yukkin!
Oh, thank heavens!
Where'd you run off to?
You had us worried sick.
[KAGIRI] What I tell ya?
She's Circus to the core.
[KIHARU] Duh. Why else would
she be standin' over the hole?
Or be all lovey
with the snowman?
You don't gotta spell
it out. I'm not an idiot.
[KAGIRI] I beg to differ.
She could've been a civilian,
in which case we'd have broken
Mr. Uro's cardinal rule
about keeping a low profile.
[KIHARU] Dude.
Hold up a sec.
Are we sure that doesn't
apply either way?
[KAGIRI] If we left witnesses.
Which we won't.
[KAGIRI] Dead men tell no tales.
Neither do dead girls.
But they can earn
us brownie points.
[TSUKUMO] How did
he sneak up on me?
That should be
impossible. Unless...
[YOGI] Heads up, Tsukumo!
We're coming out!
[KAGIRI] Kiharu!
[KIHARU] Damn,
she wasn't alone!
Yogi!
[YOGI] Everyone okay?
All in one piece?
[GAREKI] We're good.
[NAI] Yeah.
[YOGI] Something's
going on up there.
Tsukumo could be in danger!
[GAREKI] Hold on.
[GAREKI] Hey, there's no
sense in bein' unprepared.
[YOGI] Wh-Where on Earth
did you get that thing?
[GAREKI] Found it
in the library.
[YOGI] That's, uh, kind of
intense for a souvenir, huh?
[GAREKI] We're going
back to the doll room.
♪
[YOGI] Tsukumo,
we're here!
[TSUKUMO]
Yogi! How did...?
[YOGI] Sorry, hon; didn't mean
to startle you. We sort of...
Well, Gareki found a few
odds and ends lying around.
Threw together a
makeshift grenade.
[KIHARU] Hey, come on!
[BOTH] Did'ja forget about us?
[GAREKI] Varugas!
[NAI] Look out!
[TSUKUMO] Oh, god--Nai!
[KIHARU] Ah! Jackass,
that really hurts!
[GAREKI] Yeah, I know.
Kinda the point.
[KAGIRI] Dude, check
out the primo duds
that emo kid's rockin'!
That's limited edition
Research Tower winter gear!
[YOGI] Tsukumo, quick!
Get Nai out of harm's way!
[KAGIRI] It's one of the only
pieces not in my collection!
[KAGIRI] I must have...!
[YOGI] It's okay, I've
got this. Just be safe.
[YOGI] Nai-bait worked again.
[YOGI] Stay as close to me as
you can. You got that, cowboy?
[GAREKI] Excuse me? Case
you forgot, I have a gun.
And don't call me that!
[YOGI] Ah, damn it, Gareki!
I'm trying to do my job!
That's protecting you!
Which one of us is Circus
and which one of us is not?
[YOGI] Case you
forgot, I'm me.
I've got powers?
Besides, even if it wasn't
an issue of work ethics,
you're my friend!
[GAREKI] What? Seriously?
Since when, dude?
[YOGI] You're killin' me here.
[YOGI] Uh... well, like...
[YOGI] Smooth move, Yogi.
Way to make things awkward.
Maybe he doesn't reciprocate.
Can't even think of the
last time he used my name.
Oh, god. He despises
me. I knew it.
[GAREKI] Fine.
So you're a badass.
Believe it or not, I can
see that. It's just...
I'm no slouch either.
[YOGI] I...
Sure. My bad.
[GAREKI] You give 'em the biz.
I'll watch your back.
[YOGI] Perfect!
Shing! Ba-zing! Behold the epic
manliness of your opponent!
I am Circus operative Yogi!
On behalf of Airship Two.
En garde! Do your worst!
[TSUKUMO] Forgive me.
This is all my fault.
[NAI] No, it's not.
You put yourself in harm's
way for me. So I owe you one.
But from here on out,
we can't risk you getting hurt.
What would we do if
something happened to you?
You scared me back there, Nai.
[NAI] I just... I wanna be
strong like Circus. Like you.
[TSUKUMO]
Don't be silly.
Emotionally, you're as
strong as they come.
Look at what you've
been through, Nai.
You never let it get to you.
You're like an oak tree in a
thunderstorm. It's astonishing.
[TSUKUMO] You inspire me.
And I'm not the only one.
Think about your
friend, Karoku.
For us. Promise
you'll stay safe.
For the record, it sucks that
I can't scratch his damn coat.
I can't get into my groove!
Can't we just leave these guys
and focus on the runaways?
[KAGIRI] Forget Miss Priss
and the kewpie doll!
We got way bigger
fish to fillet!
These two are the jackpot!
Focus on them!
[YOGI] Wait a second.
So they're not after Nai?
[GAREKI] Hey. The guy you
answer to. What's he like?
[BOTH] Eh?
[GAREKI] I want details on
who's pullin' your strings.
[YOGI] I'm an idiot.
Of course he hates me.
Who wouldn't in his shoes?
I mean, I just stood by and
let his friend get killed.
[KIHARU] I'm guessing he
probably means Mr. Uro.
Speaking of which, he's gonna
kick our asses over this one.
I've got it!
Let's go berserk!
[KAGIRI] Eh, fine. It's a
royal pain, but whatever.
[KAGIRI] No more
holdin' back, huh?
[KIHARU] We'll show
'em how it's done!
[KAGIRI] Final Dungeon.
Boss Fight!
[KAGIRI] Here's the haps: a
signal on a special frequency
just played havoc on
your optic nerves.
In laymen's terms, you've
been blinded by the light.
[KIHARU] Hidey-ho,
pretty boy!
[YOGI] Ugh. Gareki!
Lemme hear your voice!
[GAREKI] Where...?
[KAGIRI] Sorry!
That's cheating!
[YOGI] Gareki!
Where are...?
[KIHARU] Really? Dude, I was
so expecting more from you.
[YOGI]
Ga... re... ki.
[GAREKI] C'mon, focus!
[KIHARU] Uh...
[Yogi laughs]
Let's spice things up a bit,
huh? Have some real fun.
[YOGI] Laughter may
be the best medicine.
But screaming's a close second.
[Yogi screams]
[GAREKI] Yogi!
[KIICHI] Oh, darling,
I can't believe
they've packed you
off to Rinole!
[TSUKUMO] It's
perfectly routine.
[KIICHI] Promise not to
forget me while you're away!
[TSUKUMO] I won't be gone
for long. You'll be fine.
[KIICHI] Fine?
I'm absolutely distraught!
[TSUKUMO]
Yeah. You'll live.