[AKARI] Are you
out of your minds?
[AKARI] Excuse us.
We need privacy, please.
[YOGI] What a relief, huh?
That it wasn't serious.
[NAI] So I can
be where he is?
[TSUKUMO] Captain Hirato's
making arrangements
as we speak.
Just a little longer.
[NAI] Oh. Thank you.
[YOGI] The thing to
do now is rest, okay?
[GAREKI] Yogi.
[GAREKI] So, being a "Child of
Airship Two" means... what?
[YOGI] Huh?
[GAREKI] Cap'n Four-eyes.
He asked if I wanted to be one.
Didn't feel the
need to elaborate.
[YOGI] A child of
Airship Two. Oh, man.
[YOGI] Well, uh...
You know... I'm not real sure.
[NAI] Karoku. I'm coming.
[HIRATO] I concur.
This is very likely a trap.
[TSUKITACHI]
Well, assuming it is,
they've overplayed
their hand.
We have a golden
opportunity here, guys.
If we allow ourselves
to get ambushed,
we'd make some real headway.
[HIRATO] The mansion where our
man from the Lindain Group
disappeared is
clearly the key.
It's... where Tsukumo
was held captive as well.
She ran into Eleska there.
Palnedo's granddaughter.
That in and of itself
is rather telling.
What's more, she and Karoku
are somehow connected.
That intel came from Yanari,
the Lindain man's son.
The other major tell
Is that Karoku told Nai
to come to the
"Misty Mansion."
[AKARI] So report it
to the Command Tower.
The hell's this
have to do with me?
If we wait on the bureaucrats,
the lead'll go tits up.
We don't have the luxury of
waiting for a green light.
[HIRATO] If the distress
signal was genuine,
then it came from
one of our own.
We cannot abandon him
to Kafka's evil whim.
He holds the key
to Nai's creation.
Not to mention a
certain notebook.
Think of all
your hard work.
Aren't you tired of running
down blind alleys?
Yeah, right. You've
got just as much
of a stake in
this as we do.
[HIRATO] At dawn,
we launch a sneak attack.
[AKARI] I'm in.
[TSUKITACHI]
Ha! Badass!
[AKARI] On one condition.
I get to come along.
[HIRATO] Who else is qualified
to collect the potentially
time-sensitive data
likely to be on site?
Not us. That's for certain.
[HIRATO] You wanted
to talk; go right ahead.
[GAREKI] I'm gonna be
part of your little raid.
And you can't stop me.
[HIRATO] It's classified
and you're a civilian.
Not a very happy combination.
[HIRATO] Is that all?
[GAREKI] Whatever. I'd probably
be less than useless anyway.
[GAREKI] Fine, then.
How much longer I got?
You're getting what
you need from Nai;
he's kosher with you guys.
I'm feelin' kinda like a third
wheel here, you know?
[HIRATO] I see. Someone's eager
to take their leave of Circus.
[GAREKI] So what the hell
am I supposed to do?
Stand around with my
thumb up my butt?
Fade into the background?
There's no point
in me bein' here if I'm
just a part of the scenery.
[GAREKI] Yeah, that's right.
[HIRATO]
Ah. Understood.
I'll see what can be done
about cutting you loose.
[GAREKI] Good.
[HIRATO] Unless... you
meant it about the raid.
[GAREKI] Wait. Really?
Damn straight!
[HIRATO] Time to start
earning your keep.
[YOGI]
Reassignment? But...
[HIRATO] Our target
is the Misty Manion,
estate of Mister Palnedo,
CEO of the Gald Company.
Our objective is to retrieve
Karoku, and if possible,
uncover evidence
linking Palnedo to Kafka.
Anything else is a bonus.
All personnel, standby.
Review the mission briefing
and be ready to move out.
[AKARI] Get a hold
of yourself, man.
For crying out loud, I've known
toddlers less afraid of needles.
[YOGI] It's not the
needle that scares me;
it's being this close to you.
[YOGI] So, uh...
Why exactly'd you go
to the trouble of
being here today--
[AKARI] Well, if you
must know, I insisted on
being part of the
Misty Mansion raid.
[YOGI] But you're a doctor.
[AKARI] And you're a
soldier on a deadly mission.
My job supports yours.
Bear in mind, though: field
surgery gets fairly primitive.
May have to saw off
a limb without anesthetic.
[IKAMI] As suspected,
an encrypted transmission
was sent from Airship Two
to an unknown recipient.
[HIRATO] Did you jam it?
[IKAMI] Absolutely, sir...
Nothing got outside.
[HIRATO] Everyone,
activate your bracelets.
Secure the lock. Skyward!
Commence test.
[HIRATO] Be aware of
your comrades' movements
at all times. Give your
instincts the reins out there.
[NAI] Karoku.
[KAROKU] Nai.
[GAREKI] Look, I know
he's here, so ditch the act.
I'm like his best friend;
he called me and told me
he was being held
here against his will.
[UNDERLING C] What?
[YOGI] Uh, let me explain.
This young man
came to you in tears.
He's confused, surely, but
perhaps, if you'd be so kind,
it would be possible to
lay his fears to rest?
Wait, how rude of me!
Ahem! National Defense Agency.
Circus Airship Two. Yogi.
[UNDERLING C] Your little
friend ain't here.
[UNDERLING B] Maybe you
just had a bad dream?
[GAREKI] Uh-huh.
He said you'd say that.
Screw it! I'm goin' in!
[UNDERLING C] Damn it, kid!
[YOGI] Wait!
Come back!
Just stay there! I'll have
him back in two shakes!
[UNDERLING B]
Ring the guardhouse!
[IVA] I gotta admit:
at first blush,
the plan sounded
phenomenally dunderheaded.
[HIRATO] I'm aware.
The trick of course,
is using their pristine
public façade against them.
They'd be loath to shed
blood at the front gate.
So that, naturally,
was our in.
[PALNEDO] What is going on?
[UNDERLING C] Sir, we, uh...
Well, they said Karoku
reached out to them
for help and then they...
[PALNEDO] I'm sure it's
nothing. Keep it together.
Just ferret them out.
With force. Understood?
[URO] Circus.
Interesting they choose
now of all times
to grow a pair.
One almost feels pity for them.
The proverbial Pandora's Box
won't be opened by
their kind, I'm afraid.
Let your imaginations
run wild, as humans do.
Leave the revolution
to us. It's what we do.
[YOGI] Wait up!
Time to fly!
[YOGI] Hey! Where'd you
get that thing from?
[GAREKI] Front gate. One of
the goons had it on him.
[YOGI] Wow. Artful dodger!
[GAREKI] Yeah, whatevs.
Figured they had to have a map
of the grounds, you know?
[ELESKA] Karoku!
We have to go back!
Uro was saying you need
to be in your room!
[KAROKU] Sounds like
something's up.
[ELESKA] I have no idea.
But whatever's happening,
I'm with you.
That's how it should be.
[KAROKU] Do you feel that?
The sky. The wind.
They're dancing.
[KAROKU] It's going to rain
soon. We should get inside.
That, and I have a visitor.
[ELESKA]
Wha? But... Who?
[KAROKU] Someone
very special to me.
[GAREKI] Easy! They call
themselves security?
I've cut off their lines
of communication.
[YOGI] You're really good
at this. I'm surprised.
I'd love to have a
look at the library
you absorbed all this
knowledge from.
I mean, with your smarts, you,
uh, really ought to consider...
I dunno. I mean... If you were
interested, you could, uh...
[GAREKI] Sorry. Say
again. What library?
Heard you call me a genius,
then I tuned out.
Anyway, dude, I'm in.
They're connected to
Airship Two. You're up!
[YOGI] Yeah, right.
Which button do I press?
[GAREKI] The one
in front of you!
Then to the right of that.
Then bottom left.
Then the toggle switch
next to that. C'mon!
[UNDERLING C]
Huh? Oh, crap.
[UNDERLING B]
The hell just happened?
[YOGI] Network override
is complete, sir.
[HIRATO] Move in.
[TSUKITACHI] Good morning,
gentlemen. Circus business!
If you have two brain
cells to rub together,
you'll stand down and
do exactly as you're told.
[JIKI] Right. On with
the treasure hunt, huh?
Lend me your ears, Nai.
Give me an idea of
what we're looking for.
[JIKI] If we don't uncover
something, you and Gareki...
Ah, better not
to think about it.
[PALNEDO] Why are these clowns
such a problem for you people?
[UNDERLING C] They've
hacked our network, sir!
All our data is being
downloaded by their damn ship!
[YOGI] Time to go! C'mon!
[URO] Heh. How lovely.
Our friends presume to
lead this dance, do they?
I must congratulate
them on their new moves.
But they still have a thing
or two to learn about rhythm.
[NAI] I hear
something really bad!
[the sound of sirens]
[HIRATO] The enemy
knows it's been hacked.
All units. Be ready.
They're about to get ugly.
[YOGI] Take cover!
[GAREKI] Son of a bitch.
[TSUKITACHI] Never underestimate
their desperation!
[KIICHI] Pick up the pace!
[TSUKITACHI] Oh, good.
Target practice.
[KIICHI] I've got this, sir!
[KAGIRI] What? Come on!
We're worth two of you!
[KIICHI] You're about to find
out you got it backwards!
[KIHARU] Where does
Circus recruit from, man?
They're all so freakin' cute!
[KIICHI] Then lemme put this
"cute" scythe up your ass!
[ELESKA] Karoku! Open the
door! You're scaring me!
[URO] We should leave, Mistress.
I don't think he's in there.
[ELESKA] Yes, he is! And I'm
not leaving without him!
[UNDERLING P]
There's no time!
This place is
crawling with Circus!
[ELESKA] Wait, Circus?
[KAROKU] That, and I
have a visitor.
Someone very special to me.
It can't be. That girl...
She's come for Karoku.
Shoulda known...
The two of them...
No! I'm not letting this happen!
Uro! That Circus whore has
come to take him away from me!
We have to stop her!
♪
[YOGI] Dorn Kiste!
[GAREKI] Okay,
that was a close one.
Yogi totally just
saved my bacon.
[NAI] Come on! Give me
something we can use!
[Jiki chuckles]
[JIKI] Oh, I'm sorry.
You were just so...
No offense, but you were
acting like an animal.
Your eyes. Try listening
with them closed.
I'll keep lookout. You just
focus on the sounds, 'kay?
[NAI] Mmkay.
[ELESKA] Uro! Keep that
tramp away from my Karoku!
[URO] But of course, miss.
I don't think it'll be much
of a challenge to kill her.
You go. I'll handle it.
[URO] Greetings, ladies.
To what do we owe the pleasure?
[IVA] Uro. Isn't that right?
Thanks for letting
us drop in like this.
[URO] Indeed. Although there
isn't much here for you now.
May I ask what you
were hoping to find?
[IVA] Oh, I don't know.
Everything seems to be
in order, I think.
If this were one of our
routine inspections,
you'd be in the black.
[URO] Encouraging--
[IVA] My, how brave.
Didn't even dodge.
[IVA] Surprising, for someone
of your training. C'est la vie.
I should tell you, though, the
act isn't really fooling anyone.
After all, you did just fall
six stories. Points for trying.
[TSUKUMO] You're under arrest.
Under suspicion of being a
Level Six operative of Kafka.
[HIRATO] Excuse me a moment.
[KAROKU] Been a while,
hasn't it?
Nai's come to see me,
you know. He's right outside.
But cheer up.
You can come with.
[TSUKUMO] Behold a shining
bouquet of falling stars!
Let the sheep gaze heavenward!
National Defense Agency Circus.
I am First Lieutenant Tsukumo!
[IVA] And, yeah, me!
[BOTH] Engage!
[TSUKUMO] Sterne!
[URO] Goodbye.
[AZANA] Doctor. You
really think all this
will amount to a hill of beans?
[AKARI] What the hell
are you doing?
[AZANA] Because I just
don't know anymore. I mean,
I'd like to be optimistic, sure.
It's just so difficult.
Maybe the varuga simply
needs a chance to flourish.
It's only fair, right?
They do give Circus
a run for their money. Maybe
Kafka is the wave of the future.
Think about it:
if right's on our side,
why do we keep losing?
It's a thorn.
I lost count of the
nights I've lied awake,
trying to puzzle out why it's
always such an uphill battle.
Then boom! I got it. It's law
of the jungle! Tooth and claw!
[Azana laughs hysterically]
[AKARI] Azana?
We can't conceive of it 'cause
we're an inferior species.
Biology makes us low
man on the totem pole.
The truth has
passed us by, doc!
This is a fight we're
destined to lose.
[AKARI] What on earth
has gotten into--
[AZANA] You're a smart man!
There's got to be a place for
you in the new world order!
They'd embrace you as a brother!
No question about it!
[AKARI] Azana.
What are you...
[JIKI] Leleti.
[NAI] Jiki.
[JIKI] I need you to
stay focused, Nai.
[SHEEP] Baa!
[NAI] Oh, no!
Sheep! I'm sorry!
[JIKI] It's okay;
they're expendable.
We can make more of
them any time we need.
[NAI] But we played
hide and seek.
[JIKI] They're all identical;
chances are you never
played with that one.
One sheep is just like another.
That's what makes them sheep.
[NAI] That's not true.
Everyone's different. Deep down.
[NAI] Two flowers
may look alike.
But only till you look closer.
[NAI] If Karoku dies, there
won't be another one. Ever.
That's why I have to find him.
Because everyone... Everyone...
[NAI] I talked to the sky about
how it was going to rain.
I talked to the little
creatures in the wood.
They said the
flowers were happy.
[NAI] They hear me. That's
right. My voice can carry, too.
[IVA] Krone Saphir!
[URO] You're holding up
admirably well.
My respect to you both...
Our skills are a world apart.
Your own have you at a
distinct disadvantage.
[URO] Where's your captain?
Sitting comfortably?
He must have a great deal
of faith in you, young miss.
Disheartening he
doesn't join the fray...
What? No! That door
should be sealed!
[URO] Banshees?
[TSUKUMO] This was
all a diversion.
Our captain wanted
you captured alive.
[IVA] Ha! You have no
idea how difficult it is
to pull my punches.
[GAREKI] The hell--?
[Gareki sighs]
[YOGI] Oh, god. Oh god
oh god oh god! What's wrong?
A sigh like that never
means anything good.
Talk to me, buddy!
Don't give up hope!
Don't turn your back
on the world--on life!
We're here for you!
[GAREKI] Knock it off,
will ya? I'm just tired.
[YOGI] Oh, my bad.