[TSUKUMO] Gareki.
Gareki.
You can go in and check
on him, if you like.
[YOGI] Tell me straight, doc!
Nai is gonna be ok, right?
Right? I mean,
there's gotta be...
Incoming. Duck.
[HEALER] Stop blabbering!
Ahhh! Owwww.
My patient needs
a little rest, by god!
[HEALER] Physically, he's
ship-shape.
His brain wave
patterns, however,
show several irregularities
before he went under.
He ought to be sent
to the Research Tower
for more in-depth analysis.
I see. Well, then.
There's not a moment to waste.
Please excuse us.
Do me a favor and take the clown
in the hall with you, please.
[HIRATO] You don't wish
to use him for testing?
Healer. Any idea when
he might wake up?
I failed to protect him.
I was responsible.
He'll be fine, my dear. Try not
to worry too much about it.
That said, he isn't the
only one who needs rest.
You shoulder more than your
fair share of the burden.
It's not healthy.
I'm going back. Please.
Look after Nai for me.
[HEALER] Hmm?
So even after all his pain,
you didn't find a thing.
What're you?
Some incompetent quack?
Least I'm not
an insolent prick.
Your friend is in good hands.
I was just helping
the dumb brat out.
I don't have time for friends.
You know, a wiser man
than me once said...
"You can pick your friends
and you can pick your nose,
but you can't pick
your friend's nose."
[GAREKI] Where you
goin', beardy?
[HEALER] I need a
late-night snack-a-roo.
Keep an eye on
our patient for me.
[GAREKI] Wait! What?
[KAROKU] Nai. Try to
focus on my voice.
Something's distracting
you. I can tell.
[NAI] Karoku?
Where are you?
[KAROKU] There's someone new.
[NAI] Well, yeah.
[KAROKU] How 'bout that?
You've made a friend.
Good on you for
being resourceful.
But... It's time to
part ways with him.
But we... just met.
[KAROKU] Think of the storm
cloud on your tail, son.
Best to send the new guy
packin'. You know this.
Yeah, but... he saved me.
Trouble is drawn to you, Nai.
Be a true friend.
Save him from yourself.
Unless you want him to break.
[NAI] Ga--
That was weird.
Knock it off.
I'm here. You're safe.
If you need something,
just ask. Within reason...
I...
[KAROKU] Unless you
want him to break.
[NAI] Go away, Gareki.
What?
You have to.
So... That's it, then.
I'm afraid... that you'll...
I'll what?
Save you a third time?
[NAI] Wait.
Gareki!
Oh, c'mon. Seriously?
You give me the bracelet
and I buzz off?
Oh, I see. Don't need me
if Circus has your back.
Pretending to be helpless
to get what you want?
Pretty damn low, man.
Yeah. I forgot
he's a lot stronger
than your average
wrinkly old grumpy Gus.
Hey! Gareki!
Do me a solid.
Go tell the bearded freak
his patient's awake.
No problemo.
Just, uh... Calm down.
We cool?
Where you goin'?
Something I said?
Aw, c'mon. Don't cry.
I'm not sure how to handle this.
Tsukomo, help?
[SHEEP] Out of bounds!
Out of bounds! Out of bounds!...
[TSUKUMO] Yogi?
What's wrong? Hello? Yogi?
[HIRATO] Understood. I shall
leave it in your capable hands.
Sorry. Won't find any
"late-night snack-a-roos" here.
[HEALER] It's about
that child's body.
You mean our mysterious ward?
Is he not on the mend?
Well, now. It's rather
difficult to explain.
For one, the boy's not human.
He's an animal.
Uh, doubtless
you're concerned...
[Hirato laughs]
[HIRATO] Pretty tasteless
joke. Even for you.
I can hear you!
Now pay attention; I don't
like repeating myself.
This is the child's true form!
What?
No way.
I analyzed his cellular
tissue thoroughly before
making my conclusion.
Our friend's a Niji.
Indigenous to the
Rainbow Forest.
A uniquely beautiful
and secluded ecosystem.
Home to a variety
of rare species.
How odd.
Wait a second. This...
is making my brain hurt.
Does not compute.
[GAREKI] So the wrinkled
windbag thinks Nai's
an endangered species?
That's a bit hard to swallow.
The hell's he on?
I know there are
monsters in human form.
Spent enough time around
Circus to learn that.
And sure, Nai's behavior's
always been... odd.
But seriously. A furball?
The name's Gareki.
What do I call you?
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE] Nai!
[NAI] Thank you.
[GAREKI] What?
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE] This makes
twice you've saved me!
Go away, Gareki!
[GAREKI] Now I come off
looking like a total ass-clown!
[HIRATO] I've informed the
Research Tower of the situation.
You'll be their escort tomorrow.
That means seeing Doctor Akari.
So. What's the deal
with Nai's bracelet?
Are you letting him keep it?
I was waiting to see
if it reacted to him.
Eh? But our bracelets
are isometric.
Nai's doesn't even
really belong to him.
Said it was some
guy's... Karoku.
[HIRATO] He might
well have been lying.
I don't think so.
[HIRATO] There is
the possibility
he's an agent of Kafka.
Well. Honestly, I was shocked
by the Healer's findings.
But I know a good kid
when I see one!
Wha... You're teasing
me, aren't you?
Hardly. You're still
his escort tomorrow.
You don't really
respect me much, huh?
Don't be sensitive.
I'm suspicious, yes.
But that's my job.
[GAREKI] Have a seat.
[GAREKI] Stay cool. You're
just dealing with some brat.
No. He's an animal.
He may look human.
But he's not.
He's a modified furball that
made me look like a jackass.
It's not even worth
getting angry about.
I mean, I save
your worthless ass,
then you tell me to get lost?
Do I scare you?
Not you!
Huh?
I'm scared of what Karoku
told me. That you'll break.
Karoku? Fine, I'm
all ears. Go ahead.
[NAI] Karoku said
you'd get caught up
in the trouble that
happens around me.
That if I didn't make you
leave... You would break.
You'd be safer if I told
you I didn't need you.
Weird, considering he's MIA.
How the hell'd he
tell you all this?
He speaks. When I sleep.
[GAREKI] Great. So he
dreamt their conversation.
What a nut-job.
[NAI] That if I didn't make
you leave... You would break.
You'd be safer if I told
you I didn't need you.
[GAREKI] I don't
believe this kid.
I save him time after time,
and he's worried about me?
Lemme ask you again.
Who is this Karoku to you?
He's been around as
long as I could remem--
[GAREKI]
Yeah, I got that.
Move on. How long
are we talkin' about?
[NAI] Forever.
I need more than that.
[GAREKI] Does he not know?
Okay, so...
You tell him about me?
He know who I am?
I told him you saved me.
[GAREKI] Is that it?
Then why would Karoku
try to send me away?
He's his friend, right?
Is he being malicious,
or is it jealousy?
Besides, if they
can chat like this,
how'd Nai end up on his own?
And how exactly do they speak?
If that's in his bag of tricks,
this Karoku guy
seems like a pretty
twisted S.O.B.
Yeah. It's official.
My image of this dude
is now completely changed.
He's an enigma.
Though I'm curious why he's
trying to pick a fight with me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Don't sweat it.
Just a misunderstanding.
I don't think you're
"low," or anything.
Uh... Besides--where's the
fun in playing safe, right?
I don't break all
that easy, you know.
[HIRATO] We'll conduct a
more thorough examination
once we arrive at the RT.
Guess it isn't exactly
human experimentation.
Still, you better
handle him nice.
The Healer will be present.
If you become concerned,
ask him for assistance.
[YOGI] Yeah, that's
s'posed to be a comfort?
Yogi.
Be vigilant out there.
I will. But...
What are you and
Tsukumo doing, sir?
[KIICHI] Summoned to
the Round Table of Z?
Wouldn't it have been
easier to take him
to the Research Tower
in the first place?
[JIKI] They're wise to
play it conservatively.
Until they learn more
about the bracelet's owner.
[KIICHI] Ugh. That is so boring.
[Tsukitachi yawns]
[TSUKITACHI] Five more minutes.
And away we go!
[YOGI] Yahoo!
Oh. Tsukumo, dear!
It has been far too long.
You haven't put
on weight, have you?
Now, now.
[TSUKITACHI] Yeah, sorry.
We still haven't found
any hard evidence on
corporations suspected
of working as fronts for Kafka.
Although, there has
been a sizable increase
in varuga activity
as of late.
[BYZANTE] By hook or by
crook, Kafka's gotten hold
of our banned
evolutionary research.
This, despite it
being classified.
[TOKITATSU] The mistakes
of our former brethren
have endangered countless
innocent lives.
Now, Captain.
Regarding this boy, Nai.
The Healer's report has
piqued our interest.
[HEALER]
The lab results indicate
no physical abnormalities
to speak of.
Other than your personality,
all is well.
Ha, ha. I'm taking
this crap off.
[HEALER] I appreciate
you putting up with
all this poking and prodding.
Now if we can find Yogi,
I think it's best for you
to have a little lie-down.
[GAREKI] Huh. I haven't seen
him since we landed, actually.
Please tell me it's
just the three of them.
Really no point running into--
Lose something?
Yah! Hey there, Dr. Akari.
[AKARI] I hope for your
sake you're putting on
a fresh patch every morning.
Allergies are nothing
to sneeze at.
Sure...
[AKARI] If you're neglectful
of this treatment,
we may have to resort
to a more painful remedy.
I, um... I'll go
change it right now!
This kind of reminds me of home.
That a fact?
Look.
Was it this green
where you came from?
It was a sinkhole.
Nothing green about it.
Living there was hard.
Always scraping to get by.
I left there,
but it followed me.
What was done to her.
I can't forget.
Y'know, since meeting you,
I've seen a lot that's
knocked me on my ass.
And honestly, I can't
take much more.
I don't wanna start
thinkin' life is...
Well, that it has a point.
I don't deserve to believe that.
What if... What if deep down
I never really wanted to leave?
What if Nai's just
a distraction?
A relief from the guilt?
From the memory of her...
[NAI] Gareki.
If it has a point,
that makes it beautiful.
If you can see it, that
means you're beautiful!
Was it something I said?
[GAREKI] Beautiful?
Are you kidding me?
I've got
thousand-yard-stare eyes.
They don't see a damn thing!
[TSUBAME] Gareki. Help me.
[AKARI] His genetic
sequence closely resembles
the formative pattern
of the varugas.
But that's not
the interesting part.
There's far more to it.
Nai is essentially
a new species.
Whoever's responsible
for creating him
can be described
in one word. Genius.
[MAKUNOBE] We must
know all the details.
Dissect him immediately!
[HIRATO]
Tsukumo. Sit down.
[AKARI] I cannot, in good
conscience, follow your orders.
[MAKUNOBE] What?
If he dies, a vast amount of
knowledge will be lost to us.
In the name of science,
I will not let any harm
come to such a
challenging specimen.
[YOGI] The Healer gave
us snacks for the trip!
[NAI] Yay!
Have some self-respect, man.
Come on. Least make 'em
give you the good stuff.
It's not like that!
Nai told me himself
he's making this journey
of his own free will, so...
Rainbow Forest?
[HEALER] It's the place we
believe you used to live.
[YOGI] If we go there,
we think we could learn a lot.
About you, of course.
And Karoku too.
But if you decide to strike
out on your own, Nai,
I'll be sound asleep tonight.
Okay. Let's do it!
If I join you, it might
help me better understand
what Karoku was saying.
See, if I can
figure all that out,
maybe life will be beautiful.
[YOGI] Have I mentioned
how proud I am of you, Nai?
Ugh, give me a break.
Can we just get
this thing in the air?
Okay. Plotting a course for
rainbows! Buckle up, kids!
Yes, yes. Just go.
Uhh... Yes, sir.
We are go for launch.
[AKARI] Rainbow Forest is a
unique ecosystem, and creates
electromagnetic interference.
This impacts visible light,
producing atypical
rainbows and mirages.
However, there's a catch.
Those E.M. waves
disturb our comm gear.
So the best way to
conduct a search, I'm told,
is through the use of sonics.
[GAREKI] If Nai did come
from here, it would explain
his sensitivity
to sound, I guess.
[AKARI]
Approximately an hour.
And though he
walks with purpose,
we've still found
nothing of note.
Strike that.
Let's go.
Only the house burned.
Go take a look around.
Spread out.
--Right!
[AKARI]
This didn't show up
during our aerial
reconnaissance.
Without Nai guiding us,
we'd never have found it.
Someone destroyed the evidence.
But how'd they get here?
Hey, Nai.
You doin' all right?
This actually isn't
the only place.
Huh?
Take us there.
[NAI] Right here.
[GAREKI] A cave?
Watch out!
Damn! Possessors!
Hello, uglies. You vultures
planning to take little Nai?
When everything's on the line,
there's no margin of error,
which of course
takes all the fun out.
But it seems you've
left me no choice.
[critter yelps]
No!
Nai!
[YOGI] Oh, no!
Gareki!
[NAI] Huh?
[GAREKI] Hey, what's this talk
about you being an animal?
[NAI] Uhhh...
[GAREKI] You totally
look like a human.
So you can
transform and stuff?
[NAI] What?
[GAREKI] Go for it!
Transform!
[NAI] What does
that even mean?