(static hisses)
(upbeat rock music)
(singing in foreign language)
(water rushing)
(faucet squeaks)
(water splashes)
(light music)
- [Aya] Something has to change.
I can't fight the executive
council feeling like this.
(light music)
- [Maya] Come on fledgling.
(blade whooshes)
(light music)
- All right!
(birds chirping)
- I heard that you
were in an accident.
Did you get hurt at all?
- No.
- From what I understand the
road was completely clear,
there wasn't another
car anywhere in sight.
So then what happened?
- A cat jumped out.
That's all.
(doors whir)
(car hums)
(birds chirping)
This body is pathetic.
It was that moment
there that I died.
My time is nearly up.
I can feel it.
Nagi
Souichiro.
(dramatic music)
- You've improved quite a
bit since your freshman days.
Well at least now
that you're a senior
you actually attend
your classes.
So you're gonna sit back here
and doze off for the rest
of the year, Natsume?
- At least you don't
have to worry about me
disrupting your class.
I'll just be back here
minding my own business.
(door rattles)
(dramatic music)
- [Teacher] Hmm?
- [Student] Who's she?
- [Student] Don't you know?
That's Natsume's little sister.
- [Student] Hey, what's
the Juken Club up to now?
(chalk whooshes)
(chalk snaps)
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
- [Souichiro] Yo,
dude, what's up?
Why'd you call me out here?
- I'm suppose to relay a
certain message to you.
It's from Mitsuomi.
(dramatic music)
- Hey, look, Aya, I've only got
one good shoulder right now.
And on top of that my
mind's hazy from this nice,
little nap I just had,
so what I'm trying to say is,
if you've got a beef with me,
forget this afterschool nonsense
and come at me now.
If you choose to pass
up this opportunity
I promise you'll never get
another one like it again.
So what do ya say?
- If the two of you want
to fight take it outside.
I'm not gonna stand here and
let you disrupt my class.
(Aya screams)
- I'm over this.
I'm really tired of
you acting like such a.
(metal clangs)
Stop playing around!
I mean it!
I'm really serious
about this, sis!
(blade cracks)
(Aya whimpers)
- What was that about
you being serious?
You're the one who's
playing, little girl.
- [Souichiro] Dude,
then that means.
- Mitsuomi wants to fight you.
Aren't you lucky?
(Souichiro chuckles)
You're never gonna
understand anything about me.
- Huh?
- What an asshole.
That's exactly what
Shin told me one day.
And now for two years,
Mitsuomi's been
mumbling that too.
It's not loud, it's just
a rumble inside his heart.
Nothing that I say to him
can lift the heavy load
that he carries with him.
But your fists might be able to.
- You got it, bro.
- [Tawara] Go, fight Mitsuomi.
And be sure you take him down.
(birds chirping)
- That was an impressive move.
(sisters screaming)
(glass shatters)
- Dammit, girl!
(dramatic music)
(sisters grunting)
(Aya screams)
(Maya laughs)
- I hope you don't mind,
but I need to borrow these.
- What?
You can't borrow
those, get back here!
- It's all right, let her go.
I think she's quite familiar
with katanas by now.
I think this will reveal
if blood is truly
thicker than water.
It's like we're dealing with
Shin Natsume all over again.
- Come clean,
you flipped that board
over, didn't you?
(dramatic music)
- I'm in complete bliss.
(sisters thudding)
(katana whooshes)
(Maya laughs)
- [Aya] Get back here!
- Can someone tell me
what just happened?
(dramatic music)
(screams) Natsume!
(Maya laughs)
- What a monster!
(Bob laughs)
(dramatic music)
(Maya laughing)
- [Aya] Come here, right now!
- [Bob] Huh?
(dramatic music)
(footsteps rumbling)
(Maya laughing)
(student grunts)
(student sighs)
- Come here! (grunts)
(bowl clatters)
(dramatic music)
Give it up, sis.
We are gonna fight!
- Was that the captain and Aya?
(dramatic music)
- I want him back!
I want you to give him back!
Souichiro-sama is mine,
you can't have him!
- First you go on a rant
about me and Mitsuomi,
and now you accuse
me of stealing that
foolish boy from you.
What is it that you
really wanna say, Aya?
It's time you figured that out.
(Aya scoffs)
- [Souichiro] On the roof?
- Man, those two chicks just
don't know when to stop,
do they?
They're even more
trouble than we are.
- All that I want to do is try
and be of help to
Souichiro-sama.
I want to be able to
fight at his side.
That's all I want.
When I first came
to this school,
I admit that I did
harbor a secret desire
to avenge my brother's death,
but now I find it harder and
harder to still hold a grudge
against Mitsuomi.
The more I come
to know about him
the less I think of him
as this awful person.
And the one thing that I
really don't understand at all
is you.
What makes you hate him so much?
Why do you feel the need
to fight him so badly?
(somber music)
Well I'm sure Souichiro-sama
will fight him for you.
All you have to say is that
you're gonna fight Mitsuomi,
and regardless of
how dangerous it is,
he'll be right at your
side fighting with you.
And as much as it
hurts me to say this,
I know there's nothing
I can do to stop him.
The only way that I can
possibly help him now,
the only choice I can make to
avoid being a burden to him,
is to become stronger,
so that one day I'll be
able to fight by his side.
- Aya, if that's
how you really feel,
then prove it to
me with your blade.
It's those actions that are
stronger than any words.
(Aya scoffs)
(bright music)
- [Aya] That's a long,
heavy nodachi blade.
She's gotta swing
from her shoulder
which won't give her much time.
That means I can get
inside the range of attack
way faster than her.
(dramatic music)
(Maya grunts)
(Aya gasps)
(blade whooshes)
(dramatic music)
There's no doubt,
right now sis is dead serious.
- On your feet, Aya.
You're here to defeat
me, aren't you?
(dramatic music)
(Aya panting)
(blades clang)
What's the problem?
I thought you said you
want to become stronger.
(dramatic music)
- [Aya] This was so foolish.
Why did I do this?
She's going to kill me!
(leg thuds)
- What do you
think you're doing?
- I'm calling it
quits right now.
Doesn't matter who wins this,
nothing good is gonna
come from this fight.
You know I thought you two
chicks were a little more
level-headed than this.
(Souichiro grunts)
(Aya gasps)
Oh, shit, dammit!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
- Aya, I may be totally
stepping outta line here,
but you clearly haven't
made any progress at all.
I taught you how to win a
serious street fight, remember?
It doesn't matter how badly
your opponent beats you up,
as long as you stick
with it you win.
So who is it you
don't wanna lose to?
(dramatic music)
(Aya huffs)
Who is it that you wanna believe
in more than anyone else?
(dramatic music)
Now go out there and win.
Win and enjoy it.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Yeah.
All right, let's go, sis.
- If that's what you
want, Aya, then bring it.
(Aya screams)
(Maya grunts)
- [Aya] Focus, focus.
Don't be afraid,
don't be afraid.
As long as I miss the
heart she'll be all right.
(metal clangs)
(dramatic music)
(Aya screams)
(knee thuds)
(Maya laughs)
(Aya scoffs)
- Those two seem
to be doing better.
Yo, every now and then you
go and say something smart.
But I am gonna get you
back for trying to kill me.
- Huh? (screams)
(bird whooshes)
Come on, dude, that's
a serious drop!
- [Emi] Those two sisters sure
are a whole lot of trouble.
- That may be true,
but it's better than two
brothers who can't even fight.
You see, my brother won't
even attempt to talk to me.
- Masataka.
- Do me a favor and
take care of him for me.
- That's something I'd do
regardless of your request.
(footsteps clacking)
(dramatic music)
- [Mitsuomi] You're finally
here, Souichiro Nagi.
- You're the one who went
and picked this fight.
There's no way that
I would turn it down.
(dramatic music)
(fist whooshes)
(Souichiro thuds)
- Stop it, Mitsuomi.
- I called you
here for a reason.
I want you to see how
this battle's gonna end.
Don't get in the way.
- I thought we agreed to settle
this in the preliminaries.
- Move aside, Maya.
- Forget it.
I wanna know why you're
suddenly in such a hurry.
(dramatic music)
(Souichiro panting)
- [Souichiro] No, don't do it.
(dramatic music)
(electricity sizzles)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Maya] Is this?
(Mitsuomi groans)
(Souichiro whooshes)
(both grunting)
(dramatic music)
(Souichiro roars)
(punches thuds)
(Souichiro screams)
- [Maya] Two Tashinko
attacks in a row?
That's too much power.
Even with the chakras fully open
there's no way the boy can win!
- Darkness devoured
me whole that day
and suddenly,
I realized the kind of
person I had become.
I'm just like him.
(dramatic orchestral music)
A monster that has
to be defeated.
And like him,
I wanted nothing more
than to disappear.
Souichiro Nagi, show me
everything you've got.
Now.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Don't, boy.
- There's someone out there
that I have to take
down no matter what,
because they're someone
else that I have to protect.
And that's why I wanna be...
Stronger!
(dramatic music)
- What is this form
that he's taking?
- [Mitsuomi] That's it!
That's the true martial artist.
(Souichiro whooshes)
(Mitsuomi thuds)
- His attack hit.
(Mitsuomi groans)
(melancholy music)
- [Mitsuomi] Take all
this remorse and regret,
these feelings of mine for Maya.
Take everything about
this wretched life
and dissolve it to nothing,
then maybe I'll have a chance
to redeem my miserable soul.
(melancholy music)
(Souichiro whooshes)
Finally, it's here.
This is exactly what
Shin had wished for,
but I wasn't able
to give it to him.
(Souichiro screams)
(melancholy music)
(Souichiro thuds)
- Boy!
- My body won't move.
- It was your chakras.
You were unable to
completely open them all up.
It's all right,
you experienced a
great deal of pressure.
Neither you mind nor your body
was in any position to
handle that kind of force.
(Souichiro whimpers)
(melancholy music)
- [Mitsuomi] We'll settle the
score in the preliminaries
as planned.
Be on time and be ready to die.
- I'll be there.
- [Maya] Mitsuomi.
(crickets chirping)
(students chattering)
- What?
My brother and Nagi did this?
You're kidding me.
- It's true.
Of course, he did
get beaten to a pulp.
- Well that makes sense.
- However, he showed he
had the power to win.
- Hmm?
- [Aya] Wow, so that's
what happened last night?
- Yeah, and I
finally get it now.
Now I know why I
wanna become stronger.
See, I just thought that
I kinda owed it to you
to tell you this in person.
What I'm trying to
get at is that I...
- Same with me.
I too realized something when
I was fighting my sister,
I learned how amazing she is.
- You what?
- She's so strong and pretty,
and her body's in perfect shape.
There's not one thing that I
can do better than she can.
So I guess it just makes
sense, Souichiro-sama,
that you'd fall for her.
(upbeat pop music)
But I still refuse to give up!
Someday I'm gonna be even
better than my sister
at everything.
And then when that happens,
you're gonna have no choice
but to make me your
wife, Souichiro-sama.
(Souichiro chuckles nervously)
(upbeat pop music)
And that's a promise!
- What are you talking about?
You can't make
promises like that.
There you go again,
acting all whacked out.
Get a grip, will ya?
- [Aya] I'm just
telling the truth.
- [Souichiro]
Enough of this crap!
Let's go, we've got
training to do, dammit!
- [Aya] Yeah, let's go,
no matter where it takes us.
We have to believe in ourselves
far more than anyone else.
(Bob grunting)
Never let the small
stuff keep you down.
Stop staring at the ground
and start looking at the
path that lies before you.
(Emi groans)
- [Souichiro] Will you hurry up?
- [Aya] Coming!
I mean, the sky is
so big and limitless,
so why not?
(upbeat music)