(static)
(slow dramatic music)
(energetic music)
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Yo party time
♪ Party time
♪ Yeah
♪ We try to party time
♪ Party time
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Bomb a head.
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Bomb a head
♪ Yeah bomb a head
♪ Bomb bomb bomb a head
♪ Bomb a head
- Toudou Academy senior and
Executive Council president,
Shin Natsume is ready to fight.
(dramatic music)
- I guess now we're going
from punishment time
to serious monster killing time.
(knuckles cracking)
Yah!
I can't believe he did that.
(Shin laughing)
Shit, the bastard stabbed me.
(Bunshichi groaning)
(Shin grunting)
(Shin laughing manically)
(gentle music)
(metal clanging)
(Bunshichi groaning)
(Shin laughing manically)
- Mana, I think
that'll be enough.
- Shin!
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
- [Mana] Get him to a
hospital immediately.
- [Man] Yes, ma'am.
- Has he calmed down, now?
- Yes, I'm very sorry for
everything that's happened, sir.
Shin.
Your behavior
lately is far beyond
what people's eyes
will tolerate.
You've had so many
transgressions lately,
we can't even keep up with them.
For the time being, this
katana stays in my possession.
(grunts) Let go of it,
now, that's an order.
(dramatic music)
(Mana gasps)
(Bunshichi yelling)
(metal clangs)
- Shin!
(Mana gasps)
- Hmm.
(metal clangs)
(Bunshichi groans)
- What the...
(Bunshichi grunts)
- My.
- (laughs) Just as I
thought, I noticed something,
when I was watching that
little video of yours.
Shin, that dragon eye you've
got is just second rate.
It only works when you've got
that damn katana in your hand.
I let you stab me on purpose
so I could catch you
off guard, dumbass.
(Shin groans)
(onlookers muttering)
- He let him do that?
- Unbelievable, what a
crazy son of a bitch.
(Bunshichi groans)
(Bunshichi yells)
(everyone gasps)
- Even if it kills me,
I'm taking your ass down.
I don't care if it's
the last thing I do.
(slow dramatic music)
- Hmm.
(Mana whimpers)
- What's wrong?
One little punch get you
weak in the knees already?
Come on, tough guy, get up.
- Are you okay with keeping
that sword away from him?
He will lose.
(Bunshichi grunting)
(fists thudding)
- I don't believe this.
- That kid's incredible.
(Shin and Bunshichi grunting)
(Bunshichi yelling)
- [Shin Voiceover] I hear
a small, diminishing roar
echo in my mind.
I taste the iron as
it runs down my throat
and settles in my stomach.
And that smell, I know
that smell all too well.
It's me, going up in flames.
(flames crackling)
A moth that is without its wings
is a moth only in name.
Nothing else about the creature
is as nature intended it to be.
Left to be preyed
on by something
as insignificant as an ant.
So stupid, losing your wings
and surrendering
yourself to the fire.
Why does one choose to
dwell in the darkness,
only to search for the light?
(Bunshichi yelling)
- Consider this
monster defeated.
I think from now on, they
should call me Exorcist Tawara.
(everyone gasps)
(Shin grunting and panting)
(Mana gasps)
- Get it.
Go on, now, don't get shy on me.
(Shin groans)
(Mana whimpers)
- Shin, no.
(Shin grunts)
- What the hell's
happened to you, Shin?
What are you doing,
kissing up to shady
people like this for?
Huh?
(Shin groans)
You turned my golden leg
into a freakin' pin cushion.
(Shin groans)
You've gone and betrayed
all of the friends
you used to run with.
You can't even begin
to hold your own
without that lame ass katana.
(Shin retches and groans)
You've turned into a
worthless piece of shit.
I'm covered in injuries, and
I'm still gonna kick your ass.
- But you're never
gonna understand
anything about me.
- You're right, I'm not,
and I'm sure that I
never will, asshole.
You keep doing stupid things
that don't make any sense.
(energetic music)
(Shin groans)
(metal clatters)
And that's what
this is all about.
- That kid is amazing.
- He took him down
with bare hands.
- Unbelievable.
- He went up against someone
with a dragon's eye, and won.
- Huh?
(everyone cheering)
- I'm totally impressed, kid.
- You're amazing, that
was really awesome.
- You're one serious badass.
- Wait, hold up, what
the hell's going on?
- [Man] That's one hell
of a style you've created.
- Ease up.
- [Man] You're gonna be one
mean martial artist one day.
- We could use a guy like you.
- Yeah.
- That hurts, damn it.
Are you all freakin' deaf?
I said back off.
Do I need to kick
all your asses?
- People behave so
silly sometimes.
(Mana breathes shakily)
- Huh?
(slow dramatic music)
(Mana whimpers)
(Shin muttering)
- Katana (everyone gasps)
Give me the katana.
- Hah.
- I said give me the katana.
(Mana whimpers)
- The dragon's eye.
(Bunshichi yells)
- Hey, Shin, just give it up.
What in the hell is making
you act like this, man?
- Give me the katana.
(gentle music)
- [Dougen Voiceover] You're
nothing but a shadow,
a pitch-black darkness, devoid
of a single ray of light.
- I am only darkness.
I never had a chance
to be a butterfly.
I'm just a stupid little moth,
wandering all alone in the dark.
Maya!
(sad music)
- So even now she's
all you think about.
Shin!
(bright music)
(upbeat music)
(flames crackling)
(slow dramatic music)
- No, you shouldn't come here.
No, what are you doing?
Go away, go away. (whimpers)
- Hey, what are you
doing here, Maya?
- All the butterflies
are catching on fire.
I keep telling them to go away,
but they keep coming back.
(whimpers) Don't do this,
you're all gonna die.
Go on, get away from here.
- Those aren't butterflies.
- Huh?
- They're moths and it's
useless to try and stop them.
It's something that
they're born to do.
Nothing you do will
make them quit.
Born to do something stupid.
(melancholy music)
You gotta understand this.
Let's say the whole world
went completely dark,
and this fire here was the only
light to be found anywhere.
- [Maya] Yeah?
- I, too, would be
just like these guys
and jump into its flames.
Even though I know
it's gonna burn me,
I still couldn't keep
myself away from it.
And just like them, it'd
burn my wings off too.
And then I would
fall to the ground
and become covered in dirt.
I'd become so filthy that no
one would even recognize me.
I'd know all this, and still
I'd go straight into that flame.
- But, brother...
- And for me, you are just
like this flame, Maya.
- [Maya] I was far too
young to understand
what my brother was
trying to say that night.
(slow dramatic music)
(flames crackling)
I think by then he had already
discovered his dragon's eye,
and he had probably seen where
his destiny would take him.
- And for me, you are
just like this flame.
- [Maya Voiceover]
I don't remember how
I responded to that.
(Mitsuomi panting)
- Oh, ah, Bunshichi,
oh, Bunshichi, wake up.
Bunshichi, are you all right?
- What do you think
you're doing?
- Bunshichi, come on.
- Can't you see, he's ill?
This patient was
seriously injured.
He's in absolutely no
condition to have visitors now.
You've got to leave.
- But he's my friend.
- I said leave. (gasps)
- Hey, could you guys
try to keep it down?
I'm having a hard
time sleeping here.
- Hey, Bunshichi.
- So, you made it here
pretty quickly, didn't you?
- I highly suggest
you stop that.
(Bunshichi yells)
- Seems like you're
feeling good.
That's amazing.
I can't believe that
anybody could take out Shin.
- Heh, you know, it really
isn't that big of a deal.
Things just went down
the way they went down.
- (sighs) Well, I wouldn't
have been able to do anything.
I even saw how badly he ripped
my Katana buddies apart.
And still, I couldn't.
(gentle music)
Against Shin,
against Shin, I, ah.
- I've been running with
Shin since I was just a kid,
and we had a hell of a time too.
But there were times
when he didn't make
any sense to me at all.
I don't know why, but when it
came to him protecting Maya,
Shin always seemed so
serious and desperate.
- (groans) Maya.
- I think she's the only
person he feels connected to.
It's as if she's the
only one in the world
he thinks he can really trust.
And there I was, the whole time,
completely blind to it all,
just trying to
get his attention.
For over 12 years now I've
been running with that guy,
and I just now realize this.
- Just rest, Bunshichi.
- [Fu] I want to sincerely
thank you for today.
I got the chance to witness
a very entertaining
battle, Master Dougen.
- I found the whole
thing rather ridiculous.
I need to completely
reconsider my plans for Shin.
Gather all the data we
have on Shin Natsume,
and send it to me.
- Right away.
- As soon as possible.
- Yes, sir.
- Will you do away
with Mr. Natsume?
I have to admit that
I personally find
that one to be rather amusing.
There's much power in a
darkness that seeks to fight,
even on the brink of death.
That is the power
of the dragon's eye.
And let's not forget about
his personal feelings, either.
Depending on how
you use all of this,
he could very well
have what it takes
to become the true
martial artist
that you have been
looking for, Master.
- Are you trying to tell me
what I should do, Fu Chen?
- I wouldn't think of
doing such a thing.
These are simply the thoughts
from someone from
Taiwan's underground.
Please, sir, pay no
attention to them.
But before I go, we should
discuss Mr. Mitsuomi.
- Huh.
(Mitsuomi gulping)
(Mitsuomi grunts)
(Mitsuomi groans)
- I'm so sorry.
All right, now, Makun, what
do you say to this nice man?
(gasps) Ah, Makun.
Ah, are you all right?
You're, you're trembling.
(Mitsuomi sighs)
(eerie music)
(Mitsuomi moans)
- Mr. Mitsuomi has been
acting rather peculiar lately.
His heart just isn't in
it like it used to be.
And as a consequence,
his training
has stopped showing
any improvement at all.
Do you think Shin Natsume
could have something
to do with this?
- Don't worry, he'll get
that light back in his eyes.
And when he does,
it'll extinguish
all the darkness within him.
It'll be so bright that
it will blind us all.
(Fu scoffs quietly)
(siren wailing faintly)
- (groans) Maya,
Maya, don't leave me, Maya.
- Everything's all right.
I'm not going to go
anywhere, I'm here, brother.
I have to say, I'm amazed
that you took such
a terrible beating.
I've never seen you look this
bad after a fight before.
I thought I was the only one
who could push you
around like that.
But apparently that isn't
the case now, is it?
This whole thing feels
so complicated now.
Big brother, do you
remember the story
you once told me about
the moth and the flame?
I believe to this very
day you still think of me
as that scared little
girl standing by the fire.
(whooshing)
You, you were awake
this whole time?
(whimpers) Let go.
- Don't leave me, Maya.
(Maya sobs)
(sad music)
- You're going to be just fine.
I'm not going to go anywhere.
- I'm scared, Maya,
and the flames,
the flames are
starting to burn me.
(flames crackling)
- There's nothing
to worry about.
I'm still right here.
- Maya, you are my only light.
You are my flame,
don't forget that.
- That's right, I
remember it now.
- And for me, you're just
like this flame, Maya.
- I don't wanna, I
don't wanna be a flame.
I don't wanna be anything
that's gonna hurt you.
- Maya.
- I wanna be a butterfly,
and you can be one, too.
We can both be butterflies
together, okay?
(slow dramatic music)
If the same flame
that burns my brother
were to consume me as well,
(flames whooshing)
I would no longer
have anything to fear.
(gentle music)
(singing in foreign language)
(urgent music)
Can I catch up and overcome it?
Can I actually defeat
that shadow called fear
that dwells within me?
Next episode of "Tenjho
Tenge," Yin and Yang.
You'd better catch up, too,
Mitsuomi, before it's too late.