(static hissing)
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
- I've had enough of
the small talk, fat ass.
(groaning)
(screaming)
(roaring)
- Now to finish you!
(groaning)
What?
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
That was rather impressive.
Even I couldn't have predicted
that last explosive move.
- You're the kinda
person who irritates me
down to the marrow in my bones.
The executive
council's main squad
has shut down this
whole building.
There's no way that you're
going to be able to escape.
- [Maya] You think that I'm
not fully aware of this?
I know how you people work
more than anyone else.
- Go right ahead then.
Go out there and meet your doom.
I'm tired of looking at you.
- I had planned to
do so regardless.
But we're not done.
We've a bit of business left.
I've yet to thank you
properly for this haircut.
You didn't think that I
would forget, did you?
(sighs)
You're hurt too badly
to deal with this alone.
I'll call for
someone to help you.
- Wait!
- I'm sure once
everyone finds out
they can catch a glimpse
of the much admired
Isuzu Sempei nude,
a rare opportunity...
- No, don't!
- [Maya] They'll be more
than happy to lend a hand.
- But I...
- [Maya] My generosity
knows no end.
- Wait, hold on.
I see absolutely nothing
funny about this.
- Well then perhaps
you'd be willing
to do me a little favor.
(whimpering)
- [Man] In addition
to this floor,
in the fourth floor
women's bathroom,
we have vice president
Isuzu fighting Maya Natsume.
Sagara is fighting
one of the freshmen
in the employee's corridor
on the third floor.
And Tagami is fighting
Natsume's younger sister
in the ninth floor corridor
in front of the roof access.
- [Mitsuomi] I left this
case in Isuzu's hands.
I'll wait 10 minutes.
- Right.
- If Isuzu isn't down
here in 10 minutes,
I will then head
up there myself.
- [Man] And that's it.
That's all I have to report.
- All right, it all
sounds very good.
You are excused now.
- I gotta say, I'm
really impressed.
I can't believe you
were actually able
to get rid of Maya Natsume.
- Will you just hurry
up and leave already?
- I mean, to fight
until your clothes
are all ripped to
shreds like that.
You two must have had one
heck of a cat fight, huh?
I can only imagine.
- [Maya] What were you
saying about a cat fight?
(groaning)
- I can't hold it.
- [Maya] Keeping
appearances can be so hard.
- Mind your own damn business.
So, what do you think
you're going to do now?
You heard what he said.
He's arrived and that means
you don't stand even
the smallest chance
of being able to
win this fight now.
- I heard what I needed to know.
And it was that boy's
precise location.
- What boy?
- By utilizing my chi,
I can eliminate
most of the pain.
But I stand no chance at all
of fighting well
with this injury.
That boy is my last hope.
No matter how hopeless
this situation gets,
I am the captain of that club,
and I have to do what
is best in order to win.
(groaning)
- Stand up.
I, Saga Mask, am now putting
all of my body and soul
into this fight.
I said it's time for you to use
one of your own
attacks against me.
- If you say so.
(chuckles)
I'll be happy to serve
up one more attack.
(groans)
(dramatic music)
That's about the gist of it.
Is what I did
really that amazing?
- Reuka Kiko Tanshinko.
It's a type of attack
that is executed
by utilizing hatke.
Look boy, what do you see here?
- I don't see nothing.
- Nothing, huh?
Well there's something
quite close to us
that can be of great
value to you and me.
- [Boy] Huh?
- [Maya] The atmosphere.
Atmosphere is an
essential element
that this world is filled with.
Don't think of a circle
as motion, but as power.
Many martial arts use circles
within fundamental
areas for good reason.
It's also used by
masters in their attacks.
The backhand is
basically a method
of conveying the impact point.
In other words, as long
as you have something
to transfer your power,
you can use it against anything.
As one's turning force builds,
it uses chi to evolve from
a slicing circular motion
into a lean linear motion
with an amazing amount
of kinetic energy.
And then that energy
begins to rush.
- Can I take back what I said?
How about I start the
attack on this one?
- Denied.
- [Maya] Building
within the atmosphere.
(shattering)
- [Sagara] Such a
devastating force.
Many times have I fought against
the most fearsome of opponents.
But never have I seen
an attack like this.
- Hey, what the?
How come my attack
didn't reach him?
- [Sagara Voiceover]
He missed me.
This means he hasn't
fully mastered the attack.
- That's not how
it's done, you idiot!
An attack that you just
learned earlier today, boy,
is not going to work
against these challengers.
Lose that thought now.
In the end, the martial
arts are nothing more
than a series of attacks
used to defeat people.
You should know how to
choose your attacks wisely.
If not, you'll just become a
victim of your own efforts.
Now tell me, what
are you made of, boy?
You have your own way
of fighting, don't you?
You didn't come
knocking on our door
because you wanted to be a
martial artist now, did you?
There is more than one
path to achieving strength.
- Man, you guys are
like a broken record.
I already know that I
ain't no martial artist.
I know damn well
who the hell I am.
I'm just a street thug,
and I'm gonna stay a thug,
and I'll still become stronger
than every single one of you.
- [Sagara Voiceover] Be
thankful to Natsume, freshman.
If you let your
attacks consume you
and foolishly try to
use that move again,
I will have no trouble
pulverizing that arm of yours.
Natsume's one bit of advice
has turned him into
a fearsome opponent.
- Yo, it's your turn now, buddy.
Show me what you got.
(gasps)
- [Isuzu Voiceover] Did she?
With wounds all over her
body and a broken shoulder,
Natsume walked out
of the bathroom
and defeated every
single one of these guys?
(sighs)
- Well, it was a
total mismatch then.
- [Maya Voiceover] Sorry, boy.
This is all that I can
do for you right now.
You'll have to figure a way
to finish this on your own.
(gasps)
- Be sure to keep focused.
I won't be holding
anything back this time.
You shouldn't look
anywhere but at me.
If you don't keep an
eye on the opponent
standing in front of you,
all you will see is one thing.
Defeat.
It would be a shame
for you to turn this
into a boring match
now, freshman.
- Right.
- [Sagara] Rolling turn.
German suplex.
(groaning)
Jumping.
- This is really looking bad.
- Power bomb!
- [Boy Voiceover] I
can't believe this.
How can a dude as big
as him be so fast?
- Son of a bitch!
(groaning)
(laughs)
(groans)
- From a rolling turn
into a German suplex,
followed by a
jumping power bomb,
and then into a
scorpion death lock.
What you girls and boys are
getting to see right now
is known as the saga special.
But you should never
try to do this at home.
(groaning)
- [Boy] Rope.
Rope, the rope!
- What?
You reached the rope?
I have no choice then.
- You bought that?
(groaning)
You're way too gullible,
you pro wrestling freak.
(groaning)
- [Sagara Voiceover]
Easy, a right straight.
I'll catch his fist in midair.
- How'd I miss that?
- Fooled ya.
(wind whistling)
(screaming)
- [Maya Voiceover] Damn it,
boy, you're still too early.
(soft jingle)
(screaming)
- Saga muscle power bomb!
(groaning)
(laughs)
I've just shattered your fist.
(groaning)
Don't think my
muscles serve as mere
protective armor for me.
They are solid weapons used
to defeat my opponents.
Anyone who chooses to strike me
suffers a counterattack
equal to the strength
of their assault.
- [Maya Voiceover] When
the boy struck him,
Sagara expanded his muscles,
surging power
throughout his body,
and forcing the attack
right back at the boy.
Even Tanshinko can't relay
power within the body
in this situation.
The force of that
attack was so powerful,
the damage inflicted
on the boy's right arm
will be immeasurable.
Sagara is strong.
- Perhaps I was wrong
in assuming that the boy
would be able to handle this.
- There's no need
to get up, Natsume.
Lacerations aside, with
that broken shoulder,
there's no way you
will be able to fight
an even match with me,
let alone heal in time for
the preliminaries next month.
Face it.
You're nothing more
than dead weight now.
- Wait!
I'm not even close to
being finished with you.
- Well, I think it was point.
The initial objective
has been fulfilled.
The remaining task is
to follow his orders
and pulverize what's
left of this boy's arms.
- Do what?
- Soon you can join Ryuuzaki,
and the two of you can count
the hospital ceiling
tiles together.
- Wait!
Sagara, I am your opponent.
- You're far too late.
(gasps)
(screams)
(glass shattering)
- Hmm, so, you've
chosen the rooftop.
I imagine that right about now
that the executive
council is launching
a full scale all out attack
against your little friends.
Even if you do manage
to escape from here,
Sagara has locked
down the third floor.
An exceptionally
strong opponent.
So strong that he'd be
on par with Isuzu and me
had he not joined that
pro wrestling club.
Take this.
You're distracting me.
- You can be a gentleman
at a rather odd time.
- I am proud to say
I am one of the few
remaining samurais left
in this day and age.
Normally, I would
never wish for a battle
that is as unfair
as this one is.
But with those eyes of yours,
as long as they bear that look,
I have no choice
but to fight you.
- I am Souichiro's wife.
I believe in him and in the
members of the Juken Club.
And I believe in myself.
There's no way that we'd
ever allow ourselves
to lose to you.
(roaring)
(shattering)
- What have you?
- But that's Tanshinko.
There's no way.
He couldn't pull that
off from that position.
- Pathetic.
You are just way too pathetic.
(groaning)
- [Sagara Voiceover]
This can't be happening.
How can I be losing
at a power match
against an opponent
as small as him?
- [Maya Voiceover]
His turning force.
The massive turning force he
gained from the Tanshinko.
Instead of releasing it,
he's developing it
into a stronger power
within his own body.
Can Tanshinko really
be used this way?
- Your story is so
incredibly lame.
Is that really what
this is all about, huh?
The only reason
you're fighting me
is because you're running
errands for somebody else?
(groans)
A big and powerful
guy like yourself,
living such a boring
and pathetic life.
What happened to the
man inside of you?
(groaning)
- I just...
- Pro wrestling, no thanks.
I can't say I'm really
interested in that.
- There's no way.
A samurai's not part
of a circus act.
We'd kill you.
- You do realize what
you're up against.
Even if you do create a
new club at this school,
the other clubs will crush you
before you can even
establish yourself.
- [Sagara] Thank you for coming.
Practice is going to be tough.
- How'd you get to
be so big, Sagara?
What kind of food did you
eat when you were a kid?
- Why is our clubhouse
in the freshman bathroom?
- [Sagara] It's the only
place they'll let us use.
Wait, where are you going?
- I'm going home.
There's a new game
coming out today.
(groans)
- Hey, take a look at
the muscles I'm getting.
- That's nothing, I got
way more muscles than you.
I wonder if we'll ever be
as tough as you, Sagara.
- Of course you will be.
(shattering)
(whimpering)
- I've decided to give
you one more chance.
(groans)
- It went through.
- In order for me to create
an ideal executive council,
the key elements that I'll need
are massive amounts of power
and an elite personnel.
If you swear allegiance
to the executive council,
I will provide you with
money to operate your club
and a place to practice.
If you refuse this offer,
I will simply revoke it.
However, the tragedy
you witnessed today
will continue for
three more years.
Yes, you are incredibly strong.
But not everyone that
you associate with
is nearly as strong as you are.
- Sagara, please.
- I hear your offer.
And if you honestly plan
to keep that promise,
then I, Sagara, will
train relentlessly
to serve the executive council.
However, I am doing
this only for the safety
of my club members and to
keep order within the school.
I will bow down to the
law, but never to you.
This is not just my loss.
This loss will be far
greater than that.
I can't do it.
All of the things that
I have fought for.
I can't fall to
my knees in defeat
over something as
trivial as this.
I can't, I can't.
I can't do it.
- Hey, why don't we just
call it quits here, okay?
I mean, it's not like
you and me are out here
to actually try and
kill each other.
I gotta think a fight
that's forced down
your throat by someone else
ain't gonna be fun for
either of us, you know?
If I'm gonna be
fighting a guy like you,
all I want to do is
clear all the other
crap out of my head
and get to business.
If you want to ask
me for a rematch,
I'll give you top priority.
- Huh, well that's
what I would expect.
From any freshman.
Next time.
Next time, I guarantee
you I'll win.
(laughs)
- [Sagara Voiceover]
Natsume, if someone like him
had been at my side, or if...
(crumbling)
I'm so jealous of you.
(gasps)
- Wow, you sure don't
weigh very much, do you?
- What do you
think you're doing?
- Well you're hurt, aren't you?
If something else
were to happen to you,
I got no doubt that Takayanagi
would totally rip me to shreds.
Let's get outta here.
I can't believe
that little detour
turned into this big ass battle.
You got any idea where Iyo is?
- I do.
- [Maya Voiceover]
Well, it appears that he
is turning into someone
with a tremendous
amount of potential.
To be able to use Tanshinko,
that requires a great
deal of consecutive chi.
Perhaps this is a
sign of the powers
that his family holds.
- Time's up.
Let's go.
(screaming)
(sighs)
- I guess that's it.
I don't see any more.
Bob, can you stand up?
- Yeah.
- Where's Chiaki?
What happened to her?
- She couldn't get out in time.
She's behind me,
inside this locker.
(door squeals)
(whimpering)
- Bob, if you ever do
something like that again,
I promise, that'll
be the end of us.
- I'm sorry.
- Even if I'm all right,
what the heck good
is it if you end up
getting hurt in the
process, you idiot?
(groaning)
- [Bob] Hey, sorry about that.
- [Chiaki] What's wrong?
- [Bob] Even a guy
that can take down
80 dudes on his
own has a weak spot
that no amount of
training will protect.
- [Chiaki] Wow, he looks
like he's really in pain.
We should help, right?
- Hmm.
By the way, where's
Souichiro and the others?
- Not here.
But I'm pretty sure
that they're all right.
I'll wait around for
them to get back.
You guys should get out of here.
- I know that I'd probably
just get in your way
but if Souichiro
needs some help,
then I gotta be there for him.
- You're gonna be
strong some day too.
I can guarantee that.
Until then, get outta here.
Sorry but...
- No worries.
Still hurts, huh?
- Yeah.
- [Bob Voiceover]
I can't believe it.
This guy did this
all on his own.
How much of a power
difference can there be
between the two of us?
Or even Souichiro,
for that matter?
(dramatic music)
- [Man Voiceover] If the
past and the future will be
forever linked by
what transpires today,
what can I do to
control the outcome?
There's a giant wave
waiting to swallow us whole.
This battle isn't
anywhere near over.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
- [Aya] Everyone's
emotions are influenced
by their own battles.
This is what leads
them into the shadowy
corners of their past.
Next episode of Tenjho Tenge.
Dragon's Eye.
(speaks in foreign language)
I feel like I'm going insane!