(white noise)
(intense intro music)
- Ah!
Shit!
- Souichiro!
Get out of the way!
Souichiro!
- Ah!
(metal clanks)
- You serious, sis?
You've been expelled?
- No.
No!
It's gone!
That katana.
She's gone and taken it!
(men yell)
- This is the
executive council's
headquarters, right boys?
- We don't have time
to mess with you guys.
Just go and tell your
boss we wanna see him,
you damn puppets.
- I don't think that
they're too into
getting their boss for us.
- (scoffs) Then I guess
we just gotta kill 'em!
(intimidating rock music)
You and I aren't done yet.
There's something
I wanna give you.
(paper crinkles)
(intimidating rock music)
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
(intimidating rock music)
(wind whistles)
(metal clangs)
(metal rings)
- That's amazing!
[Takayanagi Voiceover]
When they say a blade
has an overwhelming spirit,
they're talking about
a blade like this.
(birds tweet)
- See, it's a good katana, huh?
I don't think it has a name.
Since the Masakiyo was broken,
I figured I'd use
this weapon instead.
- Wow.
But how do you manage to
draw such a long sword?
It must take forever.
- There's a little trick to it.
- Huh?
- You see, this katana
was my brother's.
- This katana belonged to Sheen?
This can't be the
the Chokutou Reki?
- Oh!
So Takayanagi-sempai.
You know about my brother?
- Well, not really.
I've just heard a
few of the rumors.
- Oh you have, huh?
- But,
Isn't that Katana
supposed to be dangerous?
- Huh, So what if it is?
- Uh, it's just that
since you've picked
up that Katana, Aya,
do you feel like anything
in you has changed?
- Huh?
No, not really.
- Like your perceptions,
or I guess your powers?
- Why are you asking
me all these questions?
- Well it's just that...
I guess if you don't
feel you've changed...
everything's all right then.
- Okay then!
(heaves)
(air whistles)
(metal clanks)
You ready?
Let's get going!
- Huh?
- We're gonna meet with
Executive Council directly.
The council has a
whole lot of power.
I bet they can change
even a master's decision.
They're gonna overturn
my sister's expulsion
even if I gotta make em!
- Yeah!
(mystical music)
- [Takayanagi Voiceover]
As all this was happening,
nobody realized that gradually
we were all beginning
to drift apart.
- Man! What crappy handwriting?
(paper crinkles)
And who the hell taught
you guys how to spell, huh?
I'm guessing you boys figured
that if you were to get
your asses kicked out first
then Natsume's would be spared.
(paper rips)
Wow, you boys really aren't
all that bright, are ya?
Don't waste my time again.
(grunts)
You really think
Natsume would be happy
if she heard about this?
You need to learn to
think before you act.
First of all the stakes
in this little tiff,
are much higher than
you seem to think.
Your sorry hides wouldn't
begin to cover it.
- Will you shut up?
I'm way over everyone telling
me how worthless I am.
That's why our only choice,
is to make sure that
when we go down we take some
of you bastards with us.
- You're asking
for the impossible.
I mean just look at
you guys, you're weak.
- You know, you don't gotta
be all blunt about it.
(grunts)
Sorry buddy, but I don't take
advice from no loser dropout.
Now give me your boss already!
Dumbass!
I know we're screwed.
I know you got us.
I know there's no way in hell
our strength is
gonna match yours.
(table crunches)
(spits)
- Because we're both so stupid,
we're just gonna
keep on fighting
till we settle this
score all right.
- Could you two
be more barbaric?
- I don't care what
you think about us,
we're taking you guys down!
- Our last day of school
came just a little too early.
- What a joke.
(gasps)
(table crashes)
- The shoulder's the
weakest point for TashinkM.
All the energy that you
build up for that move
is gonna flow right
through that spot.
All I gotta do to destroy
all of your energy
is keep that shoulder
from rotating.
(inhales)
- Asshole!
(gasps)
- I think the word
"ass" applies to you,
you little asswipe!
Don't try to play me!
- Ah!
(men grunting)
(metal rings)
- Oh no!
They didn't!
(metal rings)
(breathing heavily)
Aya! What's wrong?
Are you all right?
(gasps)
- What is it?
Aya?
- You were just a
couple of street thugs
when you came here.
You only got caught
up in this battle
with the Executive
Council by chance.
You got no reason to be
acting all "macho" like this.
(metal rings)
- Stop! Stop it!
Souichiro-sama!
- I gotta reason, asshole!
- Please stop!
- (laughs) It's a
little embarrassing
but it's why I gotta
settle the score.
I'll only say it once.
Don't even think about laughing.
- No! Don't say it, please!
- That midget chink
happens to be the only girl
I've ever fallen in love with.
The moment she tossed me out
of the schools 3rd floor window
it was too late.
I was in love.
Shithead!
(gasps)
So if it's concerning her
I got no problem putting
my body through anything.
You got that? You
freaking loser!
(gasps)
(heart beating)
(sad music)
(metal rings)
- [Takayanagi
Voiceover] Suddenly,
the sound started to ring.
As if it had been awakened
from a long slumber.
I could hear it so clearly,
mixed with the
sound of heartbeats.
Softly,
it began to grow.
- Aya.
(metal rings)
(footsteps)
(pot boiling)
(gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(Ominous music)
- [Makikio Voiceover] Fox rain
the rain of the Black Dragon
Surrounded by water
from the west.
Did someone conjure
a Shiki near here?
That's impossible!
I'm the only one in this town
who has the power to
create a spell like that.
(music)
(crying)
- [Aya Voiceover] I wish...
that it would rain harder.
I want it to wipe
away these tears.
away this voice.
(metal clanks)
- You surprised me.
You know I kinda thought that
you might've fallen for Aya
but Mya is a pretty hot chick.
Can't says I blame ya.
(scoffs) Sorry dude.
Guess I was going
around this whole time
with my head in the
clouds, right Sou-chan?
- Idiot.
I've been trying
to find a good way
to tell ya for a long time now
but you know you can be so
freaking pushy sometimes!
- You think I'm pushy?
- You gotta problem with that?
What do you want me to
run every single thing
that goes through my
head past you first?
I'll try to remember
that next time.
Oh, please forgive me, Bob!
- Dude, are you trying
to pick a fight with me?
Are ya?
'Cause I'd sure like
to punch ya right now!
(raspberry)
Lookie machine gun!
- Yeah! Well take
this spit bomb!
(spitting)
- Stop with all the slobber!
The two of you punks are
gonna rot out the floors!
- Shut up!
This ain't got nothing
to do with you old man!
Are you into S&M?
Why the hell you
got us all tied up?
- Hey, just fight us already!
- All right then.
(gasps)
(grunts)
You little...
- I got your arm now!
And I'm not letting go
no matter what you do to me!
- You really are
a pain in the ass.
(growls)
If things don't go your way,
you growl like a cage dog.
And if you don't like something,
you just sink your
teeth into em.
And if it turns out you're
no match for your opponent,
you just curl up your
tail and run away.
Whether you know it or not
kid you behave like an animal.
(stretching)
(moaning)
Get a good bite or else
your jaw's gonna snap.
That's it, you don't
wanna let go now.
Your teeth haven't
fully sunk in yet.
(groans)
Take for example,
that Ryuzakí guy.
He's quite ambitious.
In fact I think
he's got his eye on
becoming the next Executive
Council president.
But, since a pretty good
rival, Takayanagí Jr.
Is in the Juken Club.
He's working his butt
off for the council
in a desperate attempt
to get noticed.
Sagara went and sold
himself out in order
to protect his little buddies
in the Pro Wrestling
Club from the council.
And seeing the way Tagamí and
Isuzu swoon over Mítsuomí,
I'm guessing they've sworn their
loyalty to the council too.
(shuffling)
They're all just alike.
(grunts)
Although they all have
different reasons,
every last one are fighting
for something they believe in.
But what about you guys?
Cause one little ruckus
and you're ready to
leave the academy.
Doesn't being so self-centered
embarrass you just a little bit?
If you're gonna act
like a "hardass",
and announce to some dude that
you're fighting for woman
that you're in love with,
then be a hardass, damnit!
Be as tough as you
possibly can be
until your very
last waking breath.
(grunts)
I mean is there
really any other way
you guys would want
to live your life?
(gentle music)
- [Aya Voiceover] I know, that
this isn't anyone's fault.
I was the one who called
Souichiro-sama my husband
and refused to see things
for what they were.
I don't know why I thought
Souichiro-sama felt
something for me too.
(clanks)
- Takayanagi-sempai!
I'm sorry if I made you worry!
- (gasps)
What we heard today
needs to stay between us.
I just don't want
everything to fall apart.
- But Aya.
- It's all right!
Now that I've cried it all out,
I feel much better!
When I go home,
I've got to be able to
look at sis with a smile.
- Aya! Takayanagi,
have you've seen Aya?
- Captain, what
are you doing here?
- I heard you were up here.
Do you have any
idea where Aya is?
- Uh well, I, uh.
- Spit it out!
(gasps)
Aya!
(clanking)
(splash)
(squeals)
(clanks)
- Aya! Are you all right?
- Aya!
- [Takayanagi] Did you get hurt?
- Stay right there, Aya!
We need to talk.
That Katana you have is...
- Shut up!
(splash)
(footsteps)
- Takayanagi, what's going on?
- Yeah.
Well...
- Tell me!
(inhales)
- This whole thing is my fault.
She's just mad 'cause,
I was making fun of her.
(stammers)
I said Aya!
Have you've been stuffing
grapefruit in your bra?
(stammers)
- [Takayanagi] Tch!
Jeez!
Why do I always end
up being the sucker?
(engine revving)
(chimes)
(elevator bell chimes)
- I know the two freshman,
came over to
confront the Council.
(hoof pounding)
(mooing)
Leave them be.
Those two freshman
and the Juken Club
may end up being
someone that the academy
as well as the council
would benefit by from
keeping them close.
(grunts)
(mooing)
(grunting)
Let the freshman be.
And be sure that those two
are able to make
the preliminaries.
- Yes sir!
(groaning)
I can't explain this feeling
of doubt that I have.
Perhaps he's beginning
to sense his draw closer.
He keeps pushing himself
further and further.
Like he's trying
to determine what,
or who will deliver
his final blow.
(intense music)
(stomps)
(mooing)
- Unfortunately, my body is
about to run out of time.
I'm sorry you had to be
involved with my training.
(purring)
(yells)
(moos)
If one is not used
to taking a life,
when the moment comes,
the fist will hesitate.
But more importantly Miss Isuzu,
is there something else
that you'd like to tell me?
I can't believe that you
came all the way over here
just to deliver that one report.
- Well it hasn't
been confirmed yet.
So I wasn't sure if I
should tell you or not.
- [Mitsuomi] Go on.
- It's the Chokutou Reiki.
Someone claims to have
seen it on campus.
(gasps)
It was being used by
Natsume's younger sister, Aya.
- Not again!
(ominous music)
- I can't blame sis for this.
I can't blame sis for this.
I can't blame
Souichiro-sama either.
I haven't lost.
I haven't lost anything at all.
I know,
this is the wrong choice.
(electrical sparks)
But I'm afraid
that I just can't
forgive you for this sis!
- Aya!
Aya!
Answer me!
- Come on, Aya!
Where'd you go?
Huh?
- [Takayanagi Voiceover]
It started to rain again.
Then there was this odd
clearing in the afternoon sky.
Then suddenly, it
struck me as beautiful
just like her eyes did
when they were
filled with tears.