(static)
(foreign introduction music)
- I know I can do it.
Please, show me.
(cries)
(slap)
(thunder foot)
(bones cracking)
(scream in pain)
(thunder foot)
- She, she knows how to.
- You had your
turn, now its mine.
(scream)
(bone cracking)
(foot kicking body)
(clink)
- Secret weapon Isuzu
(electric trumpet)
Is going to strike.
(whoosh)
(clunk)
- The executive council.
- This areas been
temporarily closed.
(electric guitar)
(electro music)
(wind)
(groan)
(shout)
(body hitting floor)
- Why are you guys doing this?
- You look a bit
lonely there girly.
(grasp)
why don't I do the right
thing and keep you company?
- Chiaki
- Uh
- Ooooaaa
(scream in pain)
(bowling pins strike)
(carnival sound)
- Thank you
- Are you sure your
all right Chiaki?
(electro music)
- Man there's just
no end to these guys.
- Don't you make the mistake
of just writing us off
as just your average
bunch of wannabe's.
Everyone here is
in the main squad
of the executive council.
- Sorry but who are you?
(sigh)
- Hey Bob, isn't
this the guy that
Notchom wiped the floor with
without breaking a sweat?
- Oh yeah,
come to think of it,
I do have a vague
memory of that exchange.
(growl)
- That's it bastard,
your dead.
- You know I think
I should thank you,
while you were busy
babbling on and on
I took that time so I
could work out my chi.
I'll create a path
to the elevator,
you guys make a
run for it. Okay?
Now get ready.
- Chiaki.
- All right.
Here goes.
(foreign language)
(gushing wind)
(explosion)
- This whole experience
is against my will
and extremely unpleasant.
The pro wrestling club is a
small part of the academy,
but the executive council
has asked us here non the less.
(swish)
It took three very hard years
for me to be appointed
as an executioner.
And now that I am here,
the task that I am given is
equal to picking a
spindly little nuisance
out of the web.
Wouldn't you say that
its rather pathetic?
- I've had enough
of the small talk.
Bad ass.
(smash)
(groan in pain)
(scream)
(smash)
(groan in pain)
- Listen I don't have time
to play with you
today, all right?
Your the freaking nuisance.
(groan in pain)
(clunk)
(screaming)
(groan)
(wind rushing)
(fast violin music)
- Ya
(sigh)
(wind rushing)
(groan)
- I don't know why this is
but I don't feel a
trace of the Ora,
that I felt back then.
- That staff can
grow infinitely long.
I can never get
into striking range,
his body is always too far away.
(sigh)
(shout)
(explosion)
(sigh)
(foot steps)
I can't do that again,
I've got to stay
focused on this battle.
- Just as I thought,
her Ora is not as strong as
it was in the court yard.
(swish)
(suspense music)
I can take her.
Right now, she is nothing
more than a little girl,
who likes to practice Jiu-Jitsu.
(groan)
(footsteps)
(heavy breathing)
(groan)
(suspense music)
- I see,
I thought it was strange
that you kept on
trying to escape
further and further up.
So that's what you
were trying to do.
- Fear of that staff
is dependent upon
its angle of attack
and its versatility within that.
But from this position
inside a narrow corridor,
the only way he can
attack is by thrust.
(heart beat)
I'll be able to evade
the first attack,
but after that,
will I be fast enough to
close the distance between us?
Or will he be faster
in launching his second
attack against me?
(heartbeat)
Lets go.
- Maya Natsume,
I think its time
that you show me
what you're made of.
- Fine, but I promise
that you'll regret it.
(suspense music)
(high heels)
(clink)
(groan)
(wind gushing)
(wind rushing)
(hammering)
(sigh)
(mirror breaking)
(chink)
(wind rushing)
(sigh)
- Looks like dodging the attacks
is all that you can manage.
Well try to dodge this one.
(chink
(door breaking)
(groaning)
(wind rushing)
(sigh)
(chink)
(groan)
(sigh)
(door breaking)
(explosion)
(door smashing on ground)
(bump)
(sigh)
(breathing)
- Perhaps I went a tad to far.
(groaning)
Takayanagi, is with
those two boys,
so I'm sure that are at
least holding their own.
But the problem is Aya.
(slap)
Silly girl,
I can't believe that she would
jump to a conclusion like that.
(wins rushing)
(bump)
(breathing)
- We're not finished.
Not even close.
You and I have yet
to settle our score.
(suspense music)
- I'm impressed
that you've managed
to resurrect this battle,
From the dyer position
you were in earlier.
Not bad.
There, I've given
you a bit of praise.
And now,
Ill show you that you are wrong.
(sigh)
This is not some ordinary staff.
(click)
(chink)
(wind gushing)
you have willingly walked
straight into the jaws of death.
- That's impossible
(foreign language)
(scream)
Souichiro
(foreign language)
(bamboo flute)
(lute)
(clack)
Souichiro
Sume
(click)
(chink)
(dong)
Souichiro
Sume
(flashback)
- What is this?
That was Souichiro Sume
His memories are
entering my head.
(orchester)
- [Narrator] Its a clan
that wards off evil.
We take the possessed
into their own bodies,
and defeat the dark spirits,
by becoming the
spirits of ourselves.
Its a polluted clan,
hated since the ancient
pass by both spirits
and man kind alike.
(chime)
But listen Souichiro,
you mustn't resent this,
anger and resentment will
only disrupt your chi.
And if you disrupt your chi,
you can't use your
power properly.
- [Boys Voice] I don't care,
I just want to be stronger.
A lot stronger Mom,
so I can find anyone who
ever caused you pain,
and then kill them
for hurting you.
- [Women] Making
yourself stronger,
just so you can
harm other humans,
is exactly the same as
making the enemy stronger
so that they can harm you.
When you selflessly
act to protect someone
without any fear
of getting hurt,
then you will have
achieved true strength.
You have many
reasons to be proud.
The Nagi family has done
a lot of good for others.
Many lives have been saved
at the cost of our wounds.
You may not understand
what this means now,
but some day,
when you truly understand
the meaning of these words
you'll find that
inside your body
dwells not just a mere spirit,
but the spirit of a dragon.
- That, that isn't fair.
Its always just me,
seeing all these different
things about Souichiro
I'm in his past.
I only hope
that someday Souichiro Sume,
will know as much about me,
as I know about him
and all the memories
that he has from,
his past.
- Give up,
you've seen the outcome.
If you continue your
wounds will be much worse.
- I'm sorry but,
in my position as his wife,
I'm afraid that I,
must not lose.
(sigh)
- She just called to me.
(dragon roaring)
- What is this?
Is this some sort
of an illusion?
(breathing)
It seems that perhaps,
I have made the mistake of
slightly underestimating just
what your capable of.
- Stay down,
don't make me school you again.
I don't have time
to hang around here
babysitting you.
(wind gushing)
(rap)
(groan)
(sigh)
- This is payback for
that ambush earlier.
Now on your feet,
I Sagamask will fight you now,
with all of my body and soul.
(clash)
Get up its your turn
to make an attack
against me now.
(sigh)
(laughing)
- Come on,
how many times are you going
to make me repeat myself?
I don't have the time
to be hanging out with
a weakling like you,
but your not leaving
me much choice.
So I'll stick around
for just one more blow.
(thud)
(laughing)
- Just where are you going?
(suspense music)
- Come here
(bump)
You wait inside here.
- But.
- Just get inside do it.
- Bob why are you doing this?
This is totally absurd.
- If you stay in here
like a good girl,
I promise that I'll
make it up to you.
- But Bob.
(laughing)
- You're dead.
(motorbike)
(pounding)
(sign)
(breathing)
- Now that I have
actually fought her,
I finally see why everyone
was so afraid of Maya Natsume.
This is why people make
derogative remarks about her.
Yet never choose to
do anything abour it.
(wind gushing)
(bump)
(sign)
(breathing)
- I have to admit that I
admire your persistence,
however if you
continue to stand,
then I must continue
to fight you.
So perhaps its best
you call it quits.
- I hate that I
have to admit this,
but I was foolish to assume
that with the
advantage of weapons,
a well though out plan
and the right location,
that I stood a chance
of winning this fight.
But unfortunately I
cannot afford to lose,
for you are the one person,
I can never lose to.
No matter what.
(drums)
(clink)
- She still has more weapons.
She's already
thrown at least 20.
(electro music)
Go on attack me again,
you're never going to win.
- Make no mistake,
I will indeed,
Win.
(wind gushing)
What gives me
strength is my title,
Vice President of the
Executive Council.
That translates to pure bliss,
derived only by
working so closely
with our President.
Same, how you were
offered this same position
only to turn it down.
You can't possibly estimate
the strength that this gives me.
(sign)
(cling)
- One, two
(sigh)
Three, four.
(wind rushing)
So there is a fifth one,
Isuzu's favorite attack,
the shadow blade.
If I can manage this one.
(clink)
(sigh)
(laughs)
(wind rushing)
(crashing)
- How did you just?
(clink)
- I simply cannot
afford to lose to her.
I am their captain,
I must get to them,
it is imperative that I
do everything in my power,
to prevent you from
defeating them.
(electro music)
The weight I carry
in my position,
far outweighs any of
your responsibilities.
(sigh)
(foreign language)
(hammering)
(screaming)
Now to finish you.
(sigh)
(groaning)
- The powers within
my body are dwindling,
my spell will be broken,
this can't happen,
nobody knows how I really look.
And of all people to find out,
it has to be her.
- I've heard of this before,
people who can alter
the size of their bodies
by using chi to
conceal their excess.
(groaning)
I couldn't figure out
how she was able to hide
all those weapons before,
but now it makes perfect sense.
(electro music)
- I can't hold it
(groaning)
- What?
(wind rushing)
There's, there's
too many of them.
(screaming)
(hooting)
(humming)
- Its always good to know
that I still look beautiful.
It looks like your finally here.
(motorbike)
(tires screeching)
(thrilling music)
(motorbike)
I've been waiting for you,
Meseromy.
(thrilling music)
(theme song)
(foreign language)
- Its your own moves that
are killing your boy.
Sagara, is not easy prey.
Your ill conceived attacks
are not going to
work against him.
Next episode of
Tenjho Tenge
Breakthrough
- This battle has just began.