(static hissing)
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
(screaming)
- Team Katana.
Mitsuomi might be able to
fill my shoes when I'm gone.
You should've seen that.
(yells)
- Kusinoha needle kokansaiso.
I'm afraid you're
not going to be able
to make it in this
school if you're fretting
over something as small as this.
- Hey, don't you think this
has gone on long enough?
(groaning)
(dramatic music)
(pounding)
(hissing)
(grunting)
(pounding)
- Practicing after school?
All by yourself?
Seems lonely.
- Hmm.
Of all the places you could be,
why did you choose to come here?
You looking to pick up where
we left off with that fight?
- Not at all.
I have no desire to
challenge you right now.
However, it would seem that
in the not too distant future,
you and I will
definitely face off.
Hmm?
Hey, what's your problem?
Why can't you look
me in the eye today?
I'm gonna take a wild guess.
I think you're seeing someone.
(gasps)
(magical music)
(laughing)
I was just joking,
but you're serious.
That look on your
face was hysterical.
There it is, that's the look.
(laughing)
- [Mitsuomi] What's
so damn funny?
(wind whistling)
- Now hold on, settle
down, you idiot.
I was just playing around.
I told you I didn't come
here for a showdown.
- Yeah well this
isn't a showdown.
It's punishment.
- What?
Don't think you can threaten me.
- How about 100 flicks
to your forehead, huh?
- Go right ahead.
But I'll serve up 100 thumps
to your ass if you do.
- Huh, you're walking
on confidence.
(groaning)
Hey, stop, you're
showing your underwear.
- [Maya] So, who cares?
No one else can see it.
- What the hell
kinda logic is that?
- It works for me.
- [Mitsuomi] Hey, you
almost hit me that time.
Watch it!
- Come on!
(ominous rhythmic music)
The chokuto reiki is gone.
- [Aya] What's wrong, sis?
- Aya, please tell me
that you took the reiki.
- No, Shin took that out
with him a little while ago.
- What, Shin took it?
- [Aya] Yeah.
- [Maya Voiceover] Shin
hasn't gone anywhere
near the reiki since he,
since the incident.
- So why now?
(engine roaring)
(tires squealing)
- [Mitsuomi] What
is it, Bunshichi?
Bunshichi, what is it?
You wanted to talk.
- Oh yeah.
I figured it out.
I think I know who's been
doing the katana hunting.
I started thinking about
the attacks collectively,
including Ishimatsu's,
and I came up with a theory.
90% certain I've got
the right person.
(engine roaring)
I thought you'd be surprised
more surprised than this.
After all, isn't she the
girl you've got the hots for?
- Are you kidding?
I'm totally shocked by this.
But in a weird way, I
know why she did it.
- [Bunshichi] Really?
(tires squealing)
- [Mitsuomi] But in a weird
way, I know why she did it.
- Really?
One more thing.
Rumor has it you're
shacking up with Kuzunoha
every now and then.
- [Mitsuomi] Who did
you hear that from?
- She's telling
everyone she knows.
It's starting to get around.
It's better if you don't
mess with her at all.
That could easily find
its way to Shin's ears.
That's all, and this
whole discussion,
it's just between us.
Don't mention katana hunting
or his chick to Shin.
When the time's right,
I'll let him know.
- All right, I gotcha.
(engine roaring)
- [Bunshichi] And
this whole discussion,
it's just between us.
Don't mention katana hunting
or his chick to Shin.
- [Man] What I mean
by fireproof alloy
is that this metal
can only be found
in the United States.
Los Angeles, to be specific.
(muffled chatting)
(baby crying)
(sirens blaring)
(people chatting)
- What the hell is
everyone's problem?
Can't you just shut up?
I can't handle it when you
all talk to me at once.
Damn it, I feel like
I'm going insane.
- [Mitsuomi Voiceover]
She comes onto me,
then turns around and tells
all her friends about it.
Why?
- I don't know if you noticed,
but those two have a
strange relationship.
They're more like lovers
than brother and sister.
- [Mitsuomi Voiceover]
Is she doing this
to get back at
Shin for something?
That's the only thing I can
think of that makes sense.
- Hey.
Come here.
(giggles)
(intense music)
- Oh shit!
Hold on, wait!
We got nothing to do with
katana hunting, I swear.
We didn't do it.
That's the truth, don't!
- Hey come on, run for it.
- [Shin] Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure you guys had
nothing to do with it.
(intense music)
I just need to blow
off a little steam.
(intense music)
- [Mana] What's wrong?
You've been awfully quiet today.
- Of all the guys, why me?
- Love, take a look.
Can't you see that I'm
madly in love with you?
Would you have
believed that before?
Your turn, Mitsuomi.
Why'd you sleep with me?
- Well to be completely honest,
'cause you're Shin's girlfriend.
- [Mana] And hear I was
hoping you might tell me
something a little bit sweeter.
- Sorry.
- [Mana] What would
you do if he found out?
Would you fight Shin?
If you were to win that fight...
- I have no intention
of fighting him.
I'd lose.
- Then you're more of a
coward than I thought.
(giggles)
But I kinda like that about you.
I'm the same way.
(phone ringing)
- [Bunshichi]
Mitsuomi, that you?
- [Mitsuomi] Bunshichi?
- Damn it, get off me!
- Oh yeah, sorry
about all the noise.
I'm visiting Ishimatsu
in the hospital.
Unfortunately, it's turned
into a big rage fest.
Just trying to get out
of the hospital right now
so we can go hunt the
culprit down on his own.
- Could you say that again?
I didn't quite get it all.
- Sure, I'm in the hospital.
That's Ishimatsu
in the background.
No, I said hospital!
- Do something!
Make sure you find
that little shit
who did this to me.
Did you hear me?
You even listening
to me, damn it?
- Will you shut the
fuck up already?
Can't you see I'm in the
middle of a phone call?
Don't you know it's not
polite to interrupt?
Now sit down.
(groans)
Look what you did!
(phone beeping)
(ominous music)
Hey, what a surprise,
you're all here.
- [Man] Bunshichi, it's
time for you to come clean.
Is there something
you're not telling us?
- I don't account to you.
Who the hell do you
think you are, my mom?
That thought makes
my stomach turn.
- [Man] We're talking
about the katana hunter.
They beat the crap
out of Ishimatsu.
We can't just go around
ignoring this clown anymore.
Katana's entire reputation
is at stake now.
- In other words, Bunshichi,
we're sick and
tired of you yanking
our freaking chains on this one.
We want to know why
you've got the whole club
sitting on our damn hands.
- The list of guys who
can take Ishimatsu down
is pretty slim.
Sic all of us on him and
we'll find him in no time.
- I'm working on a good lead.
Just give me a little more time.
- [Man] Well then,
Mr. Vice President,
why don't you at least
tell us what that lead is?
- You know, seems to me
you're doing all you can
not to reveal the culprit.
You think you could at
least give me a light?
(gasps)
- I'm not gonna stand here
and listen to your bullshit.
If you guys have a problem
with how I run things,
bring it on.
There's not a single
person here I can't take.
(gasping)
Make sure Ishimatsu
stays tied to his bed.
If he opens those wounds again,
he really will die.
(thunder rumbling)
Any second now, it'll storm.
(soft jingle)
(dog barking)
- [Mana] Take this.
- What is it?
- It's a present.
Open it when you get home
and take a close look.
You asked me why I chose you.
The answer is inside that box.
If you look closely,
you'll see it.
- So you were looking
specifically for me.
Not just anyone?
- That's right.
I only did it
because it was you.
I've been waiting a
very long time for you
to enter the academy.
I promise.
You may find it hard to believe
that I'm telling the truth,
but come tomorrow, I think
you'll start to believe me.
- [Mitsuomi] I gotta go.
- [Mana] Emi.
- Yes.
Right here.
- Whatever you do,
please don't hate me for this.
- I don't.
Miss Mana, it's an assignment,
you don't have a choice.
- Earrings and this thing.
What's on it?
- [Bunshichi] Hey.
- What's up, Bunshichi?
- Sorry to keep
calling you earlier.
Man, everybody's so
uptight right now.
Wow, this is weird.
I wonder what Kuzunoha
is getting at.
So I guess you're
still seeing her, huh?
- Yeah, sorry.
- (chuckles) Hey, you don't
gotta apologize to me.
So what's on this thing?
Porn, I hope.
- Yeah, it's me
having sex with her.
(groans)
Hey relax man, I
was just joking.
This thing kinda freaks me out.
Will you please
watch it with me?
(static hissing)
Did you get it connected?
- I'm still trying to remember
how to run this thing.
I think it's this.
- And this is for you.
Look.
- Yep, here we go.
- Looks like they're
at school, doesn't it?
- It sure looks like it.
- It isn't my fault,
it's the club.
You know I've got
responsibilities to them.
- There you go again, using
your club to cover your lies.
Well I'm tired of it.
If you want to play
with them all day, fine.
Go ahead.
- What the hell is this?
Looks like the only footage
that's on this thing
is of Shin and Mana.
(laughing)
(yawns)
- [Mitsuomi Voiceover]
This is the first time
that I've seen her
laugh like this.
(snoring)
Why'd she give this to me?
What am I supposed
to get from it?
(tape whirring)
- [Mitsuomi] Bunshichi,
Bunshichi, wake up.
- What?
- There's something weird
about this video she gave me.
- Huh, what is that?
- I noticed it earlier
but didn't say anything.
Look, right there.
That's you and me
in the background.
- Huh?
- Now, watch it closely.
We're in it there.
And there.
And there too.
It's never much, but
we're always somewhere
in the background.
Now try to think back.
Do you ever remember
someone recording us?
Tell me, why would
anyone want to take
all this footage of us?
- [Shin] You son of a bitch!
You know whose sister
you laid a hand on?
Do ya?
(intense music)
- [Woman] I'm sorry,
I'm really sorry!
(whimpering)
- Stop, please stop.
- [Shin] Fall, damn it!
- Don't do this.
- I said fall,
you freaking loser.
You ain't got a chance!
- I've known Shin
for a long time.
For more than 10 years now.
(laughing)
But that guy, I don't know.
- [Civilian] Wait,
we got nothing to do
with katana hunting, I swear.
- We didn't do it!
- Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure you guys had
nothing to do with it.
I just need to blow
off a little steam.
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
- That look in his eye.
I've never seen Shin like that.
(screams)
- What the hell's going on?
Who is this?
What's gotten into him?
(laughing)
Why is someone recording
this footage of him?
Mitsuomi.
- [Mana] You asked
me why I chose you.
The answer is inside that box.
Inside.
As head of the Gou Kishi Style,
one of the most important jobs
the Takayanagi family has
is to watch over anyone
with supernatural powers.
Shin Natsume is a
valuable data sample.
His power surfaced early
on in his childhood.
With his permission,
he has been continually
watched and recorded by
several dozen staff members
for quite some time.
And because the
Kuzunoha family serves
under the Takayanagi clan,
I had no choice.
I had to accept the role
of Shin's girlfriend.
It was merely a task I
was given, nothing else.
(laughing)
But still.
Why do I wish I was
close to him right now?
- Miss Mana.
- [Mana] The moon sure
looks pretty tonight.
I wonder if we'll see
some sunshine tomorrow.
- I don't think so.
I heard there's a storm coming.
- Brother!
Brother!
Father, mother.
Both of them are dead!
- I was surprised.
People are more
solid than I thought.
- Huh?
- I thought it'd be like TV.
That I could easily slice
through them without a problem.
But it all ended up being
more difficult and noisy
than I expected.
(ominous music)
Maya, from here on out,
nothing will separate us, okay?
(whimpering)
(laughing)
(gasps)
- I must've fallen asleep here.
It's been a long time since
I've dreamt about that day.
Chokuto reiki.
- [Maya Voiceover] A
combination of magic.
A katana that has every spell
of Onmio, Jukon, and Dokio
sealed within its blade.
It creates a
symbiotic relationship
with the powers of
whomever is wielding it,
and its aura shifts
from handler to handler.
However, no matter
which attack I choose
or how much chi I build,
the reiki has never
revealed its powers to me.
I have no supernatural powers.
I am a disgrace to
the Natsume family.
My only choice is
to become stronger.
Like a cold steel
blade that rips through
anything that stands in its way.
- Stronger!
(dramatic music)
- [Shin Voiceover]
Maya, there's no need
for you to become stronger.
You are the only ray
of light that I have
in this cursed existence.
Every power that I have is here,
ready to protect you.
So come on, Maya.
Stay by my side.
Forever.
And ever.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
- [Narrator] Power brings
forth the darkness.
Darkness leads one to terror.
Next episode of Tenjho Tenge.
Darkness.
Where am I trying to go?