(static hissing)
(droning electronic music)
(upbeat pop music)
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Yeah
♪ Bomb a head, your party time
♪ Party time
♪ Ah, yeah
♪ Yeah
♪ Time to party time
♪ Party time
♪ Ah, yeah
♪ Yeah
(fighters shouting)
(dramatic music)
(energy whooshing)
- [Mitsuomi] Impossible,
that's the Takayanagi clan's
best-kept move, Ryukei
Kikou, Tanshinkou!
- It seems both of us
were destined to lose.
In the end, we couldn't
defeat our weaknesses,
or our fate.
(energy whooshing)
(somber music)
(needle squelching)
- [Dogen] So Mitsuomi,
what brings you here?
- Well, Dad, over
the last month,
I've been thinking a
lot about that match,
so I did some research,
and you know what?
There's still one thing that
I just don't understand.
- Hmm.
- [Mitsuomi] It's this one
true martial artist bit
that I found in our
family's legends.
What did you want, for me to
become a god or something?
- Mitsuomi, do you know
the symbolism behind
our family's crest,
the Takayanagi hallmark,
the flying phoenix?
Its right wing is
called the Shirohaneshu
and the left wing
is the Akahaneshu.
The Shirohane are martial
artists and continue to thrive,
while the Akahane have
since dwindled away.
There are entire families
that are now lost to us,
and here's the reason why.
As society advanced,
their special powers
were made obsolete.
However, these people
do still exist.
They're born all the time.
Their story is pathetic
and it's my responsibility
to save their wretched souls.
That's the duty I have as the
head of the Takayanagi family
and as Kaima'a best friend,
Shin Natsume's father.
(doors crash)
(gunshots thudding)
(bullets zinging)
(dramatic music)
(bodyguard grunts)
(gunshots booming)
(bullet casing clinks)
- Eh, Mitsuomi,
what's happening?
(suspenseful music)
- Listen, kid, this
is serious, sit...
(yelps)
(fist squelches)
(bodies thud)
- Mitsuomi, have
you gone insane?
- I took a bit of cash and
hired Master Fu's friends.
Don't worry, it only cost
you a couple of buildings.
Listen, Dad, you may
have your history right,
but you're wrong
about the superhumans.
It's not salvation they need.
It's absolute power.
That is the true martial
artist I envision.
- (growls) Stand
your guard, Mitsuomi.
You're out of line!
(energy whooshing)
(glass clatters)
(Dogen groaning)
- [Mitsuomi] Every last bit
of the Takayanagi clan's
power will be mine.
You're worthless, Dad.
It's time for you to retire.
(sword clangs)
(ominous music)
- [Pei] Mitsuomi! (whimpers)
- Yes, Pei, you've done
all you can do for me.
Now beat it.
(horn honking)
(wind whooshing)
- Bunshichi and Scum are
both in critical condition.
It's gonna be at least next
year before they're back.
I don't have time
to just sit around
and wait for them to return.
I did a bit of research
on the students here.
A few dozen of them latently
possess supernatural powers.
I have to reform the Council.
It's absolutely
crucial that I expand
its present scope of control.
Otherwise, I'll be helpless
when their powers awaken.
When you're ready, come on by.
I'll be waiting.
(Maya gasps)
(somber music)
- Mi-Mitsuomi! (sobs)
You fool, you're such
a fool! (sobbing)
well, two years have
passed since then.
Tell me, big brother,
have I gotten stronger?
Do you think I might even
be able to stop you now?
Is there a chance that he will...
- Maya.
(Maya gasps)
What are you doing
in here wasting time?
We gotta hurry, we
need to get the Reiki
out of Aya's hands
as soon as possible.
Come on, let's go.
- I'm sorry, you're right.
- [Bunshichi] All
right, I'm outta here.
Tell those two idiots
they can figure out
the rest on their own.
- [Aya] Thanks for taking
the time to do this.
- [Bunshichi] So now that
you know, what do you think?
- [Aya] Well, to be honest,
I hate Maya even more now.
I mean, if she'd had a good
grip on her own emotions,
nobody would've had to die.
- Mm, well, that's kinda true.
- However, I can
stand behind her now,
now that I've heard
the backstory and know
that it's not just her being
selfish about everything.
Part of me hates her,
but another part of me
really respects her, too.
(Bunshichi chuckles)
- Hey, check out
that moon tonight.
(traffic whooshing)
(dogs barking)
- You know something, Bob?
- Know what, Souichiro?
- I'm totally starving.
- Me, too.
- Stop, Takayanagi-senpai!
You're being really
mean right now!
- I think you're the
mean one here, Aya!
What were you thinking
sleeping in the same room
with a pubescent teenager?
You put yourself
in this position!
- I think there's a problem.
Something seems to
be dripping out.
- It's just my fiery passion
for you getting ahead of me!
Welcome to puberty!
Uh?
(gasping)
(Aya snoring softly)
Oh, no, did I just?
Such a waste.
(birds chirping)
- Good morning.
- What's up?
- Hey, man.
- [Aya] I'm sorry for
intruding upon you last night.
- [Masataka] Oh (chuckles),
that's all right.
You had a lot to think about
between the captain and all
that stuff with the Reiki.
- Hmm?
- (chuckles) I mean,
damn it, what's going on!
We slept next to each other
on the exact same futon
and she's, like,
totally oblivious to it!
Stay focused, Masataka,
you still have a chance!
Tonight you'll score for sure!
- Don't worry, I'll go back
to my own house tonight.
- Great!
- Stop, you two!
(Masataka gasps)
I hope that you understand
the gravity of the
situation here.
Enough with the games.
Hand over that katana!
(Masataka grunts)
(tires screeching)
- Big sister!
- Captain, I can explain...
- Can it!
(Masataka yelps)
- [Masataka] This whole episode
has really sucked for me!
- Aya, hand over the Reiki.
- No way!
(car door clicks)
(dramatic fanfare)
(engine roaring)
(Souichiro gasps)
- Aya!
- Get back here!
- Bob, let me steer!
- Are you freaking nuts?
I know they haven't been
giving you much airtime,
but this is insane!
(dramatic music)
(sword zinging)
- [Emi] Give it up, will you?
You can't win, so just
hand that katana over
and be done with this.
- [Aya] Stay away from me!
- You're causing a whole
lot of trouble, little girl.
If you refuse to comply,
then you leave me no choice.
The Executive Council's
Shocking Pink Bomber, Emi Isuzu!
Let's go!
(weapons clang)
- [Aya] Stay away from me!
(energy whooshing)
(Emi screams)
(dramatic rock music)
- (groans) Damn it, don't
you run away from me.
- [Maya] Mitsuomi,
wait, you promised me
that you wouldn't
get involved in this!
- The Reiki's too
fond of killing,
so now it's time for
me to kill the Reiki.
- Big brother, I won't
let you touch her!
Now step back.
(energy whooshes)
- Outta my way!
- Ah!
- Make room for the leading man.
- [Masataka] (screams)
That's my face! (shouts)
- Amen.
That's our teammate, moron!
- Ow!
- Souichiro-sama!
- [Souichiro] Aya, whatever
you do, don't move!
- Okay.
- You there,
so do you always go
around harassing chicks
this early in the morning?
- Careful, boy.
(dramatic fanfare)
- [Souichiro] Those
two are standing
a little too close
for my comfort.
Back off, dude!
- Hand my damn bike over now!
- I'll hand you over
one good ass-kicking.
(tires screeching)
(Maya yelps)
- Oh, yeah, that's right.
Souichiro-sama has
his heart set on...
(Mitsuomi grunts)
(Souichiro shouts)
Someone besides me.
- [Bob] Chiaki had to take out
a loan to buy me that bike.
She's gonna be
really pissed off.
I guess I just gotta
turn up the hustle
a few more notches tonight.
- Mm, don't stop.
- Hey, Bob, it's all
that bastard's fault!
- Shut up!
- I'm sorry, but can
you just leave things
the way they are for today?
I'll make sure that Aya
and these two morons
are given a proper scolding.
- Are you gonna let the
same thing happen again?
(Maya gasps)
The mistakes from two years ago?
- Hey, you, it doesn't
matter if that stupid katana
is back or not.
Hate to say it, but things
are a whole lot different now
than they were back in your day,
- You think so.
- [Bob] The captain and Aya
have got us on their side now,
as well as your little
brother, Masataka-senpai.
- Two years ago,
you may have had
our captain's best interest in
mind, but look what happened.
Come on, say something!
- The two of them are
addressing her as our captain
for the first time.
- [Maya] That's enough!
- Get her, Bob.
- Sure.
(Maya shrieks)
- You ain't in no position
to lecture anybody.
Come on and get me, lowlife!
(upbeat electronic music)
- Did you call me a lowlife?
Your mistake.
- Big brother!
- Pay attention, Masataka.
Watch what happens
when you mouth off.
- Shut up, stop trying to act
like a freakin'
badass, you lowlife.
You look like an idiot!
What kind of a wanker walks
around with his clothes so tight
you can see his freakin' nipple?
Not to mention
that boner you get!
I don't wanna see that
shit, it's disgusting!
What decade do you think
we're living in, anyway,
you steroid-pumping freak?
Get with the time! (grunting)
- I've told you this before.
Your attacks are all
talk and no action.
- (grunts) Is that so?
Then I guess this won't
bother you at all.
- [Mitsuomi] Listen, punk,
where the hell did you get that?
- What is it, what did
the boy just show him?
- Hmm, how would I know?
- Anything goes
in a street fight.
(Mitsuomi shouts)
(both grunting)
- Hold on, captain.
I understand he can be
pretty thick sometimes,
but that's the only way he
knows to go about doing things.
(Souichiro shouting)
(fists thudding)
This is his way of
telling you something.
Uh!
- That all you got?
- What the... (Mitsuomi shouts)
(Souichiro yelps)
- Oh!
(glass clatters)
- [Aya] Souichiro-sama!
(Mitsuomi shouts)
- Eat this! (shouts)
- Huh?
Oh, well.
Forget it, I'm not gonna
repeat the same grade again!
Damn you, Bob, why
are you always gone?
(Bob sneezes)
- That's just gross.
(Emi groans)
- Sorry.
(Aya grunts)
(wind whooshing)
(energy whooshing)
(Aya yelps)
(dragon roaring)
(static hissing)
(dramatic music)
- I can hear them.
- What happened two years ago
was way beyond the grasp of a
common street thug like you!
- [Aya] It won't stop.
- You're so stupid,
you don't even get it!
- [Aya] I don't wanna hear this!
- It's not Maya's fault!
(Mitsuomi grunts)
Any guy who makes the chick
I fell for cry will pay!
You'll regret the day
you ever laid a hand
on this street thug.
I'll do anything for Maya!
- No, stop it!
(explosion booms)
(crowd screams)
(wind whooshing)
- Mitsuomi!
- Souichiro!
- [Aya] I know, I
already know all of that.
(Souichiro groaning)
(Mitsuomi retches)
- Mitsuomi!
(Souichiro shouts)
(kick thuds)
(both shout)
(Mitsuomi grunts)
(fist thudding)
(both grunting)
- On that day, what did
I decide I would do?
(soaring music)
I said I would stand
by Souichiro-sama
and cheer him on, no
matter what happened.
That's it, then.
I have no choice but
to become stronger!
(Mitsuomi retches)
(Maya gasps)
- So what do we do?
- Hey, sis!
- Huh?
- Here you go, I'm
giving it back.
(sword whirring)
(sword zings)
- Maya!
(wind whistling)
(breath hisses softly)
- Goodbye, Souichiro-sama.
Get up!
(Souichiro grunts)
On your feet!
Now listen, just accept
you're going to be
Aya Natsume's husband!
Don't cry, don't cry.
However, look at you!
Your number of defeats
are unacceptable!
Nobody wants a
weakling for a fiance!
So if you lose again,
I will just cancel the
engagement, all right?
- Aya, wait a sec.
(Aya whimpers)
(Aya sobs)
(chuckles) You mind telling
me when I became your fiance?
- You're at a disadvantage,
Natsume! (chuckles)
(Souichiro moaning)
- Stop it!
(Souichiro grunts)
(Aya gasps)
(Maya shouts)
(Souichiro grunts)
The Reiki is back.
There's no need
to continue this.
- [Bob and Masataka]
(grunting) Ours!
- I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
I can't let you
destroy it just yet.
Let it go for now.
- You think I'll just
walk away after all this?
- Come on, Mitsuomi, you've
already pushed yourself.
You know as well as I
that this is not the place
for us to settle our score.
(somber music)
In a month from now, the
preliminaries will begin.
We can settle things
then, once and for all.
- Fine, but let's get
one thing straight.
There's a reason I've
kept the Juken Club alive,
and it's not out
of pity or regret.
- I'm well aware of that.
As for you.
(Souichiro laughs nervously)
- [Bunshichi] Nice job.
- [Emi] I'm so sorry, sir.
- [Mitsuomi] Are you all right?
- [Emi] Yes.
- [Mitsuomi] There's
still plenty of tasks
that I need you for.
- Yes, of course!
- Hmm. (chuckles)
- You're a bad woman, Natsume.
- This was so not cool, dumbass.
- Captain, I just
thought that...
- Hey, forget it.
You handled it the best
way that you know how.
(Souichiro laughs)
But we only have a month
'til the preliminaries.
All five of us are gonna need
every single bit of
that time to train.
Huh?
- Huh?
(energy whooshing)
- Check out Aya.
- What's up now?
- I didn't do it.
(Masataka laughs)
- Just be that way.
If you guys wanna
stand down there
and pretend like I'm not
even here, then fine.
Oh, who am I kidding,
I don't care!
Souichiro-sama!
- [Souichiro] Oh,
God, Bob, help me!
- Don't be such a freak.
(Souichiro shouting)
- [Maya] Stop
acting like a fool!
(dramatic music)
(upbeat pop music)
(singing in foreign language)
(dramatic music)
- [Souichiro] What,
special training, me?
I don't need that crap.
Huh, the 12 God-Lords, what
the hell is that about?
Next episode of Tenjho
Tenge, "Dragon's Fist."
Wha, what the hell is this?