("Bomb a Head V")
- [Bunshichi] It's
pretty simple.
Other than each
team having a total
of only five members
there are absolutely
no other rules
you need to worry about.
Everything's allowed.
You get to choose any
showdown you want.
(shouts)
- You can't let your guard down!
(groans)
- [Maya] So this is what the
preliminaries are all about.
Kinda fun!
- Kinda fun!
- Feel free to kill as
much as you want today.
(sword clanks)
- I used to feel obligated
to follow your orders
but those days
are long gone now.
(electricity crackles)
(shouts)
- I know, too much clothing.
(tearing)
(dramatic music)
- How could you do this?
Have you no conscience?
Do you know what you're
getting yourselves into?
If Shin's powers
spin out of control
none of you will be spared!
- These are Master Fu's orders.
We're just doing
what we were told.
You should stay out of this.
(blade scrapes)
(door slides)
- [Man] Master
are you all right?
Have you been hurt?!
We warned you of this!
I knew it was dangerous
for you to see him alone!
That punk, he's
nothing but a nuisance!
- Just calm down.
- But sir.
- I guess I have no choice.
It's an incredible
barbaric approach
but we'll handle this Fu's way.
(sword scrapes)
According to the legend
every time another man
is killed by this blade
one more ripple
appears in its metal.
Kaima
is one of these
ripples the only thing
that's left to remind us of you?
(heartbeats)
- You're kiddin me.
They've already started
to fight the next match?
(shouts and whooshing)
- Come on now!
This is gettin old!
Stop takin your sweet
time with this fight!
(shouts)
(footsteps echo)
(whooshing)
(chuckles)
- [Mitsuomi] What's
up, why won't he fight?
(footsteps echo)
- [Shin] Yo.
Sorry I'm late for the match.
But who am I going
up against, huh?
- Myself, now step inside!
(door slides)
(high-pitched hum)
(murmuring)
- What the hell?
I just got a bad vibe.
I've had this feeling before.
(high-pitch hum)
- Dammit, Shin!
- You're not leaving this
match without finishing it.
- You bastard.
So this is what you were up it!
(whooshing and shouts)
- [Man] Master look!
The blade, its...
- What do we do boss?
This blade's evil aura is
spreading throughout the campus!
- Damn that demonic katana!
It knows it's
master has awakened
and it's trembling
with excitement!
(high-pitch hum)
(groaning)
(loud crash)
(shouting)
(whoosh and shouts)
- Stop.
Stop it please.
- He's so strong.
Do you remember his
friend, the street fighter?
I believe Bunshichi
was his name.
He told Shin that his powers
were only second rate.
He thought that unless he
had the Reiki in his hands
his powers were
completely useless.
But he was wrong, his powers
are so immense and vast
that he's overwhelmed
by them to the point
that he needs the Reiki
just so he can control them.
Shin didn't come crawling
towards his katana
because he wanted to win.
He was afraid that without it
he would lose control and
kill everyone around him.
Including that Tawara boy.
(shouts)
My work's done.
I've accomplished the task
that I've set out to do.
Please excuse me.
I know it's rude to
leave you ladies behind.
(blades thumping)
I'd forgotten you
had that skill.
Nicely done.
My, you're quite good with
those assassination weapons.
It must have been easy for
you to cut those ropes.
(electricity crackles)
- [Emi] Wood, fire,
metal, and water.
The chi of earth.
If that's the
energy you're using
you can assume it will
gravitate to the nearest object.
You got overconfident and
gave away too many secrets.
All right, consider
yourself warned.
Cause I'm not gonna let you step
one foot outside of this room.
- [Mana] I've got to find
someone who can help me!
Who can I turn to?!
Someone has to be willing to
stop Shin before it's too late!
(dramatic music)
- [Fu] Oh brother.
I've got a tiger
guarding the front gate.
And a wolf guarding the rear.
Do they really think
that they can take me?
(high-pitch hum)
- You're the one
that Shin is after.
Most of his anger is
targeted directly at you.
If you figure out a
way to calm him down
then maybe he'll get his
powers back under control.
(high-pitch hum)
- (sighs) People
think so little of me.
I've got a boy who can't
control his powers.
And a little girl
who's only defense
is tossing daggers in the air.
(electricity crackles)
Think you can stop Fu Chi'en?!
Do you two kids really believe
you have what it takes?!
Huh?!
- [Mana] There's more of them?
(shouts and groans)
(shouts)
Hu Quan Teng Di Bai Lian Wu Shi!
(groans)
(electricity crackles)
(shouts)
(thunder booms)
(flute plays)
(Guzheng plays)
(electricity crackles)
(shouts)
(thunder booms)
He must've mastered
the Dragon's Eye.
He was able to foresee the
flow of energy and evade it.
(exclaims)
Guess I need to not
hold back next time.
My, my, my hands!
My hands!
Wait... ju..just
hold on a minute!
(high-pitch hum)
(panting)
(shouting)
(energetic music)
(blades clang)
(shouts)
(chuckles)
(laughter)
(hisses)
- No, big brother don't do it!
Mitsuomi!
(shouts)
(groans)
Mitsuomi.
Mitsuomi!
(dramatic music)
- [Bunshichi] Hey!
I wanna know what the
hell happened right now!
Tell me what's goin
on with Mitsuomi.
And what about Shin,
who provoked him?!
Answer me already, dammit!
- Will you just shut up?!
I don't need this.
- You arrogant bitch!
- [Dogen] Oh my god.
How can this be?
This wasn't supposed to happen!
Mitsuomi!
(door slides)
- They said nothin's
wrong with me.
He gave me a totally
clean bill of health.
- [Doctor] He's
got some bruising
on both sides of his chest
from the internal bleeding
but other than that he's good.
His internal organs hardly
suffered any damage at all.
- Even you're here too, dad?
You're overreacting.
- [Doctor] You're
pretty lucky kid.
I'm betting it was these
dense muscles of yours
that absorbed most
of the impact.
I've been a doctor
for a long time.
But I've never seen
such a perfect set
of muscles on a body before.
Guess you've got some
good genetics there.
- Thanks, doc.
- I just wanted to stop
by and say thank you.
You saved my life back there.
I heard you're okay.
I'm so relieved.
- Yeah, I am.
Thanks a lot.
(growls)
But you know, I was
just acting on impulse.
I wasn't...
Hey does anyone know
where my dad went?
- He was just there
a few minutes ago.
(knocking)
(smack and groans)
- Don't you think a mangy
mutt should know his place?
Considering the approach Fu took
I'm gonna let you off
the hook this time.
But there is no next time!
- Aren't you the lucky one?
You should be glad that
his kid's all right.
- If somethin had
happened to his boy
you'd be swimming
with the fishes
at the bottom of Tokyo Bay.
Huh?
(shouts)
(high-pitch hum)
- That kid's a monster!
- [Bunshichi] Shin.
- Hey, Shin.
- Mitsuomi, sorry about that.
I was lookin over my shoulder
out of my patched eye.
You caught me in my blind spot
and when I finally
recognized who you were
it was too late.
- Big brother!
- I figured that.
I realize that it was
all just an accident.
What else could it be?
- [Maya] At that moment
the only thing I was concerned
with was Mitsuomi's health.
The fact that my brother
was crumbling before my eyes
was lost on me.
Mitsuomi was all
that I worried about.
- [Shin] How about you, Maya?
You all right?
(smacks)
- [Maya] Mitsuomi!
- Hm?
- [Maya] If only I didn't
scream when Mitsuomi
entered the classroom.
Maybe his fate would've
been different.
The Dragon's Eye.
The Reiki.
Destiny.
None of these things
are the problem.
- [Mitsuomi] What's up,
is something wrong, Maya?
- [Maya] I'm the fire that's
devouring my big brother.
You should go away!
You shouldn't have
anything to do with me!
I tried to tell him that.
I tried to get those
words out of my mouth.
But they wouldn't come.
No matter how hard I tried.
They just stayed
caught in my throat.
(somber music)
(groans)
("Aishiene Motto")
- [Voiceover] What
one hears is destiny
showering down like rain.
What one sees is the
deep river of shadows.
Next episode of "Tenjou Tenge"
"Determination".
You've got to do it, you've
got to stop these tears!