(static crackling)
(energetic rhythmic music)
(singer singing in
foreign language)
♪ Yeah
♪ Bomb A Head
♪ Your party time
♪ Party time
♪ Yeah
♪ Time to party time
♪ Party time
♪ Yeah
(blow thudding)
(Souichiro grunting)
(chains rattling)
- That midget chick
happens to be the only girl
I've ever fallen in love with.
(eerie dramatic music)
- Aya!
(metal clanking)
(Aya shrieking)
(water splashing)
Stay right there
Aya, we need to talk!
That katana you have is...
- Shut up!
- It's the chokuto Reiki.
Someone claims to have
seen it on campus.
- Not again.
(intense electronic music)
(car engines rumbling)
(tires squealing)
(footsteps thudding)
- I want you to take your group
and check out the south hall!
- [Leader] Yes ma'am, let's go!
- [Men] Yes sir!
- [Leader] I want you to
always move in groups,
and if you find her, you
are not to attack her!
- [Men] Yes sir.
- [Hoida Leader] Hoida family!
- [Hoida Family] Yes, sir!
- [Takamia Leader]
Takamia family,
search the center corridor
of the south hall.
- [Takamia Family] Yes, sir!
- [Matsui Leader] Matsui
family, take the east hall.
- [Matsui Family] Yes, sir!
- [Matsui Leader] Your
target is the younger sister
of the Natsume family, Aya.
She has hair down to her
ankles and a long katana.
- [Matsui Family] Yes, sir.
- [Maya] Mitsuomi!
- [Masataka] Big brother!
(footsteps thudding)
- What's the Reiki
doing back, Maya?
I thought you'd taken
care of that sword.
- Mitsuomi, I'll
apologize for that later
but now I need you to help us.
- Fine then.
I've already gathered
as many as I could
from the Takayanagi clan.
- Excuse me, but the
Reiki's the katana
that the captain's big
brother used to use, right?
And now that Aya has
the sword in her hands
and then if she uses it,
what kind of things are
gonna happen to her?
- [Both] That has
nothing to do with you!
(Masataka gasping)
- [Maya] Someone
saw her this way.
- Fine.
(Masataka gasping)
- Hold on, I can help out too!
- Outta the way, kid!
(Masataka yelping)
- Stay in formation.
- Hold formation!
- Keep it tight!
- You're blocking the way!
- Move!
- Don't just lay there!
(Masataka groaning)
- Geez, what the heck
is their problem anyway?
Aya?
Aya!
(Aya gasping)
We've been looking
all over for ya.
The captain, my brother,
they're all makin' a
big deal out of this.
- Oh, I see.
- You know, maybe
it's not a good idea
for you to be using that katana.
I mean, that's
the chokuto Reiki.
People tell some serious
stories about that sword.
- Listen, I have a
favor to ask you.
Takayanagi-sempai, could I spend
the night with you tonight?
I really don't wanna go home.
- Well, I understand
but I'm sure that the
captain would want you to...
Huh?
- So does that mean no?
- Huh?
Huh?
(Masataka screaming)
(gentle upbeat music)
- [Aya] I hope you don't mind.
I'm sorry that I had
to ask this of you.
- No, not at all!
- Oh, do you think we can
stop by the supermarket?
The least I can do is make
you some dinner for this.
- That's very nice,
but you don't have to
go out of your way.
But I sure would like to try
some of your cooking, Aya.
Just as long as you don't mind.
(Masataka laughing)
- [Masataka Voiceover]
Aya's gonna spend the night
in my room, is this all right?
Is this really all right?
- So what would you like to eat?
Do you want chicken or
fish or vegetables, maybe?
- Uh, you know, I could really
go for some breast meat.
- You want me to
fix breast meat?
- Or whatever, anything
would be great.
- [Masataka Voiceover] You
know, I may be betraying
the captain and the others by
doing this, but even if I am,
I'll never be able to wipe
the smile off my face!
(playful music)
(Souichiro groaning)
- I think you've
finally had enough.
Now drag your asses home,
take a shit and go to bed.
- Hey, just 'cause you took
out the midget's big brother
doesn't make you
some kinda hot shot!
- What?
- We wanna know what kinda
history you and Maya got goin'.
Tell us, did everything
come to an end
when you finished
off that Shin dude?
- Why should I?
- If everything's all over,
why does the midget
keep fighting?
Why did Mitsuomi kill Shin?
I know you know the truth,
so tell us, damn it!
(Souichiro screaming)
- Sit down!
(blow thudding)
(Souichiro groaning)
(peaceful string music)
- You remember the
first time we met?
I remember it.
And I remember that you
had the Reiki with you.
(air whooshing)
- Don't make me remember
that horrible day.
- [Mitsuomi] It wasn't Shin
or Aya who had the Reiki,
it was you, Maya.
- It was my father who
had put me in charge
of looking after the Reiki.
The chokuto Reiki
is the culmination
of every known form
of spell-binding.
It contains spells from
yin-yang, Jukon, and Doukyo.
It feels the power of its
wielder and resonates with them.
Sometimes it produces rain
and sometimes it kills people.
However, if it
happens that its user
possesses absolutely
no powers at all,
then it's nothing but
a very long katana.
Unlike Aya or my big brother,
I possess no powers at all,
I'm nothing but a harmless
protector for the Reiki,
and a disgrace to
the Natsume family.
The moment I first realized that
was the same moment you and
I first faced each other.
(knives whooshing)
(vegetables sizzling)
- So, can I help
you with anything?
- I'm all right.
In fact, you should
probably stand back
because it's gonna
get a little messy.
- Oh, okay.
It smells really good, you know!
I'm lookin' forward
to eating it.
I can barely contain myself!
- I'm afraid you're going
to have to wait a bit,
I'm trying hard to make
it really good for you.
(Aya humming)
(Masataka humming)
(Masataka shrieking)
- This is so cool!
(Masataka gasping)
- [Masataka Voiceover]
Hey, you know.
- [Dogen] I've got a meeting
with the board of directors,
I won't be home until late.
- [Masataka Voiceover]
Please come back
really late tonight, Dad!
(phone ringing)
- I'm coming, I'm coming!
Hello, Takayanagi residence!
Oh, well, hello there, Dad.
- [Dogen] Masataka, is that you?
I don't think I'm gonna
make it home tonight.
Looks like I'm gonna end up
doing an all-nighter
with the board.
(Masataka gasping)
So you're on your own.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah, sure, that's gonna
be no problem at all!
Thanks a lot, I love you, Dad!
(phone line beeping)
- I love you, Dad?
Ha, must be some girl.
Well, I guess I should
probably celebrate this.
- What time is your dad
supposed to be coming back home?
- (gasping) He's with his board,
they're doin' it all night.
- Huh, doing it all night?
- (gasping) No, no, no,
it's not anything like that!
- So what're they doing,
playing mahjong or something?
- Yes, that's
exactly it, mahjong!
- Well, isn't that a shame.
You know, I was really
hoping that I might
be able to cook for him as well.
- That's right, it's
an awful, awful shame!
(Masataka chuckling)
- Well, I'm just
about done here.
I hope you're still
excited about it.
- Oh, I'm definitely
I'm excited about tonight!
(Masataka laughing)
(suspenseful music)
- We've looked everywhere and
there's still no sign of her.
I think it's probably
safe to assume
that she's no longer on campus.
I should just go back
to the house now,
maybe Aya finally
decided to return home.
- [Emi] Would you like me
to lend a couple of men?
- [Maya] Huh?
- If your sister were to
actually use the Reiki,
I really doubt
that you'd be able
to control her single-handedly.
- You can go ahead and
disband all of the men.
I'll go with her.
(Emi gasping)
- That's not necessary!
Miss Isuzu, may I please
borrow 10 of your men?
- Of course, I'd be happy
to lend them to you!
I'll dispatch them to
your house right away!
(Emi laughing)
- You really are an
easy one to figure out.
- In the worst case scenario,
it's possible all 10 of
those men will end up dead.
I'm going to go with you, Maya.
Besides, I'm as
good as dead anyway.
(bright bamboo flute music)
(bright shamisen music)
(playful music)
(Masataka chomping)
(Masataka slurping)
- You might wanna eat
just a little bit slower.
(Masataka mumbling)
So, how is it?
- Gah, it's so good, wow!
- Glad you like it!
- It melts in my mouth!
In fact, it's melting
tongue, it's amazing!
- That's a pretty
big compliment.
Um, I hate to keep
troubling you,
but could I use your shower?
I seem to have worked up quite
a sweat making this meal.
- Yeah, of course.
Go ahead, take as
much time as you need.
- Great, please excuse me, then.
(Masataka chomping)
- Did she say shower?
(Masataka moaning)
Oh man, I can't see nearly
as much as I thought.
Well, it looks like
the coast is clear.
Masataka Takayanagi,
do your thing!
(door creaking)
Pew!
(Masataka gasping)
- [Masataka Voiceover]
Wait a minute,
what the heck am I doing?
That was really close, I was
just about to do something
that I know I would
eventually live to regret.
(water splashing)
(Masataka gasping)
But you know, I may never
get a chance like this again!
In fact, I know I won't.
This is possibly the only
chance God is ever gonna give
a poor, pathetic soul like me!
So quit with all
the anxiety already.
I should hold my head up
high and just peek in there!
(door creaking)
(Aya sobbing)
(somber music)
Oh.
- I knew it!
I knew it all along!
All of it!
- That midget chick
happens to be the only girl
I've ever fallen in love with.
So if it's concerning
her, I got no problem
puttin' my body
through anything!
- [Aya] I knew!
I knew it all along!
(Aya sobbing)
(Masataka grunting)
(blow thudding)
(footsteps thudding)
- [Maya Voiceover] If I
rely on this man's strength
one more time, will I be able
to put the past behind me
and laugh again, just
like we did two years ago?
(motorcycle engine squealing)
(both laughing)
- Is something wrong?
(Maya gasping)
- No, it's nothing.
(eerie ringing music)
- [Masataka Voiceover]
I, I hear it again.
(Masataka gasping)
- Uh...
Aya, what's wrong?
(Masataka yelping)
Aya!
(Aya panting)
(Masataka gasping)
Wow, she's running a fever!
(Aya panting)
- [Shin] Aya.
- [Masataka] I know we've got
an ice pack in here somewhere!
(dog barking)
(Masataka groaning)
- [Shin] Aya!
- Is, is that you, big brother?
(eerie breathing)
(heartbeat thumping)
- [Shin] Aya.
(eerie ringing music)
(eerie breathing)
(Aya panting)
- [Aya Voiceover] Big brother!
- [Shin] This katana will
only make you unhappy.
I'm taking it with me.
- No, wait, big brother!
I, I can't move!
I, I can't speak!
- [Shin] Don't end
up like me, Aya.
- Big, big brother, don't go!
- [Aya Voiceover] Come back!
Don't take it, please!
Without that katana,
big brother, I, I...
- All I want is to become
stronger, big brother!
Sis won't tell me anything,
all I have is some
really vague notion
that there might be something
dangerous about this katana.
Is that true?
If it is, I don't care,
I just know that I have
to have that sword!
Because I can't
lose against myself.
I'm weak and I
can't give into it.
(loud crashing)
I can't do that.
I can't do it again!
(suspenseful rock music)
So please leave it, big brother.
(Reiki zapping)
- [Shin] This is the Reiki.
It will try to pull
out everything that
you've got in you.
And when it does,
you're gonna have to
come face to face
with your own powers.
Do you think you
can defeat that?
Are you positive that you
can win against this sword?
- [Aya] Mm, I'll
make sure that I win,
because I made a promise!
- [Souichiro] Next time, win.
Win and enjoy it!
- [Aya] I swore that if I
lost again, I wouldn't cry.
(Reiki whooshing)
(intense rock music)
- [Shin] I wasn't able to win.
(Aya gasping)
- What's happening to you?
- [Shin] Remember this,
this power of ours
leaves nothing to
those who lose!
(Reiki whooshing)
(Aya screaming)
The moment that you admit defeat
is the moment your
powers will destroy you!
Remember that!
- Big brother!
Wait!
Come back!
But, big brother...
(Aya groaning)
(Aya gasping)
(Aya panting)
- Wait, you can't do that, Aya.
Oh no, not there!
Oh yeah, that's nice.
- Was it a dream?
(Aya gasping)
It had to be real.
- [Aya Voiceover]
What in the world
happened to my big brother?
How did he really die?
(eerie music)
(doorbell ringing)
- [Bunshichi] Miss Makihara,
I have a special
delivery for you.
- Coming!
(door creaking)
- They are perishable, but
you don't gotta sign for 'em.
- Hey.
- I'm home, babe.
- Now just hold on,
what the heck is going
on with the two of you?
- I'm doin' them a favor
and droppin' them off.
According to them, they
both couldn't walk.
What do you say we
call it a night?
Try keepin' your half-baked
ideas to yourself.
- Um, excuse me, but we
met before, didn't we?
Back at the bowling alley?
(air whooshing)
- Oh yeah, I'm
remembering you now.
Those nice tits
helped jog my memory.
(Chiaki grunting)
- You know what this is
all about, don't you?
You know all about this
stuff from the past.
Tell us!
(Bunshichi scoffing)
- You guys sound
like a broken record.
Why don't you make
Natsume tell you?
- [Chiaki] We did, but
she left things out.
- Sorry about havin' to
kick your boyfriend's ass,
but let me get one
thing straight,
they threw the first punch.
(Chiaki grumbling)
(both grunting)
(Chiaki sighing)
- All right, listen, back when
these two were in junior high
they were referred to
as the Knuckle Bomb.
They liked to pick fights
with just the worst odds,
yet somehow they
would always win,
and before you knew it,
they both thought they
were really strong.
But then they
entered Todo Academy
and they learned that there's
a whole lotta people out there
who are way stronger than them.
This isn't about
technique or stamina
but about having the certain
kind of strength at your core.
They'd never met anyone
like that before.
I believe in these guys,
so if they really
believe in someone else
and swore to stand
by their side,
then I wanna
believe in them too.
So now, tell me what
all this is about.
- Well, it's gonna keep
you up until morning.
(Chiaki gasping)
It's one hell of a long story.
- Thanks for doing this.
- Don't thank me,
thank yourself.
If you weren't already
hooked up with this guy,
you'd be top on my to do list.
(Bob yelping)
(door thudding)
Now, where should I begin?
(singer singing in
foreign language)
(jazzy electronic music)
(intense suspenseful music)
- [Souichiro] So, why is
the midget still fighting?
And why is Mitsuomi still
pissed off at Shin Natsume?
Next episode of "Tenjho
Tenge", "Start Up"!
I'll have him fill me
in on all the details!