(static hissing)
(upbeat music)
(speaking in foreign language)
♪ Bomb a head
♪ Your party time
♪ Party time
♪ Ah yeah
♪ Yeah
♪ Time to party time
♪ Party time
♪ Ah yeah
♪ Yeah
♪ Let's go
(singing in foreign language)
♪ In the night
♪ Yeah, feel so good
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Every time I love you
♪ Every time I miss you
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Bomb a head
(air whooshing)
(ground exploding)
- German Suplex!
(boy groaning)
Power bomb!
The remaining task is
to follow his orders
and pulverize what's
left of this boys arms.
(gasps)
What have you?
- Time's up, let's go.
- [Man] This battle
isn't anywhere near over.
(tense music)
- [Bob] That's him,
there's no doubt about it.
I felt it instinctively.
That's the head of
the executive council.
(rock music)
- You have only defeated
a measly 80 opponents.
And now you need
assistance from a freshman
just so you can walk.
You're pathetic.
- Weakling, you are a disgrace
to Takayanagi name, Masataka.
- Big brother.
- They're brothers?
- Step aside.
(men grunting)
Kagurazaka.
- Righty-o.
Would you mind if I went
all the way with him?
- Do whatever you want.
(suspenseful music)
(boy grunting)
- Move dammit, come
on you piece of shit.
Move your freakin' legs.
(Bob grunting)
(Bob yelling)
(grunting)
(yelling)
- Hmm.
(eerie music)
Excellent effort.
I think rather highly
of you, Bob Makihara.
You're in an
unfortunate position.
You have an overwhelming
amount of potential and talent
yet it rusts and decays
like a forgotten sword
because there is nobody
wiling to sharpen it.
Come, work under me.
Natsume doesn't have the
skills to handle your talent.
Let me train you
and I'll turn you into the
finest weapon in this academy.
- I haven't a freakin' clue
what you're trying to say.
First of all, who
the hell are you?
- Let me introduce myself.
I'm from the Takayanagi family,
our family has overseen
the martial arts
in Japan for centuries.
If what you're seeking in
martial arts is true strength,
there is no way that you can
avoid the Takayanagi family.
- I don't know what the
hell you're tryna' get at
but I'll let you know, I
don't care about that crap.
However, there is
something you've done
that I do care about.
And I'll never
forgive you for it.
- If you're satisfied with
your current situation,
I won't force myself on you.
But, at the rate
you're going right now
you'll never be anywhere
close to competing evenly
with Souichiro Nagi.
(Bob scoffs)
I'll say it one more time,
Bob Makihara, come with me and
become the best you can be.
You have what it takes
to rule this school.
- I haven't, but what about?
(grunts)
- [Both] Huh?
- What the?
Chiaki?
- Bob, geez, you're
acting like a pussy,
you're not some kind of wimp.
You'll get tougher,
I know you will.
And everyone else knows
that to be true too.
Maya, Aya, Na-chan,
they all know that.
But more importantly,
I believe you're
capable of great things.
So it's all right, go
and get your ass kicked,
someday we'll pay him back
10 billion times over.
(girl giggles)
(thoughtful music)
(chuckles)
- Huh?
- [Bob] Chiaki, you really
are an amazing woman.
I'm afraid I don't stand a
chance against these guys
but my girl's back
there watching me,
so as long as I can stand
on my feet, I'm gonna fight.
- [Takayanagi]
Mister Kagurazaka.
- Hmm?
- Listen, when I see
those two freshmen,
I understand what
you guys must feel.
You're all afraid.
When you see a couple of
stray dogs who continue
to crawl to their feet, and
pounding after pounding,
your natural instinct
is to fear them.
Now I want to show you
what it'll feel like
when I go all the way.
(tense music)
(man yelling)
(whirring)
- What is this, what is
this bizarre feeling?
Something's different,
she's like a completely
different person now.
(Aya giggling)
What was that?
Don't you mock me!
This isn't possible.
Even at this close range,
my strikes don't
even leave a scratch.
Is this what the
dragon's eye can do?
It's like, it's like I'm moving
exactly where this
girl wants me to move.
(ground exploding)
(yelling)
(grunts)
(girl giggling)
(sinister music)
- What the hell is
she laughing about?
Is the image of me crawling
on the ground that funny?
Or is she simply
amused by strength.
(Aya giggling)
I wouldn't have expected this
kind of laughter from her.
It's so arrogant and carnal
and yet at the same
time, innocent.
It's almost like
she's, she's a...
- [Maya] Aya is still a
child, don't forget that.
- Huh?
Yeah, I know that,
it's pretty obvious.
- Normally that's not an issue
but that changes when you're
dealing with the dragon's eye.
The dragon's eye strips
their opponent bare,
earth, fire, wood, metal, water,
everything in this world is
turned into pure information
and then consumed.
She can predict the future
and see images from the past.
- Hmmm.
- And so it seems, she's
looked into the past
and seen the two of us kissing.
(man groaning)
All right, here we are.
Aya's just up the
stairs on the rooftop.
- [Guy] Got it.
- Boy, go on without me,
you're on your own on this one.
Aya is probably fighting
the toughest battle
of her life right now,
but I have no strength
left to offer her.
- Well, what about
that Tagami guy?
Is he some sort of badass?
- Within the whole academy,
he's one of the top 10 students
but right now, it isn't Tagami
that Aya is going up against.
Right now, her challenger
is the colossal power
of the dragon's eye.
She must fight for her life
to escape its monstrous jaws.
This doesn't just happen
with the dragon's eye.
In front of any form
of enormous power,
one loses all sense of
their values and morals.
They are stripped from that
person and then tossed aside.
What remains is that
individual's true potential,
your opponent then
becomes yourself.
This is more than she
can handle right now.
What she needs is someone at
her side who can assist her.
(thoughtful flute music)
(shamisen music)
(footsteps tapping)
Boy, this information
doesn't just pertain to Aya,
the time will come
when you must do battle
with your own self
and it will be fiercer
and nastier than
anyone else before you.
(electricity buzzing)
- [Aya] Souichiro-sama.
I defeated him,
he's one of the officers
from the executive council.
It's all right, I
don't think he's dead.
I hope not at least.
He must one of their
weaker officers.
His movements were so slow,
it barely seemed
like he was moving.
And his next attack
was always so obvious.
This was the first time
I've ever had this much fun
doing battle with someone.
I never knew that
punching another person
could be so exciting.
What I've done, is
really terrible, huh?
- Hey Aya, are you crying?
- Yes, I heard it.
I actually heard it.
(man screaming)
(Aya laughing)
(man yelling)
It never let up, I just
kept on hearing it!
The whole time, all I heard
was "stop, please stop".
But I didn't stop.
His muscles were torn and
his bones were shattered.
It was obvious that the
match was already over,
and yet, and yet I didn't stop.
The voice I heard was his
staff twisting in pain,
knowing that its master
was being destroyed,
my own voice was gone,
overcome by the power
of the dragon's eye.
This voice kept talking to me,
"Just use it, use the power
and the world's yours".
Then suddenly, my
opponent seemed like
nothing more than
an insect to me.
And the voice, the voice
kept telling me to kill it.
The next thing I
knew, I looked up
and he was, tell me!
What do I do, I could
have killed him!
I didn't mean for
this to happen!
The only thing I want is to
be with you Souichiro-sama.
(man yelling)
(man gagging)
- He's still alive.
Tell me, was this the first time
you had a serious
fight against someone.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Well then, as someone who's
been in a whole lot of fights,
let me give you a
few words of advice.
Whenever I'm in a fight, I
only think about one thing.
Kill 'em, that's all
that I think about.
'Cause if I don't, I end
up getting my ass kicked.
Not by my opponent but by me.
See when you're in a fight,
it's the loser who pusses out.
Even if you pummel the
crap out of the guy,
if you puss out, you lose.
It doesn't matter how badly
your opponent beats you up,
as long as you stick with
it the entire time, you win.
That's the only rule that
matters in a serious fight.
You're gonna have to
remember that, Aya.
If you ask me, you're the
one who lost this fight.
Next time, win.
Win and enjoy it.
(thoughtful music)
- So, Souichiro-sama.
- [Woman] I think what
he was trying to say,
is that she needs
to be strong enough
to win against herself.
However, that was a rather
odd way of doing it,
but I guess that's what
I should expect from him.
- Your position sure doesn't
have a whole lot of perks,
does it Natsume?
They say stress can be
beauty's achilles heel,
be careful now,
don't push yourself.
- Well, this is unexpected.
So you're here as well, are you?
- Now just point those
tits some place else,
I don't give a damn
about those things.
I'm telling you
those tits of yours
have always been a
deadly weapon against me.
There's two things in this
world that render me powerless,
shitaki mushrooms and your tits.
- Hmph, I've had enough
of your sexual harassment.
If anything you
just said was true,
this would be no problem for
me at all, Bunshichi Tawara.
The battle between
the executive council
and us has never
interested you before.
So why show up at this
point in the game?
You a henchman for that
idiot Mitsuomi now?
Have you come here
to hunt us down?
Let me tell you this right now,
I won't let you lay a finger
on either one of them.
I don't know how far I
can go in this condition
but as the Juken club
currently stands,
I'm the only one who has
even the slightest
chance against him.
- Hold on now, wait a minute!
- Huh?
- Nuh uh, I believe that
little fight downstairs
is all said and
done at this point.
(woman gasping)
About now, they're all probably
trying to get the
hell out of here.
(crowd murmuring)
- [Man] All right,
those who can walk
should head home on their own.
If the cops stop you, the
last thing you're to do
is to tell them what
school you go to.
- [Man] You get his arms
and I'll get his legs.
- [Man] Let's go
everyone, move it.
- Come on, stop with the crying.
(Aya sobbing)
Oh, I so suck at
this kind of stuff.
- That's not it.
- Huh?
- What should I do, he,
he touched my forehead.
(thoughtful music)
This is the first time
that Souichiro-sama
has ever touched me.
I'm sorry Souichiro-sama,
I'll stop crying.
I'm all right.
(Aya giggling)
(electricity crackling)
(man yelling)
- What the hell?
(Aya giggling)
- That was for good
luck, that's all it was.
Next time I'm not gonna lose.
I will win and I'll enjoy it.
But someday I'd like
for you to initiate
these kinds of things,
okay Souichiro-sama?
Oh, and about that
incident, you know,
where you were
kissing my sister?
- Oh, yeah, right about
that it, it wasn't anything.
I just, it's not what you think.
(Aya giggling)
- Aya, boy!
I'm worried about
Bob and Takayanagi,
the fight downstairs
concerns me, let's go!
- You got it.
- I won't lose sis,
this is the one thing I
don't intend to give up.
- Come on, Aya!
The boy had passed out
because he overextended
what little amount
of chi he had,
so I just gave him some
of mine to wake him up.
Nothing else
transpired between us,
you should have figured
that out on your own.
- Yes, I understand
what happened now
but the person who still
doesn't get it, is you sis.
- Huh?
- You always do this, you
seem like you know everything
but when it's really
important, when it's about you,
you're clueless.
So I'm just gonna
have to say it to you,
I'll never let you take
Souichiro-sama from me.
Souichiro-sama, wait for me!
(girl sighing)
- You are two of a kind.
She's exactly like you
when you were younger.
- Hmph, but I would prefer it
if she didn't end up
the same way that I did.
That's why this bloody
battle mustn't be passed on
to another generation.
It has to end with us.
So what's it gonna be, are
you gonna fight or what?
- Me?
I think I'll pass,
don't like the pain.
- Hmph.
(ominous music)
(crunching)
- Kagurazaka.
(keys jingling)
We're almost done, go
down and warm up my bike.
(footsteps clicking)
I'll be down in three minutes.
(boy gasps)
- Ka-chan.
- Mr. Makihara,
Takayanagi-sempai.
- You're dead.
(growling)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
- Mitsuomi Takayanagi,
President of Toudou
Academy's executive council
and the meanest
fist-fighter there is
and he's attacking
my Souichiro-sama!
Next episode of Tenjou
Tenge, Enforcement.
I can't hold it anymore!