- ♪Your party time
(Party time)! ♪
- ♪Ah yeah! (Yeah!)
- ♪Time to party
time! (Party time!) ♪
(screaming)
(grunts)
- Just like you promised.
- There aren't too many guys who
could have done this to him.
- Listen, Maya.
You're way too upset.
You don't have to
worry about this stuff.
You're just gonna
have to trust me.
- Mits... Mitsuomi?
Go home.
Go! I don't want you
in my life anymore!
(dramatic music)
(cicadas chirping)
(water splashing)
- Hm.
Hopefully this'll cool
things down a bit.
- [Shin] Maya.
- Huh?
- Let's go for a ride.
- Thanks for coming.
Sorry to make you come
all the way out here
during summer break.
- Don't worry, it's fine.
(motorcycle engine roaring)
- Just where do you think
you're taking us to?
(tires screech)
- I've been thinking
about this a lot.
And I finally understand
how she affects Shin.
And I also see what
you were talking about.
- [Woman] Those two have
a strange relationship.
They're more like lovers
than brother and sister.
(Scoffs)
- I'm really stupid, aren't I?
It took me forever to
figure this thing out!
- It's not your fault.
You're a guy, after all.
(giggles)
- So, we're at the
beach. Now what?
- This is it.
- Huh?
- [Boy] Wow!
Man, that's totally cool!
(little girl giggles)
- [Shin] I just
wanted to sit here
and watch the waves with you.
(birds calling)
- My heart's not gonna last.
All I'm gonna have is
two or three years left.
The future I had
as a martial artist
was squashed that day.
Shin's one blow
destroyed everything.
But that wasn't enough for him.
Now he's trying to
take away from me
the one person I love
most in this world.
And I'm not gonna
let that happen.
Miss Kuzunoha.
Please don't abandon me on this.
All three of us will need you.
I know this will
be hard for you,
but I'm afraid
it's the cross that
you will have to carry.
- Mitsuomi.
(somber music)
- [Maya] Ugh! I
hate sitting around
and doing nothing!
(splashes)
(Maya laughs)
- [Narrator] The
end of that summer
drew closer and closer.
- Must you do this?
- Yes.
The only reason I
made the Juken Club
was so that I could
have this fight.
- Very well.
- Finally, this day has come.
His Benevolence loves
each and every person.
His sense of honor
reminds him to be thankful
but to never weaken.
He is incomparable in his wisdom
and can control his
supernatural powers
without any sort
of external help.
A human so supreme
that he is able
to command the entire planet.
He is the one true
martial artist.
(ominous music)
Finally. Our vision is
about to be realized.
Karma.
- [Student] Do you hear
about the Juken Club?
- [Student] You mean
the fight for the
Executive Council President?
What's Shin thinking?
He hasn't fought someone
in like, two years!
- That Takayanagi guy
is just a freshman!
Man, that's unbelievable!
- [Teenager] I
always thought that
the captain of the winning club
got to be president.
So what's the point?
Why are they fighting?
- Ugh.
Hm.
I thought they said to meet
them by the bicycle rack.
- [Student] M'lady!
- Huh?
- Hey, over here! Over here!
- [Maya] What is this all about?
- [Student] Well, I'm
not really sure myself.
Shin suddenly decided he wanted
to have a group photo.
- [Maya] A group photo?
- Hey. There you are!
- [Student] What's
up? Sorry we're late.
- This seems like
a waste of time.
- Aw c'mon, it's a good idea.
We're the original
members of the Juken Club
and we don't even have
one photo of us together.
Look!
Shin's so psyched
about doing this
he even went and put on
his fancy street clothes.
- Shut up.
Like I wanna be in
a picture wearing
our stupid school uniform.
- [Bunshichi] He's so stylish.
- Alright, here goes!
Are you guys ready?
Heh.
Time for the pearly
whites! Say cheese!
- Cheese!
(farts)
(groans)
(coughs)
- [Student] That was disgusting!
Bunshichi, what the hell
have you been eating?
- [Maya] You've taken this
old man act a little too far!
- I had to do something.
Every one of you
had this bitter look
in your eye right when
he was getting ready
to take the photo!
Let's just smile.
We make a good team.
Best club this
school's ever seen.
(upbeat music)
- [Shin] Like I said.
You're one foul bastard!
- [Mistuomi] In
more ways than one!
- [Maya] You old geezer!
- You guys asking for more?
Just believe me, there's
a whole lot extra
where that came from!
Get your little asses back here!
(upbeat music)
- All right, let's try
this one more time!
Get ready, guys!
- It's been exactly
two months now.
And I think... well,
actually, I know
that this is the
first and last photo
we'll ever take together.
So we all better
flash our best smiles.
(camera snaps)
(punching)
(kicking)
(groan)
(tense rock music)
(gasp)
(grunt)
(heavy thud)
(panting)
(exclaims)
(dull thud)
(panting)
(cries out)
- This is freakin' crazy!
Mitsuomi's showing
no emotion at all!
- You can't even call
this a real fight!
It's way too brutal for that.
- Big brother!
- [Crowd] This is bad.
Someone needs to stop em!
He's gonna die!
- Break it up!
Enough, Mitsuomi!
Out of my way, bitch!
- This is a sanctioned
match to select
the Executive Council President!
As the official for this fight,
I'm going to follow the rules!
This will end when one of them
loses their will to fight!
Or ability to fight!
- [Bunshichi] Screw the rules!
Can't you see what's happening?
- It doesn't matter! I
can't stop this fight!
(flute music)
(shamisen music)
(slashing)
(exclaims)
- Stop it.
Please stop!
Please Mitsuomi, stop it!
(slaps)
(gasps)
- You stupid little girl!
You of all people should
see what's going on here!
Why do you think he's never once
used his Dragon's Eye throughout
this entire fight?
Everything's at stake
for him right now.
He's not just fighting Mitsuomi!
He's battling that
wretched power of his
and the destiny that
goes along with it!
He's struggling against
his own weakness,
a vulnerability that
the Dragon's Eye
loves to exploit!
- [Crowd] How is
he still standing?
That's amazing!
Seriously!
Go for it, Shi! Get him!
- What should we do?
- He's nearly done.
The next blow will
finish him off.
(panting)
- Yes.
I can see it.
Beyond his fist
lies eternal peace.
This next single blow
will end everything.
Maya.
Am I still alive?
I wonder,
will I live on forever
within your heart?
(groans)
(crunching)
Death.
It's my destiny that
the Dragon's Eye
has shown me over
and over again.
And guess what?
(gasps)
I ain't going to hell by myself!
Looks like I found
a travel buddy!
I won't die alone!
- How is he...
- Son of a bitch!
He was angling for
that counterattack!
If Mitsuomi's head hits the
floor in that position...
Shin! Shin, don't!
- Maya. Forgive
me for doing this.
But I'm taking him,
as well as your tears,
down with me.
- Nooo!
(humming)
- [Pupil] What's going on?
What the hell is that sound?
- [Pupil] It's coming from
Master Dogen's office!
- [Pupil] Master, what is this?
- Don't worry. It's
this miserable blade.
It's crying.
After all these years my dream
is about to be realized.
(gasps)
- You were ready to put your
life on the line for this
and that's all you've got?
You're pathetic.
- (gasps)
- I'm disappointed, Shin.
- (exclaims)
(heavy thud)
(groans)
- [Mitsuomi] You're weak.
You're the top student
at this academy.
I thought for sure you'd
be stronger than this.
But actually,
I'm the one who's
gotten stronger.
I'm the one with more power now!
All of this time I've been
standing in your shadow!
But now I'm way ahead of you!
(laughs)
Guess what, Shin?
I finally get why
you were so thirsty
for all this power!
Ha.
What do you say we keep going?
It's just starting to get fun!
- I'm afraid
that I have to go
through with this
in order to disappear.
(ghostly voices whispering)
(screams)
- Stop, Mitsuomi!
This fight's over!
We know who won!
Please, stop!
Please!
- [Kuzunoha] It's okay, Shin.
Don't worry, this fight is over.
- I can't take it
anymore.
- You did the best
that you could.
Okay?
It's all over now.
You're gonna be alright, Shin.
Did you hear me?
You're gonna be alright!
- It's too easy.
This was all way too easy.
(explosion)
(air whooshing)
- I'm not ready to die.
- (gasps) Shin!
(air whooshing)
(wood shatters)
(gasps)
- Impossible!
That's the Takayanagi
Clan's best-kept move!
Ryu kei kiko! Punch and go!
(glass shatters)
(yelling)
(heavy thud)
(punching)
(roaring)
(somber piano music)
(screams)
(sobbing)
- Sorry, Shin.
I did it again.
I got in your way.
Didn't I?
I never learned, up
until the very end.
All I ever did was
get in your way.
Don't cry, Shin.
From the moment I
fell in love with you,
I knew, eventually,
this day would come.
I could see it coming,
even without the Dragon's Eye.
A girl just knows
this kind of thing.
It seems both of us
were destined to lose.
In the end, we couldn't
defeat our weaknesses.
Or our fate.
I've heard you say
that no one is born
completely naked.
It's true.
But that's why,
when a person dies,
they have a chance to
throw everything away.
It's God's gift.
He's giving them
a whole new life,
a chance to start again.
But even after you're gone,
a piece of you will
always stay here,
locked safe within
someone's heart.
And I guess that's the proof
that we actually lived
at all, isn't it?
Maya.
Please look after
Mitsuomi for me.
Don't make him walk the
same path that Shin did.
I'm sorry, Mitsuomi.
I'm afraid I won't be
able to keep that promise
that I made to you.
- [Maya] Big brother...
- [Shin] Even then,
at the very end,
I couldn't change the
way that I felt for her.
(melancholy violin music)
- Goodbye, Shin.
Even in this final moment,
your heart was
never mine to have.
Yet your soul
and your tears
will stay with me forever.