(static crackles)
(upbeat hip-hop music)
(man sings in foreign language)
(yells)
(groans)
- Let me inform you.
I too am very strong.
Seniors at Todo Academy,
you're now seeing the full
master of Natsume Goushin style,
Maya Nastume!
(yells)
(groans)
(dramatic music)
(yelps)
- I would like for,
for you to marry me.
Funny you should ask,
I just stopped by
to bring this lunch I made
for you, Souichiro-sama.
- (yelps) I don't!
- Yet this school is full
of all kinds of monsters
that are much more
dangerous than she is.
(grunts)
(thuds)
(electricity crackles)
- Hakka Soudou Sho!
(gasps)
(groans)
(grunts)
- Aren't you impressive?
I didn't think people like you
who use fancy and ridiculous
moves existed in this world.
Now don't you get cocky
thinking flashy tricks like that
are gonna take me down.
That ain't gonna work
on Souichiro Nagi!
- Hey, boy, that was quite
a legitimate striking move,
don't treat it so lightly.
It's an attack that
requires the use of chi,
which Takayanagi acquired
only through intense training.
Chi is produced within oneself
and therefore can only be used
within the same body
that created it.
- That's enough of this crap.
I got plenty of will
running through my body too,
it's called the will to fight!
- Hm, that can also be good.
However, be careful
how you use it, boy.
Make no mistake,
Takayanagi is several
times stronger than you.
- I'm gonna give this
first-year a handicap.
If my challenger can land
just one single blow,
I'll be glad to call it his win.
(electricity crackles)
(tense music)
- I'll kill you in
one blow! (yells)
(grunts)
(thuds and grunts)
- Souichiro-sama.
- [Bob] Look at this guy.
Souichiro can't even
hold a candle to him
in a one-on-one match.
(grunts and thuds)
(groans)
- If it makes you
feel any better,
this is the first time
I've fought someone
as tough as you are.
- (groans) You
ain't seen nothing.
Why don't you stop pulling
these cheap-ass attacks, senpai?
- [Takayanagi] I went easy on
him because he's an amateur,
and look at the gratitude.
As you wish, I'll end it
all with this next blow.
(spits)
(grunts)
What!?
- [Souichiro] (chuckles) I see.
(yells)
(all gasp)
- That was really foolish.
- What the?
(loud blow)
(grunts)
(gasps)
- [Takayanagi] Because
Aya is so head-over-heels
in love with him, I assumed
he would last longer.
- He is tough!
- So that's all
the fight he's got.
(whimpers)
- Get up!
(gasps)
Get up right now!
You are engaged to
me, Aya Nastume!
It's a disgrace to
see you tossed around
by a martial artist
of that caliber!
- Uh, a martial artist
of that caliber?
- Yeah, well, since when
am I engaged to you?
Listen, I have
never lost a fight
against anybody
in my entire life,
so you just shut up and
keep watching, got it!?
- Yes.
(tense music)
- I still think she's crazy,
but if she hadn't yelled at
me I might still be out cold.
All that mind-reading
I was doing
was just about to put
me on pace with him.
- [Takayanagi] A martial
artist of that caliber.
- [Souichiro] Huh?
- Look at Takayanagi-senpai,
his behavior has changed.
- [Both] Huh?
- Sometimes you'll find
this kind of person.
- This very moment, for
the first time ever,
I honestly feel like
beating you down to a pulp.
- That's what I've been hoping
for from the very beginning.
(dramatic music)
- Shin'irikugo.
- [Souichiro] I'm
no martial artist.
- Batei!
- [Souichiro] I'm
a street fighter!
- Hoken!
- Meet my secret barrier!
(bell tolls)
- (whimpers) This, this is...
- Aya's...
- Delicious homemade lunch!
- [Bob] When the hell did he?
What a dirty move.
- Anything's fair
game in a fight!
(dramatic music)
(grunts)
That did it.
(all gasp)
- (gasps) Oh, no!
(growls)
(grunts)
(fleshy thuds and grunts)
Stop, Takayanagi!
(yelps)
- Hey, stop that!
(wood cracks)
Souichiro-sama!
(grunts)
(groans)
(thuds)
(groans and retches)
(pants)
(screeching)
(yells)
(rain pattering)
Souichiro-sama.
(Souichiro cackles)
Souichiro-sama?
- [Souichiro] What, think
I'd be crying or something?
Well, too bad, I'm so happy
I can barely contain myself.
- You're happy?
- Up till now, the only
guys I've faced were wimps,
and I was tired of it.
Now I've finally met someone
who really is strong.
Can you imagine how
good that feels?
The best part is that this
school is full of other guys
who are even
stronger than he is.
So yeah, I'm happy.
- [Aya] Souichiro-sama,
will you please
promise me one thing?
- [Souichiro] Huh?
- Don't ever lose
again, not ever.
- You idiot!
(gasps)
Who do you think
you're talking to!?
That goes without saying.
That's because I'm
Souichiro Nagi.
- Souichiro-sama!
- [Maya] Let him go.
(gasps)
- [Aya] Sis.
- Think about how he feels.
He acts fine, but he'll
remember those scars he got.
Or not.
- [Aya] Hm.
(footsteps)
(loud crash)
(tense music)
(Takayanagi pants)
- I lost.
(somber strings music)
Not only that, I lost big.
(boys panting)
- Take that!
(all laugh)
- [Boy] He's got cooties!
- [Boy] He deserves them!
- Yeah!
(laughing)
(boy grunts)
(pants)
(paper rips)
(paper crumples)
(door opens and closes)
(slurping)
- I don't want to lose.
I can't afford to lose.
(rain pattering)
- [Takayanagi] He's
made me quite serious.
Souichiro Nagi, where
did you come from?
(calming flute music)
(calming strings music)
(birds chirp)
(eerie music)
(grunts)
(rumbling)
(crash)
- You're awfully rough today.
You do realize the stones in
our garden don't come free,
so will you please stop taking
your frustration out on them?
- Souichiro-sama never
showed up at school today.
If he's badly hurt,
it's Takayanagi-senpai's
fault, you know?
Takayanagi can be so hopeless.
- That boy of yours is the
type who thinks it's okay
to use your homemade
lunch as a fighting tool!
I don't know why you
won't leave him alone!
- I don't care!
I don't care if he's a
cheating, underhanded weakling.
No matter what he does, I'm
in love with Souichiro-sama.
- (sighs) Fine, but
he and his friends
are about to run into
a lot of trouble.
- What do you mean?
- I heard the Executive Council
seniors are on the move.
Right now is the perfect
time in the school year
for them to start
handing out a punishment
to the two freshmen that have
stirred up all this violence.
I'm rather excited to see who
the new executioner will be.
Now then.
- Their punishment?
Executioner?
(boys grunting)
(tense music)
- [Both] Huh?
- [Wrestler] Who
the hell are you?
- [Tsutomu] You guys are still
doing the same cheap tricks.
- What'd you say?
- What was that?
- Hey, you bastard, that
ring there is sacred!
- [Tsutomu] Huh, what'd you say?
What do you boys say I teach you
what real martial
arts are all about?
- [All] What?
- Quite amusing.
Let me assure you that
our wrestling moves
are just as good as the pros.
Don't think you're
getting outta here
with just a couple
of broken bones.
(grunts)
(glass shatters)
(dramatic music)
- So who wants to go next?
- [Sagara] Enough!
- [Boy] Sagara!
- This guy utilizes
the chi of fire.
None of you are going to
be any match against him.
- Huh?
Are you saying that
you can win against me?
- That's a foolish question.
I don't enjoy any battle
that has no meaning.
However, if you continue
to insist upon it,
I will quite gladly
return to you
the wounds that my club
members have suffered.
- Hmph, fine, then
I'll let it be.
I didn't come here today
to get in a fight with you.
The Executive Council
has sent out a summons
to me and to you.
- The Executive Council?
- I see.
So Souichiro-sama didn't
come to school today either?
- Yeah, but knowing him, you
got nothing to worry about.
I'm sure he'll be back to
his usual self in no time.
- Yes, but he...
- What's wrong?
Is there something
else bothering you?
- Mr. Makihara, do you know
about the Executive Council?
- Executive Council?
What the hell is that?
- Well, I'm not entirely
sure about it myself, but I,
I think it might be
where this school
is hiding some kind of secret,
like a really big secret.
(dramatic music)
- Souichiro Nagi and Bob
Makihara, both of 'em freshmen.
So you want me and Sagara
to take care of 'em for you?
- [Emi] Yes, that's
what it boils down to.
- But I still don't get it.
Why do they need the combined
power of the two of us
to carry out the task of taking
down a couple of freshmen?
- I came up with that
exact same question,
but it was the President and
not me who made this decision.
- The President?
- Yes, he seems very
interested in this matter,
especially when it comes
to that Souichiro Nagi.
(cackles)
- I've heard a thing or two
regarding that feisty
little freshman.
From what I understand,
Takayanagi beat him up
pretty badly one day.
I hate to break it to you,
but this one is all mine.
You don't have a problem with
that, do you, Miss Isuzu?
- Well, I'm not so sure.
Now this may go without saying,
but you have absolutely
no room for error.
(grunts)
- [Sagara] Hm?
- I'm just taking a little
advance payment on my reward.
(both grunt)
(cackles madly)
- That man is still
rude and repulsive.
(grunts)
- Wicked bitch.
(squishing)
(grunts)
(metallic thud)
She definitely ain't easy.
(dogs barking and howling)
(lights buzzing)
- [Bob] Fighting's all
about experience and guts.
In the end, the only
thing that really matters
is whether or not you're willing
to give up your life to win.
That's what Souichiro
and I lived by.
No matter who the enemy was,
we were never gonna lose,
at least that's what we thought.
- You're not gonna
fight him, Bob?
- Huh?
- [Chiaki] That Takayanagi guy.
- Someday I will.
- But how come?
You were really looking
forward to this!
You said there were
strong guys there.
- I took things too lightly.
You know, I had no idea that
guy could be such a monster.
(growls)
(thudding)
To be honest,
I don't think I stand a
chance against him right now.
(loud crash)
Right then, I realized
for the very first time
that there are guys out there
that are so ridiculously
strong that spirit and guts
just aren't gonna be enough
against an opponent like that.
- Huh, I don't believe
it, that's so strange.
So Na-chan lost a fight, huh?
- And in a big freakin' way.
I wish there was some way
that you coulda seen it.
- [Chiaki] So now
what's Na-chan doing?
- [Bob] Dunno.
As far as I know,
this is the first time
he's ever lost a fight.
Probably singing the
blues somewhere about now.
- No more of this stuff.
(lights buzz)
I have a much
bigger problem now,
and it's that the
beautiful home-cooked meal
that I so lovingly made for you
is now just sitting there
all alone and getting cold.
Now eat up.
- [Bob] Mm, sorry.
(grunts)
(loud crash)
(dog barks)
- [Chiaki] Hm?
- [Bob] You could
at least knock.
- [Chiaki] Hey there, loser.
- I'm leaving.
(clattering)
- Wait,
you didn't come here just to
break our door down, did you?
- Huh?
There! (sighs)
(blows)
(slurps)
- Hey, Bob.
- Don't even say it,
you couldn't help it.
You got a little desperate
and you pulled a dirty trick,
and you still got your
ass kicked in the end.
If I were you, I'd
blow my brains out.
- Right, it's just that I...
(sighs)
- All right, I'm gonna head
off to the laundromat now.
- Sure.
- And Na-chan, make sure
that you drink all that.
(door clatters)
- Okay, tell me, Bob,
do I come across as weak to you?
- Well, I'm afraid at
this point, my friend,
it's pretty clear that you're
weaker than that midget chick,
Takayanagi, and Aya.
- Yeah, I guess.
That is pretty clear.
(tense music)
(fire crackles)
(chuckles)
- Huh?
Hey, Nagi, does it smell
like something's burning?
- I dunno, maybe
somebody went out there
and set your motorcycle on fire.
- Not funny,
that's not even something I
want to hear you joke about,
you got it?
(fire crackles)
(footsteps thud)
(woman sings in
foreign language)
(dramatic music)
- [Souichiro] All
right, all right,
enough with this tedious crap!
I'll take you on right now!
Next episode of Tenjho
Tenge, Executioner.
This is where the
real story begins.