(static crackles)
(intense music)
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Let's go
♪ In the night,
yeah, feel so good ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Bomb a head
- Weakling.
You are a disgrace to
the the Takayanagi name.
- Big brother.
(Masataka grunts)
(Bob yells)
(woman giggles)
(intense music)
(Souichiro grunts)
- So you must be Souichiro Nagi.
- You're the main dude, huh?
I'm amazed you'd be seen in
public with that lame ass getup.
Man, this guy
looks really tough.
- I'm always seeking
a new challenger.
I judge by quality,
not quantity.
Fighting one exceptional person
outweighs 10,000
ordinary people.
- Huh?
- But you are not exceptional,
Souichiro Nagi.
I don't care how strong
your power may be.
No one is going to bow
down to you, not ever.
- Boys, stop it!
(intense music)
(Souichiro grunts)
- Run away, boy!
- [Souichiro]
This, this is mine.
(speaks in foreign language)
(intense music)
(Souichiro gags)
(Souichiro groans)
- Souichiro-sama.
- That attack there is one
of the best kept secrets
within the Takayanagi family.
I'm afraid that
quasi-tanshinko you tried
is but a fading
memory of the one
who stole that technique
from my people.
You'll learn how that
grieves me someday.
Just like their elder
brother did, Shin Natsume.
In case you're not aware,
he's the man responsible
for stealing the
power of my fists.
- What the hell is
this guy babbling ab...
- How dare you?
- Must you continue this, Maya?
People need just one king,
same with the martial arts.
Like so many other
methods that exist today,
the Natsume family is
nothing but a branch,
clinging to the trunk of the
historical Takayanagi tree.
It seems as if once
again, the martial arts
are converging
around our family.
Will you finally stop with
this futile persistence?
I'm surprised you can
move with that injury.
You've gotten stronger.
- Mitsuomi, I just...
- You know that
it's not too late.
Come back under my wing,
like we used to be.
(wind whistles)
(gentle music)
- I'm afraid that time only
moves forward, Mitsuomi.
I'll never be able
to forgive you
for all the things you've
done to so many people,
and for what you
did to my brother.
But the worst thing you did,
the thing I will
never forgive you for,
is taking away the only
place that I ever felt safe.
(electricity crackles)
- Please forgive me.
You offered me advice as the
executive council's adviser,
but I took control of the
squads and ignored it,
and now everyone's hurt.
Sagara and Tagami as well.
- You should never have made
the decisions that you made.
Dividing up your squads
because your opponent has
is the epitome of foolishness.
Each of them should
have been attacked
with overwhelming force,
it's quite simple.
- Yes sir.
- Tagami, alive or dead?
Yep, all's well that ends well.
Surprisingly enough,
Mitsuomi is on the move,
Natsume has suffered
a serious injury,
and the two freshmen ain't
got a chance against Mitsuomi.
I'll give 'em two
more minutes, if that.
It's a simple ending, really.
Two long years of fighting,
which must have seemed like
an eternity to Natsume,
all wrapped up within
two short minutes.
You know, I still
don't get it though.
If this could end inside
of just two minutes,
why'd Mitsuomi wait 'til
now to do something?
Well, maybe he didn't intend
on destroying the Juken
Club in the beginning.
That was something that
only developed later.
The question still
remains, though.
After leaving it
all be for so long,
why do it now?
What suddenly made him
decide to settle the score?
- It's the variables.
They're quite real,
two variables.
You can't predict 'em.
I'm sure the president
had figured this out.
- [Sagara] Even a king is
going to have challengers.
- Sagara.
- Tawara.
Take this mask, and
get rid of it for me.
It's not something that I
will be needing any longer.
Two years ago, back
when we were freshmen,
it was the exact same thing.
A king will always be
defeated by the one
who will be the next king.
- By now the soriusho I
delivered to you earlier
should have moved
through your gallbladder
and into the pit
of your stomach.
You shouldn't be able
to move a muscle now,
let alone even think about
attacking me one more time.
Tell me, Maya.
Is this it?
Is this why you're
attracted to him?
I understand why.
It's incredibly apparent.
(intense music)
Chi is usually created
within the body itself,
and as a consequence it will
only work within that body.
That's why there's a limit to
the amount of chi one can use,
so if you continue to use it
you will eventually run out.
Even I face this issue.
However, there are a few
exceptions to this rule.
There are those with enough chi
to heal themselves from my
attacks almost instantly.
It's a limitless chi
that warps the atmosphere
around the user.
Where are you getting all
this chi from, freshman?
(eerie music)
Tell me, did you
honestly think this boy
would be able to
defeat me, Maya?
Did you really believe he
could overtake the mountain
that your older brother
could never conquer?
What were you thinking?
Look at him.
Does that boy look
like a dragon to you?
(somber music)
- It's you, brother.
- I remember when I
first saw this boy's name
on the freshman roster.
I thought exactly
the same thing.
(somber music)
Nagi.
Souichiro Kengo Nagi.
I know whose name this is.
Kengo was the name given to
the heir of the Nagi family.
It was to indicate
that he's from the clan
that wards off evil.
The clan that becomes the
spirit to defeat the spirits.
I've seen him battle against
Masataka and Riyuzaki.
I cannot allow this boy to
continue to go unchecked.
- Ah!
(Mitsuomi groans)
(Souichiro grunts)
- He's actually taking hits!
Mitsuomi is, is a martial artist
with an unparalleled
ability to guard himself,
but he's really taking
some damage right now.
It's just like it was last time.
This is exactly what
happened two years ago.
Boy, you really are...
Boy, stop it!
- You truly are a
foolish woman, Maya.
What do you want?
You want to watch me
kill yet another one?
A martial artist with an
unlimited amount of chi.
Chi of this nature
is not created
within the confines
of the human body.
Some call it God, some a dragon,
others call it an
apparition or a demon.
There's all sorts
of names for it,
but they all mean one thing.
The chi that exists
outside the body
in the trees and the wind,
people call those that can
control such chi, spirits.
Spirits use their immense power
to perform feats of
constant recklessness.
Just like your
brother used to do.
You killed them both.
Your brother, and this boy too.
Senior at Todo Academy,
head of Gaokishi style,
president of the
executive council,
Mitsuomi Takayanagi attacks!
- [Maya Voiceover] Why am
I not trying to stop this?
If Mitsuomi really
is ready to fight,
that boy doesn't have a prayer,
even if he is a
descendant of that clan.
He's going to die.
The boy is going to die!
I've got to do something!
(Mitsuomi yells)
- Chill!
- Bunshichi!
- Goodness, things were
really heating up here.
I had to cool this scene down.
So tell me, who is
it now that's got you
all hot and bothered like this?
- You really don't know
when you're needed, do you?
If you had just taken
control of the squad
from the beginning...
- Now come on, I only
joined the executive council
because you said I didn't
have to do anything.
Where else can I see high
school students kill each other,
and bullshit about spirits?
You guys are all
completely whacked.
Now what are you doing
harassing such a
cute little freshman?
Huh, senpai?
- What happened?
- Relax, he just checked out.
Probably a result of
that suffocating aura
that follows you
wherever you go.
See, he's all nice and sweet
around a cool cat
like me, right?
Hey, what's your deal punk?
I just saved your ass!
You ungrateful, you're gonna
die for that you little prick!
What are you...
- Mitsuomi.
Just so that you're
clear on this,
I've no interest in
returning to how things were.
If it wasn't for my injuries,
I would've had no problem
fighting you today.
- Don't lie to me.
- [Bunshichi] Okay
stop that hurts!
If that leaves a mark,
I'm really gonna be
so pissed off at you!
Okay okay uncle, you
win, just let go!
Let go of me, damn it!
(gentle flute music)
- Nice work!
- Way to go!
- Are the police here?
- [Man] There's a few outside,
but nothing to be
concerned about.
We got the employees
here scared enough
to back us up on the story
that we had rented this place
out for a bowling tournament.
- Tell them we'll cover
the cost of repairs,
and throw in some cash
for the employees.
The Isuzu family
will foot the bill.
Kagurazaka.
- Mitsuomi is still
inside the building.
He told me to warm up his bike
like I was some sort
of common house boy.
The nerve of that man.
- [Emi] What happened
to your face?
It looks horrible.
- My face may look like
I lost, but I didn't.
I spent most of my time making
sure I kept Junior in check.
- Mr. Kagurazaka.
Now I wanna show you
what it'll feel like
when I go all the way.
(Masataka grunting)
- An obvious feint attack.
So predictable!
(intense music)
Come on, what do you
think you're doing?
You told me that I could
have my way with him!
You're spoiling this for me!
- This fight was
over, have some style.
You still have a ways to go.
You can become even stronger.
- He's such an ass,
that Mitsuomi acting
all high and mighty.
Look what he's done
to my perfect skin.
I won't forgive him for this.
What?
- [Emi] The president
was fighting
against both Bob and Masataka
and you thought it'd be
okay to just stroll outside?
- Oh relax, this is
Mitsuomi after all.
He bragged that he'd
have this whole thing
wrapped up in three minutes.
- Listen you little shit!
If anything happens to our
president, I will kill you!
- It's just, hold on!
What's with her?
- Damn it!
What was I thinking?
I should never have let
him take care of Mitsuomi.
He can't even act as
a security shield!
Ah?
If he was just fighting
a one-on-one battle,
I wouldn't care who Mitsuomi
was going up against.
But, this isn't just
a one-on-one battle.
It's Isuzu, are you all right?
- How's the withdrawal going?
- We're almost done.
Just making sure no
one else is here.
- I owe one to Bunshichi.
If I'd kept going with that boy,
I might have lost.
This is pathetic.
I chastise Masataka for
wearing out after a measly 80,
and I spend just a few minutes
fighting a couple of freshmen
and my body's completely spent.
When he saw Masataka
lying there,
defeated by me,
the anger in that boy's
eyes was so very real.
All on his own,
Masataka has managed
to earn the trust of
some powerful comrades.
It's becoming quite clear
that the Takayanagi
family is not his place.
My father never
taught me that allies
could be so valuable.
- But you have allies,
you have all of us.
The executive council.
We'd die for you
if you asked us to.
I know the core
members of the council,
like myself and Tagami,
all feel that way.
You are the bigger power
that bonds us together.
You must stay alive.
You have to do that for us,
and for yourself.
Even if it's just another day.
I'll risk it all, everything
just so I can protect you.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to come in.
- [Mitsuomi] No, I
should get out of here.
Look the other way when I leave.
- Of course.
(emotional music)
One last thing, sir.
Maya Natsume was
a tough opponent.
If by chance I had met
her before I met you,
I could easily have
become her friend.
- [Mitsuomi] I see.
(emotional music)
And I wanted to meet you,
before I met Maya too.
- Okay kiddo, rise and shine.
- Look at you.
I expected more than this.
I'm disappointed, Takayanagi.
- Wha, huh?
- [Maya] How is he?
He's not up yet?
Let me try.
- Don't you touch him!
Why do they have
to fight like this?
Just look at the two of them,
Bob and Na-Chan are
a complete mess!
I'm beginning to wonder if
all this is just about you!
Well is it?
What exactly is
all of this about?
I wanna know what's going on!
Why do they keep fighting us?
I mean, it turns out
that that president guy
is nothing more than
your ex-boyfriend!
What is this, some
kind of lover's spat?
I agree that both
Na-Chan and Bob here
have spun off into the deep end
since they started this school,
but if the two of them
hadn't hooked up with you,
things would have never
gotten this out of control!
And as for me!
(girl sobbing)
- All right.
Go on and spill it, all of it.
Everything that's happened
between you and Mitsuomi.
They need to know
what really went down.
That it's not just some
high school romance
gone horribly awry.
- Two years ago, Mitsuomi fought
and killed my older brother.
Calling it a fight
is an understatement
for what actually happened.
What it really was
was a death match.
My brother lost the fight,
and died as a result.
- What?
- No one really won that fight.
My brother took Mitsuomi's
life from him as well.
- What?
- He's still alive,
but just, just barely.
And I'm beginning to
wonder if at this point,
he'll even have enough
time to accomplish
what he set out to do.
This means I'm beginning
to run out of time as well.
I have to do something
while I still can.
I've got to settle the
score before he dies.
You're awake.
- Stop beating around the
bush already, will ya?
Tell us everything
that happened.
- Don't you think we
have a right to know
exactly what we're up against?
- All right.
But, first we have to get
ourselves out of this building.
We can continue this at home.
- You got it.
(dramatic music)
- [Masataka Voiceover]
It all happened
in less than 30 minutes,
but together the two sides
managed to put over 100
people on the injured list.
Some just had cuts and scrapes,
others seriously wounded.
I've never understood
what my brother
was hoping to
achieve by becoming
president of the
executive council.
But today I realized, that
whatever his objective may be,
he wants nothing more
than to see it fulfilled
before he dies.
The executive council
has just confirmed
that it sees the Juken
Club as a threat.
I imagine the members
of the council
will have a much closer
bond with each other now.
Ironically, by making
the Juken Club stronger,
we've made the council
stronger as well.
We're the ones who lost
the battle that day.
The five of us behaved like
individuals, not club members.
We were more divided
than all 200 members
of the executive council.
(dramatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
- [Narrator] What
the hell happened
between that Mitsuomi
guy and the midget chick?
Uh, another guy?
Next episode of
Tenjho Tenge, Memory.
What was it, some
kind of love triangle?