(soft music playing)
- [Offscreen Boy
Voice]- This is the day,
that it all started.
(man screaming)
It was the first day of my
second year at Toudou Academy,
and it started out
like any other day.
(man screaming)
There were so many
cherry blossoms in bloom.
The petals blanketed
the main field like snow
and the whole campus
was covered in color.
(motor revving)
(suspenseful music playing)
(man panting)
- [Maya] Takayanagi!
(footsteps rushing)
- Hmph.
- I'm so sorry to keep
you waiting Captain!
- Why are you late?
- My class had a, a really
long homeroom session.
So, tell me, is she here yet?
The new member that
we've been waiting for?
Our Captain's little sister.
- Hm!
- I'm really looking
forward to this.
Tell me what she's like.
Is she just as strong
as you are Captain?
- Hm, well, from my viewpoint
she's still got
a long way to go.
(bike braking)
- [Bob] So this
is Toudou Academy,
our new playground.
- [Souichiro] We take
over this school,
it'll make an even hundred.
Pretty impressive track record.
- Yeah, but this school
isn't like the other ones.
- That's exactly why
this is gonna be fun.
The tougher my rival,
the sweeter my victory.
All we gotta do is destroy
whoever we come up against.
Then you and me will have
complete control of the school.
- Okay then.
Well is your little
sister really pretty
like you are Captain?
- [Maya] I don't know, I guess
I still see her as a child.
- [Takayanagi] Ah, come on!
- Scratch those
two off the list.
I know I said destroy them all,
but I ain't gonna start fighting
little kids and pansies.
- Yeah, I second that.
(drum booming)
- I don't know what you've
imagined her to be like,
but don't expect too much.
She's little more than a child,
who up till recently was
still wetting her bed.
- No way!
(door sliding)
(wind whooshing)
(man gasps)
(piano music playing)
(sword swooshing)
I felt an electric charge
rush through my entire body.
There were chills
running down my spine
and every nerve I
had stood on end.
My heart felt like
someone was trying
to crush it with
their bare hands.
Yet, it was amazing.
And then, time just
seemed to stop.
No matter how I tried,
I couldn't take my eyes off her.
- So I guess we'll go
in order like usual.
- Sounds good.
The first people
that we annihilate
will be the seniors
from Class A, hmph.
- Uh, hey sis, were
you here all along?
- Hm, you need to meet somebody.
This is Masataka
Takayanagi, sophomore,
but he's still a senior to you.
- Hi there, I'm Aya Natsume.
It's very nice to meet you.
(man laughing weakly)
- What's wrong?
Say something to her Takayanagi!
- Hi, the pleasure
is, is all mine.
- All right, since
this is the first day,
we'll skip practice for now
and save it for tomorrow.
I suggest we have a
little welcoming party
and go to a karaoke bar instead!
- What a good idea!
- That sounds great.
Just let me wash
the sweat off first.
- Hm
- The sweaaaat.
- Off guard!
- Hey Sempai!
There's, there's no
hitting bellow the belt!
(man screaming)
(man grunting)
- What the hell kind of
first termers are you guys?
- Do you at least have a reason
for being so destructive?
- I've got an excellent reason.
We decided to skip the
orientation ceremonies.
So we're having our own
little orientation instead.
Name, Souichiro Nagi.
- Bob Makihara.
- As of today, this school
is ruled by the Knuckle Bomb.
That's us.
If you got a problem
with it, step on up.
Makes no difference to
me if you're a first year
or a third year.
I'll slaughter you all.
(girl humming)
- [Maya] You seem
rather happy Takayanagi.
- Eh?
Right.
(laughing nervously)
Well, there's no
arguing that our club
is the weakest martial
arts club on campus.
So it only goes without saying
that the more strong people
we have in the Juken
club the better.
You know, to serve our purpose.
- "To serve our
purpose," you say.
Huh, well I suppose I can
accept that reason for now.
- No, hold on, I really
meant what I was saying!
- Oh, there she is.
Ms. Natsume!
Sorry to disturb you.
I don't want to
disrupt your club,
but could you come with us?
We need your help.
- It's something
that we can't handle.
- Huh?
(man screaming)
- It's those guys.
They're just randomly
picking fights.
- It's creating a huge mess.
(men grunting)
- You see what I mean?
- What are they thinking?
(air swooshing)
(student yells)
- [Takayanagi] Those
two did all of this?
That's pretty amazing!
- [Maya] Hm, a
rather feisty bunch.
(man grunting)
(man punching)
Excuse me boys, it's quite clear
that both of you
are very powerful.
Now please put your
fists down and stop this.
If you refuse then
you leave me no choice
but to stop you myself.
(man punching)
Let me inform you.
I too am very strong.
- Bob, there's a
weird little girl here
who talks like a grandpa
wanting to fight me,
what do you think that
I should do about this?
- [Bob] I don't know.
- Don't be fooled.
I'm 17 years old!
Okay then, if my appearance
really bothers you that much,
allow me to make it a
little easier for you.
(drum playing)
(crowd whooping)
(boy screaming)
All right, seniors
at Toudou Academy
you're now seeing the full
master of Natsume Goshin style,
Maya Natsume.
- Bob, if that weird
little girl suddenly turns
into the kind of stacked,
voluptuous chick,
you'd see working in
a sketchy night club,
what should I do?
- Don't know!
- Natsume style severe
cheek conditioning 23.
For a master of my caliber,
physical control at this level
is simply a piece of cake.
I'm afraid that I'm
very busy today.
Excuse me but I must
end this quickly.
(air whooshing)
(man screaming)
(window shattering)
- Oh no, I hit him
harder than I intended!
(man crashing)
This is bad!
- Don't you worry
about him at all.
He's a lot tougher
than he may look.
A fall from this height
isn't gonna kill him.
- That's not it!
What I'm concerned
about is that room.
That room is the shower room.
(water spraying)
- Damn it, that bitch!
She's so fast.
Huh, is this someones...?
(man screaming)
- That's the shower room
that Aya should be in!
- Captain!
- Takayanagi, finish up
off foreigner for me!
- Finish me off, huh?
(wind whooshing)
(man grunts)
How the hell did he do that?
- Please, stop this now.
(footsteps running)
- Between that Takayanagi guy
and that weird shape
changing chick,
it's gonna be a whole lot harder
to take over this
school than we expected.
(water spraying)
- I don't believe
this, we're too late.
(harmonica music playing)
(man screaming)
(chiming music sounds playing)
(man yelping)
- Well hello there.
My name, my name is Aya Natsume.
I would like for,
for you to marry me.
(man screaming)
(girl sighs)
(man stuttering)
- Huh?
- Would you please marry me?
- What, what the hell are you?
Tch!
(door banging)
Dumb girl!
- Aya, that look in your
eyes, is that for real?
(motor revving)
- [Bob] What happened?
I thought we were gonna kill
them all in one fell swoop?
- [Souichiro] Shut up!
There were way too many
interruptions today!
- Glad to see that
the Toudou Academy
lives up to its reputation.
It just means more fun for us.
- That's right!
(flute music playing)
(shamisen music playing)
- [Teacher] Hajime Tanaka?
- [Boy] Here.
- Tohru Takino?
- [Teacher] Souichiro Nagi?
- [Nagi] Yeah.
Well, I'm glad that
I don't have to sit
in the same class
with her all day.
She sure is one
whacked-out chick.
(boy groaning)
That crazy chick stole
my first kiss from me!
- [Aya] Hello, good morning.
- Huh?
So you're name is Souichiro
Nagi, is that right?
What a wonderful name.
- Hey, what the
hell is going on?
What are you doing here?
- Funny you should ask,
I just stopped by
to bring this lunch
I made for you Souichiro-Sama.
Here, it's all for
you, please enjoy!
- I, I don't
want it!
- [Teacher] Where do
you think you're going?
- Souichiro-Sama?
(boy gulping)
- You didn't have to run away
from her screaming you know.
But, then again, handling chicks
never has been something
that you're good at.
- Who cares, she's nothing
but trouble anyway.
Here I am trying to take
over the whole school
and she keeps popping up and
throwing me out of whack!
Stupid girl!
I got a bad feeling.
- Oh I get it, you
wanted to come here
so you could eat in peace.
- Ahh!
(shamisen music playing)
(upbeat music)
- Here, enjoy,
your friend is welcome
to join us if he'd like.
- What, what is up with you?
Just what the hell
are you thinking?
And why in the hell are
you wearing a kimono?
- A girl should be modest.
Here, Souichiro-Sama!
Say, "ahhh."
- I don't want it!
(boy screaming)
- Souichiro-Sama,
Souichiro-Sama!
- Ahh, I can't
believe this chick's
got me hiding in a
hospital bed, damn her!
- [Aya] Well no wonder you
don't have much of an appetite,
you aren't feeling well.
- No way!
- [Aya] I'll nurse
you back to health!
(girl giggles)
(boy screaming)
(window shattering)
(air whooshing)
Souichiro-Sama?
(girls grunting)
- I can't believe you're
thinking of something else
during a match!
That's not like you!
(girl screams)
- It's a hundred years too
soon for you to toss me around!
- That hurt!
- Okay Aya, are you
serious about this?
- You're so mean!
I'm well aware of the
fact that my sister
is more talented than I am!
- I'm not talking
about this match!
- Huh?
- Any girl born into
the Natsume family
must devote her life
to the first man
she has revealed herself to.
That outdated family rule was
set over a hundred years ago.
I think you're adhering to
it a little too strictly.
- But that's how our mother
and grand-mother chose their
two husbands, remember?
- Aya!
- It's all right!
Don't worry about me.
To tell you the
truth, its got nothing
to do with that old rule.
It's just that when I saw him,
I felt the small
twitch in my heart.
And this charge
raced through me!
I knew, that was it!
- That what was it?
- Well, it was, what's
the best way to put it?
I, I'd guess you'd say
that it was destiny!
That's all!
(girl chuckles)
- Huh!
- [Takayanagi] Yes,
destiny can be quite cruel.
- [Boy] Tanuki noodle
with egg please.
- [Lunch Lady] You got it.
- The cherry blooms had fallen,
and right about then,
the irises in the school
pond began to open.
If being dumped on the same day
that I fall in love is destiny,
then routine aspects
of everyday life
do nothing but
start to annoy me.
(footsteps rushing)
Is this also my destiny?
(man yelling)
(wind whooshing)
(boy sighs)
- [Aya] Souichiro-Sama!
- Huh?
(upbeat music plays)
- Souichiro-Sama!
Souichiro-Sama, listen up!
You're going to eat this lunch
that I so lovingly
made for you today!
Even if it's by force!
- Shut up!
Each and every single
day, lunch after lunch,
meal after stinking meal!
I told you, I'd rather die
before I eat your damn food!
- There you go again!
I don't believe you!
You act as if one little
bite is going to kill you!
- It will kill me!
- How's that?
- It just will!
- It will not!
- [Souichiro] Oh, shut up!
- I'm sorry Ma'am,
- I told you it will
and that means it will.
- I will clean up after this
- [Aya] Souichiro-sama!
- But can you just give
me another one for now?
- What a mess.
- Shut up, shut up!
- Please, Souichiro-sama,
wait you have to try this!
(air whooshing)
- Huh?
- Sorry about that senpai.
I'll pay for this next one.
(coins clinking)
- He was right behind me,
I didn't even know it.
No thanks, if you really are
looking to make it up to me,
would you please tell him
to try Aya's homemade
lunch at least once.
- He's just not too
good with girls.
He's being a bit shy.
See, he likes to think of
himself as a tough guy.
Just take him with
a grain of salt.
- Here you are!
(boy sighs)
- If there's something you
want to talk about hurry up.
I would like to be
able to eat my meal
while it is still hot.
- Question, I wanna
know how many people
this school's got that
are as tough as you are,
and I also wanna
know their names.
I'm sure that midget
girl is probably one,
but I don't think she
makes the top of the list.
I've got this strange feeling
that this school is full
of all kinds of monsters
that are much more
dangerous than she is.
(coins clinking)
Am I wrong?
- Well am I wrong in
assuming that you're aware
of the whole history
behind the Toudou Academy?
- Well, I know all
the basic stuff.
- The Toubou school is what
this academy evolved from.
It was created to
revive the martial arts
that had begun to fade away
with the collapse
of the Shogunate.
Toudou Academy follows
the same legacy
of that Toubou school.
So, what you've got
is a school built
to revive martial arts.
Of course there's gonna
be tough people here.
- Yeah but there's
still top dogs, right?
- Well, what would
you do if I told you?
- We'd go and rip them apart.
(boy panting)
What did you expect?
- Hey Nagi, so you finally
shook her off your tail.
- Seems like it.
- Listen, nobody at this
school is interested
in such trivial things as
trying to take it over.
There's absolutely
no reason for you two
to keep trying to pick a fight.
- Of course there is, dumb ass.
There is nothing more exciting,
than the chance to
fight a tough guy.
Don't you ever get excited?
I couldn't care less what
my opponent stands for,
but if he happens to be a tough
guy then I'm fighting him.
Don't you feel the same?
- At this point I realized
my assessment of these two
had been completely wrong.
In fact I couldn't have
been more off the mark.
- Come to think,
I have a score to settle
with you, remember?
- Correct me if I'm wrong,
but your issue isn't with me,
but with Maya.
- It makes no difference
to me, asshole.
Huh.
- Souichiro, you're about
to get your ass kicked
and I'm not gonna help you.
(man grunts)
(whirling sound)
(electricity crackling sound)
- This guy blocked my punch
with just a chopstick!
- Huh, it's this one again.
- Souichiro-Sama.
- I realized these two weren't
just trying to act tough,
and pretend to be
kings of the mountain.
(boy yelling in
foreign language)
(boy screaming)
- Bad idea, never go full
strength against someone
who's just an amateur, he
still has much to learn.
- Something definitely
separated these guys
from the average street-thug.
Ecstasy.
These two couldn't get enough
of the ecstasy one feels
when you're in the
heat of battle.
- Well, this has been
an interesting glimpse
into the caliber of man you've
chosen to fall in love with.
- Souichiro-Sama.
(booming sound)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(suspenseful music)
- [Souichiro] The word "lose"
is not in my dictionary,
but that guy, he's as
powerful as a monster!
Next episode of
Tenjho Tenge, Defeat.
What's up with the
title of this episode?
That can't be right!