(static hisses)
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
(Souichiro grunts)
- What do you want?
You wanna watch me
kill yet another one?
Ryukei Qigong Tashinkou
Shinden, Gao Soryu Enrensho!
(hands thud)
(dramatic music)
(arms thudding)
(Souichiro grunts)
- Don't you touch him!
Why do you have to
fight like this?
Just look at the two of them,
Bob and Na-chan are
a complete mess.
Well is it?
What exactly is
all of this about?
- Go on and spill it.
All of it,
everything that's happened
between you and Mitsuomi.
(dramatic music)
(crickets chirping)
- Aya fell sound asleep the
second her head hit the pillow.
She must've been
complete exhausted.
It's late, all of you
need to get some rest.
- Don't you think
there's something
a bit more pressing right now?
- Yeah, we wanna
know what happened.
- But it's late.
- My brother didn't use
to be like this at all.
But then one day
he just changed.
All I wanna know
is what caused it.
Please tell us what
happened, captain.
- Takayanagi.
(somber music)
I'll start from the beginning.
When I fist met Mitsuomi
I was in the ninth grade.
The only thing I ever
thought about back then
was how I could become stronger,
like a steel blade that
could slice through anything
in its path.
Stronger, that's all.
(melancholy music)
(wind whooshes)
Well now, you're the
one I've heard about
from the head clan of
the Gaou Kishi style.
(scoffs) I'm so disappointed.
I was really hoping you'd
bring a lot more to this fight,
but if this is the kind of
trash you hang around with,
you can't be all that tough.
Two people can't be crowned
the strongest in this city.
You're gonna have to face
me, Mitsuomi Takayanagi.
(Mitsuomi whooshes)
(Maya screams)
(bottles clatter)
(wind whooshes)
- You're weak.
(Maya moans)
You were saying something
a few minutes ago
about being the strongest
person in the city.
Well I'm not that guy.
I know someone a whole
lot stronger than me.
- [Maya] What are
you talking about?
- I'm talking about your
older brother, Maya Natsume.
- But how did you
know who I was?
(tires screech)
- [Bunshichi] Oh, man,
is it over already?
- Well we're late because
you had to go chasing
after that chick.
What's up?
Is that you on the ground, Maya?
Don't tell me you
lost another fight.
- But, how did you?
- Shin, what's up?
- So why are you here?
- Well I got this call
from Mitsuomi yesterday.
He wanted to know
what he should do
if he ended up
having to fight you.
So I told him to stop
stressing about it
and just kick your ass.
- Why did you?
- Team KATANA,
Mitsuomi might be able to
fill my shoes when I'm gone.
You should've seen that.
Aw, don't tell me that you
dragged the Chokutou Reiki
with you tonight.
- Chokutou Reiki?
- That cursed thing's
been handed down in the
Natsume family for generations.
(Maya whimpers)
- Next time I don't want
it to have to go like this.
I mean, I really
went all out on her.
And I gotta say, having to
hit a girl ain't all that fun,
ya know?
- [Mitsuomi] Well now,
when the boy speaks,
he speaks his mind.
Listen to you.
- You want me to
give you a lift?
- Come on, stop, Shin.
- Are you hurt bad?
(hand smacks)
- [Maya] I'm fine.
I can get home on my own.
(melancholy music)
- She was crying.
She had her face
all scrunched up.
- What?
Man, I knew going all
out like that on a chick
was a bad idea.
- Will you stop freaking out?
She's gonna be fine.
Soon as she goes and
has something to eat
she'll be back to normal.
- Shin, you have a
really messed up way
of letting your sibling know
that you care about her.
Maya probably came here tonight
because she knew that you
would show up, you know?
- Huh, what are
you talking about?
- Well if you don't get it,
you're just not gonna get it.
- What's up with you?
You're acting weird.
- [Mitsuomi] You know, I
gotta say, she's really cute.
- Huh?
- I can see how I could
totally fall for her.
(melancholy music)
- [Maya] The reunion
came soon afterwards.
And then, that spring.
(birds chirping)
- The 287 students
that are here today
promise to endure hardships,
as well as share in
each other's victories.
By using our rivals
to make us stronger
we vow to master our
studies in both academics
and the martial arts.
I present this oath to you on
behalf of the freshman class.
(students applaud)
- All right,
congratulations first
termers on making it in here.
I'm Shin Natsume, head
of the Executive Council.
But who I am isn't
what's important.
But listen up, 'cause I'm gonna
tell you what is important.
This academy will be
a paradise for you.
I have absolutely no doubt
that your next four years
at this school are gonna
be some of the most
exciting years of your life.
(birds chirping)
(light piano music)
- This place is pretty nice.
Our cherry trees aren't
anywhere near this big.
I wouldn't've attended
the ceremony either
if I didn't have to
make some speech.
- Don't talk to me as
if I'm your friend.
You're ruining a perfectly
good depressing moment.
My brother swears he can
hear the blooms laughing
and cheering when they
start to fall like this.
But what I see is the empty
shell of a demolished life.
Just so you know, I didn't
lose to you when we fought
each other last time.
I would've continued
on with the match
if my brother hadn't shown up.
The fight is not over.
So don't go out there
and let someone else
rip your head off.
The next time you and I fight
I'm gonna be a whole
lot stronger. (chuckles)
(light piano music)
(Keybo panting)
(footsteps pounding)
(cat meows)
(cat thuds)
(Keybo sighs)
- [Keybo] I think I lost him.
KATANA hunting, what
a friggin' joke.
(assassin whooshes)
(Keybo grunts)
(kicks thudding)
(dramatic music)
(cat hisses)
(assassin meowing)
(cat yowling)
- [Student] What
the heck is that?
- Isn't that?
(dramatic music)
- [Student] Whoever did that's
gotta to be one
scary individual.
- Ah, guess everyone's here.
(birds chirping)
KATANA's bodyguards are
present and accounted for.
(dramatic music)
- Bunshichi, do you always...
- [Bunshichi] This is my
personal napping spot.
- [Mitsuomi] Were
you here yesterday?
- You know, you should
really find a chick
who's a bit less scary.
- [Mitsuomi] He
heard everything.
- Now, someone took
out Keybo last night.
- You mean KATANA hunting?
- Apparently.
He's the third guy this month.
- [Ishimatsu] I know our
team's made a lot of enemies,
but someone hasn't picked such
an obvious fight against us
in a long time.
- Yup, I feel bad for
the guys we've lost,
but Shin wasn't so upset.
Sometimes people
just don't know.
What an amazing
weapon a katana is,
unless you show someone
just how deep it can cut.
Got it?
(bright music)
(upbeat music)
- Step aside.
(lips smacking)
(bubble pops)
(students thuds)
- Well now, you're Maya
Natsume, aren't you?
Be a sweetheart and hand
this to your brother for me.
And then tell him
one more thing,
this school ain't gonna
be no paradise anymore.
It's gonna be hell,
now that you got somebody
like me roaming your hallways.
- Tell him yourself, I'm
not a bulletin board.
- Don't act tough.
I used to hear your
name all over the place
when I was in middle school.
But I'm guessing by now
you've probably figured out
that they were all
just going easy on you
out of respect for
your big brother.
(dramatic music)
- [Maya] Go on, say that again.
I dare you.
- What?
Oh no, what did I do?
Did I upset you?
So sorry.
Maybe you should go find out
where your big brother is
so you can tell on me.
"That mean boy made
me cry, brother.
"Will you please go and
beat him up for me?"
Brother lover.
(leg whooshes)
(Maya yelps)
Just so you know, when
I'm fighting a girl,
I hit 'em just as hard as
when I'm fighting a guy.
Amano Style Mahjong Fist!
Tenho!
- He's fast.
- Ryuihso!
(hand whacks)
(Maya yelps)
Churenpoutou!
(fists whooshing)
(Maya whimpering)
- Dammit!
But, Shin.
- You're not good enough
to walk around here
with an attitude. (grunts)
(Maya screams)
You act like you're a tiger,
but you're just some
chick with cockroach hair.
- [Maya] He's really tough.
- If we help her out
now by stepping in,
her body may not take on
a great deal of damage,
but the scar it'll
leave in heart
will be there forever.
That's a fate much worse than
death for a martial artists.
Understand?
- [Mitsuomi] Yeah, but.
- Toughen it out, especially
if you think you really are
in love with Maya.
(dramatic music)
(fists whacking)
This is hard for me too.
(dramatic music)
(fists whacking)
(Maya yelps)
(dramatic music)
- I think it's time
you consider giving up.
Guys don't like a girl
who's too persistent.
(grunts)
(kick thuds)
(Maya screams)
(Maya thuds)
- [Mitsuomi] Asshole!
- Dammit!
Maya, this fight is lame.
Why don't you
start hitting back?
You're boring everybody
to tears here.
- But, Shin.
(Maya groaning)
- Well thanks for showing up.
I didn't think that you'd
arrive this quickly.
I was really taken by
your speech yesterday.
Man, you're so cool.
- Oh, but your attacks
are so much cooler.
- And if it isn't
little Mitsuomi
standing there next to you.
So then you're
still a little shit
clinging to some big fish's ass.
- Who the hell are you?
Come on, introduce
yourself, dammit!
- Right, name's Masayuki Sanada,
Red Mahjong Devil
of Fifth Middle.
And I didn't come
here to fight you.
I just want to fight
this guy right here.
- Let me ask you something.
I just wanna know, you the
guy after the KATANA members?
- And what'd you
do if I was, huh?
- I'd say try again in
your next life, jackass.
(fist thuds)
(Masayuki grunts)
(flesh squelching)
- (grunts) Bastard!
- Now listen here,
Mr. Red Mahjong Devil,
this fight is nowhere near over.
So if you're not gonna attack,
then I guess I will.
- Wait, hold on!
(both thudding)
(students cheering)
- All right, yeah!
- You go, girl!
- So was the fan
service a bit much?
- [Student] That was awesome.
- Stop picking stupid
fights like that.
It's getting embarrassing
having to watch them.
- Oh yeah?
Then how come every
time that I'm in a fight
you show up and
check it out, huh?
Go away.
- If you want me
to leave you alone,
finish the damn fight
before I get there.
- [Maya] Don't touch me!
- [Shin] Stop making a fuss.
- [Maya] I said go away!
- [Shin] Oh, whatever.
(Masayuki groaning)
(students chattering)
- This guy is gonna die.
Someone, call an ambulance!
Hurry up!
(students grumbling)
Did you hear me?
Hurry up, he might still
be able to make it.
- You don't need an ambulance.
(dramatic music)
Kuzunoha Needle, Kokken Seisou.
- Kuzunoha?
- Now if we just
stich up his abdomen
he'll recover without a problem.
You'll see.
I'm afraid you're not
going to be able to make it
in this school if you're
fretting over something
as small as this, Mitsuomi.
- Oh, okay.
You're Mana Kuzunoha.
You're Shin's
girlfriend, am I right?
(Mana chuckles)
(students shouting)
- I wouldn't let yourself
get too worked up over this.
Shin was going easy on him.
If I didn't show up he
still wouldn't have died.
Providing, of course, that
he was taken to a hospital.
- Yeah, but the attack he
used was a Tashinko attack
that rips through muscles
with just a finger.
That move attacks
the internal organs,
especially the liver.
It's a killer.
You're not taking it
easy by using that move.
- I'm surprised.
The Takayanagi clan,
head of the Gaou Kishi
style of martial arts
has such a kind man
like you for their heir.
Who would've thought?
- You'd be even more surprised
if you met my little
brother, Masataka.
That guy's even nicer than I am.
Or, maybe, he just
seems that way
'cause he's always
daydreaming. (laughs)
- So, Mitsuomi, are you
available after school today?
- Yeah, I guess.
But are you sure that's
gonna be all right?
Shin can get really
jealous sometimes.
If he catches wind that
his girlfriend and me
were hanging out all
alone together (laughs).
(light music)
- You're getting a lot stronger
but your attacks are
still all over the place.
You gotta learn when
it's time to attack
and time to hold back.
- All right, that's enough.
- It's not enough, this is
something really important.
That type of fighting may be
good enough for middle school,
but I gotta tell you,
if you wanna make
it in this academy...
- I said I don't
wanna hear anymore!
I'm tired of you treating
me like a little girl.
Why'd you have to
help me out like that?
Come on,
did you really think that
somehow I wouldn't notice?
Don't ever do it again.
(light music)
- Maya, to be perfectly honest,
the last thing I want is to
have to watch you grow stronger.
You see, all you have to
do is stay by my side.
You should always be with me.
No matter what.
(light music)
- Hmm, did you
just say something?
I missed it.
(light music)
- [Shin] Don't worry,
it was nothing.
(wind gently whooshing)
- Ms. Kuzunoha, where are you?
Ms. Kuzunoha?
Why'd she wanna meet
in this old building?
(Mitsuomi gasps)
Ms. Kuzunoha.
Hey, don't surprise
me like that, okay?
(both thud)
Ms. Kuzunoha, what
is this all about?
- I think that you know.
Don't tell me that even
someone of your caliber
is afraid of Shin.
You said earlier that
his move was a killer.
Well it's always like that.
He always makes bad choices
whenever Maya is involved.
If he didn't have me around
who knows how many people
he would've killed by now.
I don't know if you noticed,
but those two have a
strange relationship.
They're more like two people
who are madly in
love with each other
than brother and sister.
(Mitsuomi gasps)
- [Mitsuomi] During that
fight it wasn't her opponent
that she saw before her,
it was Shin.
It's always just one
man that she sees.
Always.
- Are you going to
hate me for doing this?
- No.
(swelling orchestral music)
- Hey, don't you think
that this has gone
on long enough?
How much longer you gonna
tail me, Mr. KATANA Hunter?
I'm Ishimatsu, KATANA's
chief bodyguard,
and I will gladly fight you.
(assassin whooshes)
(kick thuds)
(Ishimatsu grunts)
(punch thuds)
(Ishimatsu groans)
(wind whooshes)
(dramatic music)
(upbeat pop music)
- [Maya] Mitsuomi, what
are you looking at?
What's this you're listening to?
Don't look away from me,
or Shin for that matter.
Next episode of "Tenjho Tenge,
"One with an Unusual Talent."
You shall know the
shape of darkness.