(static buzzing)
(upbeat music)
(Dramatic Techno Music)
(Lightning Crackles)
(Lightning Strike)
- [Voice] My Hands!
- Mitsuomi!
(Dramatic Techno Music)
(grunting)
(energy whirling)
(Explosion)
(Mitsuomi yelling)
(Mitsuomi panting)
- Mitsuomi...
(loud thud)
(Birds Chirping)
- [Girls] All right! Fight Us!
- Come on, Where the
hell is everybody?
(Running footsteps)
- Bunshichi Senpai!
- Any luck?
- No I totally struck out.
Looks like Shin, My
Lady, Even Mitsuomi
Not a one of them
are at school today!
- Isn't that great.
- We don't care if
it's five against one,
we're not holding back!
- Let's go!
- Give me a break!
If I go and punch a girl,
my popularity will drop even
lower than it already is!
- We don't care about that!
Just fight us already, will ya!
- Why don't you just
leave this to me,
girls won't be an issue
when I'm on the scene.
(magical harp)
- [Sugano Voiceover] Super
deadly gorgeous guy pose!
(twinkle)
- GET LOST!
(groaning)
- [Sugano Voiceover]
That was my best move!
- Bunshichi Tawara!
- You're through!
(Whooshing)
- Fine (grunts)
(sonic boom)
(Girls gasping)
(wood clattering)
- If you girls keep this up,
you're gonna force me
to go all out on ya!
(Tense music)
- [Dan] Those chicks
may have made it
to the fifth round,
But against Bunshichi,
they're no match at all.
- The Juken Club's
good, there's no doubt
they're going to the finals.
- Yeah!
- And if they weren't,
there would've been
absolutely no point at all
for us to create this club.
(low chuckling)
(wood shattering)
(creaking wood)
- What the hell?
Are you guys spying on us?
Well now, we got quit
a little group here.
Don't we?
- [Dan] The greatest
martial arts club on campus.
Captain of the third
karate club, Furio Suko.
Ranked fifth.
Captain of the Rouken
Club, En Chikaza.
Ranked Sixth.
Captain of the Afghan Wrestling
club, Sakuraba Kazushi.
Ranked ninth.
Captain of the First Kendo
Club, Ryuusen Kanakita.
Ranked eighth.
And then there's
me, Dan Inosato.
Head of Jun Fan Kung
Fu, ranked third.
This group was formed to
destroy the Juken Club.
(dark music)
- I have to admit
dad, you were right.
Your powers and your fighting
skills were never the best
but your ability to predict
the future was spot on.
(footsteps approaching)
(panting)
(fighting music)
(kiai)
(dribbling ball)
(laughing)
(grunting)
(kiai)
- They took five
team captains and
created their own club
just for the Freelance.
That's gotta be
against the rules.
- Well no one's ever
done this before.
But it doesn't say anywhere
that you can't do it either.
(air whishing)
(kiai)
(painful groans)
(loud impact)
(pained groan)
- Your reign is over Tawara.
And seeing how your
friend Shin is too scared
to show his face you may
want to pass that on.
- That really hurt.
- Pft, what a
bunch of blowhards.
- They sure got a
lot of attitude.
They any good?
- You know how he told us
what all there rankings were?
Well he was talking about how
they were ranked here at Toudou.
Out of the top ten
ranking guys on campus,
five of them are
in that club alone.
They're serious contenders.
- I guess you're right.
Well then, how do
you and Shin rank?
- Shin is second and
I hold the top spot.
- Huh? I thought the
Executive Council President
was who ranked first.
- The rules just say the
president's chosen from
the club that wins the finals.
Shin didn't fight
at all last year.
In fact, I didn't even see
him at a single tournament.
So the only reason I'm
ranked higher than him is
because I was the one leading
all the fights last time.
- So that's what happened.
Hey, speaking of Shin.
Where'd he and the
others go off to?
- Who knows.
- [Tawara Voice] Mitsuomi's old
man has entered the picture.
So something must be going on.
But I haven't a freaking
clue what that is.
(wind blowing)
(raindrop splashing)
A sun shower, huh.
- I've been looking every
where for you, big brother.
- What are you doing down here?
You should be getting ready.
You got to kick some
ass in the finals today.
If you're going to flake
out on the club like this,
you're really going
to screw Bunshichi.
- I'll ask what I need to ask.
So just hear me out
and tell me the truth.
You have the power
of the Dragons' Eye.
You knew yesterdays events
would eventually transpire,
didn't you?
You knew all along and yet.
You knew how awful
the outcome would be.
(crying) And still
you didn't. Why?
(sharp pinging)
(energy whirling)
(explosion)
Tell me why big brother.
And you had better
have a good answer.
Because,
if you don't.
I will never forgive you.
- The future is as
vast and as varied
as the veins on this leaf.
There are infinite
possibilities for the future
branching out in thousands
of different directions.
There's no way I can clearly
see what's going to happen.
(eerie sounds)
Actually, that's all just a lie.
Listen very closely.
You can hear it now.
The sounds of fate.
- No I can't.
I can't hear those things.
- Liar.
You hear it fine.
When a drop of rain falls from
the sky and hits the ground
it doesn't land
there just by chance.
The temperature
of the atmosphere,
the direction of the wind.
They all play a part in forcing
that drop to hit it's mark.
One necessity merges
from another necessity.
Each time swelling
into a larger purpose.
Bit by bit the pieces
are being bound together.
Until the rush is so
strong it becomes a river.
That is destiny.
It's easy to stand here and
just listen to the rain.
But to understand the meaning
behind every single drop.
That's something I couldn't
begin to make sense of.
(frightened breathing)
(evil laughing)
Kind of funny, isn't it.
Why did God give me
this ridiculous power
that's beyond my grasp.
Of all the people to
give it to, why me?
Because the guy's one hardcore
sick and twisted necromancer.
Just think about it.
Look at the path
I've had to walk.
(intense frightening music)
(frightened gasping)
Maya,
you're always on my side right?
No matter what happens.
(melancholy music)
- [Maya Voiceover]
I no longer have the
desire to condemn my brother.
When I looked into his eyes,
all I saw was an endless amount
of tears welling inside him.
(Crowd cheering)
- And now we'll begin
with the final round of
Toudou Academy
Imperial Tournament.
Our 105th to date.
In the red corner, Jouken Club.
- Yo, where's Shin
and the others?
- Man, all three of them
seem to be missing again.
- [Announcer] Blue corner,
the Comprehensive
Martial Arts club.
- They just got
two of their guys.
It's like they're trying to
make fun of us or something.
- Yeah, but it's a
good chance to wipe out
this schools top ranking guy.
- [Audience Member] Who do
you think is going to win?
- [Male Viewer] There
is no way Tawara
can wipe out five of those guys.
- (whining) Senpai.
- Well, I'll just
fight as long as I can.
(murmuring)
- [Boy Audience
Member] Hey look!
It's Mitsuomi.
So he was here after all.
(intense techno music)
- Thank God Mitsuomi,
you made it here.
- Sorry I'm late guys.
I'll go first all right.
Step aside.
- Can you believe that guy?
He just waltzes in here
and takes the stage.
- He's different.
Something about him has changed.
- Huh?
- Nothing.
- So you did show up.
I thought maybe you gotten
scared and ran away.
- [Announcer] Begin.
- [Tawara Voice] Am I crazy?
No, I know this feeling.
I know just what it means.
This is exactly like him.
- [Mitsuomi Voice]
There's someone out
there waiting for me.
Whose a lot more
important than this.
And neither of us has the time
to beat around the bush anymore.
Shin.
(traditional Japanese music)
- [ Tawara] He's just like Shin.
- Come one Furio,
stop standing there.
(surprised gasp)
(air whirling)
(loud blow)
(pained groans)
- Whoa.
(pained groan)
(loud thud)
- What the hell?
Where did that just come from?
He's a completely different
animal than he was two days ago.
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] We'll now begin
the fifth and final match.
- Get Ready.
(kiai)
(pounding blows)
(gasps of breath)
- [Announcer] Red.
Winner Takayanagi.
- All right!
He beat all five of them.
(painful groaning)
- [Announcer] Winner of the
105th Imperial Tournament,
The Jouken Club.
(crowd cheering)
- [Audience] The
Comprehensive Club is a joke!
- [Random Male] You
guys don't deserve
to be ranked in the top 10.
- Those bastards can say
what ever the hell they want.
But they didn't have
to fight that guy.
(pained groaning)
- It's like that guy
wasn't even human.
(mysterious music)
- [Tawara Voice] I
don't like this one bit.
He did away with the
five biggest bad asses
on campus in a
matter of seconds.
And he isn't even showing the
slightest bit of
confidence either.
(gasping)
- They're going to start
handing out the awards now.
Huh,
hold on.
Did you hear what I said?
Come on.
Don't turn around
and bail on us.
(intense music)
- You averaged 36
seconds for each match.
Total time, three minutes.
Just like you promised.
- I just barely made it huh.
(pained groan)
(gasp)
(retching)
- You need acupuncture now.
- I'm all right.
I just got a little
woozy, that's all.
(intense beat)
(surprised breathing)
Miss Kuzunoha,
what's going on.
Tell me what's going
happening to my body.
- Two days ago,
when you were first
taken to the hospital
there was nothing
wrong with you.
But since then,
your heart has gradually
started to increase.
The speeds it's
reached are incredible.
It's over 200
beats a minuet now.
Even serious drugs can't get
your heart rate up like that.
It most likely has to do
with the Dragons' Eye.
That was a massive amount of
Chi he blasted into your chest.
In all honesty I
wouldn't be surprised,
if your heart were
to just burst.
But there's more.
Because your heart is
pumping out so much blood,
every muscle and brain cell in
your body has been awakened.
Your mental sharpness has
increased dramatically.
Your physical abilities are
far beyond any normal humans.
These super human battle
skills you have now,
are all thanks to that.
- That's the reward I get
for shaving time off my life.
- [Mana] And for only
three minuet intervals.
Your body can't take
much more than that.
- [Mitsuomi] All I
gets three minutes.
(chuckling) I don't believe it.
I'm like a comic book superhero.
- Why did you have to
go and enter the finals.
You didn't have to fight.
You had Tawara on
your team so why?
- You know, I could care less
about winning that
stupid tournament.
- Then why'd you fight?
- Because I knew that
it would upset her.
If she saw how hurt I really am.
And that it was all
caused by her big brother.
That would be it.
It would devastate Maya.
(rain pattering)
- [Doctor] The powers that
she has are truly amazing.
Any normal person would
have died on the spot.
- Master Fu.
- Before he went unconscious,
he must have used his
chi to stop the bleeding
and connect any of
the broken bones.
After seeing this,
I can see why the
Takayanagi family
brought him all the
way from Taiwan.
(door opening)
(heavy steps)
That's all for now,
please let me know when
he regain consciousness.
- Yes, of course.
(footsteps retreating)
(door closing)
(soft moaning)
You shouldn't try
to move yet Fu.
You need your rest.
- I'll do what I want.
I'm tired of playing dead.
- You didn't pass out?
- I have what you asked for.
- Put 'em on.
(rain pattering)
(steady foot falls)
- Come on Fu.
What are you planning to do?
- Isn't it obvious?
I was simply caught
off guard yesterday.
That's why he was
able to take me
in such a low class fist fight.
There can be no other reason.
(metallic ching)
- Fu, that's really
not a good idea.
Shin is an important
pawn in turning
Mitsuomi into the
true Martial Artist.
Dougen is going to be furious.
- Right.
The true Martial Artist.
No one like that is
ever going to exist
in this world you idiot!
(vase shattering)
(painful groan)
Ugh, Dammit.
I'm still in so much pain.
I'll show him just what
this pain feels like,
starting with his sister.
I'll rip off her ears,
crush in her nose,
rip off her finger nails and
chop her fingers
into little bits.
One after another.
(laughing)
- Fu, no.
- Let's get going.
(heavy foot falls)
(heavy music)
(sonic boom)
(grunting)
(squelching)
(painful cry)
(screaming)
(gentle rain falling)
- Our little errand
here is done.
We're going home now Maya.
- What did you just do?
Tell me what you did
right now, big brother!
- Listen Maya, you're
getting way to upset.
You don't have to
worry about this stuff.
You're just going
to have to trust me.
And if you run, I'll
just kill some more.
Don't worry it's not
you that I'll kill.
It's whoever you run to,
whoever you trust
that I'll destroy.
And it doesn't matter
to me who they are.
(sirens blaring)
(voice on radio is too
soft to understand)
(light flashing)
- Coach Fu.
- There aren't too many guys
who could have done this to him.
(mysterious music)
- Shin!
Come one Shin.
Where are you?
I know you're here some where.
Answer me!
- What the hell's
wrong with you.
Show some respect.
You don't barge
into someones house.
- Tell me where Shin is now.
- My brother isn't here.
What's going on?
Why are you acting like this?
- I know what the truth is,
so tell me where
I can find Shin.
- My brother is.
- [Shin Voiceover]
Anyone that you turn to,
that you trust.
I'll kill.
- (uncertain) My
brother isn't here now.
- Why Maya?
Why do you do this to yourself?
Why do you keep
everything bottled inside?
I said I'd help.
I said I'd relieve
you of all of these
burdens you've been
carrying for so long.
You're not alone anymore.
Once in awhile, it's
okay for you to be weak.
(soft whimpering)
I can be strong too.
And if it gets too much,
then I'll just
become even stronger.
- [Maya Voiceover] Why
should I refuse him.
Maybe it's all right.
Maybe it is safe to let go.
To dive into his arms.
Mitsuomi.
(intense music)
(surprised gasp)
- Go home.
(soft gasp)
Please Mitsuomi,
go home.
(crying) Go!
I don't want you
in my life anymore.
(soft gasp)
(melancholy music)
- [Mitsuomi Voiceover]
Suddenly, it all made sense.
- Mitsuomi?
- Give me three months Maya.
No, all that I'll need is two.
All right.
You won't have to cry
about this anymore.
(slicing through wind)
I'm going to defeat him for you.
(emotional music)
- [Mana] Light is drawn
to this cursed power.
Darkness trudges forward,
closing in on it's destiny.
Next episode of
Tenjho Tenge, Curse.
Please catch these
tears as they fall.