[Intro Music]
- It's not something I can stop.
Someone's taken a
bite of my soul,
nothing I can do about it.
- So are you afraid
of my brother?
Even a guy of your caliber?
- It's been a long time.
Master Dogen Takayanagi,
head of the family that
oversees the gaokishi style.
- (grunts)
You've got to be kidding!
Bring it on! You bastard!
- You know, sitting around
waiting for someone to come back
gets old real quick, miss
assassination weapons.
Now why don't lead
me to where Shin is?
What's wrong? Is there something
else you'd rather be doing?
That's how you wanna play.
Well, don't expect me
to go easy on you, then.
(ambulance sirens)
- Please, get out of the way!
Clear a path, hurry!
- Mitsuomi! Tell
me what happened!
- I really don't know
what happened, myself.
I got this phone call from
Bunshichi and then he...
You were the Katana
hunter, right?
If it wasn't you, then who
the hell else would have?
It's really bad. They've
just been beat mercilessly.
- Mitsuomi, do...
(echoing music)
- Maya?
- Mitsuomi.
- Senpai.
- All of us went down.
Katana's finished now.
- Wait, hold on a second!
Where's my brother?
What happened to my brother?
- Where's Shin?
You don't think he...?
Did he?
- We don't want anything
to do with you anymore.
It's best if you don't show
your faces around us again.
- Could Shin have done this?
He did, didn't he?
- Man, I barely made
any money again today.
I guarantee you the boss is
gonna get on my case again.
Yes, finally some money.
What's up with these guys?
I can't deal with this.
I'm not messing around
with anything dangerous.
- Don't turn down a customer.
I'll complain to
your supervisor.
- (stuttering) Just tell
me where you want me to go.
Oh please, don't get me
involved in anything weird.
- Whatever the fair is,
I'll pay you double.
Just take me to this location.
- You say that now, but...
- Don't let me down, all right?
- Oh, okay.
- Well, fancy that.
An ID card with
an optical sensor.
Greetings, Emi Isuzu.
I thought it might be
something like this.
(sirens)
(heart rate monitor beeping)
- Why?
Why would he do
something like this?
- It's all my fault.
- You see, all you have
to do is stay by my side.
- I have to do this.
I have to go stop my brother!
- Wait, hold on!
I'll go with you.
I can't move my feet.
- This doesn't
surprise me at all.
The flying phoenix.
That's Mitsuomi's family crest.
And the Isuzu clan, well,
they've been assisting
the Takayanagis for years,
along with the KuzunoHas,
the famous spy family.
Tch, this whole thing's a joke.
(whimpering)
- Ahh!
(crash)
- Pull over!
Why aren't you
stopping the car, huh?
- All right!
- I wouldn't do that.
- Please! Please don't
get me involve with this,
this has nothing to do with me!
I'm stopping the car.
- You do that and
I'll kill this girl.
And then those guys,
they'll go and kill me.
And then the two of us
will haunt this taxi
for as long as you drive it.
Day in and day out we'll
sit here in the back seat
reminding you of what you did.
- Okay, just please stop!
Man, why did this happen to me!
- What do you wanna do?
If we get in front, we can
box them in and stop them.
- Hmm, seeing how they have
Miss Isuzu inside that car,
I have a pretty good idea
where they'll be heading to.
Just let them go.
I think I know where
this will lead us.
- You know, I've never
been a lucky guy.
I work my butt off at this
dead end job for twenty years
and I'm still nothing
more than a driver.
I put in long hours and
my wife just sees that
as a chance to
screw around on me.
And then I get involved
in something like this!
- Yeah, well I
think you're wrong.
I think you are lucky,
at least a whole
lot luckier than me.
- Huh?
- Let me tell you my day.
I was stabbed in the
hand with a kunai,
and then hit by a car.
My motorcycle, my most
prized possession,
was crumpled up into a
worthless pile of steel,
and the clincher to all this,
the guy who I thought
to be my closest buddy
turned out to be stupid
beyond all belief.
This buddy I'm talking about
has an amazing amount of power.
But for some reason, the
friggin idiot can only ever see
one way to use it.
(crying)
- Maya, it's all right,
I'm gonna protect you!
- Whenever it came down to her,
the look in his
eyes was so serious.
So desperate.
Such a waste.
He's nothing more than a
helpless, spoiled little brat.
- It appears you've mostly
been doing as you please.
The chokuto reiki.
I don't recall
giving you permission
to use that katana again.
Is it that perhaps with
both your parents dead,
you think you're free
to use that weapon
whenever you feel like it?
- It was the reiki.
It called out to me.
Just like it did
a long time ago.
(animal screeches)
I heard it.
It told me to protect Maya.
(tires squeal)
- Hey mister, we're here.
Do you hear me, huh?
Hey, wake up!
- Sorry about that, just
needed some down time.
Unlock the door.
- Are you going out there?
Look at you.
You're wounded from head to toe.
- Oh, man, whenever
your wife comes back
from cheating on you,
there's always some sign that
you pick up on, isn't there?
Something like a hickey,
or a gift you know
came from another guy.
So when you start
noticing signs like this,
what do you do?
How long can you tell yourself
this isn't what you know it is?
If I could have stayed
blind to it all,
I wouldn't have to face
this kind of pain right now.
But unfortunately, I got
the same luck you do.
And I started noticing
those signs, too.
- Well, mister, you better win.
- All right now.
Yo, Shin, I've been
looking for you.
- Well, hello there.
Whatever brings you
here, Bunshichi?
You know, people just think
of the cleverest
things, these days.
With this thing here,
wherever you decide
to go, I can find you.
- Yes, that's a receiver.
The protocol is to keep at
least three transmitters
on his body at all times.
- Shut up!
Listen here, you ugly bitch,
I got nothing to say to you.
- Ugly bitch?
Fu Chen, why did you allow him
to come all the way out here?
I stressed to you earlier the
importance of this meeting,
what were you thinking?
- I do apologize, Miss Kuzunoha.
However, I just couldn't help
but feel that there's something
exceptional about this one.
I do hope that you
will forgive me.
- For some feeling?
You ignored your assignment?
- I hate to bring this up,
but isn't the reason
we're here today
because you didn't
show enough discretion
in handing that memory
card over to Mr. Mitsuomi?
Is it not because
of this careless act
that this one was also able to
view the images on that card?
And wasn't that what forced
us to put surveillance
on him as well?
I'm just giving you a hard time.
But I really don't
see the problem.
If the two of them
want to go at it,
then let them do it.
They're both students
at the Toudou academy,
so then they're our
guinea pigs, correct?
And besides, these two are fated
to go up against each other
sooner or later anyway.
- Fu Chen!
- Shin, tell me, what in the
hell was that Chinese guy
babbling about just now?
What's that look mean?
Are you saying that
you're fully aware
of everything that
they've been doing?
Come on, answer me, damn it!
(laughter)
- Bunshichi, you know,
sometimes you really bug.
I've been playing along
with your best buddy scheme
this whole time,
then you get worked up
and decide to come
all the way out here?
Who the hell do you think
you are to judge me?
- Master, it's dangerous,
please take cover!
- What the hell's going on?
- His presence is
totally changed,
it's a completely different guy!
- Yes.
- Toudou Academy senior and
executive council president,
Shin Natsume is ready to fight.
- Guess I'll be
fighting someone else.
- Miss Kuzunoha.
Why in the world did she
decide to approach me?
Why would she want me to
see something like that?
I've got so many
questions and no answers.
But none of that seems
to matter anymore.
Deep.
Endlessly deep and dark.
He's crawled up from
the darkest alleys
of my unconscious,
piercing my gut,
eating away at my heart.
That serpent called fear.
- So that's the dragon
eye they talk about.
- I guess now we're going
from punishment time
to some serious
monster killing time.
(knuckles cracking)
- Is that kid really
thinking about fighting him?
He'll kill him!
- What style does he use?
- He doesn't have one.
Closest description would be
reckless street fighting style.
However, there's not a
student in the whole school
who's ever won a
fight against him.
He's the strongest
ordinary person at Toudou.
- You son of a bitch!
I'm not losing it.
I know what he's trying to do.
- What's the matter, Bunshichi?
You look like somebody just
snapped your body in half.
- Such a strong and
ominous presence.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he's just seen
a clear vision of
himself being slain.
If Shin were serious,
he would have killed him
in two seconds.
- You freaking asshole!
- He has an enormous
handicap as it is,
fighting someone with a katana,
but an opponent with
the dragon's eye
and the chokuto reiki,
isn't this what you refer to
in your language as bullying?
- Calm down.
Watch him closely.
You've been in fights
with bad odds before.
It's a huge risk, but
if I can thrust myself
into striking range,
a katana really
isn't all that scary.
I just gotta risk my
life to get there.
- In times of crisis,
people in this country
always choose an approach that
involves risking their lives.
A bad habit to get into.
If that's what you're
willing to do to win,
why do you even
need martial arts?
- I can't believe he did that!
Shit!
The bastard stabbed me!
- Where are you?
Come on, brother, where are you?
Hey big brother!
Brother...
(crash)
(grunting)
(crazed laughter)
- You know, Mana, it's
at times like this
that I'm painfully
aware of how useless
martial arts can be
to an individual.
Courage, justice, wisdom,
courtesy, devotion,
sincerity, distinction.
Martial arts' seven rules.
Although it hasn't been
much more than ten years,
Shin has undoubtedly
trained and been instructed
under these same rules
that you and I live by.
And still, at the drop of a hat,
he turns into such an ugly
and despicable creature.
All martial artists
are defenseless
against a magical power
rooted in violence.
That's just a reality.
- He has so much power.
So powerful that he can
hold off the strongest man
at the academy with total ease.
And yet somehow, even
though he's winning,
he still seems so
small and pathetic.
[Outro Music]
- The desire for power
peeks into darkness,
and longs for the light.
That light is like a flame
that consumes the entire body.
Next episode of Tenjho Tenge:
Hellfire.
Brother, I'm right here!