(upbeat music)
(foreign language)
- You don't like this sign,
then come and do
something about it.
If you want me to take
this dojo by force,
I got no problem with that.
- Bring it on.
(men screaming)
- With the preliminaries
being next week,
we need to figure out
how we're gonna get
two more team members
as soon as possible.
Mitsuomi, what's up?
Didn't you say that
you had a lead?
- This is Scum.
He's a little souvenir
from my class.
He mentioned he wants to
be in the preliminaries.
- [Shin] That was when
this image first appeared.
And for the past
eight years now.
I've seen it over
and over again.
(flames crackling)
I'm beginning to realize
that it's probably the
last thing I'll ever see.
(flames crackling)
This agent from the afterlife.
(echoing footsteps)
Hello dad.
- [Dad] Look what
you've done, Shin.
You've allowed yourself to
place us into this grisly state.
Not only had you chosen
a dark and bleak life,
but you selfishly
fight to preserve it.
- [Mom] You've become a pathetic
little fool, haven't you,
Shin?
- [Shin] Hello there, Mom.
- [Mom] Your heart's like
an old abandoned katana,
corroded over with
bitterness and ugliness,
rusted from lack of use.
You choose to keep it
sheathed and let it rot away
and cannot bear the
sound of it being drawn.
You can't slay anything with it.
You just bat it at people as
if it were some kind of joke,
and in the end, you're the
one who snaps and shatters.
(sword slashing)
- I've had it with you!
That's enough!
I refuse to die now!
(parents laughing)
- [Aya] Big brother?
Are you all right?
Is something wrong?
- No.
Everything's fine.
Where's Maya?
- [Aya] She's already
left for school.
Some guy riding a
motorcycle came and
picked her up a few minutes ago.
(Maya laughs)
- She has, huh?
Well, I guess I'd
better get going then.
- [Aya] Who were you talking
to just now, Big Brother?
- Aya, you mean...
you could hear that?
You could hear that voice?
- [Aya] Well, yeah.
- [Shin] I see.
- All right, here goes.
Are you sure this is okay?
You really want me
to break your cast?
Your leg may not have
even healed yet, you know.
- I don't care.
I'm tired of this thing.
- All right, brace
yourself then.
(crashing)
- What the hell
are you thinking?
- You're the one
who asked for it.
It seemed like a good
opportunity to take you out
so I could become the toughest
guy in the Juken Club.
- Give it a rest, Scum.
I assume you do want to
enter the Preliminaries.
- Hey there, my lady.
- That's not the point!
- What's up?
- Oh, hey Shin.
- Yo.
Hey.
- What up?
- Maya, don't you go
around thinking that
I owe you one for doing this.
If you're not pulling
your weight, I'll
cut you immediately.
You got that?
- Fine with me.
Same goes for you.
Drop your guard for a second
and I'll be right in your face
so keep your eyes open.
- Do these guys hate like
each other or something?
- Huh?
No, it's not like that at all.
It's just the twisted
way these two show they
care for each other.
Think about it too much and
you'll end up looking the fool,
like me.
- All right, we ready?
- Yes.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
(audience cheers)
- [Scum] Man, this is amazing!
I had no idea Toudou had
this much cool stuff.
Are we gonna fight
down there too?
- Course not, stupid.
Only the five final matches
are held down there.
- If they just do
the finals here,
where are the other rounds held?
(speaker feedback)
- [Announcer] Quiet, everyone.
Before the tournament begins,
the rules will be
explained to you by
the head of
operations committee,
Master Toudou.
Take a seat and pay attention.
- Hello, welcome, everyone.
You're all familiar
with Toudou's history.
It began in the early
days of the Meiji period.
The academy practiced
hundreds of styles back then,
maybe even thousands.
Those styles evolved into
their own organizations,
which developed the various
clubs we have today.
We currently have 96
different clubs on record.
The Executive Council was
created as a way to combine all
the different
groups together and,
guide the academy as a whole.
The club that wins
the preliminaries is
immediately crowned
the executive council.
- Hey I want to know
something.
- Like what?
- What is it that makes you
want to win this thing so badly?
You even went and
created a whole new club.
Is the president seat so cushy
you can't imagine leaving it?
- Don't be stupid.
It's nothing like that,
you try sitting in that chair.
- Well tell me why then?
[Master Toudou] Every
challenger that approaches them.
Club members should not only
fight for the teams honor
and beliefs but their own
honor and beliefs as well.
- Huh, you just lost me.
I'm not getting this
part of the rules at all.
- You're really overthinking
this whole thing.
It's pretty simple other
than each team having a total
of only five members.
There are absolutely no other
rules you need to worry about.
Fight anywhere you like
and everything's allowed,
from weapons to
hitting vital points.
You get to choose any
showdown you want.
- That is totally insane!
We're civilized folks!
We're just high school students!
- [Bunshichi] The opponents
and order we fight in
have already been determined.
You should've got a copy of
the breakdown the other day.
- That's so boring.
Why can't we just
fight anyone we want,
whenever we want to.
- Well, that doesn't seem like
a better plan to me my lady.
If it were like that, it'd be
a straight out death match.
- (chuckles) Last
year was the worst.
They were after us all the time.
We had guys from
the archery club
try to snipe us
from the roof tops.
- That's right.
Remember what
happened to Eyebrow
when he came out of class?
It was like he walked
into a hornet's nest.
- Totally!
- I suddenly
remembered something.
- Where do you
think you're going?
- Hey, come on man!
Let me go!
- I'm not letting you
go anywhere at all.
(Scum choking)
Flake on us and I'll stress
you so hard that your hair
will come out in clumps.
Got that Scum?
- Hm, if you still want to run,
I think you'll have a hard
time running past these guys.
Look.
(menacing music)
As far as our challengers
are concerned.
I believe they think that
this battle has already begun.
- That's right,
meet the five devils
from the Akutagawa's Ninja Army.
(chuckles)
And you just happened
to be our round one.
You guys are going down!
- You're going nowhere.
- You can't let your
guard down, dammit!
(screams of agony)
(punching and kicking blows)
- Yo, let the little whipper
snappers take this one.
Us old fogies can
sit back and watch.
- Hey, who are you calling old?
- So this is what the
preliminaries are all about.
- Kinda fun.
- And so it begins.
(menacing music)
- [Dad] This is destiny Shin.
This is what you've
been searching for.
You've found him at last.
The man who will
finally reduce you
and all your powers
to absolutely nothing.
(flames crackling)
- What's up with you?
Don't just stand
there, for all you know
I could've been some punk coming
up to stab you in the back.
- Sorry I spaced,
won't happen again.
It's not that I'm
afraid of dying.
It's that I can't just
stand by and let him take
everything that I care about.
And in return leave
me with nothing.
- All right, Bunshichi.
- What do you want?
- I can't hold it.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Think you can come with me.
- Huh, what do I look
like your mother?
Forget it!
Go by yourself.
- Ugh, come on man, what if
I get attacked on the way?
- You're being ridiculous.
Nobody out there thinks
there's something to gain
by picking off just you.
You moron.
- Yeah, but...
- But what?!
- All right you made your point!
I'll go by myself.
- While you're out get me
some chow mein and coffee,
and don't dawdle.
(crying)
- Huh?
(breathing hard)
- Maya!
- Hey!
- What are you doing,
I'm your opponent.
- Shut up!
(breathing hard)
- I could take him, if
I could just close in.
Get off me!
You overgrown sack head!
(yawns)
(fighting cries)
- So, did you survive?
- Shouldn't we help them?
I mean we aren't
really doing much here.
- Sit back and chill.
Let the guys who want
to go at go at for now.
If we're lucky,
those guys will lose
and then we'll get
to go home early.
- What's up with this guy?
He doesn't even care about this.
- Those two are getting good.
I gotta admit they're a whole
different animal from when
they first started
coming to this school.
Less work for me, put
those two together
and you got yourself
one badass team.
There's hardly anybody on this
campus who can touch them.
- So confident.
I guess you believe that you'll
come out of this victorious.
- Kuzunoha?
- Oh, hey there.
- Well now,
are you done already?
I should've known.
- Ms. Kuzunoha, which
club are you in?
- I'm not fighting for any club.
I'm on the medic team this year.
You'd be amazed,
there's so many injuries
that occur during this event.
Look, yet another one.
You see this pressure point?
What if this was the exact
point, that when touched
destroys your right arm
for the rest of your life?
What would you do?
- Why don't we just
see what happens?
Realize though if
you destroy my arm,
I'll have you for
lunch Ms. Kuzunoha.
- (giggles) Just a little joke.
There, does it still hurt?
- No.
- That's good.
I've decided to put my plans
to fight you on hold for now.
I've realized that no
matter which approach I take
chances are you will still win.
I don't wanna lose anymore
than I've already have.
But if I do see a
time I can beat you
rest assured I'll
hold nothing back.
But until that day we're good.
- Great.
- Well, moving on where's Shin?
- Old man Toudou nabbed him.
I saw him take Shin
aside a few minutes ago.
He said something about some
big wood coming to see him.
(menacing music)
- Kuzunoha, what's going on?
- I knew nothing
about it, I promise!
No one's even
mentioned it to me!
- Regarding the subject
we were discussing
at the bus stop the other day.
There was such a huge
commotion that broke out
that I'm afraid I was
unable to hear your answer.
I assume you haven't forgotten.
- Emi, Emi where are you?
You have to be here somewhere!
Answer me!
- We don't need
Shin to back us up.
We can handle things
just fine without him.
- Something about this is
starting to smell really bad.
I don't know why, but it
just doesn't sit right.
- I trust you
remember this blade.
It's the one Mana Kuzunoha
had taken away from you.
I'm giving it back.
- Emi!
Fu!
Fu Chi'en!
It's been eight years hasn't it.
That's when you first
picked up this blade.
Time sure does fly.
How did it feel when you
made your first killing?
Did you enjoy it?
You can feel free to kill
as much as you want today.
(laughs)
You have my permission.
- You, you can't be serious.
Master Dogen said that?
You mean, he really gave
Shin his permission.
This, this has to be a joke.
If he's allowed to reveal his
full powers here on campus.
Forget the preliminaries,
the entire school
will be in a panic.
- That's right Ms. Kuzunoha.
And that's precisely
what Master Dogen wants.
(Kuzunoha gasps)
You must realize,
that it's out of the shadows
of chaos and violence
that justice is born.
(flames crackling)
In order to finalize the
one true martial artist,
we must establish him as a
symbol of absolute justice.
And in order to do
that, there must first
be an unquestionable evil
that needs to be eliminated.
- It's round four now and I
don't want there to be any doubt
who the winner of this
match is all right.
I want there to be five
one-on-one battles.
We can hold it in this building
using five different classrooms.
Are you in?
- I don't care how we do it,
let's just get on with it.
- There's only four
of you guys right now.
Where's your captain at?
- I'll give you a freebie
and say we lost that one,
if that doesn't work for
you then I can fight twice.
- Let's get going!
- So, who am I being
paired with?
- Me.
- How's it going?
- All right, everybody
pick a class room now
and face your opponent.
- Just as I thought.
The old monster
doesn't even blink.
- You little punk!
Don't try to play games with me!
- Newsflash,
I like this school and I like
the person I've turned into.
I'm through.
I use to feel obligated
to follow your orders,
but those days
are long gone now.
We're done.
- Eight years ago when you
woke this power inside you
and went insane the 12 clans
gave an order to execute you
before you became to dangerous.
The very fact that you
are still alive today
is all because of me.
If that doesn't qualify as
a sense of obligation to you
then what does?
Or perhaps you're so
ungrateful you're willing to
destroy that too.
- Tell me, is everything
you do for your own benefit?
- [Fu Chi'en] You see Master
Dogen is the old fashion type.
He still believes 'til
this day that people can be
manipulated by things
like power and gratitude.
- Oh no!
- In the case of Shin Natsume
this is incredibly effective.
- These two are working together
as if they're one opponent.
They had to train together
for years to move like this.
- There are just a handful
of people who are privy to
this information.
But within this academy,
there's more than a dozen people
the Takayanagi Clan has
specifically placed here from
all over the country.
These people have
laded powers too.
And when their powers are
activated it will be the dawning
of a whole new day for us.
(lightning sounds)
(Maya screams)
That was the chi of earth
found within the five elements.
Technically speaking,
it's something you can
find anywhere in the world.
It's energy from
the earth itself.
Don't look at me like
that Ms. Kuzunoha.
It isn't pretty.
- Fu Chi'en!
What are you thinking?!
Do you know what you're doing?
(chuckles)
(footsteps)
- I think this picture
is rather effective
but there's something
about it that's lacking.
I know, too much clothing.
(gasps)
(ripping)
(footsteps)
(upbeat music)
(foreign language)
- [Announcer] A bad omen brings
out he darkness once again.
The shadows are nearly at
the end of their journey.
Next episode of "Tenjo
Tenge", Accidental Discharge.
What are you telling
me lies ahead?