(static rushing)
(ominous music)
(upbeat music)
(shouting in foreign language)
♪ Your party time
♪ And here yeah
♪ We're trying to party time
♪ Party time
♪ Let's Go
(rapping in foreign language)
♪ In the Night
♪ Yeah, feel so good
♪ Bin bin ba ban
to rhythm dance ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Every time love you (sings
in foreign language) ♪
♪ Bomb a head
(motorcycle roaring)
- I was surprised, people are
more solid than I thought.
(intense music)
Maya, from here on out
nothing will separate us okay?
- Earrings, and this thing.
What's on it?
Tell me, why would anyone wanna
take all this footage of us?
- I've known Shin,
for a long time.
For more than 10 years now.
(Shin laughing wickedly)
But that guy, I don't know.
- Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure you guys had
nothing to do with it.
I just need to blow
off a little steam.
(generator running)
- [Operator] Set
up, position five.
Ready, go.
(man grunting)
(siren buzzing)
- Cut it.
- The reflexes are on target.
But I'm afraid everything
else is a bit of a mess Fu.
- [Master Dogen] Looks
like an arcade game to me.
- [Fu] Master Dogen I assure
you, the complexity of this
system is far greater
than any video game.
- Fine then.
Go about this as you wish.
As Mitsuomi's coach I'll
trust your decisions.
I'll play little role in
how you decide to go about
your training, but I assume
you realize this Fu Chi'en.
For centuries now the
Takayanagi clan has overseen
every form of the martial arts.
Our final objective has
always been to develop
the ultimate martial artist.
One who can defeat
any form of darkness.
My hope to see this
dream fulfilled
rests entirely in Mitsuomi.
It's not just my dream, but
the entire Takayanagi clan's.
No, it's the dream of
Japan's entire community
of martial artists as well.
I'm trusting you.
Contact Mana Kuzunoha,
tell her I'd like to have
a word with Shin Natsume.
- [Man] Yes sir.
- Sounds like you're
pretty sure about this.
- I am.
You've heard of these
guys haven't you?
The three gambling brothers
are famous for being stupid.
- But do you really think
those three lame asses
could have taken Ishimatsu
down all on their own?
- Well if they were walking
around in our team jacket
and talking smack
they got some nerve.
- And I hear they're telling
the whole frigging school
they're doing the
Katana hunting.
(sinister music)
I'd really like to see them pay.
- [Man] I think we need
to teach those piss ants
a lesson or two then.
- Well we can't
trust that Bunshichi
is gonna take care of it.
We've gotta take this
matter into our own hands.
(doors creaking)
(footsteps echoing)
- Brother, I brought
you some rice crackers.
I know they're your favorite.
Are you there?
- Where are you?
Where have you been?
- I'm here, I'm
right here brother!
- Where am I, what
are they doing to me?!
Nobody looks at me,
nobody even notices me!
- Brother!
- [Brother] It's
always, so dark.
- It's all right brother.
You're right here
standing in front of me
and Maya's right
here holding you.
(cat meowing)
(Maya gasping)
- Why am I dreaming
about that again?
What is wrong with me?
(cat meowing)
Look at you.
Could you possibly be hungry?
(cat meowing)
Do you like it?
Aya makes a pretty
good lunch box!
(cat meowing)
I wish that I was like
you, you're totally free.
(thud)
(cat screeches)
Hey!
(punches thudding)
(man yelling)
His rhythms.
They're so passionate.
So beautiful.
(man panting)
(Maya clapping)
Please forgive me, I didn't
mean to interrupt you.
Now I can see why they
call you the plow horse
of the martial arts community.
- I think the word you meant
to use was thoroughbred.
Besides, those were just
some random punches anyway.
I was hardly even trying.
- What's going on
with your hand?
- Oh, this.
It's not something I can stop.
Someone's taken a
bite of my soul.
Nothing I can do about it.
As heir to the head clan
of the Gaokishi style,
I've gone up against a
lot of martial artists.
But this guy's different.
(dramatic music)
He doesn't attack
like a human does.
The attacks that he
uses when he fights,
aren't something that a
human would even think of.
- So are you afraid
of my brother?
Even a guy of your caliber?
- Because I call myself
a martial artist,
there was a time when
I wanted nothing more
than to try to take him on.
But now, I want nothing more
than to avoid fighting him.
Even if it means being
ridiculed and chastised
I wouldn't care.
I hate this feeling.
I don't need to have
fists like this anymore!
(punch crashing)
- One needs to have a
heart that does not sway.
You're more like
me than you know.
If I thought I could
take him in a real fight
I'd have done it,
instead I'm forced to
single out Katana members
and then hunt them down.
(airplane humming)
- Do you know you're messing
with the Three
Gambling Brothers?
Do you have any idea that
I'm Tetsu the Bakuran Fist?
- Yeah don't you know that
I'm Yasuji the poker face...
(yells)
- Shut your freaking
mouth already.
You.
(Tetsu whimpers)
Is Sanada the Mahjong
Fist one of you guys?
- Yeah he is,
together we make up
the Three Gambling Brothers!
But we didn't, we didn't
have a hand in any of this!
We're not doing
the Katana hunting!
- I'm well aware
of that lard ass.
There's no way a turd like
you could take down Ishimatsu.
(Tetsu moans)
But I do think you've
been talking a lot of shit
behind our backs,
and that won't do.
All right.
(man growls)
(Tetsu yowls)
- Ugh!
- All right asshole now fess up!
Where'd you get a
hold of our team logo?
- Okay, okay I'll tell you!
We were cruising
around town one night
and and then we passed in
front of the school yard
and that's when, that's
when we saw someone
hanging a Katana jacket
on the school gate!
I swear it's true!
I promise!
- [Woman] Their faces.
Tell us what they looked like.
- It was really dark I
could barely see 'em.
But, it seemed like a chick.
She had this hat on her head
but, there was this hair
in front of it that was
spilling out like this!
- There you go.
- And there you have it folks.
No wonder Bunshichi
tried to cover this up.
I'm afraid I'm not nice
enough to look the other way
on this just because she's
the big guys little sister.
- About time, if you can't get
here when you're supposed to
then don't bother.
(man vomits)
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Why, why are you
hunting down Katana members?
- It's the best
solution I came up with.
I'm doing it to help my brother.
He did it to protect me.
Because I'm so weak.
That's the only reason he
wanted to become stronger.
So now, I will do my best
to tear down everything
that he has tried to create.
I want to destroy it
myself, and gain a strength
that not even my
brother can match.
If I don't do this,
my brother will rage
like an insane beast for
the rest of his life.
(ominous music)
- [Policeman] All right,
all right step back.
Stay out it's not safe.
(crowd murmuring)
- Man it's getting
out of control.
What the hell are
those guys thinking?
- [Man] So what, this is just
one fight club against itself.
- [Man] I guess you're right.
- [Medic] All right, easy.
Easy.
- Okay I got it.
(ambulance siren wails)
- Yo eyebrow, you alive or what?
Come on!
- What do you think
you're doing?
All these guys are in
critical condition.
- Bunshichi.
- Just give me a nod.
Did Shin do this to you?
- [Man] Shin.
- Was it him, huh?
(man gags)
- We all quit, we're through.
Katana can go on without us.
Just please, just please
don't kill us okay?
- That's enough from you!
- I'd quit if I were you.
- Wutan, what happened?
Are you okay?
- No, my insides are shredded.
They're carrying me out last.
They need all their
medics just to lift me.
- Wutan, you know I
don't give a rats ass
about who took out who, or
which team took down which.
I'd be totally content
living a rosy colored life
where everyone at school
didn't care about this crap.
That's what I was hoping
would eventually happen.
If I could just keep a lid
on this whole Katana hunter
bullshit, but I guess it
didn't work out so well.
I'll take care of the rest.
Shin's a shit head,
he's as good as dead.
Besides, it's about
time I remind him how
I got my nickname.
- Bunshichi, don't get me
wrong, I think you're tough.
In fact, I think you're
probably the strongest student
in the entire Toto academy.
But still, I don't think
even you can take down Shin.
- [Bunshichi] What do you mean?
- Man you're so late.
- I know I'm sorry (laughs).
Look at that, that's
Tawara down there guys.
- Huh, so who's that?
- Who's that?
You guys don't know anything!
He's so big time, you're
looking at a guy who happened
to go to the same middle
school as him! (sighs)
Everyone totally worshiped him.
He so had it made.
Double Impact Tawara
He had the showdown
on Okutama Boulevard.
Operation, decimation of DR.
He mowed down 200 guys
on crazy thunder road!
There's so many legends
out there about this dude
I can't even name them all.
When Katana first formed
he was their lead attacker.
He single handedly took out
nearly all of their opposition.
This dude's a total monster!
(yelling)
- He's going off on one
of his fantasies again.
- [Man] We're outta here.
- Hey hold on, wait up!
(ambulance siren wailing)
(bicycle wheels whirring)
(Bunshichi sighs)
(girl yells)
- How much longer are you
gonna tail me with that camera?
If you keep this up
I'm gonna have to start
billing ya for royalties!
- Look big tits!
- Huh, big tits where?
(dramatic music)
That was cheap!
Well I guess the moment
I've been waiting for
is just gonna have to
wait a little bit longer.
(singing in foreign language)
You're not getting away!
Slow down damn it!
Shouldn't mess
with the big boys.
Little girl.
Not bad though, I think a
piece of that will compensate
nicely for that little kick
and stick move she pulled.
- Bunshichi, there's no way
you can win against Shin.
You're strong, but that's it.
You're not terrifying.
I never thought
of Shin like that.
I never knew a human who
could be so terrifying.
And that's the difference
between you and Shin.
- [Bunshichi Voiceover]
He sure had a mouthful
he had to get out.
Those weren't the kindest words
he could have
spoken to me either.
Come here.
(truck hooting)
Shit!
- [Kuzunoha] He's here.
You could have called and told
me you were going to be late.
- Yeah well, I had to
run this stupid errand.
- You consider placing your
comrades on the brink of death
to be nothing more
than a mere errand?
- Say hello Shin.
- It's been a long time.
Master Dogen Takayanagi.
Head of the family that
oversees the Gaokishi style.
- Kuzunoha.
Will you give us a
moment of privacy?
- Yes, but sir.
- This location's secure.
There's absolutely
nothing to worry about.
- [Kuzunoha] All right.
(Kuzunoha gasps)
(wind rustles)
(man wolf whistles)
- What's wrong, don't
you find her attractive?
I've been told you haven't
even laid a finger on her.
Perhaps it's because
you remember her name
from somewhere in your past?
- Master, what is it you want?
I know that I'm only a student.
But I'm afraid that I still
don't have much free time.
- What I want?
(chuckles) Why don't
you take a guess.
Use that dragons eye
that you're so proud of.
- There's nothing
to worry about miss.
Our finest guys are
stashed all around here
just itching to
pounce. (chuckles)
- Gone two whole years.
- I went another
day without killing.
- [Kuzunoha Voiceover]
The smell of blood
oozed from his body.
It was so thick I wanted to gag.
But even then I...
(engine revving)
- [Bunshichi] How
bout you just give up?
What you did earlier
really hurt little girl.
I'll tell you what, give me
a little piece of that booty
of yours and we'll call it even.
- If you think that a piece
of me is what you really want,
then you just go ahead
and make your move.
But you'll have to
get past these first!
- Look what you can do.
Assassination weapons.
(car screeches)
(Bunshichi grunts)
(intense music)
(car revving)
You gotta be kidding.
Trying to finish me off?
Bring it on you bastard!
Aargh!
Yeaah!
(girl gasps)
That wasn't very bright.
I just gotta say I really
don't think it's fair
that I gotta get
myself all beat to hell
'cause of some stupid jackass.
I'm so gonna get you when
I'm through with this.
You got that Shin?
- What's wrong?
Why are you acting so quiet?
You're nothing but a shadow.
A pitch black darkness devoid
of a single ray of light.
(singing in foreign language)
- [Narrator] Trembling
before their darkness
humans will invariably
fall into it.
This terror leads them to chaos.
Next episode of "Tenjou
Tenge", "Magical Power".
Brother, what is it you want
to kill with that Katana?