(fizzes)
(upbeat music)
(sings in foreign language)
♪ Yo party time, party time
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ Time to party
time, party time ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, uh
(sings in foreign language)
- I did it.
(growls)
(moans)
- [Aya] Don't ever
lose again, not ever.
(moans)
- I'm, just taking a little
advanced payment on my reward.
- Okay, tell me Bob, do I
come across as weak to you?
(upbeat music)
(fire crackles)
(moans)
- My bike, really was on fire.
- Well, it looks like
somebody already called it in.
- Who in the hell would
want to do this to my bike?
There's a long list
of suspects already.
- Hey now, don't freak out Bob.
- What?
- We're gonna find the
person who did this
and when we find 'em
we'll make 'em pay double
what they owe you.
- It won't be that easy.
How the hell are we
gonna find this guy?
- We start by grabbing
every suspicious looking guy
that we see and then we
begin to beat the crap
out of 'em one by one,
we're bound to come across
the culprit at some point.
It's a simple plan,
but it'll work.
(groans)
What's that look for?
(growls)
- I bet the guy who did this
is probably still close by.
I'm gonna find his ass
and kill him right now.
I'm generally a pretty
level headed guy
but this is really
gonna make me lose it.
- I'm sure Chiaki
will be in tears too.
She loved that bike
almost as much as you did.
You know come to think
of it, she's late,
wasn't she just going
out to the laundromat?
(grunts)
(dramatic music)
(slurps)
(pants)
You have any idea where
the laundromat is?
- No, I'm just gonna search
the neighborhood from one side
to the other, dammit, I've
got a bad feeling about this.
- Huh?
(gasps)
(laughs)
(shrieks)
(yells)
(rings)
- [Voicemail] Yeah, this
is Bob, I've stepped out,
if you've got something to
say, leave me a message.
(beeps)
- Did you find 'em?
- No, no luck, Mr
Makihara's out too.
I thought that maybe
Souichiro-sama woud
have gone there.
- I don't think you need
to worry about it so much,
the executive council
hands out punishment
as a way to maintain
discipline among the students.
The basic rules are to keep
it fair and within the grounds
of the campus.
So unless those boys fight
back in some unfair way,
the outcome shouldn't
be too severe.
- I've no idea where
this is coming from,
but I have a really
bad feeling about this.
My head feels like
it's about to split,
my stomach's roiling, I
think I'm gonna throw up.
- Is something wrong?
- I need to run to the bathroom.
- Is it that boys child?
- That joke isn't
even a bit funny.
(rings)
hello there, Natsume residence.
Oh, it's not Souichiro-sama,
it's for you sis,
some guy named Ryuuzaki.
- What?
- [Ryuuzaki] Well
long time no talk.
- What is this call about?
I'm quite busy right now.
If this isn't important
I'm hanging up.
- Come on now, don't
be so cold to me,
the main event is
just about to begin.
I'm afraid the opening
act was a little lacking
in one on one interplay.
(laughs)
this is my first job in a while,
I intend to have a whole
lot of fun, (slurps)
- What are you talking about?
- Those boys that you've
shown an interest in recently,
our president seems to be rather
interested in them as well.
In fact they're somewhat
of a special case
in the punishment
they are to receive
is one without any restrictions.
(gasps)
(heart pounds)
(dramatic music)
(pants)
This is what happens when
one decides to cozy up
with your little Juken club.
We should make an
example out of them,
for the other freshmen.
- Wait, Ryuuzaki,
you've got it all wrong,
those two boys have absolutely
nothing to do with us.
It's just my little sister
who's infatuated with them.
Ryuuzaki, Ryuuzaki.
(beeps)
(growls)
- Well, it seems our little
lost sheep have arrived.
(growls)
Impressive, that was
a rather nice kick.
(dramatic music)
- [Maya] Aya wait.
- Don't try to stop me.
It won't work.
- First of all you have
no idea where Ryuuzaki is,
and secondly you don't even
know how to ride that bike?
- It'll be all right,
I'm sure she'll teach me
everything I need to know,
and besides, I seem to
see it all pretty clearly.
I see Souichiro-sama's figure.
So maybe this is what they
call the power of love.
(engine revs)
(moans)
- Bastard.
(laughs)
(moans)
(dramatic music)
- For may generations
beings with abnormal powers
have been born into
the Natsume family.
Long ago Aya began showing signs
that she too
possessed that power.
The power of the dragon
eye, in ancient China
it was referred
to as crystal eye,
a person with this eye can
see through everything,
they can see into the past
or far into the future.
(engine revs)
It's said they have the
powers to communicate
not only with humans,
but also with objects
that don't appear to be alive.
Aya is just now
starting to realize
that she has these powers.
I'm pretty sure this
is why she fell in love
with that boy the
second she saw him.
To me that boy seems like
nothing more than a fool
who loves to fight.
But perhaps in the future,
something more will come of him.
(pants)
(cries)
- Souichiro-sama,
Mr Makihara,
(pants)
(blares)
- Yell.
(screams)
(gasps)
- You must be Natsume's
younger sister,
you got a pretty good set
of tits for a girl your age.
(gasps)
I got a message for
your two friends,
name's Sutimu Ryuuzaki a
senior in the boxing club,
tell them the next time
I see either of those two
in school they'll be in
worse shape than this,
so if they're wise they'll
submit their letters
of resignation first
thing tomorrow.
Expulsion, the executive
council has spoken.
(moans)
You should stop that,
anger disrupts your chi,
even if you were butt
naked you couldn't beat me
in the state you're in.
Don't be in such a rush, I'm
sure we'll end up facing off
against each other
sooner or later.
(moans)
(playful music)
- Hmm, a nice clean split.
- Do you think that maybe we
could weld it back together?
- It's a Masakio May
katana from Satsuma,
there aren't too many
sword smiths' today
who can make something
of this quality.
Besides, I'm afraid this katana
no longer houses any chi.
Katana's are like people,
if it's broken open it dies.
It's better to let
it rest in peace
than to attempt to
weld it back together.
- I was so angry at that point
I completely lost my temper
and my stance and form
were all out of whack.
I was basically asking
the weapon to break.
- [Souichi] I want
to become stronger.
- [Bob] I want to
become stronger.
- [Souichi] Stronger.
- [Bob] Stronger.
- [Both] Stronger.
- I know somehow you will
and you will be stronger
than anyone else.
Tell me sis,
- [Maya] Hmm.
- How does one become stronger?
I was totally useless.
I couldn't even help the
person that I'm in love with.
Much less an innocent bystander.
As part of the Natsume family,
I've practiced martial arts
as long as I can remember,
I would have thought that I'd
be relatively strong by now.
But I,
- What are the reasons that
drive you to become stronger?
And what does strength mean?
What's being strong mean to you?
Those are questions we
must all wrestle with.
The answer, however, is quite
simple and rather obvious.
Stop being a baby, Aya,
what kind of martial artist
doesn't know something so basic.
(chirps)
(kids chatter)
- Well it looks to me like you
got beaten up pretty badly.
- Yeah, well I saw
Soiuchiro land a nice blow
to you too.
- Well I think if you can
make a wisecrack like that
then you'll be okay.
- Hey,
what's up with
this Ryuuzaki guy?
And what the hell is
the executive council?
I want to know.
- The executive council
has been in existence
for a very long time, since
the school the Todo Academy
is based on, the Tobu
School was first built.
The Tobu school was built
so that martial arts
could be taught
again, as a result,
the founders of the
school brought in masters
and instructors from all
over, almost by force.
And in order to maintain
decorum amongst the ranks
in the school they had
to establish some form
of supreme power and discipline.
- So the executive council
can do whatever it wants then?
- You shouldn't try
to mess with them.
They're not the kind of
people that a street fighter
like you can win against.
- Huh?
Why is this door unlocked?
Huh?
- Oh, hi there sis.
Is something wrong?
You look really upset.
- (gasps) Aya, Aya,
you're holding,
- This?
I was thinking about
working with this instead
of the Masaki,
- you may not!
- But how come?
Is this because that katana
belonged to our brother,
but you didn't get
upset like this
when I took the motorcycle?
That bike was something that
belonged to him as well,
so if I can use the
bike, why not the sword?
- Aya!
Be quiet, you are not permitted
to use this sword
ever again understand?
- But sis.
- You're welcome to use
any sword but this one,
just not the Chokutoreki.
(soft music)
Dear brother.
(seagull caws)
- Yo, have you
caught anything yet?
- Hell yeah, I have.
I got a huge haul
just laying around me.
- You know I've always
wondered about this
just why are there so
many damn rubber boots
swimming in the
waters around Japan?
- Hell if I know.
How's Chiaki doing?
- Well, I think she's
doing all right,
at least for the moment.
- I see.
- I want to thank
both of you guys
for coming to rescue me.
Thank you.
(caws)
- [Souichi] So Bob, we're weak.
- Yeah.
But you know, maybe it
isn't that bad after all,
having to admit to yourself
that you're a loser.
- Yeah, but I refuse to be
some kind of ordinary loser.
- Then I guess we
must be the losers
that have one last blast.
- Not good enough.
The kind of loser I
want to be is the kind
that dies biting the
throat out of his opponent.
- Hmm.
(caws)
(soft music)
(booms)
- [Takayanagi] Guess
it's about 70%.
- I doubt the rib that boy
injured is fully healed yet.
So stop being so
reckless, Takayanagi.
- What, what are
you talking about?
This was nothing,
see, I'm all (moans)
- Takayanagi-senpai,
- [Maya] That's exactly why
I told you not to do that.
- [Souichi] Come on,
pull yourself together.
- [All] Hmm?
- Yo Senpai, it's been a while.
Its embarrassing to admit this
but if we were to take on the
executive council right now
they'd take us out before
we could even scratch 'em.
- You know what they
say, haste makes waste,
- Todo Academy freshmen,
Souichiro Nagi.
- Bob Makihara, same class.
- [Both] As of today
we're the new members
of the Juken club.
(gasps)
- Souichiro-sama.
- Give me three months,
you give me three
months and I promise
I'll be stronger
than all you guys.
- And then we'll kill Ryuuzaki.
And crush the executive
council while we're at it.
- Hmm.
You can't swallow the spit
that's already been spat on you.
But I like your spirit,
you're more than welcome.
- [Takayanagi] And so on this
day, what will later be known
as the strongest
Juken club ever,
gathered for the first time.
- [Ryuuzaki] What?
What do you mean?
- I just told you, Maya
Natsume has sent a request
asking that the expulsion
of Souichiro Nagi
and Bob Makihara please be
revoked as soon as possible.
- (growls)
that bitch.
Who the hell does she
think she's trying to fool?
- In addition to
that she told us
that she has allowed
the two of them
to join the Juken club.
(growls)
This drastically goes
against our president's will.
- Natsume.
- I'd like to hear
the executive council's
decision Ryuuzaki.
- I'm tired of you taking
the executive council
so lightly, Natsume.
The decision is going to be no,
those two have been expelled.
The decision has already
been decided upon.
In this school
the decisions made
by the executive council
are perfect and absolute.
There's no way they
can be overturned.
And now you want them
to join the Juken club,
forget it, you know we'd never
allow something like that.
You understand what I'm saying?
Are you even listening to me?
Don't you ignore me.
- Very interesting.
I can't help thinking maybe,
you're afraid of those two.
- Careful now, don't go
thinking that you're always
going to be stronger
than me, Natsume.
(blasts)
Now look at you all decked
out in the school uniform
that's quite unusual, how
about I char it up a bit?
I'll roast you so nicely
that people are gonna think
you got a tan.
(laughs)
- Ryuuzaki's using the
chi of fire from the chain
of wood, fire,
earth, gold, water.
Hmm, his chi is much more
refined than it used to be.
The one's that should be
defeating you right now
are those boys and
not me, but being
that I'm still in training,
I'm far from perfect.
(grunts)
I'm not so much of a
saint that I can just turn
the other cheek, far too
much has happened already.
Come on, the only thing
I need to take you out
is this little branch.
(growls)
- You sure about that?
You may regret
that when your body
is filled with holes, Natsume.
(dramatic music)
(groans)
- This guy knows Capoeira.
- What is strength?
What drives me to
becomes stronger?
I think I know now.
(grunts)
(groans)
- Loser, (laughs)
he said (groans)
(laughs)
- Strength is not
something you can compare
with other people,
a heart that seeks
to become stronger,
is not the same as
someone seeking strength.
Most people are aware of
the fact that they are weak
probably more so than
anyone else around them.
And because they know this.
(shouts)
Because they are aware,
people can become
stronger, right?
(wind rustles)
(sings in foreign language)
- [Souichi] The word impossible
is not in my dictionary
so let's create a camp that
challenges you to become
the strongest guy ever, next
episode of Tenjho Tenge,
Suspicion.
I gotta admit, those
sisters are damn hot.