When it happened, I honestly
thought it was over for me.
But then there she was,
the girl who gave
me another shot at life.
No, cut it out! You guys
have got it all wrong, I swear!
Oh my god! You're some
kinda Magical Girl now!
But my human life,
and my dignity, are over!
You see. Now I'm a zombie.
Oh, and somehow a
Magical Garment Girl, too?
Class, please note the
emphasis on the word "very".
The author carefully...
Turns out my life,
or unlife, wasn't over.
Cause now, If I make
an ass outta myself like that,
at least I can erase
everybody's memories.
I guess becoming a Magical
Garment Girl isn't all bad.
But don't get me wrong,
if I got to pick my afterlife,
this would definitely be
one of the last on the list.
It's been a week since I
ran into that Megalo thing
and there haven't
been any more since.
That may be a perk to
being a "super tranny",
but man, I hate that outfit.
I wonder if I could use it
to sneak into the
girls locker room?
I guess it's time to give
Haruna's cooking a whirl.
You're lucky you're dead, cause
my rolled omelet's to die for!
Um, I had some left over,
so it's not like I made
this just for you, okay?
I'm not expecting much,
but who knows,
maybe she's the next
Iron Chef or something.
Uh. Well, it does
look interesting.
Now let's see what
kinda side dishes
she whipped up to go with it.
I guess she's not big on
the whole "variety" thing.
Ah, well, she is
new to this world.
This could be the first
lunch she's ever made.
Hope this thing's not
full of raw eggs.
Hey, so whatcha got
in the ol' bento today,
your typical sad
white rice? Holy crap!
Did you make
all those yourself?!
Well, yeah, since I
live alone, of course I did!
Oh my god my mouth is in heaven!
Oh, b.s.
They can't be that good.
They're amazing! Everyone!
You've gotta try
these omelettes Ayumu has!
They're incredible!
Trade you a fried pie for one!
I'm home!
And, so?
So did I enjoy eating your box?
Not bad for your first time.
I am a genius, you know.
Well you might wanna harness
that brain power a bit more.
Like thinking up
some side dishes.
A man can't live
on eggs alone ya know.
Shut up. Eggs are the
only thing I can cook
so you'll take what you can get!
That's really all
you know how to cook?
That's right, and I'm hungry!
Well, if you can make omelettes,
how come you didn't
make any for dinner?
'Cause I'd rather have something
yummier that you cooked.
Alright, I get it.
I'll get dinner started.
Dig in!
Wow, so this is kimchi pork?
I can't wait to devour it!
In our world, creepy laughs
are kinda bad manners.
Oh! I guess I'm
still acting like
someone from another world, huh?
Or just plain stupid.
Hey!
Oh, of course!
I got so hungry
waiting for you, stud.
Got anything I could
put in my mouth?
Oh you bet I do!
After we're done
with that, dreamboat,
I'll scrub you all
over in the bath.
Yeah, sure, rub-a-dub-dub
in the tub sounds fun!
What's wrong with you?
Fresh outta those.
I hope this helps my powers.
I don't think they're back yet.
I'm gonna need seconds.
So give me more of
your tasty white stuff!
No prob.
Come on! Shake a leg!
Hurry it up!
Alright! I'm going
as fast as I can.
Um, since you mentioned your
powers still haven't fully
come back, does that mean you
plan on staying here longer?
Sure does, so make
with the thirds, dude!
Oh! Can I have some more of your
delicious food, you sexy chef?
I'll be happy to give
you whatever you want,
so just name it!
In that case, I'd like
some miso soup, please.
Sure thing!
Sorry. Come again?
Miso soup.
Another one, huh? Great.
Delicious.
Bossy like the others,
but at least gives compliments.
Anyone mind telling
me who this chick is?
Actually, I kinda assumed
she was one of your friends.
So do you know who she is?
Okay, I'll go ahead and
take your silence as a "no."
Listen lady.
No one here knows who you are,
so would ya mind
introducing yourself?
Very well then.
Since you insist.
My name's Seraphim.
Whoa, you're an angel?
I guess I've met
weirder things lately.
I am a practitioner of
the Swallow-Return Strike.
My special skill is the
Swallow-Return Strike.
And my hobby is the
Swallow-Return Strike!
Well if you're that into it,
it must be pretty
freakin awesome then.
What brings you to this dump?
I was dispatched
here to enlist the aid
of Lady Eucliwood Hellscythe.
I've been charged
to not only do that,
but accompany Lady Hellscythe
back to my village as well.
And where's that?
The village of Ninjas.
Oh, I was totally
about to guess that.
So, if you're from there,
does that mean you're a ninja?
Yes. And actually more.
I'm a vampire ninja.
A vampire ninja?
And how am I supposed
to kick out a Vampire Ninja?
Uhhh...
Tell me, what exactly
is the relationship
between you and Lady Hellscythe?
Well, you could say I'm
her guardian or as she calls me,
my big stud!
Aww man! Why couldn't
she call me her big stud?
Then please allow me to
become your servant, too.
You may address me as
"Sera" if you wish, my Lady.
Please reconsider.
I am far more intelligent
and capable than
this lowly maggot.
Just because I'm being
nice and feeding you,
doesn't mean
I'm some kinda boob.
Since it appears
you're the stubborn type
who will not surrender
their post willingly, maggot,
I suggest we take this matter
up somewhere more private.
I'm real sorry
to disappoint you,
but I make it a habit
not to fight girls.
You will, and I shall
make perfectly clear to
Lady Hellscythe which of us is
more suited to be her servant.
Hey.
Relax I've got this one.
I wasn't offering to help.
I just want you to get
this thing started already.
I'm sure I'm not the
first to tell you this,
but you're a real piece of work.
Taking your eyes off
me is dangerous, maggot.
If you think you're just
gonna be able to kill me
I've got some pretty
disappointing news for you.
If completing my mission
means killing you, then I shall.
Even if it is a bit trickier
seeing that you're
one of the undead.
How did you know that?
Ninjas know everything.
Whoa!
I'll slice you until
you're incapable of fighting.
Um, you do know that
zombies can feel pain, right?
Spare yourself and yield.
Sorry, no can do because
I was asked to send you away.
Alright, so be it!
I'm a practitioner of the
Swallow-Return Strike.
My special skill is the
And my hobby?
That's right!
The Swallow-Return Strike!
Brutal!
If that pitiful
excuse was all the fight
that you could muster up.
Then you're not worthy of being
Lady Hellscythe's servant.
You undead maggot!
Oh, man!
I misjudged her! She's tough!
Damn, I'm giving it my all.
But I'm still barely able to
dodge those strikes of hers.
Had enough?
What the?
Two hundred percent power!
Kinda hard to use that
Swallow-Return Strike
of yours now, isn't it?
You maggot!
Okay, ninja! I'll show
you what a "maggot" can do!
Swallow Return Strike!
Eight Slashes!
But...
How? It's because I'm a zombie.
You beat me. I now
understand why Lady Hellscythe
accepted you to be her servant.
Done?
Yes. Now that you've defeated
me, I shall return home.
You're being a
good sport about it.
It's simply my pride as
a vampire ninja. Farewell.
Seraphim the vampire ninja.
I don't know if I
could beat her again.
And I really don't want
another throwing star
in my head, either.
We're home!
Now wait a minute, what the
hell are you doing here?
You told us a few minutes
ago that you were going home.
And as you can
clearly see I did.
Oh, so then by "home"
you didn't mean your home,
but my home, huh?
Who gives a crap?
You shouldn't even be here
because you lost
the fight, remember!
I fail to see your point.
What about that whole "pride
as a vampire ninja" thing?
Fulfilling one's duty,
no matter what it takes,
is the pride of a ninja.
I'm dyin' to know that too.
Therefore, my Lady,
I am fully willing
to become the servant of
this truly repugnant maggot.
If that will allow me
to stay here by your side.
Well, if you wanna
be my servant,
then that means you have
to be at my beck and call
and do whatever I say.
Like wear a sexy maid
outfit and get me up.
I'm here to arouse you, Master.
And give me baths, too!
Well, Master, is there anything
else you'd like me to scrub?
Yes!
First things first! From now on,
you'll address me as "Master!"
No. That's repugnant.
Um. Then how about something
like "My Liege"
or "My Smokin' Hot Lord?"
No. I shall call you "maggot!"
Why do you keep calling me that?
Maybe 'cause it rhymes with--
Shut up!
Yep, this is gonna be a long,
painful afterlife, isn't it?
Nice. I finally
get a moment's peace.
What have you done?
Something painful's
caused Lady Hellscythe
to guard her emotions.
What are you, a
vampire-ninja-psychologist now?
No, but I am a woman,
far more in tune
with the female heart
than a maggot like you.
She's not much of a talker.
That's just how she is.
There's more to it than that.
Some reason why she's
closed her emotions off.
Smirk all you want.
But the way she is now,
she'll be disinclined to
help me, meaning I stay here.
Unless you find a way to
change her current state.
Her current state, huh? Well...
It's the same one she was in
when we first met a month ago.
I couldn't take my eyes off her.
I wanted to break
the ice somehow
but couldn't decide
on what to say or do.
So tell me, do you
believe that UFOs are real?
Oh, crap, what was I thinking?!
Of all the things to say to a
pretty girl, that's what I say?
Gotta salvage this situation
and do something cool!
But what? I know, break dance!
Hey! Girl! Yo, yo, yo!
Check out this bro,
dancin' on the flo', yo!
I got a pure heart,
and loved ya from the start!
I'll drink to ya shawty,
so why not take part?
Break it dow--
Serves you right, dummy!
If you'd quit earlier,
she might have just
thought you were an idiot,
but now she knows that you are!
Oh, don't worry.
What kinda person
do I look like?
Yeah, I guess I do!
Even though she didn't
utter a single word,
she still had a lot
to say, or write, I mean.
I was usually always a spazz
around girls, but not this time.
Well, aside from the UFO talk
and the painful
break dancing, that is.
Bye! If you're sure ya
don't want me to walk ya home,
then just promise
you'll be careful. Goodnight!
How awesome is it that I
spoke to a really cute girl
and she seemed
interested in me, too?
Blood?
Oh no...
I better call an ambulance!
And the police, too!
Somebody help!
What do I do? Oh, hell!
I must be nuts. I'm no hero.
What the hell can I do?
And what happens
when I find the killer?
Oh shit, I'm in way over
my head. But I gotta help her.
Her scream sounded like
it came from upstairs.
Uh! What's going on?
I can't move!
I guess now I know what
happens when I find the killer.
Oh god. This hurts so bad.
Oh, you. Am I still alive?
So. You're the angel of death.
You did, huh? Who are you?
This is way too weird!
I don't understand!
Am I alive or dead?
That's how my
zombie life began,
and Eu has lived
with me ever since.
I know she referred to me as her
"servant" to Sera, but I wonder,
is that all she
considers me to be,
or does she think
of me as something more?
Ayumu! Seconds!
Now! C'mon, hurry up!
Okay I heard ya the first time.
More miso soup, maggot.
Oh, of course. Hey!
You could be nicer to someone
who's taken you into their home.
In my life,
niceties are rare things.
And why's that?
For the simple fact
that war has been waged
in the vampire ninja village
for one hundred years now.
Oh?
That sort of thing does tend to
make someone less than friendly.
Sorry you've had it so tough.
Do not presume to empathize
with me, you zombie maggot!
Does she have to
keep calling me that?
Oh, here, Ayumu,
got another box for you today.
Wait, don't tell me, it's all
rolled omelettes again, right?
Thanks for ruining
the joke ya jerk!
Do you think maybe
you could just make my lunch
without thinking of
it as being a big joke?
Nevermind, the stuff you
packed yesterday was so good,
you can do whatever ya want.
Oh, well of course you liked it!
But I really don't need
your permission to be a genius!
Stop laughing, it's repugnant!
It certainly is.
Geez!
Um, Haruna, not to
complain, but do you think
maybe you could also put in
some white rice with my lunch?
Look, either suck it up and
eat what ya get. Or drop dead.
What! Why not?
Aw Relax, she was
just messin with me,
she wasn't being serious.
Come on,
she wouldn't hurt a fly.
Don't touch me! Put your
hands on me again, pervert,
and you're gonna
friggin' die, ya hear me?
What'd ya do that for?
Eu...
Eat it.
I'm sure you'll love it!
Terrific. It had
to start raining.
How weird. It's almost as if
the sky's crying on Eu's behalf.
And more soup
for me, too, maggot.
Way to spoil the moment!
You popped up quickly.
I'm a ninja.
Yeah, but your
name's "Seraphim."
That's another word for angel.
I'm a vampire.
Yeah, I know, but---
You don't know anything,
and if you insist on
babbling on like this,
I will have to give you
another taste of my blade.