S'up, guys?
Long time no see...
Good to have you all back...
Sorry things got a little
crazy last episode...
Par for the course, though,
if you know what I'm sayin'...
But...
as you can see, the atmosphere's
a bit more tranquil--
Whatcha doin' Ayumu...?
You filming a reality show?
Don't touch that, dork!
You lookin' at me, tough guy?
Ya must be 'cause there ain't
no one else around
around to gawk at.
Cool!
This is like the most
awesome show ever!
Of course...
You putrefying maggot farm...
A hidden camera?
What...?!
How the hell's it hidden
when it's right out here
in the open?!
That's even more disgusting...!
So not only are we
being objectified...
we're expected to be
on board with it.
It's okay, I'm kinda
used to miscommunication.
I can hear you blathering...
Don't twist my disapproval
into hentai fodder.
So...
As you can see, things are
fairly amicable around here...
Sure, we bust each other's balls
like its goin' outta style,
but we do it with love...
Which, I should mention,
is a far cry from the way
things used to be
in this house--
Time to walk down memory lane!
Get a move on, Yukinori!
Right!
Let's do this!
Kanami!
Heads up!
It's all you, Tae!
On it!
Swallow-Return Strike!
Oh, son of a...!
'Kay, best two out of three!
This is what
I'm talking 'bout...
Nothin' like an indoor pool
for livin' large.
Hey!
Eyes front and center,
perv...!
My chest would be grateful.
Sorry, but...
Have they always
been that perky?
It's called a push-up bra.
Well, yeah, it's just...
I mean, given the
raw materials and all...
It's fashion, Ayumu.
Look closer...
Her ta-tas are small...
But they're not all
a well-designed bra
has to work with...
It's rallying the troops
from all sides of her top.
That's cold.
Chicks have to do
what they can to fill out.
Preachin' to the choir.
That she's gone from a five to a
temporary seven is a testament--
Shut up...!
The only five here
is your manhood!.
Ugh!
My chest is fine!
Now don't get violent...
And don't ever take
what he says to heart.
Neckwear-mancer?
Don't stare at me
like that, stud...
You know how bashful I am.
Huh?.
Oh...
Sorry, I just
kinda lost myself.
Jerk face...
Bleh...!
Whatevs.
Hiya, cutie.
I'll take a medium smothered
in sprinkles -and when I say
smothered, hon, I mean I don't
want to see a millimeter
of the head exposed.
Huh?
I'm coming!
I swear.
Only you could
sink on a kickboard.
Please Forgive me...
I don't know what I did,
but I know it was wrong.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I'm sure that whatever god
watches over this pool
is just jealous of how good
a swimmer you are, ya know?
Oh, yes!
Sera, on the other hand,
has a built-in failsafe
against drowning.
Ayumu...
Hey, Tomonori.
Is it just me,
or is this place like the
perfect spot for a honeymoon?
Uh...
I guess?
Man...
Look at you...
It's not even fair, FYI...
What do vampire ninjas do
that you all look like models?
Well...
It's all about
training like a boss!
Um...
Random question...
Are you...
A Big Gulp or
tea cup kinda guy?
Excuse me?!
Aw Damn it...!
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
You kidding me...?
I'm having fun,
you should try it sometime!
I'm hunting the
Loch Ness Monster!
Strong.
Very strong.
So the maggot's befriended
a shutterbug...
Whatever is a self-respecting
girl to do...
about this
unfortunate infestation?
I'm tellin' ya: Nessie's here.
This pool is connected through
a series of subterranean rivers
to Scotland's Loch Ness.
There are more things
in heaven and earth
than are dreamt of
in your philosophy.
Yeah.
My adorable little roommate's
living proof of that.
After all, the Benzaiten
shrine feeds into
the Fuji Five Lakes...
so this place might actually
be connected to any number
of Scotland's lochs.
Wow, you really think so?
Please be careful
what you say...
This one'll believe anything.
Sold!
Follow me if you
wanna bag a serpent!
I'll pass.
Knock yourself out tryin'
to nab a fictional plesiosaur;
I've got a swimming
lesson to give.
Fine!
And boom...
Into the sunset.
Do what?
No way.
Answer me this.
What do you think of her?
Well, then there's no reason why
the two of you can't be friends.
She's easier to warm up
to than you think.
Target acquired!
Huh...?
What now?!
Come on, Nessie!
What the hell is she doing...?
Okay, just so all of you know,
there' no way that's
a real sea monster.
Settle down, pretty girl.
Hey...!
Don't be such an idiot!
That's not Nessie,
it's a blow up toy!!
Ayumu!
Yeah, what is it?
Wanna kick it with me?
Kind of in the middle of some--
Oh, yeah?
Aw, son of a...!
I gotta go, sorry...
See ya!
Great, I take my eyes off her
for a second and she's gone!
Um, Ayumu...
Holy crap...
Could, you...
oil me up, maybe...
please?
I'm...
sorta busy...
I see...
So, no?
Her skin is delicate.
No...
No, I can't...
I wouldn't be right...
I've got to...
Do...
Something...
Else...
I forget what, but...
Oh god...
Maybe just a quick slather.
Good girl.
Way to go, chica.
Haruna...
Oh no.
Are you man enough
to take a dip with me?
But I've already
wasted so much ...
Is that so...?
You're not tempted?
Damn it!
I keep getting distracted!
No!
She might fall in too.
Come now...
What could possibly be wrong?
This...
sounds weird...
But I have to leave you for Eu.
I see how it is.
I'm a party girl...
The easy pickin's you come
to when you're in need of
a distraction.
What?
If that's how things stand...
I'll have to brave
the water alone.
Uh-oh...
Wardrobe malfunction
in the works.
Can't let her walk off untied...
Have to fix it...
Without her noticing...
Okay, it's not what
you think it is!
I was just trying--
You vile, simpering,
booger-twirling troglodyte
of a maggot farm!
Float like a death's head moth,
sting like when you pee,
you bitch!
Uh...
Why am I dressed like this?
Good, you're awake.
Um, hi?
Get off me!
I'm drowning here!
Wait, is that...
Of course.
Observe the fate of sexual
deviants who presume to snap
covert pictures
of girls underwater...
Similar punitive measures are
in store for bikini snatchers.
Come on!
No mercy...
Swallow...
Return Strike!
That's it, kiddo; let loose...
Oh, teenagers.
Avast, me hearties!
Thar she blows!
Hey, when did you become
a Loch Ness Monster?
When do you think...?
Ugh.
Get me out of
this stupid thing.
Killjoy.
So what's your deal...?
Why're you acting like this?
Oh I dunno...
I just...
wanted quality time
with Neckwear-mancer.
Now I get it...
Haruna wasn't really thinkin'
she'd find Nessie here.
She just wanted
to hang out with Eu.
That explains the weirdness
with everyone else, too;
they didn't want me
to butt in on the bonding.
Goofballs.
That's cool and all...
But, I mean why
disguise your motives?
Well...
Because, butthole...
I'm embarrassed.
Hey-hey...!
Good news...
Haruna's actually all about
bein' buddy-buddy with ya.
And there you have it...
Friends doin' what friends do:
drivin' each other nuts.
Out of love, of course.
What's the old saying
about death and taxes?
You know the one, right?
Two things in life
that are certain.
I'd add to that list a few
observations of my own, though.
Stuff like homework, dropping
chopsticks on the floor,
stepping on thumbtacks,
getting your prints all over
a piece of scotch tape, blisters
from breakin' in new shoes.
Etcetera.
Sure, sounds like
a parade of suck when
you start naming 'em
all off, but I dunno...
In a way they're comforting.
Hey...
You really need to work on
building up some non-violent
communication techniques.
Now's not the time
to whine; what have you got?
'Scuse me??
That's what I get for
expecting a half-way house
forcoprophagic beetles
like you to look at a calendar.
Oh crap.
Eu's birthday is tomorrow?
Yes.
But I've got it covered...
We're throwing her
a big surprise party.
Nice...!
And surprisingly thoughtful...!
We've got to get Tomonori and
Orito in on this thing, too.
Don't forget yours truly...!
If anybody knows how to milk
a surprise, it's a genius.
So...
like, what are we doin' in
the way of birthday presents?
You're on your own.
Me...?
I'm giving her something
she'll love: a new accessory...
And it's only fair I warn you,
whatever you come up with,
you don't want to follow me.
Confident, huh?
Would that be an invitation
to some one-upmanship?
Whatever gives you hope
in the eleventh hour, maggot.
Challenge accepted.
I will not be ignored!!!
Whoa...!
You're inviting us to a party?!
Yup
I haven't been asked to a social
function since kindergarten!
Come on...
Hey.
Don't cry...
You're a late bloomer.
So,,, I can come too?
Yeah...
Of course.
Oh...
Thank you!
I totally need to
go shopping for a gift.
Hey, uh...
What cup size are you?
Oh, I'm an E...
Wait...!
I didn't meant to answer you!
Calm down...
I'm just using you as a proxy...
So if you're an E,
Eu's probably...
I'm so gonna rack you!
Wack me?
Rack!
Like rack your balls!
Hey, I'd be cool with that, too.
The items requested
by Seraphim.
Unless you prefer me
to force-feed them to you,
I suggest you take
them off my hands.
Uh...
Oh-kay...
You are hereby entrusted
with ingredients sacred
to Vampire Ninja tradition
so don't screw it up...
Or sneak a bite.
Not a problem.
Help me!
I'm being sexually harassed!
Take my word for it, perv:
this isn't sexual!
She's a man-eater!
A man-eater!!!
Which means you'd have a real
problem, if you were a man!
Hope Eu gets
a kick outta all this.
So, uh...
Got Anything in mind for dinner
or are we just wingin' it?
Distract Lady Hellscythe however
you can till the house is ready.
We'll need some time,
so lay it on thick.
Tell you what...
Why I don't I let you
decide tonight?
Let me give it some thought...
Pot stew would be
absolutely divine!
What kind of
pot stew ya like?
Let's see...
The kind that's layered
like the strata of hell...
Each infernal level more
harrowing than the one
that came before...
A horrifying hodgepodge
Dante, at his best,
would scoff to invent.
Not gonna lie:
you make it sound delicious...
What's with the look?
Something wrong?
Play it off.
Ruin the surprise
and it's my ass.
Huh...
Totally slipped my mind.
Hey...
I was joking back there
about letting your big day
slip my mind; in fact we've been
workin' on something for you.
Let's get to the house and I'll
show you what I'm talkin' about.
It's a birthday, not Halloween!
Haruna, I swear to god!
"If we don't proceed carefully,
we may never get back out.
I told you we geniuses
know how to milk a surprise!
Is Sera in on this?
Leaf Lady's happily doing
her part -in the kitchen.
Treat your taste buds to my
Periodic Table Double-melt...!
High in thallium,
low in sodium.
This is nuts...!
It's a party!
Oh my, someone's gonna be
turned into sausage,
'less they can
find the way out.
Hardy har...!
Is this your idea of a joke?!
If you don't want to be smushed,
massage the sweet spot
with your index finger.
I see it!
Boo-ya!
Well done!
Son of a...
This isn't funny anymore!
Now then: which rope to ascend?
The silver?
The golden?
Or the Copper?
Damn it.
Ugh...
I am gonna ram my foot
so far up your--
Well done again!
Seriously...?!
This is getting real old!
Your next challenge--
Forget it; I'm not
pushing any more buttons.
Right on the money!
Screw this.
What is it...?
This isn't your fault...
No...
Haruna's just a moron.
Cheer up.
Well, we made it...
Barely...
Do me a favor...
See to it the rest of
your day is awesome-sauce.
Yo... Hope we're not
running behind--
Welcome to the party.
Dude, seriously...!
You're sparkling
like a Mormon vampire!
Hey, I thought it'd be
appropriate because birthdays
are a celebration of survival.
Fair enough...
but...
a little bit extreme.
Look, thing is,
Magical Garment Girls
are always fighting Megalos...
It's hard...
Make it from one birthday
to the next and you're lucky...
Like, really lucky...
Can't expect it
to hold forever...
I mean, it's only a matter of
time before your number's up.
It may seem lame to you guys,
but the way our culture sees it,
is birthdays are just a
reminder of your mortality.
Wow, leave it to you
to bring the room down...
Can we switch gears, please?
Hey!
It's time for some yummies!
A special meal
for the birthday girl!
That looks weird.
Have you never
eaten shabu-shabu?
It's like sex.
I am not eating
anything remotely like that
with you around!
Okey-dokey, prezzie time!
Yay!
Start with, the one from Sera!
Next up, open mine.
Bazonga-X!
You, are an all-occasion perv.
Oh, and I guess you got her
something better?
Well, duh!
Ta-da!
You can never have too much
of this stuff, am I right?
Actually that was
pretty kick-ass.
Yeah...
You're always using
that little teacup...
So I thought maybe you'd like
some variety for your beverages.
Glad you're pleased.
I'm likin' the smile.
Just out of curiosity...
Who's birthday gift was your
favorite out of the bunch?
Yeah!!!
Wow.
Thanks a lot.
Alright.
Time for cake.
We're all unlucky
sometimes, sure...
Hell, every now and then
things get so rough
it's all you can do
just to carry on.
Who hasn't been there, right?
But birthdays are special.
They should always see
you tilted to catch the wind;
give you the kind of smile
that makes people wonder
what you're up to.
So, uh...
Exactly how many years
we celebratin' here?
Um, how old are you,
Lady Hellscythe?
Sweet dreams, everyone.
Thank you all for making
this the first birthday
I've been happy to celebrate.
But a lady never
reveals her age.