Alright, scram!
Guys, look!
I found his right arm!
And I his left leg.
Aren't I lucky?
His head!
I find it hard to believe.
But he looks even
more repugnant this way.
Give 'em a break.
He is a zombie after all.
Why ain't he moving?
Yes, good question.
Leave it to me.
Hey, that ain't your job!
It's his bride's.
So get outta my way!
That's it! It's on, you heifer!
I've known Ayumu way
longer...
Hands off my man...
How typical.
Well, in that case.
I guess I'll have to
use the secret medicine.
It's been handed down
in my village for ages.
Wait, this isn't medicine.
I think I must have accidentally
grabbed a bottle of
secret poison by mistake.
I couldn't have
asked for better weather.
A sky full of clouds.
It's almost perfect.
What a beautiful day for dying.
Why won't he wake up?
I think I know why.
With Lady Hellscythe gone he
feels he has no more purpose.
Haruna?
The reason why the
neckwear-mancer left
is 'cause you've
got no backbone!
No, I-I do.
No, you don't,
you repugnant maggot!
You could have gone after Lady
Hellscythe, but you didn't.
I couldn't because,
I had to save Haruna.
I'd never marry a guy like you.
Tomonori?
Bye, Ayumu.
Wait!
We're leaving
you behind.
Hold on!
Have fun stayin
here forever, loser.
No, things can't end like this!
Hey! Don't leave! Come ba...
Excuse me.
Would this happen to be
the residence of Ayumu Aikawa?
I just don't understand it.
Why isn't he waking up?
You're obviously troubled,
not only by his condition,
but by something else
as well, aren't you, dear?
Um, well.
It's okay, you can tell me
what's vexing you so much.
I've always encouraged
you and your classmates
to speak whatever is
on your mind, Haruna,
Class Refrain-Rising
Student Number Six hundred,
thirty four million, five
hundred twenty-six thousand.
Well, if I hadn't let
that bomb get attached
to me like that then
he would still be here!
This whole thing
is all my fault!
This young man isn't a
magic user, but it's apparent
that he's managed to weave quite
a spell over you, hasn't he?
Uh, I guess so.
And by working his magic,
he's made a big
difference in your life.
So now it's only fair
that you return the favor
and do the same for him, 'kay?
It's so quiet.
No one else is here.
Maybe I should just close
my eyes and sleep for awhile.
What kinda sissy-talk is that?
You're just a weenie
who can't come through
when things get tight.
Haruna?
You really think you're gonna
solve your problems
by doing even less?
You lazy ass. Only
people who've done something
worthwhile deserve to sleep!
Yeah, and you haven't!
Well, then what
am I supposed to do?
You should disappear.
Yeah, disappear!
You're a loser as
a human and a zombie,
so why bother sticking around?
Yeah. Why?
And if you do it,
life'll be a lot easier for you.
Then that's it. I'll do it.
I'll just disappear.
Do it! Disappear!
Disappear.
Disappear! Disappear!
Disappear! Disappear! Disappear!
The only thing that's
gonna disappear are you fakes!
Why are you
doing this, you moron?
I thought she was the
one person in the world
that cared for me,
but I was wrong.
The rest of you guys
can get outta here, too!
Let me get this straight.
You honestly think that
the neckwear-mancer
doesn't like you?
Well, if she did, why didn't she
take my hand when I offered it?
Stupid butthole!
Don't you know that she's
always considered you to be...
Look. If you
want to be more than
just friends with
the neckwear-mancer,
all you have to do is tell her!
When I reached out to her, she
chose to leave with him instead.
Honestly, I don't
think I have what it takes
to change the way she feels.
Man up and grow a pair!
Just be direct with her, like
I'm being with you right now!
But if I do that, won't
she think I'm being a pest?
Oh, so I guess you're
saying I'm a pest, then, huh?!
No! Please don't hit me!
You gotta come back to us.
Everyone needs you,
especially me.
You mean that?
Aw, forget it, I take
back everything I said.
If all you're gonna
do is just mope around
and feel sorry for yourself,
then you can stay holed up
in here forever for all I care!
Geez, Haruna.
You don't even hold
back in my dreams, do you?
You know me. I mean
business all the time.
Looks like I need
to cheer you up now.
But yelling and kicking
isn't really my style.
Yeah, I know.
Aha, you see,
I knew you'd be able
to cast some special
magic of your own.
Sarasvati.
I think you're going
to be needing that.
Check it out, Leaf Lady,
I finally got Ayumu up!
Ayumu. Do you see it?
Yeah. And this is all his doing.
Everything that's transpiring
is because of you, my dear.
Tragic. Because you
will not allow me to die,
I have no choice
but to destroy this city.
Thank you for coming.
It's time to go home, 'kay?
Come on. Everyone's waiting.
Yeah, it is. But,
it just isn't the same.
It's no fun without
you being there with us.
I've never
thought that about you!
Oh how touching.
But ultimately, pointless.
Don't interrupt them, butthole!
What the hell are you
trying to pull here anyway?
I had our friend
summon a Megalo.
She may not say much, but she's
actually quite upset right now.
Don't you just love
that look on her face?
You're a real sicko!
This city and all
who live within it
will perish in moments.
Just because you stubbornly
refuse to grant my deepest wish.
Think of all the needless
deaths that will happen.
You could prevent them, though.
All you have to do is kill me.
If not, millions will die.
Such a poor, conflicted soul.
She does truly hate me.
But she hates killing much more.
She doesn't realize
it's the kindest thing
she could do for me.
Please give me the only gift
that would end my suffering.
Ya know, I feel sorry for you.
Why?
It's obvious. You think
you've got her figured out,
but you're not even close.
The only thing that can seal
the gates of the underworld
is the tune
of a vampire ninja,
played by one with
a specific attribute.
She must have Lady Hellscythe's
blood flowing within her.
You are that vampire ninja.
But I've sinned.
Yes, I know, you have
gone against vampire ninja law.
Nevertheless, this is something
that only you can do, Seraphim.
Only I can do.
Very well, then.
May my song bring peace to
all of the wandering spirits.
When I first attained
immortality, I was so happy.
I really thought living
forever would be a blessing.
But it turned out to
be a monotonous curse.
You'll learn that soon enough.
Dying may be painful, but
living day after day without end
is even more unbearable. That's
why I need Eucliwood's help.
Still the same as ever.
I guess I'll just have to keep
hurting people until
you change your mind
since you've left
me no other choice.
Why don't I start with him?
Perhaps that will
persuade you to grant my wish.
No way, asshole!
Try all you want, but you won't
be able to lay a hand on me.
There are just
too many of them!
Resilient, isn't it?
The body of a zombie
can take so much abuse.
Pipe down! C'mon,
we're gettin' to the good part!
Say what?
Eucliwood. Watch closely now.
Because you refuse to help me,
your friend here is
going to suffer for it.
Ayumu! Let's transform together!
Is that really even possible?
According to
Mystletainn, it totally is!
C'mon, let's lay some
smack down! Whattaya say?
I say, "hell yes!"
Ready?
Nomobuyo. Oshi. Hashitawa!
Dokeda. Gunmiicha! Deh Ribura!
Whoa. So I guess we
really can transform together!
Does this mean
you and Mysteltainn
communicate with each other?
Of course! I've been telling
ya since day one I'm a genius!
That mist is gonna be a problem.
Can we get rid of it?
I think I know just the thing!
Oh no.
Sounds like you need some help!
Sarasvati. And the others.
Just like back
in the village, huh?
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Yep!
Double Mystletainn Kick!
How quaint. Forgoing magical
power for physical combat.
Wait! That's not a kick!
Now let's give 'em hell!
Right!
This is incredible!
You're getting cuter
and cuter by the minute!
Thanks, so are you!
Oh my god! We are
such little 'ol cutie pies.
Insane.
Ayumu! Promise me you'll
kick that creep's ass, okay?
Haruna!
Four hundred percent power!
Fine, I'll use
five hundred percent!
Six hundred percent power!
Eucliwood's the most
caring soul I've met.
She'd never cause
pain to anyone. So tell me.
Why can't you get that
through your thick skull?
Seven hundred percent!
Still so new
and painfully naïve.
Wait 'til you've
known her as long as I have.
That's exactly what pisses
me off so much about you!
You might have known
her a lot longer than me,
but even so, buddy,
you still don't understand
a damn thing about her!
Eight hundred percent power!
Ever seen her smile?
It can light up the entire room!
But why the hell would
she ever smile at you?
Her smile?
Do you know anything about her?
Do you know
what makes her happy.
Huh? Do you?
What about her favorite food?
Do you have any idea what
that is? You think you know her?
Huh?! You don't know shit!
Using her powers as a
necromancer causes her pain!
A lot! But it
doesn't affect you,
because you don't give a
damn about her life!
But why the hell would you
when you don't even
care about your own?
Someday, you will
come to know the pain
of not being able to die.
It'll happen. Believe me.
But when that time comes,
please, don't blame
Eucliwood for it.
I would never
dream of doing that!
Because she's taught me
that life means a lot more
than just living for
yourself! I'm not like you.
Alone? Definitely not.
Well, Eucliwood,
haven't you seen enough?
Any more living would
be cruel to me. So, please.
This may sound ridiculous,
but I have one last request.
Would you please make me
a penguin? I love penguins.
I'm sorry for
all I've done, Eucliwood.
Promise me you're
not gonna run away again.
Promise me you'll stick around
for good this time, please!
You can't just
keep living in fear
of what could
happen to all of us.
I'll take care of
things no matter what.
You make life worth living!
And my life doesn't mean
anything if you're not in it!
I'm not losing you again!
You can try and fight it,
but I'm not letting you go
until you promise me to stay!
I'm just letting
you know what I want.
Call me selfish,
I don't give a damn!
Maybe you should do
something selfish for a change,
like letting yourself
get close to someone!
I don't believe that!
It's true.
From now on,
no matter what happens,
I'll stay by your side, Ayumu.
I can't guarantee
that it'll be easy.
I can deal with that.
But Ayumu, are you
sure you really want this?
You're positive?
You bet.
Is it selfish of me
to want to stay with you,
even though
I'll more than likely
end up putting you in danger?
No. You deserve to be happy.
I've always wondered
if I could live like this.
I guess we'll find out?
You're hurting me, Ayumu.
Oh! My bad,
sorry 'bout that.
Your wish. Did it come true?
That makes me very happy.
Yes, me too.
Incoming! Look out below!
I just traveled
all over the world!
That mist stuff can
be pretty freaking handy!
Welcome back, Haruna.
Whoa! So, she talks now?
Pretty surprising to hear her
voice for a change, isn't it?
Oh yeah, and she's
got a pretty cute one!
You should talk more.
Yeah, totally!
Duh, why do you
think I said that?
Hey, guys! I won passes
to the Yggdrasil resort!
Oh, hell yes!
We're gonna have
so much fun there!
A resort episode?
Finally! It's swimsuit time!
I don't want to see any
more of your flesh, maggot!
Gonna show some skin!
Gonna get real wet! Oh!
Come on Sera. You don't
even know what you're missing!
I saw you naked, remember?
I can speak.
I never thought I'd be
able to talk to you like this.
At last I can say--
"I love you,
big, strong stud?"
Ayumu, stop being so delusional.
Sorry.
Don't rush things. We have
all the time in the world.
You are a zombie after all.