Boop boop be doo...
Wow!
Hey...
Is this Ayumu speaking?
How are things going?
Honestly, since
we lost Mystletainn,
things are going nowhere fast...
And that's me
being optimistic.
I'm between a rock
and hard place here.
I've got something
that'll brighten your day.
I'll be back!
Whoa!
That's really him!
Killer news, Haruna!...!
It looks like we're actually
gonna get Mystletainn
really soon!
That's awesome!
Hot damn!
I can go to the festival
and not be expected to be
some gender bending icon!
Is it a pride festival?
Ayumu Aikawa was beginning
to get comfortable in the silky,
lacy trappings
of a cross dresser.
Hiding his manhood
had become second nature.
But time moves on, and the
budding fruits of youth ripen,
bursting with sweet,
sticky vitality.
What test will Gaia
place in his lap this time?
Festival...!
Fe-fe-fe-fe-festival!
The menu will be
fried eggs only!
Excuse me.
You, with the hair!
Are we really gonna do
actual SWAT team exercises?
You bet your tight
little tookis we will...!
We're gonna
be shootin' paintballs
outta real live AK-47s!
Trust me, I know Haruna
has no business in front of
a classroom like this...
I mean, "think of
the children."...
But Tomonori thought
she could share her wisdom
as the egg-slayer.
This girl can show you how to
fry your way into a man's heart.
OMG teach me...
please!
Preying on human weakness,
Haruna also put Orito
to work on her social campaign
Because of everything that she
did for the Summer festival,
even I almost got some!
No way!
Now where are we supposed
to get these assault rifles?
Hey, "Miss genius"!
This plan of yours
isn't gonna work.
Are you kiddin',
it's a great idea!
So Ayumu...
Do you have a better idea?
Uhhh...
Ooh ooh!
A "bottomless" café!
Shut up!
I dunno...
Hey...
We could go spooky...!
Sound cool?
I know...
That was lame...
just forget about it.
Love it!
Yeah...
A spooky café...
I'm in!
Me, too!
Pretty cool...
I think that sounds hot.
Okay, but no lame
twinkly vampires.
Alright everyone...
all in favor of Ayumu's
spooky café, gimme an "aye!"
Aye!
Then let's get this
party started!
We'll serve fried eggs of doom!
Now that the theme
has been chosen,
we cut to the day
before the big day.
Festival eve.
I'm outta here.
I'll be coming
before too long ...
I just gotta finish
packin' my little box.
You're gonna
be there again today?
Well, I can't expect to leave
everything up to you losers!
You know what they say,
the more the merrier...
You don't wanna be mean
and play with yourself.
Yeah, okay you won me over...
Well...
Guess I'll see ya up there.
Yupper...!
You should really check out
the school sometime...
They have a a buttload
of cool tools there.
And some decent brains to pick
for advice on making stuff.
I'm out too, don't wait up!
Festival...
Great, now Haruna's
rubbin' off on me.
Oh my god- are you okay, sir?
Yeah...
Nice weather
we're having, eh?
Damn it!
My doctor says I shouldn't try
to break the ice with smalltalk.
I think he needs
a second opinion.
Here...
Take this, kid.
Uh, sure...
but... why?
In time...
You will know the
value of that ring.
Say what?
Damn it!
My doctor says I need
to stop trying to sound like
an action movie mentor.
So do you think that this
cape will work for Dracula?
You're such a creeper.
Um, Ayumu...
Hey, what's up?
I got a couple of hanging things
if you think you can use them.
Sure, that sounds great.
Cool, I can get
more if you want.
Yeah, that would be awesome...
And if you wanna
grab a handful of...
Do you mind...?
You're being way too loud!
The hell is that?
Something I don't have time
to explain to you , dumbass!
Hey Ayumu...
Looks like we're gonna
have to make a run to go
get some more material.
Cool.
Get your hands off,
you molester!
Hey, you're askin for it
by goin' commando.
This is a bra top,
you asshole!
What sorcery be this?
The top has cups built in,
so it's just like wearing a bra.
Oh man!
You are such a tease!
You're a future
syphilis carrier!
You know you love me!
Weird when you
think about it...
But these past few weeks,
things feel like
they're falling into place...
Like I'm starting to get
my groove back, you know?
Prob'ly sounds
stupid coming from me.
I know there's nothing
lamer than a guy who peaks
in high school and
never gets over it...
But being a teenager...
It feels pretty cool right now.
It makes me giggle
like a schoolgirl...
The way all of us kids
are coming together
for something larger
than ourselves...
I feel ya.
When you are raised up high in
victory by comrades who share
the same goal as you...
It is far superior to the depths
of despair you're thrown into
when you've been crushed under
the heel of your mortal enemy.
It carves a trench into your
heart that will never be filled.
No matter how many
centuries you might live.
Are you sure you're
not over-medicating there?
Whoo...!
That's the shiz-nit!
Goodnight.
And I'll just take that
as my cue to leave...
Maybe you should save a little
for some hair of the dog.
Good boy...
fetch.
Get momma some more fishy.
Okay...
now...
where was I?
Oh, hey there.
I hated knowing that you
were up here trying to work
this out all by yourself...
So I came to try
and lend a hand.
Oh yeah?
If you want...
I don't mind...
I mean unless...
You'd rather be
alone or something.
No I'm glad you came...
I could really use
a handy person like you.
You mean it...?
That's sweet of you.
Yeah, of course I mean it...
You're doing me a
humongous favor right now...
So let's knock this sucker out.
Sure!
Do you think we should
slide this guy in right here?
It's like he was
made for that spot!
What if I put
my thing in like this?
Oh yeah!
Well I'm satisfied.
Me too.
I think it looks pretty
pro-fesh, don't you?
Yeah, Definitely...
except for that part.
Uh...
what is it?
Hey, what are you two
still doing here?
Didn't know you were
still here, Mr. Kurisu.
Time to wrap it up
and head home, kids.
Right.
Shall we go?
Mm-hmm...
Ya know...
There's something
different about you lately...
I can't quite put my finger
on what it is exactly...
But people seem
to wanna follow you.
Ah, you're just sayin' that...
But I appreciate it.
No I mean every word of it...
And...
I think tomorrow
is gonna be awesome.
Yeah...
me too...
It'll be fun.
This is what
I've wanted all along...
To be young, full of "life" and
looking forward to another day
Oh my, kids these days
sure are bold.
Especially that one,
he's that transvestite, ya know?
He is?
Is that a boy
he's with or a girl?
They're so wild and freaky.
I'm home.
Wipe that stupid frown
off your face!
We got our friend
Mystletain back!
I said hasta la vista baby...!
But I also said...
I'll be back...!
I'll be back!
Yippee ki yay !!!
Do ya feel lucky, punk?!
Well do ya?
I don't believe it...!
You finally came back!
That's right baby.
I'm back!
I'm so unbelieveably happy
to see you right now!
Good for him ...
he'll be stepping up from
a rotten piece of feces
to one of the flies
that buzzes around it.
Mmmm-hmmmm.
It's time for me to put
on my big girl panties,
rise up and be the man
who can live without shame...!
Gaia has forgiven me!
I can go to that stupid
cultural festival
with my head held high...!
As a brand new man!
Nomobuyo, oshi, hashitawa,
dokeda, gunmiicha, deh ribura!
Behold Gaia...!
Feast your eyes
upon me, world...!
This is who I am!
My name is...
Ayumu Aikawa!
Congratulations
on your restoration!
Thank you very much!
Hey...!
Good morning!
All-right ladies, there are
gona be a lot of people
looking at us today,
so remember to smile
with your mouths and your eyes!
Big smizes all around!
Let's knock 'em dead!
Once again I'm able
to get a fresh start,
shed the skin
of the boy I used to be...
And become
the man I really am.
That is gonna rule, dude!
Once again I spoke too soon...
This is so not me.
I hope you're ready for
the wedding night, sweetie...
I hear the groom's
a real monster!
I never pegged you
as anybody's bride before,
but that Dracula
sure is a lucky guy.
Thanks.
I'm honored.
Though now that I'm seeing it,
but I'm getting a weird
Déjà vu thing going on.
You are such an amazing
cross-dresser I can hardly
believe it's your first time
to put on a dress!
She's right...
And it really brings out
some of your natural beauty...
I'm so jealous...
I would kill to
have legs like those.
You got a tight
little body, sir.
You know I can't
un-hear this stuff.
This is the best
you have ever looked.
You're not even looking at me.
Alright, princess, let's roll.
Where are you taking me?
To my booth, moron!
Huh?
Hold it, ladies!
You can only leave if you're
gonna advertise the goods.
If I really got to choose what
my life would revolve around,
"shame and ridicule" would
not be a recurring theme.
Hey Yucky!
Oh it's you...
We blowin' up or what?
We haven't sold
a single copy yet.
Damn illegal
downloaders, I bet.
Ayumu...
What's going on here?
And why are you
dressed like that?
You guys have a CD?!
These should be
selling like omeletes!
CHA-CHA...
♪ Gonna put my hands
on ya, cha-cha oh yeah! ♪
♪ Hold on a second
you're going too fast ♪
♪ Now gimme dat
donkadonk cha-cha-cha! ♪
♪ Stop it you're hurting me! ♪
Chugga chugga chugga chugga
cha cha cha!
cha cha chikky chikky!
The only place
that music belongs...
Is in a torture chamber!
♪ Now gimme dat
donkadonk cha-cha-cha! ♪
♪ Stop it you're hurting me! ♪
Time to unleash my
amazing marketing skills
on this crowd...
But I'm gonna need some
assistance from you, leaf lady.
Okay.
And from you too,
neckwear-mancer.
Should I be getting scared?
No, but you're bad
for our image, so disappear.
With pleasure.
Now let's sell
this pile of crap!
And how will we do that?
Hey, hold on a second...
I uh...
I kinda need to talk to you.
"I'll be waiting under the tree
behind the school building."
Hmmm...
But no one's here.
And there's no name on it.
So you don't know
who it might be?
No clue...
Thanks a lot for taking
the time to walk with me
and wait for whoever
sent this to show up...
I'd be a nervous
wreck by myself...
That's like practically
the whole reason
I asked you come with me.
Whadda ya mean practically?
Well I mean...
There's another thing that I
wanted to talk to ya about...
If there was some other guy
who had feelings for me...
it wouldn't change the way
I feel about you...
For real...
Listen...
I'm still your wife, and
there ain't no man on earth
that's gonna come
between us, okay?
What the...
Where's this coming
from all of a sudden...?
Wait a second...
this is the spot on campus where
people are supposed to reveal
their romantic
feelings for someone.
Right where we're standing?
That's right...
It's one of those stupid
things that girls say...
If you declare your love
for someone here,
you prob'ly
won't get shot down.
Oh...?
Well then doncha think it's
kind of a weird coincidence
that it's the two of us standing
smack dab in the middle
of the place where people
are supposed to get all mushy
and romantic
and stuff like that?
Oh my gosh is that
what this is about?
I can't believe you really
thought you had to bring me here
just to tell me what your
true feelings are again
when I already know
how you feel about me!
I--!
I didn't--!
I don't--!
I don't understand--!
Gah!
I--!
I didn't--!
Tomonori...?
Hey, are you alright?
Fine okay!
Whatever , I get it...!
You don't have to...
Holy crap!
And that about does it!
I got a surprise for ya'.
Irregularity
detected in matrix.
Self-destruction will
commence in thirty seconds.
I wouldn't not tell you
how to stop that!
Who the hell is this?
Show yourselves!
Oh man, you again?
Eww...
So gross!
My doctor says that I need
to stop trying
to phrase things ironically.
Look...
don't blame yourself
over this kid ...
It's just the
rotten hand I was dealt.
Goddamnit...
My doctor says I should stop
using cliched hero lines, too.
Final countdown commencing...
No...!
Please don't do it!
Use the damn ring!
The ring?
Okay, it's on!
Not on you!
On her!
Geez, you should've
told me that before!
You just got rung!
Hey Tomonori...!
C'mon talk to me.
That ring holds
a great magic...
It's the only item that can
suppress the awesome power
hidden deep inside her...
With this ring,
she will be controlled.
Everything's okay,
I'm right here.
Hey...
Ayumu...
What happened?
Where did this
ring come from...?
I've never seen it before.
Just don't ever
take it off, okay...?
I have no idea why...
But for some reason if you
keep wearing that ring, you-
Oh my freaking god, you actually
got me a real wedding ring!
So this was some
elaborate setup, huh...?
You were the one who sent me
that letter, weren't ya...?
It explains why
we're here at this spot,
but not quite why
you're wearing the dress.
About that...
I wouldn't even know
where to begin.
Oh wow...
To think, even though I was
already technically your wife...
You went the extra step
to give me this
to make it more official?
I just don't know what to say,
I'm so overwhelmed right now.
Take it outta gear
for a sec, I...
Don't say another word
I swear I'm about to die
from embarrassment!
Wait...
Slow down...
Look...
Get a hold of yourself, please!
It's happening too fast!...!
If you're wanting
to seal our wedding vows,
I'm just not ready...!
It needs to be special!
You got it all wrong,
ya dingbat!
Hey dumbass!
Now what??!
We got a Megalo on our hands!
Damn girl,
what you workin' with?
Come on baby doll,
I just wanna know how big
them sweater kittens are.
Oh, monkey likey.
Let's rock a double stuff!
Are you sure you're up for it?
I made this magic siphoner
thingy to refill my power
from the neckwear-mancer.
Whoa, where did you learn
how to make that thing?
I got mad skills
and a magic pink chainsaw...
Get with the program!
Okay, let's roll!
Nomobuyo, oshi, hashitawa,
dokeda, gunmiicha, deh ribura!
You ain't gotta be embarrassed.
They're huge...
That's no secret!
Yeah smush 'em together.
Hey!
Let me feel
them coconuts, momma.
Over here creep...!
Yeah, I'm talkin to you...!
Watch out!
No boobies mean no mercy.
Stupid stumpy baby fingers.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's time to make
a coonskin cap!
You with me, Ayumu?!
It's on!
Double Mystletainn Kick!!
What a killer panty shot!
That's not a kick!
Oohh Monkey likey!
We got 'em...!
Yeah we did!
That's the genius
Magical Demon Baron
Garment Girl Haruna for ya!
And what the hell
is a Demon Baron again?
This is not good...
Seems the Megalos
are making a comeback.
Wonder why...
Perhaps it was Ayumu and
Haruna's combined magical power
that drew them out
of hiding to come here.
Perhaps...
But I'll bet it's someone else.
Try not to lose focus.
Oh...
I didn't!
I'm payin' attention.
Holy crap that really hurts!
It feels like a damn jackhammer
busting through my skull!
What's happening!
Hey!
Haruna!
"Roo-roo-roo-roo-ree-roo-
ree-roo-roo-roo-roon-roon!"
I don't think that
will be long enough.
Let's add "poon-poon-pooi-pooi-
poo-roo-roon skin" to the end!
Ready...
"Roo-roo-roo-roo-ree-roo-
ree-roo-roo-roon-roon!
Poon-poon-pooi-pooi-poo-
roo-roon skin!"
That's so much better.
I think it could use
more "poon" though.
Hey, real Eu!
What do you think?
You should transform...
But we're too sickeningly cute!