This time, you're gonna burn
and there'll be no coming back!
So, you've finally
come, have you?
I've been expecting you.
Welcome to the party.
Eu!
Wow, I can feel your
power from here. What a rush!
You're even stronger
than I thought!
But even the strong
can be brought down.
So let's see how
you fare against this.
No, don't?
Whoa, she's using Mystletainn?
Lady Hellscythe.
It's finally
starting to make sense.
This must be why I was
able to absorb Haruna's powers.
Hey, stop gawking
at me, you pervert,
and give me back
my powers immediately!
This instant!
And not just that.
I came here
because I was drawn by
the power of a
Magical Garment Girl.
But also why Megalos
are being drawn to me.
It's because the greatest vortex
of magical power in the world.
The center of everything.
Is her, that's why.
It's all because of her.
So, Eucliwood Hellscythe,
necromancer of Hades,
why does someone of your power
choose to stay in this world
when you could be reigning
over your own realm instead?
You've grown attached to that
undead pervert, haven't you?
Wasting magic of your
magnitude is a shame.
Very well, since you don't
seem to have any use for it,
then I think it's only fitting
that I take it all from you!
Oh yeah. I'm gonna love having
that kind of magic inside me!
No!
Neckwear-mancer!
Eu.
How touching.
You're trying to protect
your pitiful little friends.
How human! Oh, and
speaking of which.
Did you know that human beings
have a limit on the percent
of strength their
bodies can use?
But for someone like me,
who has a stock of lives,
I can use all I want!
One hundred percent!
One hundred and fifty percent!
Two hundred percent!
Three hundred percent!
Four hundred! Five hundred!
She's strong.
Yes. But what makes Lady
Hellscythe truly powerful?
Would you please
just fall over already?
No! Not yet!
It's neither her
armor, nor her magic...
but the power of
her words instead.
To fell an opponent,
Lady Hellscythe has only to
utter a single word.
Just one word from her,
and someone'll die?
Then drop dead!
Yeah, of course.
That why she's
sealed away her powers.
If she didn't restrain herself,
she could kill someone.
Based on what she
told me, she feels pain
when she uses her powers,
so she must be in agony.
This is horrible.
She feels the pain of
others when they die,
and she's feeling it
with Kyoko right now.
To protect us.
Your words can't affect me
if I can't hear any of them.
Just as I expected,
you're incredibly powerful.
But not nearly
enough to stop me.
Get out of there!
Total magic power, release!
Eu!
How ironic. Over and over
she kept saying "die"
but it looks like she's
the one who's life has ended.
No coming back now or ever.
Ya know, usually
when I see someone
getting beat up like this,
I think it's kinda funny.
But something's weird this time.
Seeing what that girl is
doing to the neckwear-mancer.
It's making me get
really freakin' angry.
And the only thing I wanna do
is kick that blonde chick's ass!
Good, because I think that's
exactly what we're gonna have
to do if we want Eu to
make it outta this in one piece.
You're right.
So let's do it then.
Ayumu. I just thought
up a new technique
that may prove to
be our finishing blow.
When we get back
to the house later,
perhaps you can help
me think up a name for it.
Eu put her life
on the line for us,
so we've gotta
do the same for her.
Let's go.
New strike.
Name to be decided!
Eat this, blondie!
Haruna!
You have to get back up
before she can strike again!
What the? Is she nuts?
Ah! That feels better.
Those ruptured eardrums were
screwing up my equilibrium,
but to regenerate them,
all I had to do was kill myself.
Eww yuck!
Geez, you're even
more zombie-like than me.
I don't stay dead, do I?
But I've lost many
of the lives today
that I've worked
so hard to collect.
So I'm going to
have to replace them,
and I'll do that by
taking all of yours.
Alright.
Even though the sight of you
in that outfit disgusts me.
Yeah.
Nomobuyo. Oshi. Hashitawa.
Dokeda. Gunmiicha! Deh Ribura!
Your killing. It ends tonight.
You look adorable in that!
Well, since you're the
first person to step up,
and because I've always
liked you, I'll kill you first!
Don't just stand there!
Yeah, at least try to dodge her!
No. I won't fall
like all the others.
I refuse to give this
psychopath the pleasure.
After all the pain she's
caused, it's payback time.
I'll make sure that
she won't ever kill again.
Oh, well, in that case,
it'll be your funeral, Tranny.
Die! Die! Die!
I'm sorry to
disappoint you, but I can't.
Eu. When we get home,
let's have dinner.
So! You want dinner,
huh? Then feast on this!
I can't die.
You see. I'm a zombie.
And a Magical Garment Girl.
And a moron!
I was. But death cured
me of that. I was so stupid.
Stay back!
I used to take life for granted.
But ironically, once I died,
I could finally appreciate
what it means to live.
Thank you. You see,
you actually changed my life
for the better by taking it.
And now.
I'm gonna do the same for you.
Like hell you are,
you cross-dressing creep,
I've got multiple lives!
Yeah, well that may be so,
but that just means
I gotta kill you
over and over again.
Until all your
stolen lives are used up!
No, you let go
of me right now! Die!
No. This isn't happening!
How dare you!
From the way you're acting,
that must have been
your last stolen life.
Please! Stay back!
No. You've taken the lives
of too many
innocent people for that.
It's time to pay up.
But, I don't wanna die.
Neither did any of
your victims. Including me.
No!
This ends here and now!
You're okay.
For now at least.
Not what I was expecting,
but I'll take it.
You're right, I did.
I'll start dinner as
soon as we get home, okay?
You're hungry!
Impressive work.
But to be honest,
I was worried that you might
have killed my student.
Who are you?
Good thing you didn't,
because I would've killed you.
I won't let anyone
lay a finger on my students.
Hold on a minute.
"Your students?"
Uh? Head Teacher?
Wait! You mean that's her?
Poor dear. I wonder how
a Magical Garment Girl
could have strayed so
far from our school's path.
Since you're her teacher,
maybe you should've
given her some better direction!
I have hundreds of millions of
students back home in Villiers,
so it's hard to keep up with
them all, but I do try my best.
You should try harder then!
I think you need to learn
what can happen when you say
such things in the
heat of the moment.
Yowch! That burns!
Head Teacher, please. Stop it.
Don't worry, I'm done because
burning zombie smells awful.
And fighting
won't solve a thing.
Anyway, it certainly
appears that I'm going to
have to re-educate this one.
So I'll be taking her
back to Villiers with me.
If that's what
you came here for,
why didn't you do it sooner?
You're mistaken.
I didn't come here for her,
but for that delicious
Kyo-tofu that you promised me.
Uh.
I'm sorry ma'am!
I hope it's still okay.
Oh, don't worry, I'm sure
I can make something out of it.
I hope, 'cause I don't
wanna get fried again!
It looks like our
wayward student is waking up.
Come, dear, you'll be
going home with me to--
What an
entertaining little show.
What's going on?
Well, if it isn't
Eucliwood Hellscythe.
I'm so glad to see you're well.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not planning
on doing anything.
Well, at least not yet, that is.
The King of the Night.
So you're the one
who's possessed my student?
But of course.
I've heard about you.
You're a Megalo?
Not quite.
I'm much like yourself.
And I'll see all of you again.
You can count on it.
Stop right there!
Give me back my
student this instant!
I'll see you
real soon, Eucliwood.
I can't just sit
here and let that monster
run off with one of my pupils.
So, what'll you do.
Well, I'm afraid I have no
choice but to go after him.
Now you keep up
with your studies
and apply yourself, you hear me?
Yes, ma'am!
Bye now!
Eu, what was all that?
Most people live their
lives without ever knowing it,
but the world is
full of weird stuff,
like magic and
supernatural serial killers.
Sure, we put a stop
to Kyoko, but knowing that
King of the Night
guy's out there
doesn't help me
rest that much easier.
Still, things have
settled down enough
that I can kick
back just a little.
Despite what you've
heard about zombies,
we don't go around
looking to munch on brains.
My favorite snack is still
these cheap little rice balls.
Awww, why'd my
pudding turn out so crappy?
Well, if I were to guess,
I would say you
did something wrong.
What! Don't come in here acting
like you could do a better job!
At least my pudding isn't gonna
melt down the entire house,
you bloodsucking freak.
Vampire.
Well, bite my ass!
Oh, hey.
I don't know why,
but these balls taste so yummy!
But then everything
tastes better with you, tiger!
It makes me purr! Meow!
Whoa, nice tail.
Can I ask you something?
Are there other
zombies besides me?
Like this "King" guy?
Sorry to pry, but he
wasn't your boyfriend was he?
Um. Look, you don't
need to worry.
I'll always be here for you.
Y'know, 'cause I'm immortal now.
Of course, that's all
thanks to your power.
I know the girls have
your back, too. We all do.
Wait. Did she just smile?
Bam! Dessert is served!
I made one of my famous
rolled omelettes! So dig in!
Not to complain, but I
thought you were making pudding.
You are complaining,
but since you must know,
I had a little
problem making it!
Look, I do appreciate this and
all, but I wanted some pudding.
So you're a pervert
and an ingrate, too.
Well no one's forcing you
to eat it, you whiny maggot.
Wait. Bring it back,
I'll eat it.
Hey, I worked hard on that,
so if you toss it,
I'm gonna toss you!
Sorry, the cross-dresser
doesn't want it, so it's trash!
What's the use?
Well, things are still crazy.
But I guess it's our
home now. Whaddaya think?
Reactor 1's reached critical!
Release the safety
valve, but carefully!
Thermal levels holding!
Magical output 1 gigaton!
Ready!
Red Two, Blue One,
commence infusion!
Wanna make beautiful
music with me, Taeko?
I dunno, I mean,
we're not even dating!
I meant karaoke.
Oh.
I can't win.
I'm sorry. It's just everyone's
been saying you've gotten
more perverted and weird lately,
so I thought you
were being gross.