I'm counting on you to keep
things relatively decent
around here while I'm gone to
the village, is that understood?
And by decent you mean?
Just keep an eye on the maggot
so he doesn't try
to violate Lady Hellscythe.
You think you're up for that?
Say no more!
I've got this one.
Don't worry: if he so much
as looks at her wrong,
I'll clobber him!
Spoken like
a protective big sister.
Big sister?
Oh, I like the sound of that!
Underworld necromancer
Eucliwood Hellsythe
experiences a mysterious
reversal of fortune.
Will the peace and tranquility
of Ayumu's impromptu family
be forever shattered?
I was supposed to work
a double shift today.
Why they gotta call us back
for costume measurements?
I mean, is something
goin' down?
I'm sure the village elders know
exactly what they're doing,
whatever it is.
Probably ties in to all the
"incidents" popping up lately.
Sounds mysterious.
Will you please hold still?
Wha-- Ow!
I'm not squirmin'
around that much!
One of the most crucial
aspects of a vampire ninja's
battle prowess is
freedom of movement.
To anyone here who's
gone up a dress size lately,
know that fat is the enemy!
Ma'am!
And now to
the business at hand.
Okay, this sucks.
How can things be this much
more chaotic with Sera gone?
It's like the sun's
moved closer to the earth;
I can't even go out
for groceries.
We've gotta have some kinda
food squirreled away.
Yo, Haruna.
Can you hit up the--
Sorry.
Busy.
Better luck next time.
Yeah, don't work
too hard or anything.
I've never seen someone peel
a tangerine so thoroughly.
Don't mind if I do.
Thank you.
That's really good.
I peeled these for you.
My lover shall eat no rind.
Only fruity sweetness!
Enjoy!
You want every single bite to be
an explosion of citrusy goodness
in my mouth, don't you?
Sorry what?
Fret not, sweet prince.
I'm fine.
'Tis nothing at all.
I love it when you talk
all fantasy damsel-like.
Uh, Eu?
Hallway's spotless.
You're welcome.
Hey.
Let me check out your
forehead for a sec--Oh crap!
Don't you touch her!
She's totally burning up!
Haruna!
Bring me some ice!
You got it!
And maybe try not
to kill yourself?
Shut your ugly face!
I've got to get her
out of this outfit
before the sweat
makes her worse.
Easy, tiger.
You're about to casually
break a major taboo here.
Oh my darling.
I'm so vulnerable.
Pull it together, dude.
This is driven by necessity;
there's no reason
to get uptight.
If you don't do something,
the sweat's going
to give her a chill.
And you can't wait
on Haruna to get back.
There's no other option;
you're just gonna have
to be a man and do this.
And by "be a man,"
I don't mean "be a man,"
so don't even go there, okay?
This is strictly clinical!
I will see no evil.
I will touch no evil.
We've made contact!
Calm down, perv.
It's not about her--
To enter the valley of wisdom,
I must first come over the
mountains-- What am I saying?
'Kay, it can't be good
that this is wobbly!
Uh.
This is awkward.
Be gentle with me, love.
I'm delicate.
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to hurt you!
What?
How did you?
You're over there?
Okay.
Think I'm at the shoulders.
Least I hope
that's what they are.
Weird.
Shouldn't I be in the
neighborhood of a pilot wire
or whatever those
things are called?
Oh god!
She's not wearing a bra!
Please darling,
I'm so terribly cold.
Won't you kindly warm me
with your strong, manly touch?
Step aside!
High IQ to the rescue!
You dirty pervert!
Only you would try to
take advantage of a sick girl!
I was trying to be good.
Think you can
stomach some porridge?
Well then, let me just whip
some up for you, patient zero.
I hope you like it
made with eggs!
Try to relax.
You know Haruna.
She'll have it ready and down
your gullet in no time.
Yeah, no kidding, right?
I'm a little bit
jealous of you right now.
Spoken like a
protective big sister.
I'm starting to think maybe
we should call a doctor.
Well, except she's
an underworlder.
I'm not too sure what
a doctor would make of that.
Wait, that's it.
An underworlder!
Of course!
Shimomura?
Yeah, it's me.
Do you have a minute?
Absolutely.
What can I do for you?
Well, Eu's got a fever.
Really?
Do you think it's okay if I take
her to, like, a regular doctor?
I'm not sure how this works.
I doubt a "regular doctor"
would have the first clue
about what to look for.
Underworlder
pathology is unique.
Scratch that, then.
Still, is there anything
we can do for her?
'Cause I got to tell you, man.
She's not lookin' so good.
Exactly how far
are you prepared to go?
You willing to
swallow your pride?
Hell yeah!
Whatever it takes, I'm there!
All right.
The last time I got sick, the
only thing that broke my fever
was a friend's yodeling.
Do what?
Deep breath; you'll need it.
Good.
Now do some sidewinders and
strip down to your undies.
How's me being
half naked gonna help her?
Come on, man!
Step up the intensity!
Forget you're inhibitions!
How am I doin', Eu?
You feeling any better yet?
Please say yes.
Dude, I'm giving all I've got
and she's still looks like hell!
What gives?
You're doing fine; keep at it.
Now get on all fours and blow
on her while shaking your butt.
Are you serious?
As a heart attack, my friend.
Do it!
Egg porridge on the--
You--
You, boney-assed bacon wrapped
hedgehog molestallion!
For the record,
I'm worried about her, too,
and you don't see me ripping my
clothes off and trying to shove
my tongue down her throat!
I should've made
the porridge out of you!
But he told me that it was
the only way to help her.
Sorry.
He was acting so valiant I had
to see how far I could take it.
You sneaky son of a--
Relax.
It helped more than you know.
Think about it.
In her shoes, how awesome
would it be to know your friend
is willing to make himself
look like a complete jackass
on the off chance
it'd break your fever?
That's strong medicine,
believe me.
I guess you're right.
A little R &amp; R will
take care of the rest.
Tomorrow morning
she'll be good as new.
Got it.
Thanks.
Here.
Have some grub.
Sleeping like a baby.
Good.
I'm glad she's on the mend.
Makes me feel better.
Huh?
What the--?
What are you doing?
Doctor's orders
are to stay in bed!
Not gonna lie.
This is, um, uncomfortable.
How is it she's lived under the
same roof with me for so long
and this is the closest
we've ever been?
Oh man, the sound of her
breathing is so-- I dunno, hot?
Settle down.
She's sick.
Girl needs rest.
Hey, perv?
Damn it!
I mean, hey!
How's it goin'?
What do you need?
Unless you know where she is,
Neckwear-mancer's gone MIA.
And after all the trouble I went
through getting it for her.
Uh.
Trouble getting what, exactly?
You have no idea what a pain
in the ass these things
are to come by.
Don't fight it, pipsqueak!
So, is that s'posed to help?
I mean, good for you.
It just looks like he could
use a little tenderness.
Yeah.
It is standard practice
to let them get comfortable.
It's a nice thought.
But Eu is an Underworlder,
you know.
Duh.
That's why I got her these.
You know, so her hands
don't get all frostbitten,
or whatever.
So considerate.
Wow.
Kinda out of character for you.
Who'd have guessed
you'd go so far to nurse
a rival back to health?
Please!
As if I'm such a hard-ass.
I'm the surrogate big sister,
so it's my job
to nurse her back to health!
'Sides, I'm following
Sera's orders,
so don't get the wrong idea.
This isn't a lesbian thing!
There may just be hope
for you yet, Madam Curie.
Just shut up you!
Look, just give the mittens
or whatever they are
to me for right now.
Please don't eviscerate me!
Oh good.
I was kinda starting
to get worried.
You're not pissed?
Special circumstances.
At the moment, she needs
you more than I do.
Now.
Try any funny stuff on her
and I wrench your brain
out through your nose.
I'm not gonna try anything!
Why do you have to treat me
like I keep rufi's
in my dresser drawer?
Because you're a rubber duckie
floating in a tub of temptation!
Here!
Stay with her
till she gets better.
Only till she gets better.
It's cool.
I got this.
Sleep tight, Eu.
'Kay, freezing my ass off!
FYI, I don't even
feel bad that that's hot.
Ah.
Morning, nurse.
Is there a reason you're here?
I just stopped by
to check on Eucliwood.
Oh right.
So where--
There you are.
You okay?
Never better, my darling,
and I owe it all to last night's
tender loving kindness.
I'm a little concerned
she's not quite back up
to par this morning.
I need to reconsider
my diagnosis.
Pardon me for a moment,
I'm sorry.
That's decidedly not good.
What is it?
What's wrong?
Orange welts,
arranged in a floral pattern.
Oh no.
Has Eucliwood been
force-fed tangerine peels?
I don't treat her
like a garbage disposal!
Relax.
I'm messing with you.
Just tell me you've
been peeling them well.
Even the smallest amount of
tangerine pith is poisonous
to an underworlder.
Uh.
Now that you mention it.
Nah.
She picked the
stuff off like a bird.
Perhaps, but there was bound to
have been a piece here or there
that she missed.
Chances are she ate
some without knowing it.
That's the culprit.
We haven't had anything else
to eat for days.
Oh yeah.
When an Underworlder eats fruit
that they're not supposed to,
they break out in a fever, an
icky rash, the whole nine yards.
Yep.
See, just about every
fruit is questionable.
Think Adam and Eve
in the Garden of Eden.
Okay, so tangerine pith is bad.
How do we knock
this crap out of her?
No idea.
What?
Fear not.
I'm not above firing
in the dark here.
Me neither.
Let's avail ourselves
of Occam's Razor.
Ah!
Process of elimination!
Not happening, guys.
You can't use her
like a guinea pig.
But.
I'd like, if I may,
to pick up the conversation
where we left off.
About the, uh, well, thing.
Yeah.
Not even I can anticipate the
shape of its choosing when
the beast becomes manifest.
What it wants is unknown.
We have to stay sharp.
Keep the worm
under close scrutiny.
I will stay vigilant.
This stuff feels
like a milk bath!
Actually, it's
forbidden to swim here.
Huh?
I need to teach you how to
loosen up a little, Seraphim.
What is she doing?
How 'bout this?
Drinking tea while turning
the cup counterclockwise.
Dude, seriously, that
wouldn't cure indigestion.
That's not right.
If you don't do it while patting
your stomach with your leg
in the air and a crown of
seaweed cocked to one side,
you might as well be
chugging vegetable oil.
Are you out of your mind?
That's the most random
assortment of wrong
I've ever heard!
Wait, I think she may be on
to something with the seaweed.
Fine!
You freaks do
whatever you want!
Don't come crying to me when
they make you snort cinnamon!
Oh god.
What have I done?
Condition unchanged.
Didn't there used to
be something about bathing
in warm soymilk with
bamboo in your mouth?
Yes, yes!
And a jar of kosher salt
on your head!
And can't the toxins be flushed
out by putting old CDs wrapped
in spinach under your armpits?
Yeah.
That could work.
Damn it!
There are too many options!
Ah-ha!
I can't believe you're actually
starting to feel better.
So, what brand of mumbo-jumbo
you think finally did the trick?
Hey, as long as it worked
I couldn't care less which one.
Sera's gonna punch me into next
week when she sees this mess.
I'm gonna have to clean.
You contemplating how
crazy-fabulous it is to have
a genius around the house?
Uh-oh.
Looks like your cheeks
might be a little flush.
Huh?
What're you talking about?
Gimme you forehead for a sec.
She's burning up.
Was Eu's stuff contagious?
It's a disease specific
to Underworlders, I'm afraid.
So, uh--
Think you're
coming down with the flu.
The flu does not
dare attack geniuses!
Well, if there's fine line
between genius and madness,
why not illness?
What the hell does that mean?
Tell me that
I'm gonna make it.
For the record,
I'm worried about her, too!
It's okay.
You'll be fine.
Ugh!
Don't you even, start!
I am nobody's big sister!
I'm going to lay out
the futon, okay?
You don't have to treat me
like I've got polio!
Look, you're independent.
I get it.
Give it a rest.
Stay with her
till she gets better.
Only till she gets better.
You cuddled up next
to her because
you needed to feel secure.
I'm not blind.
I just didn't
see it at the time.
What can I say?
People surprise me
every now and then.
I can take my own clothes off,
thank you very much!
Thing is, I get not wanting
to be a burden on people.
But friends want
to be friends, you know?
Please.
This is so ridiculous.
Look, if you wear that
you're gonna sweat like a pig
and freeze your butt off.
I'm back, people.
Take 'em off!
C'mon!
You repulsive swag-bellied
tentacle-monster discharge!
Homeward-bound.
Mama Bird's Return
Strike Pervert Kick!
You're lucky I don't
grind your grapes to dust!
It's good to have you back.
Glad you're home safe, Sera.
Hey, Ayumu!
Step it up, bitch boy!
My porridge isn't going
to prepare itself!
If it's porridge you want,
allow me to make it.
With my special ingredient.
Wrinkly homunculus!
Those are very
hard to come by.
Well done.
A classic Villiers cure-all.
However, he has
to be sterilized.
Stand back!
I feel for you, pal.
I really do.
I've made a special batch of
porridge for my dashing prince!
Don't forget to let it
cool a little bit first.
Oo, I wanna help get it cool!
And blow!
Huh.
This is taking
a lot longer than I thought.
Hey.
It's Actual Eu!
You need me, too?
We're almost there!
Just a little more;
I can feel it!
This porridge will be like
banana pudding when we're done!