So tell me?
Have you missed me as
much as I've missed you?
Guess that's a "no." My,
you're worked up, aren't you?
From the look in your eyes,
I presume that you're
wondering why I'm here.
I saw how much you were
enjoying yourself today.
Good times with all your
little friends left you
feeling so happy and content
and like "one of the gang."
That's exactly why
I appeared when I did.
In the midst of all
that sweetness, I show up,
the person you
least want to see.
Now we've finally been
reunited, let's get caught up.
There's so much to say.
I hope I'm mistaken.
But my superiors may have
grown weary with my lack of
progress with Lady Hellscythe.
What do you mean?
I'm under orders to kill her,
but I've thus far failed
to carry out that command.
The hell? What are
you talking about?!
You said you came here to
take her back to your village!
Why the hell would
they order you to kill her?
It doesn't make sense!
Have you just been
lying to us the whole time
we've been living under
the same roof? Answer me!
Why, yes I do.
I put my trust in you
but then look what happened to
me. You can make it up, however,
by simply agreeing to grant
the fondest wish that I have.
You're still angry.
I imagine the fact that
I killed the Seventh Abyss
would be a sore spot.
Because when you
found out, you said, "begone."
A hurtful, and in
your case, powerful word.
I did disappear at the time.
But of course,
I wasn't exterminated.
Oh, no. I will remain in this
world until my wish is granted.
I'll tell you, but first...
I have to admit I'm amazed.
Seeing you living in
a world such as this one
is an enormous surprise.
But even more stunning
is that you've made friends.
And I'm going to use them to get
the wish that I want fulfilled.
My superiors believe
that megalos are attracted
to Lady Hellscythe's
magical powers,
therefore, the recent
increase in attacks
and the order to
assassinate her.
No way. They really
want you to kill her?
What is wrong with you! How
could you be so cold-blooded?
It isn't as simple as you think!
You're really going to kill her?
Knowing how duty-bound
I am, do you have to ask?
Then it is as simple as I think!
I am a ninja, after all!
So what if you are?
This is pointless.
I'll simply search for
Lady Hellscythe on my own.
No, wait a second! Why do
you vampire ninjas always have
to be so damned
inflexible all the time?
This is wrong. Don't do it!
You don't
understand the importance
of a ninja's duty, maggot.
We always gotta
follow the rules!
That's the whole reason
we're married now, remember?
So you're saying her life
is less important than that?
It's not fair to put it
that way! To a vampire ninja...
Don't even try to
give me that crap!
All I wanna know is if
you really plan on killing her!
You know my dedication, so you
shouldn't have to ask me that!
No, that's not what
I wanna hear from you!
I wanna know if you're really
okay with killing your friend,
but I don't wanna hear
it from some vampire ninja.
I wanna hear it from you!
No, of course I'm
not okay with it!
So now what?
Hey, that's enough,
knock it off!
Instead of you two chuckleheads
wasting our time fighting,
shouldn't we be searching for
the neckwear-mancer instead?
Yeah, you're right.
Good, then let's go!
Yeah!
Sorry I called
you a liar earlier.
Save your weak apology.
Don't waste your breath.
Gee. Thanks a lot.
However. I now see
due to your counsel,
there are some duties
that are worth dismissing.
Glad to help.
Now what say we
go find her, okay?
Hey, wait up, would ya?
We need to stick together!
How sweet.
They're searching for you.
I'm sure you'd
grant their wishes.
So why won't you grant mine?
Come here and take
a look at something.
My treat, of course.
Please, let me show you the
friends who mean so much to you.
Come over here.
Now.
I'll give you a little
preview of what can happen
if you continue to deny my wish.
What the!
Ayumu!
Say something!
How did this thing happen to
fall apart right here and now?
Was it just a coincidence?
Hey, are you alright?
Yeah.
But, your face,
it looks injured. Wait...
That's how it always looks.
They might have gotten lucky
that time, but before too long
something far more
serious will befall them.
Losing control of your emotions?
Holy crap!
Is that a Megalo?
I don't know.
I thought those things wore
school uniforms for some reason!
It looks like the
neckwear-mancer's doll!
We gotta get outta here!
Haruna, no!
Why the hell are you
petting me? This is degrading!
Listen you overgrown jackass,
get your paws or whatever
and your big, fat,
yellow ass offa me right now
or I swear
you're gonna be sorry!
Here, take my hand.
I'll try to yank you out.
Move, let me try!
Hurry up, maggot!
It's crushing her!
We'll get you outta there,
I swear! Just hang on!
This isn't my doing.
You're the one who summoned
that thing, aren't you?
It's as clear as day,
isn't it, Eucliwood?
Whenever your heart stirs
with emotion, disaster follows.
That's why you swore
to speak no words
and keep your feelings buried
deep inside yourself, isn't it?
Of course it is.
'Cause after all,
you are someone with
the power to summon death.
I'm terribly sorry to
interrupt you while you're busy.
However...
Well, well, if it
isn't you again.
You're that teacher
from the Matelly.
The Magic School
in Villiers, right?
Oh, my! You didn't mention
it the last time we met,
but you know who I am?
Yes. Believe it or not,
stories about you
have even reached the
depths of the underworld.
Goodness gracious me!
What kinds of stories exactly?
That your powers are quite vast.
Oh stop. You're
starting to embarrass me!
To what do I owe the
pleasure of your visit?
I won't let any of
my students come to harm,
and seeing that one
of them's in danger,
I'm here to lend a helping hand.
Swallow-Return Strike!
Dammit!
My turn.
I'll give it three
hundred percent power!
Four hundred!
Five hundred! Six hundred!
Seven hundred percent!
Oh, crap!
Please stay with us, Haruna!
I've got an idea!
Huh? Wait.
What are you doing?
Draggin' this thing
off before it kills her!
Haruna!
Get off of her, you freak!
Guys! One of
you pull Haruna out
while the other one
pushes this thing back!
It's no use! It's not budging!
Don't give up!
Come on! Move! Move!
Get off of her now!
What the?
From that impressive
little demonstration,
I can see your
reputation is well-deserved.
That's very kind. But I
assure you I'm nothing special.
Oh, no. Tomonori! Are you okay?
Say something! Please!
Come on Mael Strom,
please get up!
Ya need some of my blood?
Irregularity detected in matrix.
Operation restrictions lifted.
What the hell just happened!
Rise and follow my command.
First incantation confirmed.
Operations released.
Tomonori, what are
you talking about?
I shall walk the path of life.
While thou shalt
walk the path of death.
Second incantation confirmed.
Chew them to bits, Manticore.
Final incantation confirmed.
That caused the blast?
That thing breathes fire?
I don't wanna get roasted!
Oh, dear me.
I guess Haruna
didn't have a reason
to bring it with her tonight.
Mystic weapon of saw and chain,
come here quickly
and bring the pain!
Mystletainn?
Huh? But how?
Who cares, just
hurry up and transform!
Swallow-Return Strike!
I bought you a chance!
Thank you, Sera!
Nomobuyo. Oshi. Hashitawa.
Dokeda. Gunmiicha! Deh Ribura!
Unleash my hellish
heart upon the world.
First incantation confirmed.
Operations released.
May its flame turn
even the breath of gods
into a raging firestorm.
Second incantation confirmed.
Burn them all.
Absolute. Destruction.
Final incantation confirmed.
Oh, dear me, I think
it's gone out of control.
You don't say?
Would that happen to be
your ultimate magic weapon
I learned about
by possessing Kyoko?
Why, yes, you are correct.
That is indeed it.
And I was hoping for
Ayumu to take control of it
because he's strong
enough to shut it off.
But it appears to
have taken control
of the vampire
ninja girl instead.
Unfortunately, it doesn't
have a power switch.
You see,
it's designed to normally
turn itself off automatically,
but if it happens to go
out of control like this,
there's a good chance
it'll blow itself up.
But I wouldn't
worry too much, dear.
And why is that?
Because Ayumu
is incredibly strong,
and I'm sure that he'll
come up with something.
He also has one of my
students down there with him.
Haruna's stronger than she
looks and claims to be a genius.
What's going on here?
Why is she like that?
Come on think! There's
gotta be a way we can stop her
before she turns
us into barbeque, right?
We'll have to take her down.
Sera, no!
Why are you stopping me, maggot?
We have to do something.
But we can't risk
hurting her in the process!
We just spent a
great day with her,
and now you think
we should attack her?
She's our friend, remember!
Yes, but even so vampire
ninjas do not hesitate
to fight at any time.
It's one of our sworn duties.
I had a feeling you
were gonna say that.
Just let me handle
this my way, okay?
Very well then, maggot.
But if your way fails,
I'll be the first one
to say, "I told you so."
Sounds like a deal to me!
What the hell, Ayumu!
Did the heat melt
your brain or something?
Tomonori. What are you doing?
We're your friends.
Don't you recognize us?
It's alright. I can
take it 'cause I'm a zombie.
Like I said,
we're friends, so talk to me.
Tell me.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I really don't know.
But would you please help me?
Of course.
That's what friends do.
Irregularity detected in matrix.
Self-destruction will
commence in thirty seconds.
Oh, no, that's not good!
Get out of there, Tomonori!
Huh? Ayumu? Wait.
What's happening to me?
What is this?
What's going on here?
No! Get back!
Don't come any closer!
I can't do that! I'm not
gonna leave you here to die!
Ayumu.
Please stop.
Just get out of here.
No.
I don't want you
to worry about me okay?
Just go on. I don't
want you to get hurt too.
Ten. Nine.
Uh-uh, no way!
I'm not gonna leave you!
Let go of me.
Go on, get out of here!
Didn't you hear
what I said, Ayumu?
I'm about to get blown
to bits any second now!
It's too late for me!
Let me go and save yourself.
Don't throw your
life away for me!
Didn't you hear me?
I'm staying with you! Yuki!
I'm glad that's over.
Ayumu.
Aw man. Good to
have you back, Tomonori.
Call me Yuki!
I told you he'd
come up with something.
That Ayumu really is
quite impressive, isn't he?
Why yes, he is.
However, I have the
suspicion he might not
look so
impressive after this.
Do I make myself clear?
Your friends can
expect more of the same
until you grant my wish.
So perhaps now
you'll reconsider?
Not again! Come back here!
You still have to answer to
me for messing with my students!
Feel this?
He smells worse than usual.
Like a fried diaper.
Lady Hellscythe!
Hey, where have you been?
We've been looking
all over for you!
It doesn't matter now.
Let's go home, okay?
Hey guys.
My place is over this way.
Oh, right. We'll be seein'
ya later then. And be careful.
Ayumu. Um. Thank you.
For what you did today.
It's okay, don't mention it.
See ya!
Hey, if you're gonna get
a snack, I can come with you.
Okay. Just try to hurry home.
We're all really stinky, so I'm
gonna get a bath started for us!
Ah, it's nice to be home.
Well it was pretty fun today,
except for that last part.
"Farewell."
"This was all my fault."
"I'm sorry.
If I hadn't been around, none of
this would have happened today."
"Ayumu, Haruna, and Sera.
You've all been so
incredibly kind to me.
You made me feel so happy."
"Far more than
you'll ever know."
"But I can no
longer be with you.
I'm to blame for everything."
"I'm sorry for what
I've put you through."
"If I continue to stay with you.
You'll all remain in danger."
"Bad things will
happen because of me.
All of you would
get hurt, or even worse."
"Because after all,
I can summon death."
"So, my friends. Farewell."
"Please give me snow."
Lots of it, understand? Enough
that everyone here can see it!
"May my cooking
skills be doubled."
And may my food be tastier
and far less dangerous to eat.
"I pray thee."
"May I forever be together with
Ayumu and all of the others."
Why this one?
Why? Did my wish have to be
the only one that came true?
And why did I
have to write something
so stupid like this down?
Eu. Eu. I'm so sorr--!
Get it together and
stop being a crybaby!
She's correct, maggot.
This doesn't have
to be a final farewell.
Yeah, think positive! Like they
say, "Never give up on dope!"
You're right, I really needed
to hear that right now. Thanks.
Um, but the saying is actually
"never give up on hope,"
and I won't.
Have you heard of
political correctness?
Is that a band?
No, it's about treating
both sexes as equals.
Oh, like how men can
be flight attendants, too?
Yes, and the same is
true for vampire ninjas.
Really?
Men, not maggots,
so don't get your hopes up.