It'd been a few weeks since
everyone saw me, well, you know.
Thing is, even celebrity
pariahs need time off.
Sunday was gonna
be just for me.
A solid twenty four reserved
for yours truly alone.
Ah-ha, look at you.
You're adorable!
Models have come
a long way since I was a kid.
The current state of metal
die tech is proof civilization
is on the right track.
Oh, Kashim.
Love you, bro.
I'd tell the two of you
to get a room.
Except you'd use it.
We're in a room!
Yes, and you're
using it to spend
your "Me Day"
drooling over toys.
Must you aspire to validate
every creeper stereotype?
I'll have you know.
These happen to
be collector's models!
And?
It's a completely
respectable hobby!
They're merchandise
from a mech anime.
You know what, I'm not gonna
get roped into a discussion
about model building
with a female.
You're mind isn't
wired to appreciate--
And I'm not going to
dignify that chauvinistic
remark with a response.
As if you're
the resident expert.
Don't tell me that's
a real Arbalest?
Uh.
An herbalist?
What?
It's an infantry drone
from Full Metal Panic,
equipped with a Lambda Driver!
Silly me.
Bitchin'!
I'm actually kind of impressed
you'd even know that.
Hello?
High IQ?
Oh my god.
Please tell me you're good for
putting together a Demon Baron!
There's no such thing
in the FMP universe.
I know that.
He's one of the
defenders of Villiers.
What does that mean?
Look, you can't just cross
pollinate two completely
different universes and expect
it to play realistically.
Says the Magical
Garment Girl Zombie.
Watch it.
If you're gonna play
with 'em, you have to be--
Sousuke!
Roiling underneath the banal
trappings of everyday life
are dark secrets
few would suspect.
Still juggling the
repercussions of his exposure
to uncomprehending classmates,
our hero heaps lie upon lie
to maintain a
semblance of normality.
Can his karma hold?
No way.
She busted it?
Totally.
I wound up having to work it
into a kind of battlefield
graveyard diorama.
An elegy to the
great fallen mechs.
Tried to make it look like
a burned out Hong Kong.
Seems like a pretty reasonable
way to deal with your grief.
I slew five other models!
I feel like a
freakin' Aztec priest!
Well, better they be destroyed
by someone who loved them
than some random girl.
Stop being so
damn philosophical.
Yet another wrinkle.
I mean, I knew
you were into models,
but I had no idea how deep.
Seems the whole thing means
more to you than a simple hobby.
Gives you layers, man.
It'd mean a lot to you, too,
if you were in my shoes.
Hell, I'd jump out of
a window to escape reality.
A model's like a friend
you don't have to justify
your existence to.
It's okay, I understand.
Some people deal with it
by burying their heads
in the sand; you smash toys.
Models.
S'cuse me while
I whip this thing out.
What?
Don't let the family
friendly shtick fool you:
they only recruit girls
of a certain quality.
Girls that'll get your mind
off of model building.
Um.
Okay?
They've got it tucked away
in an inconspicuous
lil' shopping center
down a back alley.
Ah.
And the world shudders
as two perverts put
their heads together.
Cosplay?
Nice try, dickwad.
Count me the hell out.
Don't run away from this.
Like it or not, this is
an important step for you
on the road to recovery,
and it's my job to make sure
you take it like a man.
By which I mean to sit you down
in front of some hot cosplay
chicks in hopes of giving you
a better outlet than wanting
to wear the same panties.
Now, go get you some!
Ugh.
Alright.
Welcome home, young masters.
How may we serve you
this evening?
Uh, hello.
Oh, sir; you look
terribly exhausted.
Yeah, no.
The usual spiel's
not gonna cut it.
Dude, please.
Two, for the VIP course,
if you would.
The what?
Very well, master.
Right this way.
Why thank you, madam.
Better men have died
for the privilege
of peering behind
those curtains!
Turn back.
Or face the music!
Get lost!
The VIP course is
a real ball-buster.
Is there anything else
you do on the side
that I should know about?
Before I came along,
this place was just a boring,
family friendly watering hole.
Thanks to me,
it's now a fully interactive
cosplay coffee house.
You do know you're sideline
stuff is usually awful?
For your information, the
vampire ninjas happen to be
in the red right now and we're
doing all we can to recoup.
And I'd hardly call
adding some flair
to our fundraising
methods "awful."
Kirara!
Babe!
Doll!
Love!
Coming near me
without permission
is strictly prohibited.
Is that your idea of flair?
Don't criticize her, Ayumu.
She's maintaining a proper
distance between herself
and rabid fanboys.
You're completely
hopeless, dude.
Do you deny finding me
irresistible?
Please, we both know
I look great in this dress.
'Kay, whatever.
You know, there is a little
thing called personal space
I think you should do
some studying up on when
you get a chance.
Oh.
I'm an expert.
Hey, Kinobori!
What's the haps?
You'll take the coffee,
and you'll like it.
Whoa.
What are you doing here?
Hey, the food's decent and
the atmosphere's interesting.
Fact; I'm a regular here.
Well, isn't that an awesome
thing to learn about someone.
Anyone else here know me?
And don't take all day
deciding what the hell you want.
Do a lot of people opt
for the VIP treatment?
The second I infused
this place with attitude,
our sales went
through the roof.
Huh.
Must be a lot more freaks
in this town than I thought.
Look over the menu and
make up your minds before
I kick those
smirking faces in!
Now there's pair o' legs
that go all the way up,
am I right or am I right?
She could look like a burn
victim under those panty hose.
Okay, first of all.
They're not panty hose!
A real lady wears stockings!
Could you be
a bigger pain in the ass?
As a matter of fact, yes!
Sera?
Oh, you've got to be kidding!
If Mama doesn't work,
Mama doesn't get paid.
This is what you do when you
leave the house on an "errand?"
I have no choice
but to obey Saras.
Oh yeah.
I keep forgetting she outranks
you, or whatever that's about.
If I may say so, madam,
your body totally rocks.
For every second you sit there
undressing me with your eyes,
I will peel back an inch
of skin from your skull!
Hey, uh.
Yes?
Well, not to be that guy
but we're still waiting
on our water.
You demanding little maggot.
Don't act like you're here
for anything other than
the off chance of looking up
one of our skirts.
So we're not getting water?
If it's that important to you.
Sorry to make you wait.
Not you, too?
Tomonori, I knew you'd be
great in the cowgirl position!
Thanks!
Always good to see
you two gentlemen.
Hey, do me a solid when you
fill out the guest questionnaire
and give me high marks so
I can maybe get a lil' hike
in my salary, yeah?
You vampire ninjas
are so whimsical.
You guys know
what you want yet?
Everything on
the menu is awesome.
Are you eating with us?
What, are you crazy?
I'm your waitress!
Take all the time you need; I'll
come back when you're ready.
Oh, wait, no.
I mean stop
wasting my time, jerk!
The attitude's a bit
of a stretch for you.
Saras says we have to treat
the customer like total crap
or our marketing angle
goes out the window.
And it is adorable watching
you come to terms with that.
Say what you will
about the atmosphere;
the food's pretty good.
You ready to get outta here?
Nice try, my friend,
but not quite.
Oh.
We gonna go in
for some dessert?
Every hot-blooded male
needs a little
dessert in his life, right?
See, they've got a kind of
challenge here that if you
can get five waitress
to go ga-ga over you,
you dine for free.
Free is always good.
If you accept it and fail,
you owe double.
This hole is a total sham!
Don't forget why
we came here, man.
The risk is what
makes this so therapeutic.
Here we go.
Now if you're gonna have any
hope of winning this thing,
it's absolutely crucial
that I spend as much time
with the waitresses as possible.
Just so you know,
you're not fooling anybody!
Excuse me,
we'd like a free meal!
Hello, and welcome
you dirty bastards!
If you lose, darling, you'll pay
double not with your wallet,
but with your body.
Embrasse moi.
Je t'aime a la folie.
Tout ce que tu fais,
ca fait battre mon coeur forte.
Hello, and welcome
you dirty bastards!
Prepare yourselves,
my tragic sirs.
Or should I say,
you disgusting vermin?
What?
Who the hell are they?
Silly, boy.
This is my Elite Force.
Let the hellish banquet
of your defeat begin!
Leading the charge will
be Yuki Yoshida a.k.a.
Mael Strom!
Stop staring at me!
'Kay, look, this is me
being temperamental
so order a stupid dessert
before I blow a gasket!
You're trying to hard;
you can't just announce it.
Go easy on me,
I'm still learning.
Being a volatile she-bitch
the caliber of Sera or Kirara
takes a nuanced approach.
One where you don't
whine about your so-called
apprenticeship status right
out of the freakin' gate.
Don't patronize me, jerk!
Look, no one's saying
you don't have other
exceptional qualities.
The trick is finding where
they give you the advantage.
Uh, what?
He's saying maybe there's
other jobs out there for you.
Do you not like me
working here?
Whether I like
it isn't really the point.
Think about it for a sec.
Aren't they're other
things out there you can do
to earn a buck that'd
you'd actually enjoy?
Well of course there are!
And let me tell ya:
it's easier to move around
in this than in that dress.
I'll bet it is.
You always give
the best advice.
He executed the
advice gambit perfectly.
Point goes to Ayumu.
Wha--?
Are you saying
I won that round?
Shoulda seen that coming, huh?
What the hell's so funny?
Don't rest on your laurels yet,
noble adversary.
She was the weakest.
The true test
has only just begun.
Tremble at the
thought, maggot!
Let's get the second round
under way, shall we?
Elite Two!
Oh yeah!
Time to bring some
genius to the table!
Oh crap.
Awesome-sauce!
Wait, you're-- Since when
are you a part of the whole
ninja vampire thing?
This is insane!
I work part-time.
Huh?
If you don't stop glaring at me
I'm going to break your neck.
This one comes off
a lot more real.
The elite team's definitely
throwing its A-game at us now.
You twerps have
five seconds to order!
5-4-3-2-1 bzzt!
Uh.
Don't do this to me, man.
You laugh like that,
I think you snapped.
This is how a bitch-off
should be; a no holds bared
free-for-all where
it's anybody's guess
if she's gonna strangle you.
That'd usually be bad.
Ha!
My enormous IQ
gives me the advantage.
I'm not the kind of girl
who's gonna starting battin'
her eyelashes over advice.
She's got a point.
We'll have to tailor
our approach carefully.
The straightforward method
isn't going to get us very far.
What to do?
More water, please.
Huh?
Hey Cowgirl, get your
saddle bags over here!
Coming.
Lookin' kinda
shaky there, kiddo.
I've got this,
leave me alone--
Let me help.
My hero.
I'm the one who pours water
for Ayumu, thank you very much!
Now sit the hell
down and drink!
And order your dessert
'cause I'm bringing it!
Okay.
Uh.
Why are you so pissy
all of a sudden?
'Cause I'm the only waitress
you should care about!
A woman's heart has reasons
that reason knows nothing of.
Get out of there, Two.
This round goes to the vermin.
We made it through another one?
I was totally kidding!
Don't do this to me, please!
I demand a rematch immediately!
Elite Three.
Seraphim, It's my turn.
She's in bondage gear!
Oh.
Seems as though my handiwork
disturbs you, gentlemen.
I cobbled it
especially for today.
You didn't even know
we'd be here!
I'd just like to say
that sitting at a table
with pieces of human garbage
like you counts as a new low.
Words can't describe
my revulsion to this.
I've never been so humiliated.
That's right!
Pull no punches;
tell us we're worthless!
I'll thank you not to speak,
as every syllable out of
that rancid pie hole which
serves you for a mouth
makes my ears secrete puss.
Yes.
Every insult brings him
closer to ecstasy.
Oh, Sera.
I'm out, bro!
So it appears you're
the only one remaining.
I have a special request.
What?
I want you to
make me something.
Whatever you're playing at,
Seraphim is not
allowed in the kitchen!
That's cool.
Would you please, though?
Uh.
I suppose so.
As you wish.
I thought seasoning it with
nitroglycerin would give it
a little extra kick.
She's good.
That dish would take out
a wildebeest in
the throes of passion!
Let us hope he can't
force it down.
Impossible!
I'd like another.
Ugh!
You don't have
to choke on it for my sake!
No really.
Aside from the blowin' up
part there at the end,
it was delicious.
Good for you.
I would expect nothing
less from the mind
attached to that delectable
ass, my filthy darling.
But let's see you pit
wits with Elite Four.
What?
This is bullshit!
You'd tell me if this outfit
was too much, right?
It's just, I'm a little
self-conscious about
how short the skirt is.
No, it looks perfect.
Anything you wear is
automatically made fabulous.
She's supposed to be
acting that way over you!
And he's trumped before
the final battle even begins.
We're finished.
I got nothing.
This one's a total wash.
Wait.
I won?
Are you serious?
Well that was a battle
for the ages, wasn't it?
I have no idea.
What just happened?
That one only counts
as a scrimmage
for the real last round!
Like at a demolition derby?
I can take whatever
you dish out, Saras!
Give me your best shot!
Ha!
You think that
I'm your final opponent?
Excuse me?
The one you'll be facing off
with is someone I scouted out
especially for today.
Who in the hell
is she talking about?
Me!
Kanami Mihara!
I am completely
and totally screwed.
She doesn't have
a ga-ga bone in her body.
I'm about to have my ass
handed to me on a plate!
So, you're, uh,
working part-time.
Yeah.
The pay's pretty good but
I gotta tell ya; if I knew
I'd be dealing with you
I would have taken work
grooming some
old guy's butt hair.
Yeah, well, sorry
I came out to eat.
Why aren't you wearing
a pretty little dress?
Look, that whole thing,
I mean, seriously.
It's not what it seems.
No kidding?
Must be a hell of a story.
Not that I wanna hear it.
Just do us all a favor
and keep the frilly crap
under control, huh?
It messes with Taeko's head.
Look, whatever
you might think,
I never meant
to freak her out, 'kay?
Hurry and lose!
Huh?
Two things: you're boring me
to tears, and I'm not even
technically supposed
to be on shift today.
But I can't just give up.
Poor guy doesn't have
a snowball's chance in hell.
You're finished, Ayumu.
Man up and admit defeat.
Those scrumptious
hind quarters are mine
whether you like it or not!
So I was, uh, thinkin'
maybe you, uh, could poss--
Ayumu!
Orito?
You fought like a beast, dude.
Now it's my turn
to get your back!
He's about to tank
their chances even lower
than they were before, huh?
I'll take over
from here, my friend!
Prepare to meet
your match, Kanami!
Oh, this is adorkable.
Should I be shaking
in my stilettos, or what?
Kanami!
I love you!
Idiot, you never go all in
without at least a backup plan!
I'm sorry!
She's a Martian ice queen;
what were we going to do?
Ugh!
Next time just stay unconscious
and let me handle it, huh?
Leave him alone.
He was only trying to do
what he could as your friend!
What?
Seriously?
Did we just win this thing?
How the hell
was that going ga-ga?
I believe that's a wrap.
We made it!
We survived to the end!
Oh, come on!
I let my guard down for,
like, a millisecond!
And that
millisecond was enough.
It was a great fight
til the end, though.
I hope you die
in a fire, Orito!
I'll never wash
this hand as long as I live.
You really should.
It's got to be said:
you put on quite a spectacle.
Nicely done, Eucliwood.
Funny, I never pegged you
as a connoisseur of pageantry.
How'd you know her actual name?
Well, you know, I just
happen to be an Underworlder.
What?
We're home!
You guys were out late.
Tell me you didn't.
Haruna insisted
we buy you one so--
We were in the neighborhood.
Boy, work sure was
somethin' else today.
Don't just sit there,
make me some tea!
Sure.
I could go for some myself.
This is about a far
from something I'd put in
my collection as you can get
and still call it a model!
I get the wrong one?
Was the power out?
Did you have to
shop in the dark?
Well I think it looks cool!
Welcome to the model workshop!
Hooray workshop!
Girly applause!
Let's get prepared!
First you check that none
of the parts are missing!
Then rinse off the mould-release
agent with soap and water!
I'm opting out of
this segment, girls.
But it won't be as much fun
without the real Eu!
You've just gotta help!
You can read aloud
from the instruction manual!
Let me just talk to Ayumu.
Oh, that's sweet!
Good for the two of you!
Eu and Ayumu,
sittin' in a tree.
K-I-S--