As many of you know,
Mr. Kurisu is kind of
on sabbatical for
the next few weeks, so...
Let's all extend
a warm welcome to our
substitute homeroom teacher...
Say hi to Miss Rie.
Hello, everyone...
I can't tell you how
excited I am to be here.
Awesome!
Isn't that the lady
from the mixer?
I would kill
for her waistline.
You'd think being raised from
the dead to slash through
high school as a cross-dressing
occult warrior would guarantee
a lonely existence.
But I've learned that
no zombie is an island.
And now that Miss Ariel has
moved to the head of the class,
so to speak, looks like things
are getting even more crowded.
No rest for wicked, huh?
Look...
Whatever you're cooking up here
I think I'm entitled to know!
Can't you put it together?
Chris has us at Def Con One...
You know from firsthand
experience the havoc
she could wreak if
we just let her run loose.
I was caught off guard
-I can still --!
Answer me this.
She was my teacher
once upon a time...
You think you're cut out to take
on someone of that caliber?
I do.
Very well!
Then it's my job
to make sure your butt
can cash the check
your mouth just wrote!
What kind of test?
The kind that if I fail
my memories get erased.
Memories of what, exactly?
A thousand times no!
I can't bear the thought of
being exiled from your brain!
Wow...
Dumbass!
I get deported if you
go back to the old you,
so your dumb memories aren't
the only thing at stake...!
You damn well better
pass with flying colors!
I'll be lucky to pass
with colors at half-mast
for all I know what's in store.
I'll be your new student
teacher, Miss Haruna...
'sup, yo?
Subtle as a heart attack.
Thanks.
Since when is she on the
student teacher program?
Well, she's been turning up
in Home Ec a lot to show us
how to cook eggs, so I guess
for a little while at least...
Score...!
My harem fantasy is coming true
one hot new teacher at a time!
Today's lesson:
the science of fried eggs.
Um, excuse me.
Where is that in the text book?
Welcome to a little thing
I call real world experience,
where textbooks are for losers.
Oh.
Slow down, genius
-you're losing us.
Gotta admire her style.
Something she was a little
short on before coming here...
Clearly someone's been
a good influence on her.
Yeah, who knows?
Step one: crack that
puppy into your beaker.
Is it weird that
I'm all excited to learn
her famous fried egg
recipe, or what?
I know, right?
Next you mix for
all you're worth
or I don't even wanna know ya.
Then insert your philosopher's
stone -or nearest equivalent.
Not really sure
what that'd be.
If this is your first time,
I suggest using an eraser.
That's the secret?
Now, I'm stirring
at a speed of Mach 3,
which you wanna do
for about half an hour.
Is it supposed to--
Oh son of a...!
Interesting factoid:
fried eggs have a very
similar consistency to slime.
The formula for both
is next to identical.
Nice to know that now!
I've known professional
chemists who'd give their arm
for a culture this large...
Excellently done, Haruna.
Woo-hoo!
Compliment from teach!
Hold on a sec...
What is it doing?
Whoa!
Indecent slime is indecent!
Have no fear, children.
It only dissolves clothing.
Yeah!
The slime is still rated PG-13!
I didn't do this so you'd
get your rocks off, jackass!
That's the furthest thing
from my mind right now!
It's like being stuck
inside a really pervy anime!
My poor students trusted me
and I've let them down!
So it leaves the socks
and underwear intact...
What kind of bullshit
is that supposed to be?
Shut your pie-hole, dude!
Whatever can be done to rectify
this peccadillo, Ayumu?
Time to improvise!
I'm rather eager to see
what you'll come up with.
Ha...!
Human limitations don't
apply to the undead--
Aw, Come on!
Crap!
Stay with me, Taeko!
Here!
Give me your hand!
You're practically naked!
Don't come near me!
Orito!
Incoming!
Haruna!
Listen...
You need to know this.
I only took this stupid
teaching job so that
when the time comes
you'd have some backup!
Yeah, duh...
Don't thrash, okay?
Gah!
Don't touch my lady parts!
I asked you not to thrash--
I've seen quite enough.
Holy crap.
Oh...
Extra credit!
My eyes!
Help me!
I'm blind!
Uh...
Thank you, teach...
Couldn't ha'
done it without ya!
Such a shame...
For a while there, I fully
expected you to power through.
Huh?
Not to be rude, but you'll
have to explain why I'd let
freaks like you
stay in my house.
Moron...
Sorry...
The name is Ayumu.
And you're also a moron!
Well this is a most
unfortunate turn of events.
Sorry, I wish there
was a better way...
But in the interest
of keeping the boy safe,
it's best we let him
luxuriate in blissful ignorance.
What you really mean is that we
have to protect Ayumu from us!
But she's right,
Haruna -it's no use...
This is for his own good.
I think we should get going.
Um...
Excuse me...
I don't see why you
have to leave, necessarily...
Fact I kinda feel
like I want you to stay.
You're such a mess.
C'mon, please?!
Sticky situation, huh?
I'll just say it...
Coming from me this
might be a little odd, but
I sincerely feel walking away
now would be admitting defeat.
Head Teacher, please!
I'm beggin' you, here...!
You can't let Ayumu
forget about us...!
It's not right!
Well, I haven't
finished my tea yet...
I don't wish to be rude...
Perhaps there's
time for another test?
Seriously, that
would be awesome!
You'll have your
work cut out for you.
If, traveling through
his mental topography,
you're able to make
contact with his core self,
his memories of the past
few months should reemerge.
Best of luck.
This is phenomenally reckless.
I think she's the sort of person
whose burden requires her
to be reckless
from time to time.
Lady Hellscythe,
you're voice has been restored!
Only because we're projecting
ourselves onto the astral plane,
free from our bodily tethers...
Once we've returned,
I'll be mute again.
Magic is quite strange...
Oft times even cruel.
Dumb Ayumu!
Wassup?
I didn't mean you!
Uh, sorry...?
I'm guessin' my actual
form is givin' you gals
a bit of a headache right now...
What are you
supposed to be exactly?
Sort of like
a leftover memory...
At least I think so.
Come.
As long as you're sure
I'm not too much of a hassle.
Ah...
Those are the breaks, kiddo...
If you're going to be
an exemplar of our kind,
a trial this simple should
be a walk in the park.
Otherwise...
Jeepers, my head seems
like a pretty crazy place.
I've seen crazier.
Actually as minds go,
this one suits you well.
huh...
What kind of person was I?
A repugnant maggot.
Score!
Is it me or does this look like
the stage for a burlesque show?
Nyuh-uh...
We're in boss country!
I'm gonna go out on
a limb here and assume I was
a little awkward...
Welcome, dirt flecks.
Glad you could make it.
Please, girls:
call me Asmodeus.
Do what?
He's a demon.
The vilest indiscretions
of lust incarnate.
Someone's a know-it-all,
aren't they...?
Good thing you're cute ...
He's really grossing me out!
This explains a lot more
than I want it to.
Ladies.
My name's Beelzebub.
I am called Behemoth.
Wow.
Rather awkward.
Ugh...
That's the truth.
I'm Lucifer.
There's no way you guys
are part of my mind!
Call me Leviathan.
Stop announcing yourselves!
It's freakin' weird!
For the record,
it makes you look
like a bunch
of adolescent tools.
Satan.
These are aspects
of Ayumu's unconscious.
Hold on...
You mean these
chodes are part of me?
Why do I suddenly feel like
I'm crawling with poison ivy?!
Not to rub salt in your wounds,
but it's a little unnerving that
you took this long to react.
We're here to retrieve
our friend's memory...!
Get in the way and be prepared
for my foot up your ass!
Full of piss
and vinegar, I see.
You think you've got
what it takes to tango
with Ayumu's sins made flesh?
If so, I highly advise
you get a second opinion.
Or at least promise
to make this interesting.
For the record,
I refuse to accept
responsibility
for these assholes!
They're his adolescent
coping mechanism...
If we can get
past them, we're in.
Really?
In that case...
Prepare for an ass-beating!
On the astral plane I can
take whatever form I choose!
Nomobuyo!
Oh shit...
Oshi!
Son of a bitch!
Hashitawa!
Dokeda!
Gunmiicha deh ribura!!
Wusses.
So much for his
coping mechanism.
That was easier than expected.
Don't think you have triumphed.
We are the Alpha and the Omega;
Stop talking like that!
You're not all there is to me!
Huh...
So, yeah...
Let's go!
Hello...?
Hey Ayamu?
There you are!
Yo...!
Get off your butt...!
We're blowin' this
popsicle stand!
What'd be the point?
Huh?
Like it matters.
Don't even start, Ayumu;
we're taking you home.
For your information,
the name is Belphegor.
Whatever...
Let's go already.
The lightweights
you hustled past
to get in here
were just bouncers
-they'd kowtow to
anything in a skirt.
Your friend's real form
won't be so easy to subdue.
You said Belphegor...
The incarnation of slothfulness.
So his true form's
a lazy ass...?
I hate to say it, but this is
making a lot more sense to me.
All I wanted was to follow the
path of least resistance...
Then you came knocking down
my door with your drama,
your bullshit and
whatever the hell else...
You don't represent his final
thoughts on the matter,
you're just one aspect.
Are you so sure...?
I mean, no doubt you're a
powerful sorceress and all,
but I don't think mind-reading
falls under your skill set.
If you could, you'd blush
at how hard it's been for me
to be nice up to now.
No one asked you to be nice...
So don't.
You think Ayumu Aikawa is
really a "caring soul"...?
He's probably just trying
to keep the peace between
all you hotties, the guy
sounds like a doormat.
Ha!
You're full of it!
As of today, his caring side
goes on permanent vacation.
No more ass-kissing!
Ah.
Come back to yourself,
have we?
I, uh...
I think so...
Could you, uh,
give me a second?
Sure?
And I'd like it if you called
me Belphegor from now on...
Think you can do that?
I can...
I suppose...
Yes.
I'll also accept
"Alterna-dude Ayumu." ...
Point being,
the old me's gone bye-bye.
Do you mind if I call you
Dark Ayumu just to keep
things a bit simpler?
Fine.
Whatever...
As long as you know who's
givin' you the business.
Payback's a bitch!
Oh dear
Clothes really do
make the woman, huh?
Sorry, I was lettin' Lust take
the wheel there for a sec,
my bad...
You try to keep
the boggarts at bay,
but the bastards just won't
give you a moment's peace.
I'm assuming Haruna
and the gang failed
to retrieve your memories?
No, They got it right...
I'm afraid this was
the real me all along.
Ah.
I see.
Gotta run; don't
wanna be late for school.
I'll have to kill you on
account of that panty shot,
just so you know.
Boop beep boop!
Holy crap...!
Where's Ayumu?!
Oh, you just missed him,
I'm afraid.
You let that recalcitrant thing
loose upon the world...?!
Great.
Yeah.
I brought enough for everyone.
Okay...
so what are you supposed to be?
You look like you
just got out of bed...
Everything's such
a royal pain in the ass...
The hell do we even
bother to breathe?
Somebody please tell me he's
not starting an emo phase.
No offense, but I uh...
I mean you look like
you've got a lot more
on your mind than usual...
No shit...
You'd think that keeping all
of the world's darkest secrets
would be a breeze.
I envy the cow-eyed ignorance
you jerks nourish yourselves on.
Wanna see the nurse?
You'll have to excuse your
brooding classmate, children:
he's not feeling
quite himself today...
Try not to engage with him.
Mr. Aikawa, I expect
to see you after class,
thank you very much.
Only if you promise
to be a bitch.
You little cockroach!
Haruna?
I'll teach you to be
an unappreciative maggot!
Clear a path, children.
Remind me why I should be scared
of a gal who's lost her power?
Seriously?
Thanks, babe -but I'd much
rather you sit on my face,
if it's all the same to you.
Bona fide sexual harassment!
Gotta say; the fact that
you never talk makes you
every hot-blooded
male's wet dream.
Owie owie owie owie owie...!
Attention all ladies: Ayumu
does not speak for all men!
You and me are
stepping outside!!!
So we're gonna hash it out
on the school yard, huh...?
You know, if I gave a damn,
I could see myself
getting nostalgic.
I know my dirty darling...
And this is not who he is.
Whoever's in there...
I am not a fan.
Do we really have to do
this now, sweetheart...?
Seems like such
a waste of time.
Okay...
Not something Ayumu'd say.
Actually...
I'm not having
a hard time buying it.
You go, neckwear-mancer!
Kick this imposter's
lazy butt into next week!
Alright.
Kinda cool.
300%!
I really want you
right now, babe.
No.
You're not the Ayumu
I fell in love with.
Huh...?
I'm not a friggin' psychic
-you've got to write it down.
You care too much, babe;
that's your problem.
Interesting.
Sorry, toots.
Not a good tactic...
Don't get upset, though...
You've only got
yourself to blame.
She might be on to something.
Stop that...!
I'm not...
I can't...
You...
No...
I mean...
I...
What's with the
waterworks, neckwear?
The real Ayumu's coming back
-that's a good thing!
Give it to him real good!
I won't cave in to this!
I am not your
precious Ayumu...!
My name is Belphegor
and I'm in charge here!
You're Dumb Ayumu
so shut your stupid face!
Come back to us!
My name is...
Ayumu...
We need you!
Eu...!
What the hell
is wrong with you!
Stop it!
Snap out of it right now or I'll
cut you into a million pieces!
Huh?
Oh, right.
I'm, uh.
Wait...
Why you gotta be
such a stupid jerk?
Anything you'd like to say
to all of us, worm food?
There's, uh...
No place like home...?
Oh, and...
Would you mind
grabbing my lower body?
You pervert...!
What do you take me for?!
How predictable...
We could've gone to hell
and back for you twice over
and you'd still be
an insufferable prig.
I suppose there are
worse ways to pass a test
than by the skin of your teeth.
Most people live their lives
without ever knowing it,
but the world is filled with
all kinds of weird stuff...
Despite being human,
this Ayumu fellow is
a fascinating creature,
don't you think?
Meow meow!
Forgive me for letting
things get out of hand.
Meow meow meow!
Knowing what I do now,
though, I'd do it all again.
Well, hope you're
not the jealous type,
'cause Lady Ariel's taken
a shine to your little protégé.
The more the merrier,
that's what I say.
That's a relief, 'cause I'm
taking the kid under my wing,
too, ...
Now you're just being catty.
You know, I do
need an assistant.
Can't believe I was
on the brink of being
indifferent to all this.
What a shame that
would've been, right?
Good thing my memories
made it in one piece...
You'd be sleeping under
an overpass otherwise.
Ha!
Bet you'd like to believe
that, wouldn't you...?
For the record I have tons
of places I could've crashed,
so don't go thinkin' this place
is special to me 'cause of you!
Why would I get
that impression?
Could you stop being a maggot
for five minutes, please?
Oh, hey.
Not that I expect much of you,
but once the five minutes is up,
by all means, carry on.
Kind of nice that things
are back to normal, huh...?
Even if by "normal"
I mean whatever this is.
Wouldn't have it otherwise.
I can't believe
it's the final episode!
Don't say that!
It's not true!
We'll totally
be back next week!
Look at it this way:
endings mean the start
of something else.
I may be cute,
but I know when someone's
blowing smoke up my butt!
As long as you don't forget us,
you can blow all the smoke
up our butts you want!
Remember your counterparts
on the flip-side!
And if you enjoyed the show,
that goes for you people too...
Alrighty?
Oh fantastic, now she's blowing
smoke up the audiences' butt!
Bye-bye!
Please try not to forget us!
Thank you for watching!