Yello?
This is some kind
of joke, right?
What?
Seriously?
Ticklish under the ribs?
I'm sorry?
That's Chris'
Achilles Heel...?
Please tell me
Kyoko's pulling my leg.
Oh wow...
That takes me back.
When we were little,
Chris was guaranteed to pee
herself if you kept at it
long enough.
Good times.
Okay, explain something: If
she's so easy to incapacitate,
why is this such
a royal pain in the ass?!
No idea...
I mean, she's
unbelievably powerful,
but the gal has had
her share of losses.
Wait, what?
The Queen of Villiers
got the best of her
in a little one-on-one...
The aforementioned King of the
Night took her down a peg not
so long ago...
Wow, him too?
Matter of fact, an
Underworlder relatively famous
for giving Chris the biz
just happens to live
in your neck of the woods.
Believe you me, by the time the
dust settled on that fight it
was the stuff of legend.
To wrestle Haruna's
pilfered magical powers away
from the clutches
of a pink-haired imp,
our hero must find a way to
defeat an enemy whose reputation
for havoc is as enormous
as her stature is adorable.
From whom can he enlist aid
in this, Gaia's latest trial?
All right...
So...
There's yet another powerful
under-worlder that's slumming
it up in our neck
of the woods, huh?
That's right...
What's the story
on this one anyway?
Wait, what...?
You mean they actually exist?!
Is S-class really
that big of deal?
Bigger deal
than your stupid head!
It takes a whole group of
Magical Garment Girls to deal
with Triple A-Class Megalos,
and they're a rung below
the S-Classers: you can
run a whole army of us
at those guys and they
wouldn't even flinch!
Okay, but if that's the case...
Maybe you should get off
your magic ass and do something?
Hey.
Stockpiling awesome here.
This was back before Villiers
invaded the Underworld;
when I still had a voice,
and a good deal of magic
at my disposal...
Why tarry you here
so often, milady?
I love the view.
Yea, it is breathtaking
though the highest poetry would
fail to capture its essence.
'Tis something beyond words.
This kingdom...
All its vistas...
I gladly lay down
my life to inure.
A brigade of stout-hearted
warriors congregated voluntarily
to defend the Underworld
against Villiers.
They were called
the Seventh Abyss.
Thus it begins...
The dark.
The poison of war.
I will meet them.
Naegleria, wait...
I pledged to defend this world
even if it means my life,
Your Majesty.
And so the mightiest
Underworlder struck flint
against the mightiest
Garment Girl.
Mind you, this was well
before the Megalos served us;
she fended off Villiers
almost single-handedly.
"Her strength and
bravery endure in legend."
Guess I forget how much
bad blood there is
between the two kingdoms.
Shocking.
How tragic is it to have the
attention span of a ferret?
How can you stand
to live under the same roof
if your people
are sworn enemies?
Just 'cause the brass
declares war doesn't mean
I make it my beef...
I'm trying to live
in the moment, you know?
Can we establish that this
warrior is as trustworthy
as she is strong?
"She personally fashioned
the gauntlets that kept
my powers from running amok, so
I'd say she's a safe bet." Okay.
Good point.
So should I just knock on her
door and ask for help or what?
No way...!
Are you out of your mind?!
Huh?
You have no clue what
you're up against, do you?
Apparently not...
Ugh...
The cost in lives
could be catastrophic...
Whatever happens,
my friend -don't call me.
What the hell, man?!
I'll send you an email.
Best of luck.
Shimomura being scared
gives me the bends.
There you are.
How's that ass?
Knock it off.
Surely you mean
"knock it off, Kirara." ...
Knock it off Lovely Kirara
if this were a concert...
Speaking of which, love...
In two days I'll be giving
the performance of a lifetime.
Your attendance is expected.
Ah...
Way to take the guerilla
approach to marketing...
Fine.
These better not
be nosebleeds, though.
What is that?
This?
Milk coffee.
Perfect...
That's legal tender
for the ticket.
Yeah...
It's kinda creepy that
you want to drink after me...
I'm afraid it's the milk coffee
or nothing, my darling...
Give it to momma.
Umm...
Look...
I'll stop by the concert
if there's time.
What does that mean?
Don't get upset!
I'll come, I promise.
You promise...?
Stand where I can see you...?
Right up front?
Sure...
I can do that...
Just look for me
near the speakers.
I can get to like this whole
"I promise" thing from you.
And not just because of...
that sweet ass!
So she can act like
a normal girl.
... that sweet ass!
Aw, seriously?!
Not home, maybe...?
Excuse me?
Hello?
My name's Ayumu...
Um, hello...?
Oh my god oh my god
oh my god oh my god
I'm chin deep
in milk bladders!
Don't get a boner,
don't get a boner...!
Uh, please don't
be dead or anything...
Yes...
Thank you.
I was wondering if there's any
chance I can get another day?
Oh.
There's an overage fee...
Ah.
Well I guess if
that's your policy...
Insanely spank-worthy bod...
No, no -I'll have it by tonight.
Sorry about that...
I have quite a bit on my plate.
So...
You draw stuff
like this, huh...?
Nice work, Miss Naegleria.
Don't say "Miss"
it makes me feel old...
Matter of fact call me Nene...
No point standing on ceremony.
Sure thing, Nene...
And if I may get
right to the point...
Oh come on...!
I'm not a fanboy!
Damn it, I'm here on
very important business!
Can you please
try to stay awake?!
Hey, hey...
I was just resting my...
Hope has left us!
Okay, I'm awake...
Look, your Eucliwood's
friend, right...?
So, yeah...
You've changed your hair.
No offense, but how
would you know...?
Anyway, about this Magical
Garment Girl Chris debacle...
Ah...
Oh, yeah...
I guess it will take someone
of my caliber to take
that little minx down, huh?
Does that mean we can
count on you to help us?
What...?
Oh honey, no...
You don't know
what you're asking...
If Chris and I scrape shields
there'll be an all out war
between Villiers and the
Underworld right here
in our own backyard--
But why?
It's simple politics...
She and I are the strongest
of our respective people...
Whatever, look, I'm not
bowing out, per se...
But I am gonna need something
in the way of quid pro quo.
And that would be what...?
Give me a hand with
my manuscript...
Sound good?
How in the world does she think
one person's help is gonna
push her through to
tomorrow's deadline?
Just a gazillion more to go!
I'll totally have to
skip out on the concert now.
Yell-o!
Haruna's Mortuary
-you stab 'em we slab 'em.
How can I help you?
Oh good, it's you.
Listen, I'm up to my eyeballs
in this thing right now
and nothing less than
the help of genius will do.
Ha...!
Well, go on!
I've got a map up in my room...
Yep-yep!
All over it!
They were all out of
the diet kind...
Oh man...
This can't be good for me.
It just can't.
Ah, you're back...!
Thanks for the grub run.
You're a doll.
Dear god, I can totally
feel them touching my back!
Ugh...!
Wake up!
If someone saw us like this
I'd never hear the end of it!
Aaaand...
I just jinxed myself...
Come on!
Please...?
There's already enough crap
about me going around!
Oh...
sorry.
It's okay.
Getting up now.
Yes, I'm coming.
Alrighty...
Must've gone away.
That's a relief...
No harm, no foul -right?
I see nothing...
Absolutely nothing...!
Hello--
Damn it, Haruna!
You're late!
Um.
I beg your pardon?
Oh, sorry.
I thought -never mind.
What's up?
You're still coming, yes?
Tomorrow night?
You bet.
I haven't forgotten.
As I thought.
I just wanted to make sure
you still have your ticket.
You do, right?
It's on me right now.
No worries.
So you're really gonna
try and make it...
Well, yeah.
I said I would.
Relax.
Very well, then...
I shall be waiting.
Sure took you long enough...
What the...?
Ugh!
I get so lonely when you're
not around-I couldn't stand
not being near you
for another moment!
Step aside!
Take a wild guess why
we've come here, maggot farm.
You wanted to help me out of
the goodness of your heart...
I'm so disgusted with you
right now, I have half a mind
to dispense with
talk altogether!
Don't kill him, Leaf Lady
-it's not worth it!
This paragon of innocence left
the house a little while ago
to lend you a hand...
All I could make out between
her torrential sobs was
"Ayumu has become
a Sexual Harassment Overlord!"
That's an exaggeration...!
I don't sob!
What do you take me for?!
Gah!
You can guilt-trip the pervert
without having to make up
lies about me, damn it!
Look, she just
misunderstood...!
I...
Gaaah!
Wow!
Did this place
become Grand Central
when I was sleeping or what?
Did you cut your hair?
Ah.
Of course...
Who am I talking to
-you're the same as ever.
Hey!
Don't be fraternizing
with the bimbo
who tempted Ayumu with
her giggly-flop bazongas!
Stop!
It wasn't what it looked like!
I'll put it to you politely...
Was there or was there not
any untoward behavior
between you and this tramp?
C'mon...
Even if there was,
what are you gonna do?
Boys have no control
over themselves.
No!
I'm not ready for puberty!
You shameless maggot!
Well, as long as you're here,
you might as well help us out.
Here Eucliwood, you can
color in all of these bits
that are X-ed out.
And you- Haruna, yeah?
You think you got a couple
of castle scenes in ya?
It's okay.
She's saying she needs
a genius's help on
the background stuff.
Ah, yes of course...!
Well, if you insist.
I'm more than happy to be
the gofer, if you would like.
Perfect!
You can start by cleaning up!
You know, I really
don't care for your tone...
But this place is a mess...
What's the matter?
You're darn right it is.
Heh.
What better medium for
telling Your Majesty's story?
I get it...
These are the soldiers
from the Seventh Abyss.
Sort of.
It's pure fantasy...
I pretend that the King of the
Night never did what he did...
That Eucliwood never
actually lost her voice...
Basically that we all
lived happily ever after.
Hey, when life hands you lemons
you use what you've got
to work with, right?
Yeah...
It'd be nice, huh?
We might get in under
the wire at this rate.
Alpha males...
Kitty cat tails...
Oh no...
Please tell me
she's dying yarn.
I'm frightened, my lover; please
don't let whatever's in the pot
crawl out and eat me
while I'm sleeping...
Creme l'diabolique.
I don't speak French,
but it sounds bad.
It gets it's name from
being so good as to blow
the lid off of hell.
Yeah, sure...!
Or send us there!
Boo-ya!
What are you doing?
That's a background?!
No.
That's what I call
a castle scene.
It's stealing focus!
Hot hot hot hot
hot hot hot!!!!
Nice going, fire marshal!
You idiot!!!
I'm awake.
Definitely awake...
Bit close for comfort...
Another second and
I'd have been out...
Not good.
Uh...
How goes it, gang?
Um...
Actually...
Not so hot.
Looks like you used it
as a coffee filter!
I, can't tell you
how sorry we all are...
Oh, it's hardly the end
of the world you guys...
Besides, I can draw
manga whenever I want.
Nene...
what if...
Uh, I mean
there's still time...
We can fix this!
Please allow us to.
Well...
If you're that broken up,
I guess you should.
Right...
We won't let you down, promise!
You should get some rest...
Here.
So...
If anyone wants to sleep--
♪  Shining just like a ray
of light Can't help but look ♪
♪ But don't you dare put
your filthy hands on me  ♪
All right!
Who's ready to put their
necks on the chopping block?!
♪ Your eyes may
give me what I need ♪
Undying worship's how I feed
'Cause I live in your fantasy
Time when somebody passes by me
A perfect vision
of timeless beauty
Creature of the night
Lives among
♪ you here at home--all right!
I won't show my fangs...  ♪
You got a hot date
or something, kiddo?
You seem to be
obsessed with my clock...
Either it looks like something
or you need to be somewhere.
Oh, uh...
You can go if you need to...
I think we'll be good
on our own with the rest.
No way...
You and me had a deal.
And you've held up your end.
You all have.
Thanks, hon...
Eucliwood will be very pleased
with the way it turned out.
Now get outta here.
Done.
I'm pathetic.
I can't beat Chris.
I can't help Haruna.
Look at me.
I can't even keep
a simple promise.
The hell I can't!
He actually made it.
Who's ready for
the grand finale?!
If you're feelin' suicidal,
show me your neck!
Sorry I'm late.
Knock it off with
the groveling...
It's silly, you haven't
done anything wrong.
Sure I have.
I mean--
You're a man of your word.
Sure...
I can do that...
Just look for me
near the speakers.
Okay, so you weren't
near the speakers,
but that's a small thing...
You said you'd come
to the concert and you did.
Don't think I don't
know how busy you are.
I wish I could've seen more.
Look, that you came at all
is more than adequate, love...
It was childish of me
to force a promise on you
in the first place...
I'll try not to be so
disproportionately needy
in future...
Don't say that.
You're perfect
the way you are...
Seriously.
So I told Saras
what she wanted to hear.
What else was I gonna do?
Thank you, my dirty darling.
I don't suppose we can
find a different nickname?
Well...
We could, but it wouldn't
have the umph of the one
already lodged in my psyche.
That's a lame excuse.
I'm not one-hundred
percent about this...
Feels like we have an
obligation to be fighty.
Lighten up, huh...?
No reason we can't enjoy a
little girl time off the clock.
Aw, that's the stuff!
That Ayumu kid came over
to my place today.
Oh yeah?
What'd you think?
I think he's...
unique.
I gotta tell ya,
I'm tempted to adopt him
as my special little helper.
Kid must've really brought his
A-game to make you say that...
Guess the Underworld's
primo badass has a soft side.
Yeah, well...
My soft side
can still roll you.
Oh, I'm sure it could...
Heh.
Alright, Mister...
Bring on the fried tofu!
Coming right up, ladies.
Careful now, it's hot.
Crap...
Crap.
Why you gotta be so harsh?!
Manga's hard!
Let's see you do it!
Yeah!
Fine then.
Look, Actual Eu wrote a Yaoi?!
OMG that's hot!
The cover's making me
lightheaded -ah!
So pretty...
What is it about
two cute guys in love?
Show us more, Eu!
Show us more!