Today's forecast...
With these cloudy skies, I doubt
we'll see the sun at all.
There's a seventy-five percent
chance of scattered showers.
So if you plan to be
out today, bring an umbrella,
because you'll need it!
We'll, I'm headin'
to school, so see ya later.
What a perfect day.
Are you serious?
Yeah!
Was that quiz tough or what?
I used to be like them.
Just your average
high school student.
My life was pretty carefree.
I thought those days
would last forever.
But as I found out
recently, they don't.
Are weather people ever right?
Dude, please tell me you'll
lend me your physics notes!
Sure thing.
Sweet! You saved my life, Ayumu!
Then you can repay me
by buying me lunch today.
Much like today's forecast,
my previously held beliefs
on life were wrong.
Most people live their lives
without ever knowing it, but the
world is full of weird stuff.
Things like magic and monsters,
and the thing that I've become.
No, kid, wait!
Aww, don't worry. I'm a zombie.
Oh, crap!
Noooo! I'm not some
weirdo flying pervert,
so please don't look at my junk!
Did I imagine that kid?
No, there's my hairpiece.
Oh, man. If I weren't
a zombie, I'd be street pizza.
What's with your hair today pal?
It looks like a porcupine
decided to camp out
on top of your head.
Hey I'm home.
I guess I just pumped the thing
a little too hard this morning.
Oh man that sounds bad. Uhhh.
Hey that reminds me, what's
the difference between...
Um, Eu? Did you hear me?
Uh, I don't know.
Neither one of
'em is in my garage.
With a porcupine,
the pricks are on the outside.
Oh, sorry. I know I'm late,
but I kinda got creamed
by a truck on the way home.
Geez! This is just your
tough-as-nails exterior, right?
What you really meant
to say instead was:
Ayumu, I'm oh-so-hungry.
Would you please
hurry up and make me dinner?
And I feel dirty, so you
can scrub me til I'm clean.
Yeah. Of course.
That's what she meant.
Aw. Don't worry
about it you know
what they say
about "too many cooks."
Anything exciting happen
around here today?
Ohh! My nap today would've
been much nicer with you.
That sounds so nice.
Hey, you've got some
rice stuck on your--
It sucks that
zombies can feel pain!
Uh-no. If you hadn't brought
me back, I'd still be dead,
and a fractured wrist
is way better than that.
I wasn't trying to
complain just then.
Besides, if I'd stayed dead...
I couldn't search for
the person who killed me.
Eucliwood Hellscythe - Eu for
short - necromancer of Hades.
She started living
here a month ago.
But I still can't
say I really know her.
Orito. Hey, what's up?
Holy crap, are you
watching the news?
Uh, no.
Dude, there's been
another murder!
How many does this make now?
I think one was too many.
No joke, a serial killer on the
loose is some scary shit, man.
You should probably
be extra careful
since you live alone, ya know.
Yeah, sure, "Mom."
You don't have to be a dick.
All kidding aside, I'm serious
about stopping the killer.
That's why I go out
every night in search of him.
I've gotta stop him from
doing what he did to me,
to anyone else in this city.
But it's a big place. Finding
him is easier said than done.
Strange as it sounds,
I find this spot to be
a lot more calming than home.
It shouldn't be
much of a surprise.
I am a zombie after all.
Yep. This is my new happy place.
Holy crap!
What in the hell is that!
And now, you lousy bastard, it's
time for you to friggin' die!
The hell? What was that?
Some kind of cosplayer?
Hey, wait. If you attacked me,
then that must mean...
You, you're the
serial killer, aren't you!
What?! I wasn't attacking you!
You just got in the
way of that freak!
Aw man!
Oh. Guess you mean this freak?
Dammit, I'm gonna
lose points for that now!
Anyway, don't worry,
'cause I'll avenge you,
so be a good boy and
rest in peace, okay?!
Um, look, about that...
Shut up and go into
the light! To the light!
I don't see a light,
you dingbat!
Mystletainn!
Magical power to full!
Let's go! Ultimate technique!
Mystletainn Kick!
Cutting into someone
with a chainsaw
isn't a kick, you psychopath!
That may have been a little
grisly, but I got the job done.
You forgettin'
about me over here?
Or did you mean to do that?
Hey, why aren't you dead, pal?
Because I'm a zombie.
Hold on, you mean
you're not human?
Well, I used to be. But for the
last month, I've been a zombie.
Eew!
Show some respect
for the undead.
So, you gonna introduce
yourself or what?
I'm a genius
Magical Garment Girl!
The name's Haruna!
The fur ball was a
Megalo named Kumacchi!
A big part of my
grade comes from
how well I can take him down.
And I gotta say
I kicked major ass!
Too bad it was mine...
Sorry, but if you were a
real genius, you would have
found a way to stop that bear
thing without cutting me in two.
Oh, yeah, Mister smart-mouth?
Well, I'd love to tell you
you're gonna regret that,
but you wouldn't
remember me saying it!
Ya know why? Because
I'm gonna erase your memory.
Say what?! No, wait!
Your clothes!
Um. Where'd they go?
My clothes? What the
hell are you talking about?
I'm wearin' em ya dope!
Crap! I'm naked!
Hey, stop gawking
at me, you pervert,
and give me back
my powers immediately!
This instant!
Post-haste! Lickety-split!
Now, now, now, now, now!
You dirty creep, you're not
a normal human, are you?
I told you,
I was a zombie, remember?
Oh, and on that topic,
would you mind grabbing
my lower body up there for me?
Lower body? You pervert!
I'm not a pervert, I'm a zombie!
So, um. Why would
a magician like yourself--
Magical Garment Girl!
Why would a "Magical
Garment Girl" like yourself
want to come to my house?
I'm at your house
because you put me in a bind.
You absorbed my magic powers.
I did? Is that some zombie
ability I didn't know I had?
So you owe me big time!
Well, how am I
supposed to pay you back?
I'll tell you how!
You may be a disgusting zombie
and a pervert,
but until my powers return,
you're gonna let me stay here.
Stay here? Well, um.
As long as you don't
disturb the neighbors,
I guess I'm okay
with that arrangement.
Plus, you'll provide me with
high-quality meals, snacks,
and a bedroom, too.
Now wait just a minute.
And who is this chick?
She's a necromancer from Hades,
Eucliwood Hellscythe,
or Eu for short.
Oh, really?
A "neckwear-mancer" huh?
"Necro," not "neckwear."
Oh, yeah.
Um, hey, what's-your-face?
My name is Ayumu.
Let me use your phone.
So what am I lookin at here?
It's a cell phone.
A what?
By the way you're looking
at it, I take it you don't have
cell phones in your
magic world.
That's no phone!
Back in Villiers,
phones are stylish machines
you talk into like this!
"Hello? Hello?"
"May I ask who's calling?"
Cell phones work the same way.
Look. Just open it up and
dial the number you wanna call.
Oh, wow. This thing is
just like a phone, huh?
I told you!
It is a phone!
Yes, is this you, Head Teacher?
It's me. My student number?
Sure thing.
Six hundred,
thirty four million,
five hundred
twenty-six thousand.
I'm from Class Refrain-Rising.
Name's Haruna.
The reason I'm calling?
Something kinda went
wrong with the mission.
I hit a little snag.
I've lost my
magical powers, okay?
I guess she really does
come from a world of magic.
Ya know. Not too long ago,
I would've thought someone
with a story like that was
full of it. But that was before
I was brought back to life
by a Necromancer from Hades.
And before the little tummy
tuck that one gave me with her
chainsaw earlier tonight.
But, like I said before,
the world is full
of weird stuff.
Thank you for
being so understanding.
Wait, how much am I gonna
get charged for that call?
Magical Garment Girl. Detected.
Am I nuts? Trying to
live life as a normal
high school student when
I'm actually one of the undead?
And what happens if
everyone finds out?
Gross, you mean my best friend
is some kinda
flesh-eating freak!
You haven't left yet?
Still here.
Dude, what's the dealio;
it's like I barely
see you outside anymore.
That's 'cause zombies
can't walk in the sun.
Eh... It's these
killer allergies.
Yeah. You could
still go home, though.
Things are a little
crazy there now.
But, you live alone.
Oh, I almost forgot,
I got a new zombie flick!
Wanna go watch it at your place?
No!
It's hard enough keeping secret
the fact that I'm a zombie.
But if word gets
out that I'm living
with two female roommates,
one a necromancer and the other
a so-called
Magical Garment Girl.
I'm screwed!
Okay, no problem!
I'm sure you've got a
real good reason to say no.
Some other time
then, dude. Well, see ya!
Yeah, have a good one, ol buddy.
Okay. That was weird.
What's up his ass?
Speaking of which,
it looks like I'm now stuck
with two female roommates.
Oh, well. I guess life can't get
any stranger than it
already has been, right?
Who's this freaky old guy
and what does he want?
What I want,
my boy, is you.
I want you!
Oh, no, does that mean
what I think it means?
Now it's time, to get
to the bottom of things!
Ahh!
So it's not enough that
I died and became a zombie,
but now I have to get
molested by this creep, too?
Help me!
Haruna!
What are you doing here?
You like old guys?
Hell, no!
Yeah right. But any idiot would
know that this guy's a Megalo!
How would I know!
Don't worry,
I'll be gentle.
Oh no way!
Uh! He's a crawfish?
Yep, a Double-A Class Megalo,
the incredibly diabolical Zari!
At least I think he is.
Correct, that's me!
I came here because
I was drawn by the power
of a Magical Garment Girl.
But I'm perplexed as to how that
power resides in this human!
That's gonna take
a while to explain.
I hate long stories!
I wasn't talking to you!
Super Magical Garment Change!
Nomobuyo... Oshi...
Hawsh-tah-wah.
Do-kay-dah... Goon-mee-cha...!
Deh Ribura!
Whoa...
Oh, no, why is this
happening to me again?!
I don't know exactly,
but when a Magical Garment Girl
loses her powers, she not
only becomes helpless,
but so much easier to kill, too!
What the hell happened
to all of that bravado
you had back in the graveyard?
I dunno.
You're scared,
aren't you? Admit it!
Me being scared of
some dumb crawfish Megalo
is the stupidest
thing I've ever heard!
Gimme a break! I'm a genius
Magical Garment Girl, remember?
If you don't think I
can turn scissorhands here
into etouffee, then screw you!
But before I can
suck out your heads,
I have to pinch off your tails!
What?! How could a
human have so much power?
Simple, you
bottom-feeding bastard.
You see, humans can't use one
hundred percent of their power
because their bodies always have
to keep some of it in reserve.
But me? Well. I'm a zombie.
So I can use a hell of a lot
more power than humans can!
Like one hundred percent!
And even one hundred and twenty
percent if I feel like it!
Yee-ouch, that hurt! Crap!
Oh my god that totally
snapped my arm like a toothpick!
Stop flapping around
and heal!
Oh, no! He may be strong,
but he's no good
if he loses his limbs.
I gotta think
of something quick.
Your undead body might
be tough but it's still human!
Listen up Zombieboy!
You gotta use Mystletainn!
Your chainsaw?
Yeah, since you stole my powers,
you can become
a Magical Garment Girl!
What? I don't
want to become a girl!
Man up and turn into
a girl or we're toast!
Dammit! Alright, then!
Now say it with me!
Nomobuyo... Oshi...
Hawshtahwah.
Dokeda... Gunmiicha...!
Deh Ribura!
Oh, my god!
I feel it!
Here it comes!
It's coming!
What! Not this get up!
It's gonna make you
stronger and way more brave
so don't knock it, ya jackass!
For real?
Oh, you're a pervert, too?
I am not! Dammit,
I'm sick and tired
of everyone
calling me a pervert!
Now what was the name of that
ultimate technique
thing Haruna used?
Let's see. Oh, yeah, now I
remember. Mystel-tainn. Kick!
Cutting someone with
a chainsaw's not a kick.
You cross-dressing pervert!
I'm not a pervert!
That freakin hurt.
What the hell? Ayumu?
Uh.
Eww, gross!
Is that cosplay?
Wait. It's not what
ya think. I can explain! Um.
Don't tell me you're
some kinda tranny?
No! Don't take pictures!
Cut it out!
You guys've got it
all wrong I swear!
Hey!
Haruna, please!
Tell them I'm not a drag queen!
Listen up, folks! Ayumu.
He isn't a drag queen!
But he is a Magical
Garment Girl! Now and forever.
I used to live the life of an
average high school student,
and I thought it would last
forever, but now those days,
like my human life
and my dignity are over!
What a perv!
Cross-dresser, huh?
That's so not cute!
Now I'm a zombie.
Oh, and somehow, a Magical
Garment Girl, too.
Is it weird that I'm a zombie?
Yeah, I guess so.
Zombies get a lot of bad press.
The word's definitely
got a negative connotation.
Why not call
yourself something else?
Like what?
Hmm? Life-challenged?
No, wait, how 'bout a living
impaired Magical Garment Girl!