I fail to see what charm
the maggot can possibly
hold for you.
Is it his looks?
Or something more, elusive?
The boy's looks
do nothing for me.
His personality
is no less repugnant.
Then why do you
obsess over him?
It's his butt.
I'm sorry?
You heard me perfectly!
His rear. His luscious rump.
His ass. 'Kay?
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
My brain refuses to register
it as something you'd say.
One of your many
limitations, Seraphim.
Excuse me?
You know, when he saw
Emperor Napoleon on horseback,
the philosopher Hegel
was nearly moved to tears.
"Lo! There sits the
World Soul," he said.
Wait, what?
Ethics. Tradition. Morality.
All of them folded
in their common dust.
Perished. Dispersed in the
wake of History's momentum.
And now there is no going back.
I'm stricken by a perfect ass!
All this waiting around for
my life to go back to normal
is making me crazy.
Fresh miso soup
hot off the stove.
Poor fellah's
seen better days, huh?
So, uh, how long til he's
up to snuff again, you think?
You can't rush a delicate
operation like this.
He's part of a genius's
arsenal, after all;
it's not like changing
a stupid flat tire.
I didn't figure it was.
Things are
different in Villiers.
We like to take our time
with old things!
Rub-a-dub-dub,
thanks for the grub.
I only brought it up
'cause I don't know
how much longer I can
take the notoriety.
It's not without
a few perks, though, right?
The internet crowd can't get
enough of those exquisite legs,
my darling.
What the hell is it
that people are downloading?
Just your
personal information.
My what?
The world needed to know
the real you. I couldn't just
stand on the sidelines and
let the rumor mill grind you
to pulp. Don't worry, my blog
is very fair and balanced.
Aw, that's so sweet of you.
Wait, I mean knock it off!
Stop feeding the sharks
my information!
What's with you?
You're staring at me
like I've grown a tail.
Mind your own business,
perv. I'm preoccupied.
Wow. A very reasonable response.
Look, all I'm sayin' is the
sooner everyone forgets
what they saw, the better.
Um, hello? Head Teacher?
It's Ayumu.
Morning, sweet pea.
How're you?
You busy, or is this
a good time to talk?
Ah. I am all ears.
I was hoping for an ETA
on Mystletainn's repairs.
Well, as of right now,
I think--let's see.
Yes, according to my records,
the repairs-request form
has pushed through
to Window 1241.
There's a window 1241?
Quite so. At this rate,
he'll be a third of the way
through the process in no time.
Kinda seems like a whole
lotta red tape to me!
We like dotting the i's and
crossing the t's in Villiers.
So Haruna likes
to keep telling me.
All good things come to those
who wait, my turtledove.
Alright, that does it.
Time for the one person in this
house with chutzpah to step up
and take charge
of the situation!
Okay.
Mystletainn counts as
collateral damage! The brass
isn't going to be sympathetic
to a predicament like his!
Huh?
I'll fix him! After I eat!
Stop looking.
Okay, then.
I'm headed off to school.
First off, let's get you
out of these tight clothes.
Please, no! I'm begging you
not to do this.
Don't distract me, worm bait.
I'm commencing with
a very delicate operation!
Fight it all you want,
I'm seein' your insides.
Ugh! My dignity!
Don't look! I feel so dirty!
Don't be afraid.
It'll only hurt at first.
Promise.
What a bedside manner!
Hmm. What to pop out first?
Wow. So many pretty
lil' bits to choose from
I hardly know where to start!
You're a psychopath!
Quit squirming!
You'll only make it worse!
I'm just gonna think about
what I want to fix for dinner.
Hey, I'm home.
Oh, hello there, little guy.
Subject is
sufficiently prepped.
Drill me.
Well done. Build up
enough centrifugal force
around the bill area. And I can
bore through the exoskeleton
as if with a diamond bit! Nice!
Ugh! Damn it, this is
surgery, not bath time!
Perfect; just what our patient
needs to feel more comfortable.
Perhaps we'll improvise a song:
"tinkle tinkle, little--
we're not trying to teach him
how to drop a friggin' deuce!
I'll have dinner ready
in about half an hour.
That's a light machine gun!
Where are you pulling
this stuff out of?
You gonna eat? You don't
want it to get cold.
Dinner can get bent! I can't
walk away from this right now!
Whatever. No worries;
I've got you covered.
I'll whip up something
you can eat later.
I think the primary issue
is that the conductive sheath
protecting his magic circuits
got overheated during the fight
and made the shaft hemorrhage.
Naturally that's gonna overload
the super-dimensional inductors.
So, if I bypass the
fuselage here, I should.
Ah-ha! Exactly! Makes perfect
sense! Now I've gotcha!
The unflappable Haruna
and her stupendous brain
are on the case!
The hyper-causality engine's
exhaust controls malfunctioned
and caused a build-up of sparkly
in the combustion chamber.
The Fessenden field
imploded like a sinkhole.
That caused the breakers
to fail, which screwed up
the antiphase valve torque.
Somebody's been working hard.
Just look at that moon.
I take it the old man's
up and running?
Oh, hey.
I'm sure you've been waiting for
this moment with baited breath.
Like a kid for Christmas. Any
longer and a four page spread
of me in full regalia would've
wound up in the yearbook.
I'm ready for this mess to end.
Then by all means,
get on with it.
Stand back.
Nomobuyo.
Oshi hashitawa dokeda
gunmiicha deh ribura.
How 'bout that? You're going
with the classic look tonight.
Poor Haruna worked herself to
the bone for my sake, I owe her.
Alright memories. Here I come.
Emashite resuwa moka
monina momeyu moia!
You disgusting little vermin!
This whole charade was just...
It's about the capacitors.
Heh. One point twenty- one.
I can do better.
When I see it for myself,
I'll believe it.
I'm sorry, really.
You got yourself into this,
girl. We Vampire Ninjas
don't have it easy.
Mark my words,
ladies and gentlemen!
Mystletainn will be back!
Someone's taken Mystletainn!
Way to go streaker;
now we have to wait
for the bureaucrats to fix 'em.
I'm so done. Just kill me.
Something stuck
in your craw, Mr. Aikawa?
Stuck in my--?
Nevermind. I just wanted
to let you know as a courtesy
that I'm gonna need
more time to sort things out.
Huh?
I wasn't prepared for the
revelation you sprung on
all of us the other day.
It made me realize the person
I thought I knew was a fiction;
takes some getting used to.
To paraphrase Walt Whitman:
you contradict yourself
because you contain multitudes.
How's a straight-shooter like
me s'posed to deal with that?
Damn it. The thing is.
I can get my head
around what you are,
but it will be a long time
before I can trust my heart.
Uh, yeah.
You're losin' me, dude.
Truth is a harsh
mistress to some people.
And that means?
His mind has been forced to
adapt to a new kind of reality.
All the stereotypes he's
fed on up till now have been
reduced to shadows
in the wake of seeing
his best friend in drag.
What?
Don't worry, he's fighting
for you; the friendship means
too much for him to let the
negative stereotypes win out.
Like a soul struggling to be
born anew. He fights to be real.
Orito crouches poised
to burst from his cocoon.
A butterfly merely
waiting to emerge.
Hear me, Higher Self. I know
you're in there somewhere
and rest assured that
one day I swear I'm gonna
turn the reigns over!
Okay, Gaia.
I don't mean to complain,
but if this is
your idea of a new age.
It's kind of ridiculous.
All I wanted was something
a little closer to a normal,
you know?
Now that's shot to hell.
We don't want it
too warm, now.
Seriously. Is it really so much
to ask for a little obscurity?
The limelight sucks.
Oh yeah. This brand rocks.
You need to try a sip, Tea Pot.
Once this stuff gets a
toehold in your system
we can switch to vodka.
Oh, potato vodka! That'd
put some curl in your pubes!
Look, kid. Some days are shit.
That's when a good friend pours
you a drink and the pair of ya
toast to tomorrow.
Then you pour a few more
till things get weird. Then of
course you keep knockin' 'em
back out of a sense of
obligation and forget about
the lonely vodka. And ask
why as you blow chunks.
Works, too. S'how
D-list celebrities deal
with their pain.
Yeah.
Get this, kid.
Anyone can splurge on vodka,
but it takes guts
to be a D-lister.
Holy crap! I've been a total
wuss about this whole thing,
haven't I?
You're amazing! Seriously!
I've been wallowing in self-pity
when what I really
need is some balls!
Bring on the potato vodka!
Idiot. If he'd have
just left him alone
the grafts would've taken.
Big, stupid Ayumu.
I can't breathe! The hell?
Knock it off with the dance
curse, you stupid idiot!
My lungs are
exploding into my--
Okay. Let me get this straight;
so you had no idea that
was a dance curse?
Of course not! I could never
do something like that!
It's just that Sarasvati is
performing another concert and
I sorta got talked into being
one of her backup dancers.
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight!
Now turn it around and strike
a pose. Then twist that thang.
Now back it up
like a diesel truck.
Bam!
Tell me that
wasn't secret recipe!
I've seen decapitated chickens
with better moves than you,
Mael Strom.
I so fail at life.
Like hell you do!
What kind of talk is that?
It's not every day you meet
a gal who can fell everything
in a three mile radius
by shakin' her money maker.
That's not the kind of
dancing I want to be good at!
In that case,
maybe give it up.
Screw that! If Sarasvati can
make a thousand shrieking
fanboys foam at the mouth,
there's no reason
I can't do it, too!
If you worms want to die,
come to me now!
Vampire ninjas never give up;
we toil in the shadows
until the job is finished.
So what are you whining about?
Because the moves are
too hard for me to memorize!
Alright, that does it!
When I'm done with you,
your moves will be the stuff
of legend! Get to know me,
girl; I'm a genius.
What the hell?
And you throw your hands in the
air like you just don't care!
Knock it off with
the dance curse!
My lungs are exploding into my--
Uh-oh.
Why you always interrupting
me when I'm knee-deep
in something important?
You guys are killing everything
in earshot, dumbass! Look up!
Oh wow! When we dance together,
the curse gets amplified!
That's awesome!
Alrighty, look.
Whatever you're doing,
put the kibosh on it right now.
But we're just dancing.
Cursing?
Stuff it, jackass!
Sarasvati's doing a concert,
and I wanted--
Ah, yeah! Check it out!
Read 'em and weep,
these moves are sweet;
If dance were a city
I'd be main street!
And scissor lift,
and spinin' some gold,
Then spring and summer
gonna play it bold!
Now one last trick
fo' the ladies, and boom!
Whoa! That was sweet!
Point is. That's how you
dance without killing stuff.
Big deal.
I'm never gonna be able
to dance like that either.
Pathetic beyond words.
Sarasvati? How did
you know we were here?
I simply followed
He of the Fine Ass
on his way home from school.
Fair warning, Mael Strom.
You have twenty four hours
to become a
passable backup dancer,
otherwise I'm shipping
you back to the village.
Seriously?
What the hell's
wrong with you?
The girl made an oath.
If she can't fulfill it,
she is subject to our laws,
no one else's.
Hang in, Yuki!
I think I'm getting it, sensei!
So Yuki thinks she can become
a backup dancer for Sarasvati?
Yeah. Pretty much.
She trying to kill
everyone at the concert?
'Cause they do know
that's what will happen, right?
We're gonna try to
avoid that, if possible.
Here's the deal. I've got till
tomorrow to turn this gal into
a dancer. If I fail, she gets
shunted back to her home town.
Which, frankly, would suck.
That's harassment.
The prospect only bothers you
because she's easier
prey for you here.
But surely I'm the only one
you want to do naughty
things with, right?
Forget this perv, Yuki.
Stick to my program
and we'll have you rockin' like
a hurricane well before sun-up!
Sounds like a plan to me!
Hear that, world?
I'm gonna be a hurricane!
Come on! I don't care
how much it hurts,
you keep on keepin' on!
We're breakin' through the wall!
I'm in it to win it!
This is a tragedy.
That's the word for it.
Exactly how long can two people
do what they're doing
and call it dance?
It's go-time, ladies.
Now we get serious.
You with me?
One, two! One, two!
Don't forget the break!
Watch it! Gotta keep
those legs straight!
One more time! One, two!
One, two! Step, step!
Spread those arms and turn!
You gotta let go, Tomonori!
Forget the choreography!
Become one with the beat and
allow pure animal instinct
to take over! Shut out every
thought but your desire
to be the best!
The light is yours!
Reach up and grab it!
It's been long enough.
I'm ready.
For what?
I've clawed my way through
the seven circles
of Hell for you, dude.
Seriously?
I'm sorry. There's not
a less dramatic way
to describe the
process. It was hell.
But I now know the
role I have to play,
I don't need a cross-dressing
head case in my life.
But you need a normal
one in yours. Me.
Butterfly of the status quo!
Stop and take five.
Towel yourself off.
Uh, thanks?
Don't worry.
The show'll kick ass.
Um. Awkward.
Yeah.
Show me those pretty necks!
Who wants to be first
on the chopping block?
I wanna have your babies!
Or however that works!
It's okay, I'm here for you.
You pushed yourself to
the limit in rehearsal.
Show all these people
what you're made of.
Now get out there
and knock 'em dead.
You got it!
Let's rock their socks off!
Yes, sensei!
Break a leg, you two.
Damn it, that's not what
we practiced! Son of a--!
Like the choreography
was that hard!
Not like that! Cmon, we just
did it five minutes ago!
What the hell? Why is my body
suddenly ignoring my brain?
Hey! What are you guys doing?
Somebody do something;
the curse is sapping
my ability to resist!
I can't breathe.
This is a thing of beauty!
With Ayumu in step,
the curse is like a
gazillion times stronger!
Stop dancing!
Dear god. It's perfect.
Someone I know?
I have reason to
believe so, yes.
Or am I wrong to presume
you met the man who
used you face to face?
Oh, you mean him.
Mind if I ask a few questions
about the King of the Night?
You can ask.
But I know nothing.
I'm expecting too much.
Well, if you think of anything,
do let me know.
Oh Ayumu, soon we will
be reunited my dear.
I hope you've
been thinking of me.
Hello, I'm Fantasy Eu A!
Fantasy Eu B!
I'm the C version!
And together we form,
Fantasy Eu Triple Threat
Cirque du Pervert!
It's been a long time,
girlfriends.
Too long!
I can't remember the last
time we all got together!
No kidding! How've you
two been in the meantime?
Oh, pretty good!
Ayumu's feverish imagination
is so active, I've been
doing all sorts of things
just to keep him happy.
His naughty side has definitely
been in overdrive lately, huh?
I feel like such a tramp!
I think he's ruining us
for other guys so he can
have us all to himself!
Of course! We're gonna make
Ayumu a very happy man someday!
In his dreams.