That stupid zombie
butthole practically broke
Mystletainn in half.
Now we're totally up a creek
if a Megalo drops by,
which means my grades
are completely shot, too.
Don't ask me.
Knowing him, he's probably
out pervin' it up somewhere.
Now son, I don't
want to see you again.
Of course, sir.
Sorry for the trouble.
At least the weather's nice.
What are you doin' here?
I was looking for the worm
who decided to make
his pitiful privates
a public spectacle.
No doubt scarring
dozens of young minds.
You got the wrong idea
about me Sera--
Most people already think
you're a sex offending maggot.
You don't have to go out of
your way to prove them right.
Life, or whatever this is,
might be a lot of things,
but never predictable.
If Gaia sees fit to slam another
obstacle in front of me,
I've just got to man up
and power through.
Ya know.
Being the chosen one
kinda sucks.
That ass is like an onion.
Brings tears to my eyes.
I'm home.
You are blowin' up!
Whaddaya talkin' about?
Rackin' up a hefty
number of views.
No!
Now that I've come out
of the magical girl closet,
I don't expect my
classmates to treat me like
the belle of the ball.
But once again I've got no
option but to meet whatever
fate throws at me, head on.
We chosen ones travel rocky
paths, sure, but it does
absolutely no good
to cry about it.
Hey, superstar!
Oh my god it's him!
You're practically
an A-list celebrity now!
I'm surprised this place
isn't paparazzi central yet,
but I bet good money
they're on their way!
Mm-hm.
You know they are!
Are you serious?
Oh yeah, I'm sure there's
gonna be a juggernaut of press
here in no time
So cool!
Hey, Ayumu.
All last night, I was thinking
about everything that happened
and I gotta admit that
I kinda like you even more now.
Even she drank the kool-aid?
We have got to get you
into counseling.
This is crazy!
Like some sort of
bizarro world.
I need a life line.
Someone I can trust!
Orito!
Hey man.
Uh.
I just wanted to tell you,
your legs are gorgeous.
I mean, handsome?
It's too rocky!
Gaia, this path is too rocky!
Miss Goth chick!
I'm so glad you're here!
I need your slurred words
of wisdom more than ever!
Cool.
So what's crawlin' up
your crotch-huggers this time?
I'm getting it sideways,
lengthwise, up and down!
No matter what I do,
everything works against me;
if there's a way to turn it
around, I'm out of ideas.
It's hard out there for a wimp.
I hear ya, MooMoo.
I just can't handle being
the center of attention.
You need a little
liquid courage?
Well, it's not like I've aged
since the last time so, no.
That just means
more hooch for mama.
If I were older this'd be a
great excuse to pickle my liver.
This is what they talk about in
religious philosophies, kiddo.
And annoying sports songs
that just won't ever die.
Ya get knocked down into
somersaults seven times but
ya get up like eight
or nine times at least!
But I sure am glad to be
sitting down right now.
Uh.
Gossip's not forever.
Only about three billion,
five-hundred million,
six-thousand, five-hundred
and seventy five days.
I always heard a season,
but I get ya.
And you're right,
all of this will pass.
Guess I just have
to roll with it.
Thanks for the
perspective Miss Goth Chick.
I can get through
this rough patch
and come out even stronger.
You bet your ass!
And don't be a stranger,
ya hear?
The one thing that can
heal all wounds; time.
Nomobuyo!
Where's the Nomobuyo guy?
He's not here right now,
but he'll probably be back
in a little bit.
That guy is so hot right now!
I wanna be just like him!
Nope!
Not gonna do it!
Hey, where ya goin?
Tomonori?
Oh please.
What am I gonna hafta' do to get
ya to call me by my first name?
And "Yuki" feels way more
intimate if ya know what I mean.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Old habits.
So, whaddaya say,
you and me go up
to the mountains tomorrow night?
What for?
What's gonna happen?
Nomobuyo!
On second thought, the
mountains sound marvelous!
You wanna see stars?
Maybe.
That sounds like a
mountain-ney thing to do.
Escaping sea-level
reality, huh?
So manly.
I've got a few peaks
you might be interested in.
I'm not gonna lie, an escape
from the maddening crowd
just might be
what the doctor ordered.
And the way
she described everything.
Once you breathe that clean
mountain air and see those
billions of stars,
it's like you become
a completely different person!
I think I just need to hit
that big reset button on life.
To get a fresh
perspective on things,
get my priorities straight.
I gotta cut through
the noise and B.S.
of the modern world, ya know?
So it's just gonna to be
the two of you out there?
Yep.
Uh.
Hey.
What are you gettin' at?
Hey!
I'm over here!
Yo!
Hope you weren't
waiting too long.
I thought you'd
be coming alone, is all.
Is that a problem?
It's cool.
I don't have any kind
of problem with that.
But the sock and sandal
combination is definitely
gonna be an issue!
Aw, don't get
your panties in a wad.
Let's roll out!
I wanna get an eyeful of that
big ol' spangle starred sky!
Sea urchins in my belly,
squid ink in my belly.
How much will it cost?
Hey!
Are we ever gonna get there?
Course we are.
If you don't drive us
all off a cliff first.
Ugh.
Walking hurts my feet,
can't we just fly up there?
Look!
Your feet hurt 'cause
you're wearing sandals!
Hikin' mountains
is serious stuff you guys!
So quit your cryin'!
Or go home!
I gotta go water some flowers.
Are you crazy?
We're in the
middle of the forest;
there isn't any toilet paper!
I'll use a leaf!
Savor this moment.
She can't pee forever.
Looks like the stars
are coming out.
The place that we're
headin' the stars are like woah!
Oh man!
You won't believe it!
Oh, yeah?
Yeah!
I swear the view up there
is gonna knock those troubles
right out of your head!
That's exactly what I need.
I see.
You've come all this way
just for his sake, have you?
No it's not just
because of him!
I come here by myself
every single year!
It always makes me
feel way better.
So I thought this year,
I'd share it with him
'cause he needs
some cheering up.
The view alone
would cheer him up, eh?
Listen, you guys have
totally got the wrong idea!
And anyway, she is
taking way too long to potty.
There're ferocious bears
and stuff in the woods!
I'm so glad I have a big
strong stud here to protect me.
The peace is over.
I'll go try to
track down Haruna.
Stay right there, and I'll be
back as soon as I can, okay?
Hey!
Wait!
I'm coming with you!
Whoa, are you okay?
Oh!
Uh.
Yeah thanks a lot.
Actually, I should be giving you
a big thank you right now.
No, I mean it.
You went out of your way
to take me somewhere to enjoy
the peace and
quiet for a while.
It's not that big a deal.
Don't worry 'bout it.
Well it's a big deal to me.
I needed it.
I owe ya.
No really it's nothing!
Ya don't have to do
anything special for me!
I'm not trying to get
any kinda favors from ya.
Hey, listen.
Forget about me, okay?
It's what I should be doing.
I'm your wife and I
at least need to make ya
feel better sometimes.
But if ya did wanna
do somethin' for me.
I guess, there is one thing
that I can think of.
Just sometimes,
let me call ya--
Call me what?
It's nothing too weird.
Good.
I would kinda hope not.
I mean, like,
somethin' special.
A pet name.
Huh?
It's what a wife's
supposed to do for the hubs.
Or I can just call ya Ayumu
if that's what you want.
Well I'll always answer to it.
Like, even for me?
Yeah.
It is my name.
I'll just say it
like a pet name.
Oh-kay.
It's gotta be cute.
Super cute.
What's wrong with me?
Now.
Okay.
Maybe like.
Ayumu!
Get your head
outta your ass and listen!
We got trouble
with a capital B comin'!
Be careful walking along
dark paths at night!
Ah!
No more hentai!
Get your head
outta your ass and listen!
We got trouble
with a capital B comin!
What in the hell?
Bees?
Ayumu!
Wait for me!
I need you!
Haruna.
Are you serious?
You really feel that way?
Special Move!
Ayumu Barrier!
I should have known!
Oh my god!
Let's make tracks!
Try not to scare him!
Oh I'm sorry.
I always thought
bears gave hugs.
My bad.
Yeah.
You should run now.
You gotta get us outta here!
I can't even
see what's happening!
We're getting chased by a bear!
Yeah I know,
but where're we going?
Ow.
Ayumu.
This is an
unfortunate situation.
Tell me why it shouldn't become
a painful one for you as well.
Right.
It's kind of a
heart-warming story actually.
You see.
My eyes!
He's such a
cuddly-wuddly little guy!
I don't think
that's very smart.
I'll have you know that
every animal that walks this
earth finds me irresistible.
Rare, and drizzled
with soy sauce maybe.
Perhaps a nice
baked potato on the side?
Don't be such a playa hater.
I don't even know
what the hell that means!
Obviously the effects
of lifelong rejection.
Don't psycho-analyze me!
Must be nice.
Seems like you all
have so much fun together.
Prob'ly cause you're
spending time with him.
You'd better pump
your brakes, girly!
Cause it sure sounds
like you're sayin' we're all
in some weird love harem
with this graveyard reject.
Never.
The mere idea is
nausea-inducing.
Hold on.
Why the heck did you
follow him up here then?
What's the deal?
Do you hate me or somethin'?
I don't have any
kinda problem with ya.
I came here tonight 'cause
I thought I'd have fun
hangin' out with you!
That's why I'm here.
I'm an idiot.
Sorry.
I'm bein a killjoy.
We were s'posed to see some
stars and have some laughs.
So let's go see some
freakin' stars!
We're here.
This is the spot!
This means no more
climbing, right?
Have I mentioned how much
I love flat ground?
That's cool.
"The stars in the sky
are eternally beautiful."
"But the constantly-changing
stars are beautiful, too."
Mm-hm.
Yep.
This is the big show
that I wanted you to see.
So, uh, it's pretty, isn't it?
Oh yeah.
Beautiful.
It's just what I needed.
Really?
That makes me happy.
Thank you.
I told ya.
Ya don't have
to thank me for this!
I know.
Okay.
What do you say we make plans
to come back next year?
Ayumu.
Holy crap that's good!
It's amazing!
Try to contain yourself please.
Gorging is unbecoming.
Yeah I'm a kind of a badass.
Every egg-layin chicken dreams
of getting their little babies
beaten up and fried in
the skillet of yours truly.
That's why I'm called the
Genius Egg Whipper Master!
I'd let you whip
my eggs anytime!
You're gonna have
to get in line, lady!
I may have started up
that mountain a boy,
but now I'm a boy
that's over the hill.
I mean I'm an
over the hill man.
I mean I'm a man
that conquered a mountain
(with three teenage girls).
The point is-- I'm a man.
A new man.
I wonder if he'll
sign my boxer shorts!
Maybe I'm not a
completely new man just yet.
You have so many admirers.
It must make you
feel really popular.
But they're all weirdoes.
Who wants that
kind of attention?
One for me please?
I can't do this much longer.
Is never being noticed by
anybody again too much to ask?
Ayumu Aikawa.
Whassup?
Okay, fine.
Don't be stupid!
That is a very
important message from me.
Run that under water.
I just prayed to live the rest
of my days in total obscurity,
so of course I get a stalker!
My feelings are
hidden no longer.
If you wanna wax poetic you
could say my life is a boat
cast into stormy waters, and
the sharks are always circling.
Hey man!
Just what the hell
is your problem?
How come you bailed
on me earlier?
Ya' know, you can't just
give up on your bro job?
Mr. Aikawa.
Huh?
What in the hell?
Are you high?
Quite the opposite.
I am a man trapped
in the abyss staring up
at the face of Polaris.
Say what?
And you're a star
looking down at the world
in which you once lived.
At the people who crave
nothing but your light.
This is crazy talk, man.
I'm still me!
Yeah, I'm getting treated
differently after flashing
my sushi roll at
the entire school.
But below this popular exterior
I'm the exact same guy
that I've always been!
Sir.
I'm sorry.
The boy I called my BFF was
not a cross dressing pervert.
Nor was he the most popular
kid in the whole school.
The bromance is over.
It has to go both ways
to be truly healthy.
Oh-kay.
Give me some space.
I need time to work
this thing out.
Form a clear mental picture of
what your transformation means.
And get a firm grip
on my manhood.
I understand.
Don't you worry, bro.
You and me are forever, right?
I thought he would
always be around.
For better or worse.
My yummy man-meat dumpling.
Are you talkin' to me?
Don't ask such
stupid questions!
Do you see anyone else here
that would fit that description?
Do you, idiotic Adonis?
Listen loverboy.
I'm intensely and intimately
aware of your beguiling assets.
And rest assured I will
treat you as you deserve.
Home sweet home.
You are on a roll!
Oh man, what now?
An embarrassingly assertive
assembly of assorted Ayumu ass!
No!
Alright world,
prepare to be ass-tonished.
I admire your persistence, but
why don't you call it quits?
It's time Kyoko.
You may act all sweet.
But I know what
you're capable of.
Come now.
I just need for you to
give me honest answers
to a couple of questions
I have for you.
Make it nice and easy for me.
And things won't
get ugly for you.
Hello, my name is Fantasy Eu A!
And my name is Fantasy Eu B!
But together you can
call us Fantasy Double Eu!
Please stop embarrassing me.
It's real deal Eu!
How do you feel about the
dress and panties that Ayumu
has to wear when he's being
a Magical Garment Girl?
It was actually
shocking at first,
but I've gotten
used to it over time.
It's really something!
On anyone else it would be
a huge fashion faux pas,
but somehow he pulls it off!
I bet he can rock any
outfit that he wants!
I'm not so sure.
I have a great idea!
How about we let him wear
our costume sometime?
Oh my god!
So cute!
That's it.
Say bye bye, girls.
Bye bye, girls!
Bye bye.