Shakespeare wrote,
"Men are April when they woo,
December when they wed. Maids
are May when they are maids,
but the sky changes
when they are wives."
Shakespeare also wrote,
"To climb steep hills requires
slow pace at first"
and "How poor are they
that have not patience."
That exam was so tough.
It's also said. "People
never realize the true worth
of something they care
deeply about until it is lost."
Nice catch.
I believe these belong
to me, thank you very much.
Let's see here.
If I were to guess,
I'd say you were
being perverted again.
You're repugnant. You're nothing
but a crude, obscene person.
Forgive me, I misspoke.
You're not a crude,
obscene person but
a crude, obscene little maggot.
I know, I know, I'm a filthy
zombie, a magic tranny pervert,
and a crude
obscene little maggot, too
Hey, hot stuff.
You're late. You dim-wit!
Why in the hell are
you dressed like that?
Don't you remember? I snatched
away all your special powers.
And your outfit. See?
Don't come near me!
Just stay back perv-bag.
I mean it! Let me go!
You really are sexy ya know?
Not to mention, beautiful.
The other girls
don't even come close.
What're you doing?
Now close your eyes.
My gorgeous little angel.
What's wrong with you?
Noooo!
Eu, you're so naughty.
You really think I
should take off my pants?
How dare you try
to do nasty things
to me in my dreams you big
pervert! Say you're sorry!
You should count your blessings.
After violating her in her
dream like that, you're lucky
she didn't throw you
into the sunlight to fry.
How the hell am I
responsible for her sex dreams?
And although I don't care for
her, I can't help but feel sorry
for Mael, since you
forced yourself on her as well.
That was an accident!
That's so sweet.
Thanks for sticking up for me.
That stupid jerk.
What the hell did he
have to kiss her for anyway?
Ayumu, what is up, bro?
I've been Jonesin' big
time for more of those eggs.
Let me just grab
a couple. Uh. What the hell.
That looks like a box of
burnt sperm, what gives?
Seriously? You're Japanese
and you've never seen
boiled seaweed before?
Not the most delicious stuff.
But Haruna thought I
deserved it for some reason.
Oh mama! That's amazing!
Give me some!
I want a bite!
Wow! So good!
Yeah!
Yuki! One more lap to go!
Oh my god. Did you see
that big box of seaweed?
It wasn't that bad I guess,
but it looked totally gross.
Yeah, I thought he was
supposed to be the eggman.
Well. Maybe seaweed's the
next big thing or something.
They say it's supposed
to be good for dieting.
Really? I wonder
why he had it then,
he's like super scrawny.
I could use some though.
Hey, Kanami.
What's up?
You're in the same
class as Ayumu, aren't you?
Oh yeah, totes.
You got something going on?
Oh, not really.
But could you give me a
little advice about him?
What you wanna fall
in love with him?
Hey, this is private
information so do me a favor
and keep a lid on it!
Are we talking about
the same guy here?
He's always hanging
out with that creepy nerd.
You said fall in love, right?
Not that you fell in love
already. Are you even going out?
You can do better than
a guy like that, can't you?
I can't help it, okay?
It's a law, so it ain't my...
I mean, I uh...
Look, it's a really long story.
But the bottom line is this:
I have to fall in love
with the guy eventually,
no matter what it takes.
Here we go with
another long story.
He ain't my first choice
in guys or anything,
but I gotta fall for him.
The real problem is
it's my first time,
so I don't know what I'm doin'.
And it's a super big deal
cause we're gonna get married
so I gotta make
sure he doesn't hate me!
Hold on a second. Now you
two are gonna get married?
Uh, well, I have to, okay?
If me and him are
gonna be together forever
he's really gotta like me.
He's gotta like fall in love.
All right just keep your
dress on okay,
let me think here for
a sec. Showing a little skin
will get him to notice you
but if you want him to love you,
you should totally
make him some food!
Sexy food!
Welcome home, you big stud.
Anything you wanna eat?
I'll do anything for you.
I'm your little slave.
That's doesn't
sound like me at all!
Hey! You spazz! Don't freak out.
Take a deep breath!
Hmm?
Shut up.
I'd start out
making lunches for him
every day before
he goes to school.
I'll get on it
first thing tomorrow.
Then again, he seems
to be stepping up
his lunch game lately,
so it might be tough.
You're gonna have to
work your ass off on 'em.
Yeah. You're right.
You giving up that easy?
Not on your life!
Because the tougher
they come, the harder they fall!
It'll be just like one
of your track meets, Yuki.
Yeah, whatever.
I ain't giving up!
And one more thing.
You really are gonna have
to do something
about the way you talk.
How I talk? But why?
There ain't nothin' wrong.
Ain't "ain't" a word, you know?
Why is that such a big deal?
Just take my word for it okay?
Now you gotta try and wow him.
Yeah? But how?
Find out what he's
into and be that for him.
Try to be what
he fantasizes about.
Of course,
word on the street is
that he's into
little girls, so...
If you be my big strong man,
I'll be your sweet, little girl.
Wanna play?
Um. Gross.
Yeah well. That's his thing.
Maybe, but I
ain't... Uh, I mean.
I'm not really
that type of girl.
Aw come on you
just gotta put on
your big girl pants
and make it happen!
Well, I'll try.
So that's what
boys like. Okay.
Here ya go.
You made me lunch.
And I'm gonna keep
makin' it for you everyday.
From here on out. A good wife
has gotta keep her man happy.
Wow, that's really nice of you.
As long as it's not that ramen
stuff you made me before,
I'll definitely take it.
Sorry bout that.
Aw. Come on.
I'm just messin with ya.
It looks really good.
Nicely done.
Guys just love that box.
Come on, Tomonori, you gonna
share the wealth or not?
Hyyahh! No.
Hands off four eyes!
I made it especially for him.
All right, I don't mind if I do.
Hold on!
Lemme season it a little.
Well, bon appétit or whatever.
Uh, thanks. I think.
A secret message?
Let's see here.
Uh... I feel like I
drank a gallon of gas.
If someone put a match to me
right now, I'd go up in flames.
Okay. So after I make him lunch,
then what am i supposed to do?
Duh! You gotta work
on your chemistry together.
What kinda chemistry
are you talking about?
Well, what kind do you think?
Really? Aw this sucks!
I'm just not a
make-the-first-move kinda girl!
Listen. Just trust
me here, okay?
And if you play
your cards right,
who knows how far it'll go!
Seriously?
All right.
Hey Ayumu, do you
wanna walk home together?
Uh... Okay.
Hey. Is this the
way home for you?
Yeah. Sure is.
It'll get me
close enough at least.
So. Tell me,
what kinda house does
a vampire ninja live in? Is
it like some ninja compound?
Hey. You're gonna
blow my cover!
Being a vampire ninja's
a secret, you know.
And if you wanna
keep it that way
you should lower
your voice ya dummy!
Look at that, right in
the middle of the street.
Kids these days sure
are bold, aren't they?
Uh... Tomonori.
Sorry 'bout that.
Come on. I told you
before I don't like that name.
It just sounds
way too formal for me.
Well, how 'bout
I call you "Kooky Yuki?'
That's even worse!
I was just kidding.
Call me whatever you want.
Hey, listen.
Hmm?
I didn't agree to
marry you, so do me a favor,
don't go around saying
you're my bride, okay?
I've already made up
my mind to be your bride
so am I just supposed
to ignore how I feel?
And what?
My feelings don't matter?
Sorry, but the law's the law.
But don't worry,
I know I can be
the kinda girl
you're looking for!
I promise.
You sure are stubborn.
I guess you're
gonna start talking about
moving in with me too, right?
I'd love to move in
with you, but since Seraphim
is living there I don't think
it'd be all that
great of an idea.
Oh yeah. That whole thing.
I forgot that you two are
kinda at odds or something.
Our two factions haven't gotten
along for like a hundred years.
So we wouldn't make
very good roommates.
It sounds like it's
off the table to me, then.
We don't really
have the room anyway.
By the way. What happened
to your ramen machine?
Yeah, that.
It broke.
Well. I'm this way.
Oh. I'm the other way.
Hey, can I tell you something?
Sure.
I really think you
and I could mesh well.
But what if we didn't
use words like "bride"?
What if we say
we're just friends?
I thought I made this clear,
but I ain't doin' that! I can't!
Yeah, but--
I'm doin' everything I
can to fall in love with you!
So you have to do everything
you can to fall in love with me!
That's how this works.
So you have to try harder!
Aww, look at that,
a lover's spat.
Kids these days sure are bold.
Hey! You don't have to shout
it out from a mountain top.
It's embarrassing
enough as it is!
Oh shut up! It's even
more embarrassing for me!
Oh yeah? Well, I'm the one
who's really embarrassed here!
What the hell? Haruna? That's
a lotta hat you got there.
What's with the outfit?
Well excuse me. And you look
pretty ridiculous yourself!
But what are you
doing all the way out here?
I was going to come
pick you up, you big dummy.
What the heck was that for?
'Cause I'm in a bad mood!
Yeah, thanks,
I gathered as much.
Look, next time I have a
day off, I'll take you out
and we'll have
some fun, so cheer up.
You really mean it?
Yeah. It'll be my thank you
for helping me
out with that test.
So, it'll be the two of
us and no one else, right?
Wait a sec. I want you
to take me with you too!
I mean, we're supposed
to be together,
so it only makes sense.
Sure, why not?
And while we're at it,
why don't we invite the
other girls to tag along.
How does that sound?
Yeah, but--
Well, all right then,
it's a date!
I never said that,
we'll just be hangin' out!
We got a date! We got a date!
We got a date and
it's gonna be great!
Hmm. I wonder if this
will affect the economy.
Well, the ladies always
get my stock to go up.
Wow, a zombie
in a mall huh?
I think I might have
seen this somewhere before.
Hey, Ayumu?
Can we maybe hold hands?
I think we should.
I'm your bride, remember?
Come on, didn't I ask
you to stop talking like that?
What's the big deal?
We're a couple, right?
Everywhere we go,
they're all over each other.
Oh my,! Get a room you two.
What's the hold up?
We don't have all freakin' day!
Oh, sorry.
We've got shopping to do.
Ta-da!
How much cash is
this gonna cost me?
Hey. That would
look really good on you.
You should try it on.
What?
And then, try these.
You'd look absolutely amazing!
No, you festering
pile of maggot dung!
Sorry.
Meow.
Ah! My eyes!
These panties are cute, huh?
Yeah, but I think this
nighty is more my style.
My eyeballs have
finally regenerated.
Oh wow. That's some
pretty fancy underwear.
I guess it's
for "special occasions".
That bed looks so nice,
it's almost a shame
we have to mess it up.
We do?
Don't you worry about
a thing. I'll be gentle.
You will?
Well at first.
Real nice and gentle.
There's no way
I'm ready for that!
Wow, this is great!
I buy all this stuff for you
guys and I get to carry it too.
I'm so hungry.
I need you to fill me up,
you big sexy stud you.
Well, should we go
get something to eat?
Yeah, I'm starving!
Me, too. What should we get?
Need some help?
Eh... Don't bother.
I hope you have a lovely day.
Yeah, I know it's fast food, but
I hope everyone's okay with it.
Oh, yes! You sexy beast!
If you're hungry,
I've got something you can eat!
The food looks great,
so let's eat it up!
Put down that sauce right now!
I can't let you
disrespect the beef like that.
No good?
No good.
It's impolite to the chef, too.
All right then. If you
say so, I'll give it a try.
I don't get it. Why the
hell'd you have to kiss her?
You're still
going on about that?
You know it wasn't on purpose.
It never would've happened
if you hadn't pushed me anyway.
Nu-uh predator,
this was all your fault!
Don't just sit there!
Come on and have some fun!
Yeah. Sure.
Hey do me a favor
and watch the bags okay!
Oh, Mommy, I want that one!
You need to watch
that attitude young man.
I like this one.
And this one, too.
You've gotta be in
grade school to think
a kiss means that
you're married to someone!
She doesn't exactly
have a choice in the matter,
it's the law.
We've kissed, so
according to your rules
we must be married too!
That was different, I had
to suck your blood to survive.
Besides, you're a woman.
Girl-on-girl
action doesn't count.
Hey, what's up?
You want something to drink?
Ayumu, there's something
I want you to do for me.
What d'ya want?
Look at me.
Make up your mind.
I want you to kiss me!
Here I am, out for a nice
stroll, and I run into you.
Well. Quite an
unlucky coincidence.
Wouldn't you agree, Eucliwood?
What are you
waiting for? Kiss me!
Just be a man for
once and get on with it!
I don't think
that's a good idea.
I mean things are
complicated enough as it is!
Are you trying to
play hard to get?
What's your problem? I'm a bad
ass genius Magical Garment Girl!
Hold on!
Why in the hell you
would pick that girl
to be the only one you kiss!
She ain't got nothing on me!
Stop it!
And what kind of
scumbag invites someone out
on a date and then
brings other people?
Are you trying to turn this into
some kinda gross group thing?
Haruna? Please be
gentle with me.
You're gettin' off
easy this time, buddy.
Hank you berry mush,
das berry kind.
Sorry that took so long.
Hold on. Where's
the neckwear-mancer?
I know it's kinda weird,
but I'm really excited
about our marriage, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm completely overjoyed.
Awesome! I knew
you'd come around!
Let's start making
plans for our real wedding.
I've got colors picked out and--
Look, I'm way too
young to get married, so--
Ah shut up and get to
work on those invitations!
Hope you like licking stamps!