Some of the best I've ever had.
Brains. Brains.
What wrong with my brains?
If I don't pass
this test, I'm screwed.
If you don't watch your
grades, you're gonna end up
in summer school with
the rest of the dummies.
I may not be the smartest
zombie, but I know that
the only thing
worse than having to
drag my ass to school everyday
in the heat of the summer
is frying up like a piece
of bacon on the way there.
Quit daydreaming! Now a
spiral galaxy spins around
and around, exactly
like a top. Picture it.
That top spinning around
just like this, but to get
this thing going you're
gonna need a humongous string!
That's the whole idea
behind "string theory".
Wait. Oh yeah.
Since we're on the subject,
lemme tell you some more
about universal string theory.
A long time ago,
in a galaxy far, far away
this lesson
stopped being useful.
I just asked for
some help on a math problem.
Haruna, you know
what this one is?
Root of three minus root of two.
So genius. How'd you find that?
What?
The answer. Why does this
equal what you just said?
What's one plus one?
It's two.
And why is that?
Because it just is. That's why.
That's right!
Okay. But I have
to show all the steps
I take to get
there on this test.
I can't just say
"it is because it is."
It won't be easy,
but get ready to learn!
And for some reason
to get to the solution
of this math problem,
we have to start back at
the beginning of the universe.
It's a long journey
and way more boring
than I could
have ever dreamed.
Hey! Don't fall asleep on me!
See these. Besides just
being cute, I put these animals
on the board for a reason.
Although it's very complicated
and will probably take the
rest of the night to explain,
so I hope you're ready.
You look like you could use a
hand, if you know what I mean!
Oh, you have absolutely no idea
how happy that would make me.
Whoa! Awesome! The whole
thing's completely done already!
Let me do it, so you'll
be able to understand.
Eu already wrote
everything down for me, so...
Yeah, but this is gonna
make a whole lot more sense.
So, you get it now, or what?
Oh yeah. Clear as gravy.
Geez. You're so stupid.
Take a look at this one here.
It moves like a snake
and chases the bunny rabbit
in the rocket...
Yep, I am totally screwed.
I don't know how it happened,
but I think Haruna somehow
taught me something about math.
Maybe there's a reason
she calls herself a genius.
She's actually pretty
talented in a lot of ways.
I mean, she can cook up
a mean rolled omelette
and it looks
like she can cling
to the window
without too much trouble.
Ayumu! We got a Megalo
sighting, so let's go!
Okay! You don't have to yell!
Whoops. Just got a
little too into it I guess.
That's great so how am I
supposed to find this thing?
I feel your pain.
Yes, what is it?
Sera? Are you able to
sense Megalos, like Haruna?
I don't have that ability.
But hold on just a moment.
Perhaps Lady Hellscythe
can help you.
Cool, I'm sure she can.
There's a block of
condos on 3rd street.
Haruna and the megalo are
in the alley behind them.
Great, thanks.
Wait. I have a message
from Lady Hellscythe.
She says "hurry".
Got it.
Hey, this is Ayumu?
I know, ma'am, you called me.
That's right!
I'm calling because
I need you to do
me a wittle bitty favor.
Tell me what you
need and I am on it!
Aw, you're just
like a little puppy,
always just so eager to please.
Anyway I hate to bother you,
but there's something
that I'd really love
for you to hold for me.
It won't be long,
I just need for you
to keep a finger on
it until I come, okay?
What exactly are
we talking about here?
I could try and explain it,
but I think that would be
a waste of time.
It's very sensitive,
so promise me you'll handle
it as delicately as possible.
Oh-kay.
Thank you so much!
It'll be coming
in two shakes of a lamb's tail!
And it's our little secret,
so don't tell Haruna! Bye bye!
About one hundred
meters in direct sunlight.
It's fly or fry time.
Oh crap that's hot!
Hot hot hot!
Come on, just a
little bit farther!
Shade! Shade!
I can't do it!
It's killing me
for good! Bansai!
Man, that hurts!
Aw, come on, don't be mad.
Whoops! Nuh-uh! Missed me!
Choke on it!
So rank.
I love it when they go down!
Ohhhhh yeah! That's it!
There they are!
Ayumu!
What the hell! Let go a me!
What do you think you're
doing out here all by yourself?
Well I was just... You
shoulda been here way sooner!
It's okay, I got
here just in time!
Take this, you
damn fly! Now buzz off!
That did the trick!
Hurry up and transform
for cryin' out loud!
That thing is a
class double-A megalo!
He's the super scary
horse beast, Wanderlei Siuma!
No more horsin' around!
So, I guess I gotta do this.
Nomobuyo. Oshi. Hashitawa.
Dokeda. Gunmiicha. Deh Ribura.
Oh yeah. That's it! Oh my God!
Alright! Now I feel
like a man again!
You want some?
Yes! Yes! I'm gonna
make you squeal!
Look out! Behind you!
Yeah! More, baby! More!
Hey listen! I'm really not
kidding here! Look out!
I told you!
I like to call
this move "the shocker".
Calm down.
Let me see. Where is it?
Ooh, just a little tickle.
Oohh yuck yuck!
Not what I wanted.
Bad touch! Bad touch!
Now that's more like it!
Give me some sugar!
Hey! Get your
slimy paws offa me!
Let go of her!
Yeah. That's it.
Don't be stingy!
Please! Somebody!
I don't care who! Help!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What the? Who are you?
Here ya go.
Did that? No way?
OWEE! Noooo!
I don't believe it.
He's killing those megalos.
With bowls of ramen?!
Oh! What a world!
What a world!
No! Please don't!
Holy crap, that must
be some really bad ramen.
They can't take it at all.
You forgot about me!
Seraphim! It's great
to see you again!
It's been so lo--
Do not approach me
as if we are friends.
Ow. Seraphim,
that hurts! Let go!
Please! You're gonna
break my arm!
Sera. You know this dude?
This is an
acquaintance of mine, yes.
Well, he saved our asses,
so the least you
could do is let him go.
Who is it, by the way?
They go by the name, Mael Strom.
A Vampire Ninja,
aligned with a reformist faction
I do not care for one iota.
Geez, Seraphim.
What in the hell?
Were you tryin' ta
break my arm for real?
He's right. You went kinda nuts.
Hey, are you alright?
Don't touch me!
Leave 'em alone.
The megalos are gone,
so we should just go back home.
Let me take a look at your arm.
Is it really broken?
I said don't touch me!
I'd kick your ass if
you weren't a middle schooler!
What the hell
are you talking about?!
I'm a high schooler,
ya little brat!
No way! I'm a high schooler!
You're way too
little to be in my class!
Hey! Listen to me!
I'm talkin'
over here, you dumbass!
What is this world coming to?
Oh baby,
I think I'm coming, too!
My first kiss,
and it's a dude? Uhh.
You're a cross-dressing
rapist pervert!
You little maggot!
How dare you make me
witness something so foul!
If you're gonna go
around tongue-raping people
out of the blue like that,
have the decency to
brush your teeth first!
Right. Please
forgive me, ma'am.
Our secret base
is behind these doors.
Inside this factory?
Well, yeah.
You said you wanted to see
where we make our soup,
so I brought you here.
You got some
kinda problem with that?
Uh. No, 'course not.
So good!
Ain't it, though?
I would've never thought a bowl
of ramen could be this good!
I love your pork!
Take it.
Thanks. Not big on pork?
Pork rules.
So why did you give it to me?
Just shut up and
put it in your mouth, okay?
Okay. But if you
love it so much.
Listen, just eat it, will ya?
You bet. But, hey,
it's your loss. Thanks!
Mmm-mmmmm!
This is so freakin' good!
It's like a party in my mouth.
Okay.
There's like, a ton
more if you want it.
Oh you don't mind? That's cool.
Well in that case.
Go ahead and pork me! Uh...
Isn't the whole reason
we came here so you could
explain how you used this
stuff to beat those megalos?
Yeah, I forgot.
Wanna know? It's so cool.
We tried every single ramen
cart, stand and restaurant
we could find.
We ate bowl after bowl
and developed a
complex rating system.
We would mark the shops with
stars. Three being the highest.
We then went back to all the
three star places,
stole the recipes, and then
through countless hours
of experimentation came
up with the ultimate recipe!
That doesn't really
explain anything.
What I wanna know is how come
when you threw it on those
megalos, it made them
disappear? Why does that work?
You sure are curious.
It's a long story,
but I'll have to
start at the beginning.
Is it? Great.
Another long story.
Ya get it now?
Cause if not. Don't ask me.
I ain't gotta clue about how
any of this stuff really works.
Yeah. That's pretty
obvious to me now.
I don't know nothin'
about noodle theory
or any of that kinda crap,
either. But if ya want,
I might could find someone
around here that does.
No, it's cool.
Oh yeah!
Don't worry about a swarm
of megalos invading the town,
'cause we got this bad boy here
to make it rain soup on 'em.
Pretty cool, huh?
Oh man! Really?
Then we'd all be living in
the capital of yummy land!
That's it! I have to go before
I lose any more brain cells.
Wait. Seraphim.
There's somethin'
I need to ask you first.
Yes. What is it?
I'm not sure it's true but
there's a rumor going around
that somebody wants to destroy
this machine. Know who it is?
No, I don't.
You swear?
I do.
Lemme ask ya something else.
You think you'd ever
wanna join our side?
Definitely not. Excuse me.
Hey, wait up.
Hold on. You're goin' too?
Yeah. I mean, I guess I am.
Okay. Fine then leave!
That machine was
pretty impressive, I guess.
But I'm not so sure it's
all that great of an idea.
It's not. Its use would surely
cause an environmental disaster.
It would?
Sounds pretty bad to me.
My superiors have been trying
to develop a containment plan.
Oh, yeah?
Guess all's well then.
That's where you're wrong.
What do you mean?
Listen carefully.
You kissed Mael Strom
and for a vampire ninja,
a kiss signifies a sacred bond.
It does not matter
when or how it happens.
Therefore as a result of
your foolish mistake earlier,
the two of you are married now.
Huh? But that was an
accident! We didn't mean to.
You're just
screwing with me, right?
No, I'm not. You should
be careful around those
you know nothing about.
Ah! So that's why you never
wanted to suck my blood?
That's part of it, yes.
But honestly the mere thought
of you in my mouth
makes me violently ill.
Well, if it was you
instead of her back there,
could you have prevented it?
I'd rather die.
Geez, sorry for asking.
Anyway.
Changing your mind?
I'm almost certain
Mael doesn't feel
that was a real
wedding ceremony.
Although it doesn't matter.
We vampire ninjas place the
law above our own feelings.
Let me get this straight.
If I just up and kissed you
right now without
you expecting it,
the two of us
would be married?
We would. I would
pledge my love to you alone.
That's assuming you were
able to survive your attempt.
Yeah, I'm dead enough, thanks.
Oh great, now what?
Hey look,
it's Lester the molester.
I'm just gonna
pretend I didn't hear you
and ask, "what is that?"
Geez, could you
be anymore clueless?
It's from your stupid culture.
Our very own Christmaween tree!
Furiously riding
down the river of stars.
A big fat man drives a sleigh
led by two huge creatures.
Covered head to
toe in blood and guts,
he flies like a bat
outta hell through the night
in search of unsuspecting prey.
He carries a bag big enough
for a grown man with him,
and under the cover of darkness.
He sneaks in through
the windows of houses marked
with fancy-looking bamboo
trees in their front yards.
And even though
he's actually a demon,
Thunder Claws grants wishes.
But only to those people who
wear their hair in ponytails.
Ya see? I swear.
You can be so stupid.
I'm not so stupid
that I'd believe a word
of the crap I just heard.
Don't worry, you don't
look any worse with that.
How would you know?
You're not even lookin' at me.
No reply, of course.
Now let's see
what everybody wrote.
Hey, what the?
Stop peeking at 'em!
It doesn't work if you
read them, you stupid butthole!
That another rule
you just made up?
You shouldn't worry
about mine anyway!
Hurry up and write
your own dumb wish!
We're all sick
of waiting on you!
I told you the ponytail
doesn't change how you look.
Look at me and tell me again!
Come on. I know
what you really want.
And I want it, too,
so let me give it to you.
Oh, you'd like
that wouldn't you?
Okay! Since we're
all done writing,
we should go to Ayumu's
room to get ready for tonight!
We'll come down and grab
you when we're done, okay?
So get crackin!
Are they freakin' serious about
all the bull crap they wrote?
This is so dumb.
Okay, we're ready!
Let's go trick or caroling!
Yeah, I'm definitely
done playing along.
You're Ayumu Aikawa?
Yep, that would be me.
You've been briefed, yes?
Here is the item.
I leave it in your care.
Item? Oh, for the Head Teacher?
Yes, it's me.
I see. And what of it?
Stop asking stupid questions
and think for yourself!
Are we clear?
Hey. Wait a sec, I,,,
Eyeglasses? What's so
special about them?
Uh. Ayumu it's me!
Oh. Hey, uh. What're you
doing here in my class?
I-I just came
to bring you this!
I mean I'm your wife now, so I
should at least make you lunch.
It's the pork you like.
So you believe all that?
What happened between
us... It means that...
Yeah, yeah, Sera
told me everything.
But I'm not
gonna hold you to--
Stop! We can't get
outta this so easy!
It doesn't matter why it
happened, just that it happened!
There's no going back,
we're in this together,
you and me, understand?
I'm yours now, okay? There's
nothing that'll change it!
But it's just not right!
It's just how it is.
You're still my husband now,
whether you like it or not!
I can't believe it,
but you're actually serious
about all this, aren't you?
Of course I am!
My people have lived like this
for centuries and
I honor their traditions!
That's why I'll be your wife.
No matter how hard you
wanna pretend that I ain't!
I mean I gotta get
married to someone eventually
or die alone in
a house full of cats.
Well, I appreciate
you really spelling out
the alternatives
to me here like that.
What's up, Tomonori?
That ain't my name, ya creep!
Hey, man. You know this girl?
Oh yeah,
this is Tomonori Yoshida,
from the class next door.
I told ya, Four Eyes,
that ain't my name!
Whaddaya mean, that's always
been your name you crazy freak!
For the last time, stop
calling me that, you hear me?
My name is Yuki! So get
that through your thick skull!
Say my name! Yuki! Yuki!
Hey, guys? Do either of you
feel like clueing me in here?
You see?
"Tomonori" clear as day.
If you say so.
Are you blind? Put on your
glasses and tell me what ya see!
Watch it!
X-ray specs? Hell, yeah!
You know, I'm not feeling
the love connection here.
Yeah, I think of you as
more of a friend, I guess.
Definitely one without benefits,
though if you know what I mean.
Oh.
Speaking of friends,
that Orito is super slimy.
I think he uses
too much hand lotion.