Hiya, peeps...
Been a little while, hasn't it?
The more things
change, am I right?
Some seriously
good popsicles here.
Thank Haruna if you
like them so much...
Apparently someone online has
the time to blog about sweets...
And she of course has the
time to follow their posts.
Kudos.
Internet foodies: it's an
exciting time to be alive.
If there's a better way to beat
the heat, I don't even care.
Who knew popsicle technology
would come so far?
It's like a party
in my mouth!
Trying to focus on
my snack here, babe.
Target locked...
Watch me swoop in and destroy
a green tea one next.
Easy, chops:
that's your tenth one...
Your tummy's
gonna bitch you out.
Yeah, right...
I have a crazy
high pain threshold...
A little stomachache
never killed anybody.
That's a healthy attitude...
Should I dial for
an ambulance now?
Don't say I didn't warn ya.
So, yeah.
Welcome back to Weirdsville,
ladies and germs.
Never a dull moment.
As our reluctant, perverted
hero picks his moment to pry
Haruna's stolen powers from
Chris' grasp, Gaia hovers
to drop an even greater
challenge in his lap.
Of course, he's oblivious.
And by "greater," I mean the
single most ruthless challenge
he's ever faced...
Not gonna lie:
being undead has its cons.
Wrinkles, for one.
Little buggers keep poppin' up
even when I'm not in the sun.
Rise and shine!
Bit early on a Sunday to be
dealing with you, isn't it?
If I'd waited
till you woke up,
we'd have missed
the flea market.
And I should care
about this, why?
Clams, bro...
It's a good way to stack up
a few while you
get rid of old crap.
Of course...
It's boring as hell 'less you
know how to add some spice.
So... I challenge you
to a sell-off!
Coming at you Sunday,
Sunday, Sunday...
You and Lady Hellscythe
get the booth set up...
While you do that,
I'll grab more boxes...
Sound good?
Okey-dokey .
Guess you can start
by puttin' these guys out.
I would do anything I can,
to help my Big Stud.
That's my girl...
Nothing like a menial
task to bring us closer.
Seriously?
You're in on this?
Question...
Level with me...
What exactly was the point
of tripping the wire
on Haruna's competitive streak?
You know the old saying:
when the wind blows,
the bucket guys
make out like bandits.
I do?
Wait...
I fudged that...
Basically it's the same
as saying one in the hand
is worth two in the bush,
know what I mean?
Point is...!
If Little Miss Hates-to-Lose
is on the case,
I know I gotta dig deep
and bring my A-game.
That's good for business.
Pink elephants on parade...
And the idea of her throwing
every dirty trick she knows
at me is kind of appealing.
It's winner take all,
my friend...
But the loser might just get
a whiff of moth-balled panties
in the bargain.
What is wrong with you?
You have quite a lot to learn
if that's your idea
of displaying the goods...
Put the box down
and find somewhere else
to stare into space.
Hello, beautiful!
Slow your roll.
Oh, don't get
your panties in a wad.
Look, I'll get the stuff
sorted; you help Haruna...
Think that's
something you can handle?
Hey, uh...
You could come and be the mascot
for my booth, if you want!
Must your voice go up
three octaves every time
you address me, filth...?
It's like nails
on a chalkboard.
Right, right...
Tone is everything
to potential customers;
don't want to scare them off...!
Free tip from the
master saleswoman!
I don't think she meant
for you to take that
as encouragement, dude.
So?
How's tricks?
Anything I can do
to lend a hand?
As if...!
There'll be popsicle
stands in hell
the day a born
hocker like me needs help!
Yeah, about that...
Your prices aren't
exactly competitive.
Don't tell me
how to run a business!
'less you know a way I could
unload some of this junk.
Well, let's see,
you could, uh...
start with some nicer stuff.
Huh...
Like this little do-hickey,
for example.
Except...
You might wanna
put a price tag on it.
This "do-hickey"
isn't for sale.
Then what in the heck
is it doin' out here?
What's it gonna take
to get this stuff movin'?
'kay, look.
For starters, take a couple
zeros off what you're asking.
Think cheap.
Alright, fine.
Pleasure doing
business with you, hon.
Uh...
Did she escape from the zoo?
Hey now...
Don't look a gift cheetah
in the mouth.
I could've taken her
for more...!
I swear on my life,
if four-eyes wins this...!
Feast your peepers on value!
Anybody get a look at what he's
tryin' to pawn off over there?
Come n' get 'em while
they're hot, folks...!
Oh sweetie, don't
look at this trash.
Seriously, what kind of fascist
dystopia are we living in?
It ever occur to you
that a flea market
isn't the best place
to sell these?
Whatever, dude.
Sexy's always in demand.
Who the hell gets
turned on by cartoons?
These are precious.
How much?
300, please.
Quite a bargain.
Be sure to tell
all your friends about us!
Ayumu.
How's it goin'?
Whoa...
Did'ya make all
of these yourself?
I'm kinda crafty.
Trust me, this girl
knows exactly what to do
with a bun in the oven.
I can tell.
This stuff looks
good enough to eat!
Pay up!
Say what?
You touch it, you bought it.
It's wrapped.
I'll take a couple of those,
too, while you're at it.
That'll be an even 300,
good sir.
The second one...
I'll throw in free.
Oh, uh, thanks.
Hey, Ayumu!
You know, ramen does sound
pretty good right about now.
Hop on over and have a bowl!
You know you want some!
Yeah, okay...
I was just sayin' how
some would really hit the spot.
Here ya go!
Holy crap...
Might just be the
best bowl I've ever had.
Oh...
Stop it, you're gonna
give me an ego.
Just callin' it
like I see it...
I know my ramen; nothing
I've had compares to this.
And you're not
just saying that...?
Well, here then.
Try this out and
tell me what you think.
Wow.
Fancy.
On the house.
It's sensei's recipe.
I guess you got
Haruna's secret out of her.
Sort of...
But I've got a ways to go
before I'm good as her...
What's the verdict?
Honest...?
It's pretty darn close.
Really...?
This may sound a little
kooky, but, I had a feeling
today's batch was gonna turn out
to be an extra special one...
Oh...
That's right...
Have a lookie.
The Kira-Kira Shop
is doing a cross-promotion
with Ninja Ramen.
So you get a special,
today-only,
10 percent discount
on all their merch!
Nifty, huh?
♪ Your eyes may
give me what I need ♪
♪ Undying worship's
how I feed ♪
She may need to think
about getting a new agent.
And...
every CD on sale today features
one of 33 special collectible
pinup photos of everyone's
favorite dark queen
in lots of sexy poses.
Some are available
for individual sale...
Boom.
I must have all of them!
"Sexy's always
in demand" right?
Thank you very much...
May gleaming viscera ooze
out of your enraptured ears.
My headphones'll be so sticky!
Hit me, Kirara!
I can't wait anymore!
Love the enthusiasm.
Hate the rudeness.
Cut in line again...
And I'll see to it your
entrails are used to rope off
the next one,
you sloshing sack of offal.
Uh, yes ma'am!
You tell him, Kirara!
Man, that was seriously hot.
What's wrong with you people?!
I'm totally drowning in value!
And don't get me
started on variety!
If you can't find it here,
you just ain't lookin'!
What does that horndog
have that I don't?
Guess it's that time of day
when his target audience
comes crawling out the woodwork.
Sorry, guys; limit one copy
per customer, please.
Whoa, dude!
Is this...?
Ah...!
Good eye, sir!
Yes, that's a premiere
edition you're holding there.
Clientele like that is
every merchant's wet dream.
Jackholes...
Why can't they give
pink elephants a chance?
Oh, come on, you've still
got a shot, Haruna...!
Just break out
your secret weapon!
Sera's sweet you-know-what...
Thank you very much.
Um...
I think I like this one.
Hey...
Mind if I pick it up
and have a look?
She's luring 'em
in like gangbusters.
Could you maybe
hand this one to me, miss?
Of course.
That's our whole economy...!
I see it now!
Haruna...!
That's the answer!
What is?
Never mind...
We might as well pack it in.
Don't even talk to me
like that!
I'm a Magical Garment girl
with top notch brains...!
I'm not just gonna
throw in the towel...!
I've still got a shot...
I can win this thing.
I agree.
Now is no time to quit.
You wouldn't want to
disappoint your customers.
Where did they all come from?
Sensei!
We can do this together!
Just put us to work.
Okay...
What's going on?
Ah, yes...
I see it now...
The bargain-hunting public has
come to its collective senses...
Step right up savvy shoppers...!
Everything on the
blanket is half off!
Hell yeah!
Step right up!
Spoiled.
Thank you!
What about this...?
There's no price tag?
Oh, I dunno...
That thing's not even mine,
it belongs to the Leaf Lady.
Name your price and I'll pay...!
Whatever you want, it's yours!
Alrighty, then...
How 'bout all the earnings
from your flea market till...?
Which would also mean
that the victor
in today's
little contest is moi.
Okay I give up!
Up up up
Son of a--where the hell
did it go?
Oh man...
All in a day's work, huh?
Yuck...
This stuff tastes like piss
squeezed through a dirty sock...
Haruna...
What is this?
Crap, crap, crap!
It's gone!
Uh, Haruna...
Is this...
like, uh...
supposed to happen?
'cause if it is, this stuff
should have warning label!!!
Hey!
You don't have to treat me
like I'm invisible!
That's what you get.
Maybe next time
you'll think twice before
helping yourself to my
super secret invention...
Sneaky dill weed.
Guzzling my elixir while
I'm on my hands and knees
searching for a
philosopher's stone!
Why would ya leave
an invisibility potion
lying around?
To who...?!
Peeing Toms?!
I advised her not to.
Just so you know,
your thirst cheated me
out of a small fortune...
Maybe I'm mad...
Maybe you owe me.
Am I ever gonna change back,
or am I stuck this way?!
Relax...
It's not designed
to last forever, okay...?
You oughtta be able
to check yourself out
in a mirror again real soon.
Oughtta?
What do you mean oughtta?
Never mind that for now...
I'd like us to focus more on
the philosopher's stone Haruna
lost at the flea market.
We need to find it and seal it
up as soon as possible...
Left outside of its
special box long enough
it's bound to go rogue...
It'll spontaneously
produce things like
that disgusting slime again.
So the fact that it's out there
floating around on its own
right now is a big deal...
Probably.
Then we need to get it
back, don't we...?
But you sold it and
you don't remember to who...
Could be anybody.
Yeah, no kidding.
The whole damn student body
was jostlin' your tchotchkes.
It's unlikely whoever bought it
is aware of its significance.
Remember that blond hottie with
the midriff who was browsing
for a present to herself?
I have a sneaking
suspicion it was her.
Of course it was.
Good instincts.
World's most adorable
detective right here...
Wait a second.
If it's true our culprit
was a girl, we're screwed...
The school's doing
physical exams tomorrow.
You're invisible, silly.
And it goes without
saying you're brave.
That makes you
the perfect private eye.
You do have a point there...
Alright!
Let's do this!
Swallow-Return Strike!
Don't even put into words
whatever vile shenanigans
you're dreaming up!
That's right, kids.
I'm a zombie, a Magical Garment
Girl, and now, evidently,
the Invisible Man...
Complicated life.
Right.
I'm out.
Don't have
too much fun, jackass!
'kay...
Commence Operation Creeper.
You know, I could
get used to this, actually.
Invisibility's a breeze.
Speaking of breeze...
Hmm...?
Oh, right...
I'm naked as a jaybird...
I'm about to hop the proverbial
garden wall in my birthday suit!
Oh, man.
How's a guy
s'posed to concentrate?
Ugh.
Pull yourself together.
Get in, get out.
Oh my god!!
I've gained, like,
so much weight!
Whoops.
My bad.
Oh...
that was kinda weird.
Something wrong?
I just felt some creepy touch.
Must've just been
your imagination.
Wow, twenty centimeters,
look at you...!
Somebody's been doing
Pilates on the side.
Pilates and whole milk.
Snap out of it, dude!
This is beyond wrong...!
Two times two is four;
two times three is six;
two times four is eight.
Tomonori doesn't have the stone.
Moving on.
Alright, Kanami;
give it your best shot!
You can do it.
Way to go; fourteen point five.
Not bad, but
I don't think she has it.
Looks like you hold
the record so far, Yuki...
Your turn.
Okay.
Stay strong...
Yowza!
Seven centimeters.
Give me a break, Tae,
you're not even trying...
Now go down there
like you believe it.
Hey...!
Be nice, I'm doing my best.
Try bending more from the waist.
Well where else am I
supposed to bend from?
Looks good,
but no sign of the stone.
Alright, girls!
Upper body extensions are next!
Show us how it's done, babe.
I'm on it.
I love physical fitness.
Look at 'er go...!
Well, I can safely rule out
these two, I think.
Maybe it's on her.
Don't even think about it,
girl: just go for it...
I've got your feet.
Wish me luck!
Good luck!
You got this!
Show us the merchandise!
Okay...
No dice...
Well done, though.
That's it for, me!
Oh wow...!
that's gotta be a new record!
Awesome-sauce!
That girl...
Wow.
Just, wow.
Didn't hurt yourself, did ya?
Uh-uh...
I just felt kinda...
I don't know how
to describe it, really.
No, no, no, no!
Not now!
I'm gonna get busted.
Wait, bad choice of words!
Damn it, man!
Focus!
An invisibility technique...
Who is this?
Oh crap...
I have ways of finding out.
Excellent muscle tone...
What's my dirty
darling up to now?
Listen to me...
I'm not doing
what you think I am.
Ayamu, you cheeky bastard.
Way to let your bud
suffer out here.
That's the story, I swear.
I take your word for it...
Letting the stone
float freely invites disaster...
You're going to need my help.
That'd be awesome.
Very well.
Standby...
It's Saras.
You realize I'm gonna
owe you my life for this?
Form a dragnet.
We're doing lost and found.
Guess I can head back home.
What?!
You've got to be kidding me!
Oh god!
Not here, not here, not here!
Like my yearbook blurb
isn't already gonna read
like a rap sheet!
Where was I s'posed to stash
an emergency pair of pants...?!
I've got to find something...
I'll never hear
the end of this!
Hello?
Someone back there?
Why does my luck
have to suck balls?!
Ah, what the hell.
I'm already a
cross-dressing perv;
why not a full-fledged
streaker to boot...?
Maybe they'll name a piece
of legislation after me.
Oh...
What are you doing in here?
Oh...!
You know...
I'm looking for
my contact lenses!
Funny, I thought
for sure you'd be Orito...
He's more of a creeper.
Of all the people
to be confused for...!
What did you expect, man?
Put yourself in her shoes!
Please...
I know this looks bad...
But I'm honestly
not up to anything...
perverted...
Worst.
Defense.
Ever.
It's cool...
I believe you.
Seriously?!
What is wrong with her?
I wouldn't!
You know, if you'd like me to...
I could bring you
something to cover up with.
Yeah, That would be wonderful...
Cuz...
I left all my clothes
at home in the wash.
I see...
Interesting...
How did you get
to school today, then?
Uh...
I ran like a maniac?
Way to sell it, dumbass.
I'm gonna go out on a limb
and say you're not
looking for contacts.
And you would be correct.
Problem solved...
Here'ya go.
Oh my god, you're a lifesaver!
Could you maybe turn
around for sec, please?
Oh...!
Yes, of course.
Hey, mind if I ask
what this is?
Pretty cute, isn't it...?
Just a lil' something
I bought from Haruna
at the flea market yesterday.
Is this for sale?
I'd love to have it.
Sure, no problem.
I'll even give you
a special helper's discount.
This is actually what
I've been looking for.
What a nice coincidence.
Seriously, Tae...
I owe you big time.
Oh don't mention it...
Glad I could help.
Now, why exactly
did you have to be naked?
What?!
Haruna was "mistaken?!"
I found the real one
under a couch cushion,
as per orders from Saras.
'course you did...
and it explains why
this one says "fake" on it.
My goof guys:
this one's totally on me...
Kobo falls from his branch...
Sometimes even monkeys
let the brush slip...
Yeah, that's not gonna cut it...
You have any idea how many
hoops I jumped through for you?
I think someone needs a crash
course in responsibility.
Nothing.
I'm good.
Then why are you giving off
steam like a boiling octopus...?
Are your brains evaporating
from an excess of filth?
Like I just told you:
it's nothing.
Hang on...
Where's that bottle of potion I
had sitting here a second ago?
Well, boys and girls:
that's the story...
Hope you enjoyed it
as much as I did.
One day they'll pass
a piece of legislation
with your name on it, maggot!
I propose we do it again
sometime, eh...?
Give us a little while and I'm
sure there'll be plenty more
stories to tell.
Hey butthole...!
Chuck it up or
I'll siphon it out of ya!
What the...
Where The hell is your...
bra...?
Jerk!
Zombie.
Magical Garment Girl.
Invisible Man.
X-ray vision guru.
Like I said,
never a dull moment.