[EINA]
Let me guess. Something really,
really good happened to you.
Hm? Is it really
that obvious?
(Giggle) That goofy
little smile of yours
is a dead giveaway. Well?
(Laugh) Okay, now get this...
My most recent Status update
was the best one I've ever had.
[WELF]
I just want to join
a Party, alright?!
[BELL]
I have a new skill and
everything!
(Misha laughs nervously)
There's gotta be
at least ONE
out there that's
not full yet!
Yeah, I'm really
sorry, but uh...
[EINA]
WHAT?!
[BOTH] Huh?
You mean you
hit level 2
in just a month
and a half?!
Uh...
(Nervous laugh)
(Opening Song)
[BELL]
I can't believe it.
I can't believe
I really beat a minotaur!
[HESTIA]
Okay, all done!
I guess that means I'm
officially up to level 2 now.
But how come I don't
feel any different?
Hmm...
"Such incredible power!"
Is that actually what
you expected to happen?
Well, yeah,
I was hopin'.
You'll get a feel
for it eventually.
[HESTIA]
In the meantime, would you like
to hear some fantastic news?
(Mystical humming)
[BELL]
What is it?
[HESTIA]
A Skill.
Huh?
Your second, I mean,
your very first one! See?
After all this time your Skill
has finally been activated!
[BELL]
"Argonaut"?
Wow... A Skill!
A real Skill!
Look at that Goddess Hestia,
my own Skill!
(Giggle)
It's Argonaut...
or Heroic Aspiration.
Uh... wait, why do you have
to say it like that?
Because if you manifest this
particular kind of Skill...
It means that you still
have yet to grow out of
Uh...
your big dream of
being a fairy tale hero!
Uh!
Well, yeah, but
it's not like...
It's not like
what, Bell?
(Embarassed whimper)
[HESTIA]
Oh, you're so cute!
[BELL]
Hey, cut it out!
GODDESS!
[HESTIA]
Well anyway, the important thing
is that now you have a Skill.
So all you need to figure out
is how it's supposed to work
and practice with it.
Fine...
I have to go out for awhile,
so try to cheer up
before I get back, okay?
[HESTIA]
See ya!
Where are you
gonna go?
Well, today happens to be
Denatus Day,
so all the gods will be
having their quarterly
meetings back in town.
What's that like?
Well it's very important.
We get to pick second names for
all those who've leveled up.
And that will
include you, too!
Huuhh?!
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Hello, Hestia.
Uh!
Oh, hey there, Take.
A little bird told me your
adventurer reached level 2
in a mere month,
is that true?
Uh!
Yeah, sorta
kinda...
Impressive!
Took the Sword Princess
a year to get that far!
All the gods
are very excited.
EVERYONE is
talking about it.
[HESTIA]
The Takemikazuchi Familia will
be having one today too, right?
[TAKE]
Yeah, the name's Mikoto Yamato.
I'll have to use all
the leverage I can at
the council today.
Her name can be nothing
short of spectacular!
Same here.
So let's hope we both
end up with good names...
...for the sake
of our children!
(Doors creak)
(Laughter)
I betcha they'll give me
some sweet new armor
to go along with
my second name.
I wonder what kind of badass
cool name I'll end up with.
Maybe Fire Blizzard?
Or Tornado Typhoon!
OR BURNING BLAZE OF DEATH!
Ha! Oh Man!
[BELL]
But this armor's been
pretty great though.
It's really easy to move in.
Welf Crozzo... Hm...
[HESTIA]
Bell! Bell!
Hm?
(Panting)
You are going
to be so happy!
Ah, oh, yeah?
What is it?!
Um, well it's not terrible!
(Giggle)
Uh... Wha‐?
(Bar chatter)
[LILI]
"Little Rookie"?
Is that really
what they call you?
Yep. What do
you think?
Let's see... honestly?
Totally lame.
Yeah, right?
I mean she did say it's better
than it could've been, but‐
[SYR]
Actually I think I like
"Little Rookie".
[BOTH] Huh?
Congratulations
on ranking up.
Great work.
So you go right ahead
and drink to your
heart's content!
Tonight is your night!
Woo!
[RYU]
Woo.
Huh... that must
be the guy.
Double‐timed his way
to level 2, I hear.
[BELL]
Um, are those people
talking about me?
[LILI]
Yeah. That sorta
stuff happens
when adventurers
get famous.
Huh?
You should just try to take
it as a compliment, okay?
Now, bottoms up,
you guys!
Uh, sure!
Wait...
aren't you two
supposed to be working?
Mama Mia said you can feel free
to order as much as you like.
And she told us to
come sit with you.
[RYU]
I think she wants you
to spend more money.
(Laughs)
Well, alright then.
[ALL]
Cheers!
[RYU]
I have a question.
Did I hear that you and
Miss Arde are planning
to go down to the middle floors
of the dungeon sometime soon?
[BELL]
Oh, yeah.
We'll be playing it by
ear for the most part.
Is that so?
I hope you won't think me
rude for saying this,
but you two have no
business down there.
Anything below 13
is too much.
Hm?
Huh?
Are you trying to tell me
you don't think
Master Bell and I
are tough enough
for the middle floors?
That's not what
I'm saying at all.
But, they're nothing
like the upper floors.
You will see more
monsters there...
and they'll be stronger.
Look it's not that
you're not good enough,
but you will not be
able to do it yourself.
[RYU]
You must join
a Party first.
I see what you're saying,
but it's hard to find
people you can depend on.
(Hearty laugh)
[MORD]
Havin' trouble
makin' some friends?
Are ya, little fella?
Huh?
If you wanna join up
with our party,
we got plenty of space
for you on the team.
We're a buncha
level 2's.
We like to hit
the middle floors.
[BELL]
Well...
On one condition...
[MORD]
...you're gonna have
to bring these hot
little barmaid babies
along with ya.
Huh?
Hmph.
[MORD]
Partners are s'posed
to share their goods,
y'know what I mean?
(Annoyed sigh)
Hey‐ Uh?
[RYU]
Get lost.
You don't deserve someone
like him on your team.
Huh? Listen here,
sweetheart,
you know I can offer you a much
better time than this little
wimpy half‐pint ever could.
What do you say?
[RYU]
You need to back off.
[MORD]
Ah! OH! (Pained yell)
Understand it's not wise
to insult my friends.
Ah!
(Shattering glass)
I don't care if you're
a chick or not,
I'm gonna kick your ass!
[MIA]
Hey!
(Steaming)
[MORD] Huh?
[MIA]
This ain't that kind of
establishment, boys!
If you wanna have
a tickle fight,
you need to take it outside!
(Both gasp)
O‐okay. We were
just leavin'‐
[MIA]
And don't forget about
your bill, you jackass!
(Both panic)
[BELL]
Nope...
Not this one, either.
(Sigh)
None of them are his.
What's the deal here? Hm?
[WELF]
Hey man, why is my stuff
always in the back?
[SALESMAN]
Sir, please.
[WELF]
I put my life on
the line to make it
and you can't even gimme
some decent shelf space?!
Up nice'n high.
Eye‐level!
Ah, welcome, Sir.
Can I help you find something?
Yeah, I can't find
any Welf Crozzo armor
anywhere in the shop,
did you stop selling it?
Huh? Uh...
Huh? What?
(Snort)
(Loud laugh)
Wha‐?
(Laughing continues)
[WELF]
Shop 'til you drop, kid!
Armor by Welf Crozzo.
(Chuckle)
[WELF] Well, well, well.
How 'bout that?
The Famous Little Rookie's
interested in my work!
Oh, come on...
I never thought I would ever
meet THE Mr. Crozzo.
(Annoyed grunt)
Look, cut it out
with all the
"Mr. Crozzo" stuff,
would ya?
That's way too formal
for my taste.
Mr... Welf, then?
Still "Mr." huh?
Ah well, never mind.
(Clears throat)
So, Bell Cranel!
[WELF]
You've purchased my armor
twice now, haven't you?
I suppose that makes you
my very satisfied client.
Uh, what's going on.
(Chuckles)
Huh?
It's nothing.
It's just a little
territorial dispute.
Now then, Bell...
How would you like to do
business directly?
What do you mean
by "directly"?
I will give you a special
deal on any weapons
and armor you need, but...
I do have one little
'ol request in exchange.
It's not much.
Hm? Okay.
Bell, I humbly ask
to join your party.
Huh?
[WELF]
Finally, I made it
to Floor 11! (Laughs)
Sorry, Bell, I guess
I shouldn't have asked you
to do this right away.
Nah, it's
no problem.
You're doing it to build
up your smithing ability,
so in the long run
this'll benefit me too
as someone who has
a contract with you.
Well, I'm glad at least ONE of
us is excited about all this...
[BELL]
Hm?
[LILI]
Don't you think
you should be adventuring with
somebody from your OWN Familia?
(Grunt)
Uh, actually, Lili...
Mr. Welf and his Familia
don't, uh...
Hmph. He doesn't get
along with them?
Hmm.
So you fell for this
guy's sob story
just because he bribed
you with some stupid armor?!
Uh!
Huh?
[LILI]
Why didn't you discuss
this with me first?!
(Welf clears throat)
[BELL]
I'm sorry.
Am I THAT much of a burden?
Huh, Pipsqueak?
Hey, don't call
me Pipsqueak!
I have a name and it
happens to be Liliruca Arde!
Oh! Pardon me, Little Bit!
Put 'er there!
Uh!
I don't think so.
Lili, please...
I'd appreciate it
if we could all get along.
I mean Welf Crozzo makes
really good armor, so...
Crozzo?!
[LILI]
Did you say "Crozzo"?
(Welf groans)
H‐hm...
[LILI]
The cursed magic
swordsmiths from the
failed smithing nobility?!
Hm?
Wait, what?
You really didn't
know about that?!
[LILI]
The Crozzos used to be famous
for being able to make
powerful magic swords.
But then, one day, they lost
all of their abilities, and now
the family's ruined forever!
Really? None of that
rings a bell?
[WELF]
Yep, the Crozzo name
is worthless.
[BELL] Huh?
Who cares about what
we USED to be good at?
Yeah, but‐
(Crumbling rock)
[ALL]
Huh?
(Ground crumbles)
I don't think right now is the
best time to talk about it.
(Growling)
[WELF]
Okay, you can leave
the orcs to me.
They shouldn't be too hard
for me to handle by myself.
[LILI]
Right. Then I guess I'll try to
back you up the best I can.
[WELF]
Aw, thanks, Little Bit!
I think she likes me.
No, you totally make
me wanna puke.
[WELF]
PFFT! HA!
[LILI]
But I can't let you get
in Master Bell's way.
Hm.
(Growling continues)
[BELL]
Alright, let's do this.
These guys are mine!
(Screeching)
[BELL, THINKING]
Was he slow... or...
Huh?
Hyah! Gah!
...have I gotten faster?
HYAAH!
AGH!
(Distant clashing)
Huh? Holy...!
(Panting)
Mr. Welf! Lili! Look out!
(Roaring)
(Both scream)
Fire Bolt!
(Boom and fizzle)
[BELL, THINKING]
My magic is stronger, too!
It's working...
I'm finally starting
to get closer...
...to Ais Wallenstein!
(Bete yelling)
[TIONA]
Move it, Bete!
I don't wanna
cut you up!
[BETE]
Like that weak‐ass weapon could
even put a scratch on me! AH!
[GARETH]
What's got those two
all outta whack?
They can't teach the
others acting like that.
[RIVERIA]
It seems they were inspired by
an adventurer they met earlier.
Hmm. I take it you're talking
about that skinny young fella
you ran into before
we all met up here.
Indeed. His name
is Bell Cranel.
[AIS]
I'm going, too.
[GARETH]
Uh, and what's with her?
[RIVERIA]
Hm. Would appear he must have
lit a fire in her as well.
(Slicing)
[WELF]
Whoo! Sure is good to be
in a party, am I right?
[BELL]
Totally, there's not
nearly as much stuff
to worry about this way.
That's the idea, y'know?
Whenever you have more fighters,
it changes the way
you're gonna behave
in combat.
[BELL]
Huh? Another party
just showed up.
Let's eat lunch after
Little Bit finishes
picking up all
the magic stones.
Hm.
We'll leave the
monsters to them.
Hey, sparkles.
What's that?
Huh?
(Twinkling)
I don't know...
(Screaming)
[BOTH]
Huh?
(Panting)
(Heavy footsteps and roaring)
[BOTH]
HUH?!
[MAN 1]
Get outta here!
It's a Dragon!
HUH?!
[MAN 2]
RUN!
Wait, where's Lili?!
(Roaring)
(Man screams)
AH!
(Lili gasps)
[BELL]
Lili!
Get outta there, now!
Ah!
(Roaring)
(Panting)
HAH!
Fire Bolt!
AH! Ugh!
(Boom and fizzle)
(Gasp)
(Both speechless)
(Heavy thud)
AH!
Huh?
[HESTIA]
Uh‐huh, no doubt about it.
That right there was
your Argonaut Skill.
It gives you an opportunity
to turn the tables.
Since you always wanted to
become a hero so badly...
I guess you can consider it to
be kind of a shortcut, you know?
Whenever you find
yourself with the odds
all stacked against you...
you can still be able to win
with the small bit of power
you have left.
That's what we like
to call a Hero Shot.
And it fits you
just perfectly.
I mean, don't you think?
Huh...
[BELL]
I wanted to ask you...
Have you ever heard of
a disgraced family of
nobles called Crozzo?
That's your friend's
family, isn't it?
They used to be super famous
because they could create
magical swords,
but that's all I
really know about them.
Uh‐huh...
But if you're asking about
Welf Crozzo in particular,
they did tell me a little
something about him at the shop.
He has the ability to make
magic swords, too.
(Choking)
Huh?!
And from what I've heard they
are like ridiculously powerful.
Apparently the rest of
his Familia refers to him
as the "Unused Treasure."
Why is that?
Because the dummy never
actually makes them.
I'm sure he could easily
have all the fame and riches
he could ever want
if he just made a few,
but for some reason, he refuses.
(Sigh)
Unfortunately,
you've made yourself a
contract with someone
who's got insane talent
but has no desire to actually
put it to good use.
Hm...
(Laughs)
[WELF]
So, Little Bit's
taking some time off?
[BELL]
Yeah. The father of that gnome
that runs the boarding house
told me she's sick
and needs to rest.
She said she's sorry
she can't make it.
Ah, that's too bad.
In that case,
do you maybe want to come
hang out with me for the day?
Huh?
Just think of it this way:
I'd like to say thank you
for letting me be in your party.
[WELF]
I want to make you
a new piece of gear!
(Happy gasp)
(Door creaks)
[BELL]
Is this... where you make
your weapons, Mr. Welf?
Yeah, sorry about the mess.
Didn't expect a guest.
Oh, no! That's okay!
[WELF]
So what do you need?
Feel free to try
something out.
I don't need anything.
The light armor you gave
me is perfectly fine.
You should always be looking
for better armor, Bell.
Adventurers need to make sure
they're as prepared as possible
at any given time. Right?
Uh, well, that's true.
Huh?
(Amazed gasp)
Hey, you mind if I
take a look at this?
[WELF]
Try it.
(Sheen)
[WELF]
That one didn't sell.
Seriously?
It's awesome.
(Chuckle)
Wait, what's so funny?
Thought you'd be looking for
MAGIC swords, that's all.
Huh?
[WELF]
I assume Goddess Hestia's
already told you about my
special talent
for making them.
Wah! Ah!
(Sigh)
Apparently, she's been
asking around about me
for the past few days.
Ah! Sorry...
It's really not a big deal.
I mean, I contracted with
a member of her Familia...
I get it.
But... I thought that you
might think badly of me
if I told you...
so I didn't.
Huh...
I am sorry I deceived
you like that.
I‐it's okay.
Now, let's get back to
what I should make for you.
Did you get that
from a monster?
Huh?
Uh, yeah, it's
a minotaur horn.
I couldn't let myself
throw it away.
[WELF]
Well, why don't
we use that?
For what?
[WELF]
To make you some
equipment out of,
what else?
(Gasp) You mean you
can do that?
[WELF]
Can I do that?
Well then, of course!
(Chuckle)
(Coals fizzling and popping)
(Loud sizzling)
[WELF]
I despise magic swords.
[BELL]
What?
[WELF]
They always bring out
the worst clients.
Everybody comes to me because
they want a magic sword
and they know I'm a Crozzo.
[WELF]
I'm so tired of it.
All they ever talk about
is how they want something
that'll "make them strong"
or "make them famous."
But that's so wrong.
They're missing the point.
That's not what
weapons are for.
[WELF]
A weapon's not a means
to conquer the world.
It's an equal partner
with its user.
[WELF]
No matter what happens,
your weapon is the one thing
that should never betray you.
But magic swords
aren't like that.
They always break
and leave you with nothing.
They destroy people.
The user's pride, the smith's
reputation... everything.
That's why I have always
refused to forge one.
(Sizzling)
Uh!
Hm.
(Amazed gasp)
[WELF]
The material was
really nice.
Of all the things I've made,
this might be the best one.
So then,
I think we should
call it... Ushiwakamaru.
It's an ancient warrior's
name that was derived
from the word for "bull".
Hey, now! I don't think
we really need to put
all THAT much
thought into it!
Huh? So you don't
like Ushiwakamaru?
The name is not
what matters here!
Yeah, well...
We gotta call it somethin'.
Here.
Huh?
I really appreciate this,
Mr. Welf.
Huh? Hm?
I know we just met
and all...
and you don't have any
reason to trust me.
But, Bell...
I'm your friend now...
How about you stop
calling me "Mister"?
Hah...
(Laughs)
Okay. It's a deal.
(Ending Song)
It's time to begin
the final meeting!
[LILI]
That way leads to Floor 13
and the middle floors.
The monsters down there can use
fire and other ranged attacks.
Don't let your guard down
even for a minute!
You understand?
Gotcha.
Hm.
From here on out
we'll be moving in a
specific formation.
Master Welf
in front.
(Welf laughs)
[LILI]
Master Bell's
the middle guard
Hm.
since that's the
most crucial spot.
And I will be at
the back of the line.
However, putting a supporter
in the rear position
won't give us much firepower
to work with,
so don't forget to‐
(Bell laughs)
What do you think
you're laughing at?
Cut it out, Sir!
I really need for you to
take this seriously, okay?
I'm sorry. I'll stop.
But isn't this somethin'?!
[BELL]
The three of us, going on
an adventure together!
(Chuckle)
(Hearty laugh)
(Bell laughs)
That's right, dude!
Glad to see you're looking
forward to it as much as me!
[LILI]
You guys should not be
goofing off right now!
Huh?
But, yeah, I know
how you feel.
(Both laugh)
[BELL, THINKING]
This... feels good.
We may be from
different Familias,
but we are a team.
[LILI]
Alright, guys,
are we ready to do this?
[WELF]
Yeah, let's do it!
[BELL]
Right!
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Pass Parade"