(Panting)
Ugh. Bell, are we almost
to the city yet?
My feet are freaking
killing me!
Oh don't worry, Goddess,
we're gonna be there
before you know it.
Just keep on walking.
[HESTIA]
Okay...
Ugh. So much for
some time alone.
You just HAD to invite
those two dirty homewreckers.
And great, you brought
everybody else too...
(Sigh)
Master Bell!
Come 'n look!
(Bell and Hestia sigh)
Huh?
[BELL]
Wooow...
[AIS]
The monsters visit Floor 18
just like we do.
[ASFI]
I would actually say it's
a place for the monsters...
and not the adventurers.
Everything needs
a place to relax.
That is
incredible.
The world's a beautiful
place, isn't it?
You're so right...
Yes it is!
(Chuckle)
(Opening Song)
[BELL]
I'm not sure
what that means.
[AIS]
This is Rivira.
A city built down here
by adventurers.
[WELF]
Seriously?!
13,000 valis just for
this little whetstone?!
That's crazy!
And they want 20,000 for
this ratty old handbag?!
You gotta be kidding me!
If you don't like it, then
take your business elsewhere.
Grr...
[TIONE]
Ugh... And all the inns
are extremely pricey too.
[TIONA]
Yeah, that's why we
decided we should all
camp out in the woods.
[BELL]
That makes sense...
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Are you looking
for her?
Huh?
[BELL]
How long ago did
she slip off?
Guh!
Uh! Ah!
Uh, s‐sorry
about that.
Huh?!
Hah?
(Mord groans)
Well, well, if it
isn't Little Wussy again.
Oh, yeah.
I owe you for what you
did at the pub.
Ngh! G‐guh!
[GUILE]
Uh I wouldn't
do that, Mord.
Why not?
See for yourself.
[BELL]
Huh?
Huh?! This tool's with
the Sword Princess?!
Let's go.
[TIONE]
What's with them?
[TIONA]
They're just losers.
(Mord grumbles)
Gah!
(Amazed gasp)
[HESTIA]
Hey! Bell!
Huh?
Look! So, uh,
what do you think?
(Sniff sniff)
Oh, it smells
really nice.
Doesn't it, though?
I knew you'd like it
the very second I found it!
You actually bought expensive
perfume in this dump?
You do know they totally
ripped you off, right?
Yeah? Well aren't
you one to talk
after you went and bought
that horrendous backpack.
Guh! I had to get SOMETHING
to carry our stuff
until we get out of here!
I needed some perfume!
Not that a rat like you
could ever understand that!
(Both growling)
Bell! You don't want me to smell
like stinky sweat, do you?
Uh... well I hadn't really
thought about that...
[TIONE]
No worries, guys!
We were thinking we might
go for a quick bath
a little later if you
wanna come with us.
[TIONE]
Does that sound good?
Sounds great to me!
What are we waiting for?!
Yeah! I wanna go!
[GIRLS]
Hm?
[OUKA]
Hm? Hm.
Ah! We would like
to go too.
[TIONA]
Yay! We can all
go together!
(Girls laugh)
Lord Hermes, don't
scare me like that!
Say, Bell. When we get
to the campsite...
could I maybe talk with
you for a bit?
Huh?
[FINN]
Thanks for your
hard work, Bete.
Yeah, well, it's not like it
was very hard to carry
one load of antidote all the way
back down from the surfaaa‐!
[BETE] Ah! Eh! Uh!
Thanks to you, we'll be
able to set out tomorrow.
[FINN]
The plan is to split into
two groups. You'll be
in the lead Party‐
[LEFIYA]
I guess I'd better go ahead
and take care of it myself.
Why the hell is that
stupid Tomato Kid here?!
Yeah... it's kind
of a long story.
(Finn laughs)
YOU TELL ME NOW!
RIGHT NOW!
(Footsteps)
[BELL]
Lord Hermes?
I know you said you wanted to
talk to me alone, but...
why do we have
to climb up a tree?
Don't worry. You'll find
out in just a moment.
Okay... whatever...
Shh...
Huh?
I brought you up here
for a good reason.
[HESTIA]
Haha! I am
clearly the winner!
You haven't told anyone what the
contest is, Goddess Hestia.
Winner!
(Shocked gasps)
When women are naked, it's
a man's responsibility
to try and sneak a
quick peek, little man.
I don't know where
you got that...
But it is SO many
levels of not okay!
Listen to me, kid.
Spying on chicks is how
a man expresses his feelings.
Huh?
[HERMES] Duh.
[GRANDPA]
Bell, spying on chicks
is how a man expresses
his feelings.
[BELL]
Grandpa?!
It's Rrrrrromance!
[BELL]
GRANDPA!
(Grandpa laughs)
Huh?!
Mm‐mm.
Let's just go back
to camp, alright?
(Hermes laughs)
[BELL]
Huh? Waah! WAAAH!
AAHHH!
(Girls shriek)
Oops...
(Coughing and gasping)
[TIONA]
Hey!
It's Mr. Argonaut!
Did you wanna come take
a bath with us too?
Wow, and here I was thinking you
were all sweet and innocent.
Wha? I just... I don't...
mean to...
(Annoyed grunt)
Wait...
(Groan)
Um... I didn't mean to...!
[LILI]
You shouldn't be in here,
Master Bell!
Well, well, aren't you
a naughty boy?
(Shriek)
Ngh!
(Nervous gasp)
(Bell stammers)
(Shy exhale)
AAHHH!
I... I'm SORRY!
AAHHHH!
Uh!
(Panting)
(Wheezing)
That was bad.
Hang on, where am I?
Uh... Let me think...
(Water splashing)
Hm? Is that water?
Huh?
(Slow gasp)
Who's there?!
(Boom)
Guh!
Hnng...
[BELL]
I'M SORRY AGAIN!
Oh, Mr. Cranel?
[RYU]
You're fine.
I know exactly
what happened.
There's no need for you
to worry about it, okay?
What? You're letting
me off that easy?
But how do you know
I'm not lying to you?
[RYU]
I realize modesty is a virtue
and everything, Mr. Cranel,
but I'd appreciate it
if you didn't grovel.
It's an unflattering
habit of yours.
Oh... Never
thought about that.
Uh... h‐hold on.
[BELL]
I've been meaning to
tell you thanks for
coming all the way down here
to rescue us, Miss Ryu.
It really does
mean a lot.
[RYU]
No, think nothing of it.
I was planning on coming
here again soon anyway.
You just gave me
a good excuse.
Huh?
Uh. Wha?
[RYU]
I like to come here every now
and then to bring flowers...
So Mama Mia occassionaly
gives me some time off.
So, uh... where are we?
[RYU]
The grave of my comrades
from my original Familia.
You see... we fell into a trap
that was set by an enemy
Familia.
I was the only one
who survived.
The rest... they were
all murdered.
(Sigh)
Hmm.
I want to...
to tell you something.
Huh? Sure.
Since that day...
I have been blacklisted
by the guild.
Huh?
[RYU]
Because I killed every
last one of their members.
[RYU]
Sneak attacks,
booby traps, ambushes...
No method of revenge
was beneath me.
I was driven
purely by rage.
And malice.
[RYU]
Eventually, when my revenge
was complete...
I found myself alone...
in a dark, empty alley,
drained of every last bit
of my strength.
I thought I was done.
A fitting end for me after
doing something so foolish.
But...
Are you okay?
And that's when you went
to work at the tavern?
Yes. They took me in...
even though they knew everything
about what I had done.
Sorry, I probably shouldn't
be bothering you with my
sob story like this.
Uh! That's okay.
[RYU]
So, in the long run...
I'm nothing but a reckless,
bloodthirsty elf.
I will only disappoint you
and break your trust.
(Grimace)
[BELL]
Miss Ryu...
Hm.
You really shouldn't put
yourself down like that.
Don't do it... it's ugly.
What was that? I don't
really know what to say.
Uh... let me
take that back!
That was too harsh.
You are a kind person,
Mr. Cranel.
You are a Human worthy
of the utmost respect.
(Gasp)
(Crickets chirping)
[MORD]
AW! Dammit!
Aw c'mon, just give it
a rest already, Mord.
[MORD]
Shut your face!
Hey!
That punk bastard musta
used some kinda trick
to get this far.
That little shit‐stain!
Are ya jealous, bro?
(Laughs)
What?!
You think it doesn't
affect you too?
That little wuss made it all the
way down to the middle floors
as soon as he leveled up.
He's makin' a mockery
of guys like us.
We've been doing this
for years!
[MAN] Mm‐hmm.
We adventurers gotta
follow a certain code.
And somebody'll have
to teach him that.
All we need to do
is get him alone...
[ALL]
Hm?
Hey... who the
hell are you?
I cannot believe you!
(Whimpering)
[BETE]
Why did YOU get
a chance to see
Ais Wallenstein
take a bath?!
Ngh!
Eh?
I don't believe this!
(Whimper)
That is total bullshit!
[TIONA]
Ugh. Would you please
let it go already?
(Bete screams)
[TIONE]
Lord Hermes made him do it,
and he's getting
punished as we speak.
(Laughing)
Worth it!
Hey, stop it!
Put me down, you nasty freaks!
That idiot shouldn't
even be here in our camp
in the first place?!
[TIONE]
Ugh, will you shut up? You're
making a spectacle of yourself.
(Bete struggles)
(Lefiya swoons)
Uh!
[TIONA]
For seriously...
[BELL]
You're leaving
pretty soon, right?
Yes.
And it looks like I'll be
a part of the lead party.
You've been assigned to join
the trailing party, I assume?
Yeah.
Um... so...
be careful, okay?
Hmm.. And you too.
Be careful.
(Growling)
What is wrong
with you, Bell?!
If you're want to
get peep at me,
you should do it
when I'm all alone!
Hm? MMF!
Hm.
Huh? Goddess?
Huh?!
(Wind blowing)
Hmm...
Hm! Hm!
Hah! Hng!
(Running footsteps)
Huh?
(Panting)
Hmm.
[MORD]
"Little Rookie.
We have your goddess.
If you want her back
in one piece,
meet us at the big crystal,
east of the central woods.
And come alone."
Hm.
(Struggling)
[HESTIA]
This isn't gonna
end well for you!
You can't just go and
kidnap a goddess, ya know!
(Both laugh)
Gah! Ah!
(Panting)
Huh? Huh?
Hey.
Uh! Where is she?!
Hm. Come with me.
Hm...
[MORD]
We didn't hurt your
little girlfriend.
I'm not stupid enough to get
the gods all pissed off at me.
Okay. So what is it
you want from me?
Relax, kid. Don't worry, we
ain't gonna gang up on ya.
I was just hoping maybe I could
interest you in a little duel.
You and me.
A duel?
[MORD]
Sure. It's simple.
The winner can ask whatever
he wants from the loser.
If I win...
you have to hand over everything
in your possession.
And if I win,
you let the Goddess go!
[MORD]
I like your spirit.
But I'm not sure
you understand.
I'm not here to win...
I'm here to make you suffer!
(Shattering crystals)
Ngh!
Eh? Huh?
[BELL]
He's gone!
Huh?
Uh. Hm.
Gah!
Huh?! AH!
[MAN 1]
What's the matter?
Can't see 'em?
(Concussive blows)
[MAN 2]
Teach him a lesson, Mord!
[MAN 3]
Yeah, cut his pretty
little nose off!
(Coughing and choking)
NGH!
(Grunts continue)
Woah!
[MAN 2]
What's the matter?
You takin' a nap?
[MAN 4]
Get back in there!
[MAN 3]
Yeah, I thought you were
the legendary Little Rookie!
(Punch)
AH!
[MAN!]
D'you see his face?!
(Kick)
NGH!
[HERMES]
That's the magic item
called "Hades Head".
It's quite a sight,
isn't it?
You're sick in the
head, Lord Hermes.
Have you got something
against that poor boy?
Hmm. I'd rather think
of it as some tough love.
After all, Bell is still blind
to how nasty humanity can be.
[HERMES]
Maybe I AM sick
in the head...
(Kick) AH!
but I wanted him
to witness this.
Though I'd be lying
if I said I wasn't at
least little entertained.
Okay, well what
are we supposed to do
if this breaks
him for good?
(Laughs) Then that would
mean he didn't really
have what it takes.
Ah. The cavalry has
finally arrived.
I swear. Adventurers
are fascinating.
(Whistling arrows)
Huh?
We got company, guys!
They must've wanted
to get Bell alone!
What a buncha
damn cowards!
Agh! It's his stupid friends!
What? How were they
able to find him?!
I don't care,
just chop em' up!
Chigusa, let me see
that spear!
Right!
[OUKA]
AAGGHH!
(Blades clashing)
Hey, what's going
on over there? Hey!
Ooh, sounds like they're
startin' to get rowdy.
Man, why'd we have to get
stuck here babysittin'.
You can't just ignore me like
that! Do you know who I am?!
Hm... Shall we?
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Let's go take a look!
(Both laugh)
Ugh! Don't leave me here!
Ah! Argh!
(Leaves rustle)
Huh?
[BUNNY]
Heh!
Ah?
(Chirping)
E‐easy there.
[LILI]
"The clock
strikes midnight."
Ah!
Wait! What are you
doing here?!
And how'd you do that?
Not only do Chienthropes have
a super‐keen sense of smell,
but that perfume you wasted your
money on is kinda hard to miss.
Ignite, Heretic Spell!
Will o' the Wisp!
(Both chanting)
AH!
C'mere!
Urgh! AH!
Oof!
Grr...
[MAN 4]
Stand down, they're
way too strong!
[MAN 2]
Yeah? Well we've got
'em outnumbered!
Take 'em out!
(Yelling)
Dammit! Now we
can't reach Bell!
Huh? Uh!
Hyah!
Guh!
Huh?
AGGHH!
Gah!
Oh I got you now,
you piece of‐
Ugh!
[RIVERIA]
When will you learn
it's a bad move to cross me?
It's you...!
(Quick blow)
Gah!
Let me help out.
Uh... sure.
(Punch)
Ngh! Gah!
(Cough)
(Growl)
Ah?
(Clang)
Ah!
[MORD, THINKING]
It can't be.
(Charging up)
Huh?
AGH!
Ah!
I don't get it!
How can you see me?!
[BELL, THINKING]
I can sense him.
I can sense his eyes on me.
Hm.
Ah!
AAGGHH!
NGH!
Oh...?
(Panting)
Arrggh!
You're mine!
AAGGHH!
(Shatter)
Huh?
Yaaaggh!
AHH!
Hyah!
Hng. YAH!
(Shatter)
GAH!
Ugh!
That's it...
you are dead!
[HESTIA]
Stop!
Goddess Hestia?
(Panting)
(Blades clashing)
(Both grunting)
(Deep resonance)
[EVERYONE]
Huh?
I said stop.
[OUKA and MIKOTO]
Oh!
[HESTIA]
Children, please set
aside your weapons.
(Cowering)
Uh... AH!
Wait!
Where are you going?!
Uh!
(Resonating continues)
Well look at that.
Hestia's decided to
unleash her godly wrath.
Looks like the show's
over for now.
(Sigh of relief)
(Gasp)
Bell! Ah!
(Muffled words)
[HESTIA]
Oh, Bell, I'm so
glad you're safe!
Geh...
You scared me!
G‐Goddess...
(Crying)
I'm sorry!
It's all my fault you came
down here and got hurt!
It's not!
(Crying)
I should've...
been there for you.
I'm sorry.
[LILI]
All's well that
ends well, right?
(Loud explosion)
[ALL]
AH!
[WELF]
What was that?
It's a quake...
An... evil one.
(Gasp)
[WELF]
Did you say "evil" quake?
Oh, come on!
(Rumbling)
(Panicked breaths)
(Quiet shock)
(Ending Song)
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Familia Myth"