[ASFI]
What is this?
[HERMES]
The dungeon wants
to express its revulsion.
...so it has chosen
to trap us all inside.
Makes me wonder.
So what about your
prayer, Uranus?
This was never supposed to
be part of the agreement.
(Crystal shattering)
(Roaring)
(Boom)
(Adventurers scream)
(Snarling)
(Roaring)
(Gasp)
(Continued roaring)
[HERMES]
Just as I thought.
It's the Floor Boss.
(Grunt)
(Opening Song)
(Roar)
(Screeching)
(Monsters growling)
(Screaming)
Come on,
we gotta help!
No, don't.
Are you sure you would
be doing them any good?
[RYU]
Think about it.
(Sigh)
(Distant boom)
(Chuckle)
Hm.
We're doing this.
[RYU]
I'm not sure about
your skills as a leader.
But, that doesn't
make you wrong.
Chigusa, you protect
the Goddess.
Everyone else,
let's move out!
[GROUP]
Alright!
[HESTIA, THINKING]
Everyone...
Don't push yourselves
too hard.
(Growling)
(Screaming)
Ah! Let's get
outta here!
GAH!
(Roaring)
What the‐?!
Ah!
Guh!
Agh! Dammit!
(Pained grunts)
Son of a...
(Snarling)
(Grunting)
[MORD]
What the hell
is going on?!
Gah!
(Minotaur grunts)
(Mord whimpers)
(Blood splatter)
(Pained roar)
A‐ah!
Aahhh!
(Lili grunts)
(Battle sounds)
[LILI]
I need to make sure you don't
get in Master Bell's way!
[MORD]
Ugh!
[LILI]
I hope you're grateful.
This is far better than
you deserve and you know it.
Pbbbt!
(Shocked gasp)
(Roar)
[BORS]
What in the hell's
going on here?
(Goliath roars)
[ASFI]
Bors!
Huh?
Gather every fighter
and weapon
that you can find.
We're taking
that thing down.
Are you crazy, Andromeda?!
Look at the size of
that frickin' thing‐
We have no choice.
There's no escape.
[ASFI]
Every single exit on this
floor has been cut off.
(Group gasps)
[ASFI]
So until we
defeat the boss,
I'm afraid we're
stuck down here.
(Laughs)
Well, shit.
Listen up! Looks like
we're gonna have to kick
some monster ass!
(Group cheers)
[BORS]
Now round up every
adventurer in town!
[BORS]
If you turn tail and run,
then don't bother showin'
your face here again.
[BORS]
Now, let's show this beast
what adventurers can do!
(Roar)
(Mystical charging)
(Impact)
(Slow growl)
Haaaah!
Haaah!
[BOTH]
Hyah!
AH!
(Both scream)
Get out of here
right now!
(Screaming)
(Roar)
(Gasp)
Look out!
Will o' the Wisp!
(Pained growl)
Guh?!
(Angry growl)
[WELF]
Uh oh!
Hng!
Hyah!
Thank you!
[RYU, THINKING]
This is no ordinary Floor Boss.
Its potential has
increased to lv. 5!
(Goliath growling)
(Boom)
[ASFI, TELEPATHIC]
We have reinforcements!
The mages from the town are
casting spells as we speak.
All you have to do is
keep Goliath busy!
[RYU, TELEPATHIC]
Understood!
Then why don't you and I work
to divide his attention?
[ASFI, TELEPATHIC]
Okay. So what do
you have in mind?
Huh?
(Maniacal laugh)
[BORS]
Pay attention, boys...!
Andromeda's playin' decoy,
so let's get involved.
Now start castin'
those spells!
(Chanting)
[BORS]
Take that bastard out!
Take him down with one shot!
[ASFI]
Thank you!
I won't forget this, Bors!
(Battlecries)
(Arrows whistling)
Fire!
Buy us some more time!
The incantation needs to‐
Huh?
(Goliath roars)
[BORS]
AAGGHH!
Huh?
(Continued chanting)
(Laughs)
Nicely done.
[BORS]
We've got all the
weapons you need.
If you lose or break yours,
just grab another one!
[BORS]
This army was scrapped
together at the last minute,
so we don't have time
to strategize.
Just stay out of
each other's way...
and go fight like hell!
(Battlecries)
(Goliath roars)
Hyaaagh!
(Scared panting)
AH!
(Whimper)
(Growling)
(Panting)
[WELF]
Bell!
(Grunt)
Yaagh!
AH!
AGH!
Hng...
YAAGGHH!
(Pained roar)
[BORS]
Vanguard, take cover!
This is gonna be a big one...
(Growling)
(Thunderous impact)
(Mystical resonance)
Let him have it!
(Extended roar)
(Slashing)
(Crackling ice)
(Static)
(Pained roar)
Alright, now let's
finish the job!
(Battlecries and cheers)
Not good.
Huh?
(Low growl)
[BORS]
Son of a...
(Growl)
He can heal.
(Angry roar)
(Adventurers scream)
(Grunting)
Ugh... Ngh...
(Goliath growls)
(Slow growl)
(Quick explosions)
(Monsters snarling)
[BELL]
Hyah!
(Minoatuar screeches)
Hm.
[RYU]
Mr. Cranel.
Whatcha thinkin?
[RYU]
You take care of
all the other monsters
while we try
to distract Goliath.
Wait, what?
[RYU]
We can't afford to lose
any ground here.
If we can stall him, then
the mages who can still fight
will be able to cast
another spell.
And if it doesn't work
the first time,
we'll just repeat it
as many times as we have to.
Uh, Miss Ryu...
[RYU]
Good luck!
Ah. Huh?
(Twinkling)
[LILI]
Goddess Hestia!
There you are!
Are you okay?
We have to gather up
all our supplies!
Did you guys hear that?
Please go to town
and everything!
[MAN]
Right!
Where's Chigusa?
She disappeared during
the huge explosion.
I think she
ended up with Ouka.
(Gasp)
[LILI]
Isn't that...?
(Goliath growls)
[RYU]
Hah!
(Screams)
Watch out!
You'll get yourself killed!
(Roar)
[RYU, THINKING]
This is going to take
every bit of our strength...
[ASFI]
Don't worry about
the Magic Stone!
At this rate,
we won't make it!
[RYU, THINKING]
...and the full extent
of our deepest desires.
(Explosion)
(Long roar)
(Successive explosions)
(Men scream)
(Both scream)
Ugghh...
(Grunt)
[CHIGUSA]
Ouka!
[OUKA]
Chigusa, I need my shield.
Ah...
Ah! But you can't...
you'll die!
I can't let
that happen.
Listen, Chigusa.
Huh?
I won't be the kind of
man who's all talk.
If they are willing
to risk their lives...
then I shall do so as well!
Alright?!
(Whimper)
(Light chuckle)
(Twinkling intensifies)
Mr. Cranel!
Ms. Lion, you need
to pull back!
(Charging roar)
FIRE BOLT!
(Thunderous explosion)
(Heavy breath)
(Gurgling)
(Growl)
Bell! Get out of there now!
[BELL]
GAH!
AAHHH!
(Roar)
(All gasp)
[OUKA]
HAH!
(Sharp impact)
YAAHH!
(Goliath roars)
(Ouka straining)
Ahh!
What happened?
Dear God... Tch...
Please no...
GOD DAMN YOU!
[MIKOTO]
Sir Ouka! Answer me!
[CHIGUSA]
Ouka...
[RYU]
Say something,
Mr. Cranel!
(Blades clatter)
Huh?
[LILI]
Master Bell!
He'll be okay.
I mean, won't he?
Well his injuries are severe,
but he's still breathing.
[ASFI]
Leave it to us.
We've got this.
[MIKOTO]
Take care of things, Chigusa.
Please.
You need to go back now.
And stall for as
long as you can.
[HESTIA]
Bell is gonna wake up soon.
And then he's gonna
defeat that monster.
[RYU]
Goddess Hestia...
I know you've seen him
fight before!
And I know Bell can do this!
[HESTIA]
He can take
down Goliath!
(Light chuckle)
As you wish.
[HESTIA]
Please, Bell,
open your eyes!
Please wake up!
[LILI]
Master Bell!
[HESTIA]
Everyone is out there
risking their lives
fighting that horrible thing!
You can do this,
I know you can!
You're the only one
who can save us!
I know it!
[HESTIA]
Wake up, Bell!
We're all
counting on you!
[BELL, THINKING]
Goddess Hestia...
I can hear everything
you're saying...
But no matter
how hard I try...
my body refuses to move!
Come on, Bell,
snap out of it!
You have to keep fighting!
For the goddess...
and for everyone!
Keep fighting!
[HERMES]
Not just anyone
can be called a hero
It isn't the kind of title
you can earn simply because
you brandish a sword
or carry a shield.
And it's got nothing to do
with magic or strength.
[GRANDPA]
Bell, a hero is someone
who sacrifices himself.
He is willing to lose
his life for the sake
of the ones he loves.
You may take a few lumps
along the way,
but don't lose heart, boy.
The victor will always rise up
from among the rabble.
Hold on tight
to your wish.
Cry out with all
your desire.
[BELL]
If you do...
...then you will see...
...that it's...
[ALL THREE]
...what makes a hero
shine the brightest!
[BELL, THINKING]
I want to be strong in her eyes.
And I want to protect
all the people
who've become
so important to me!
You're up!
[HESTIA]
I believe in you... Bell!
(Goliath growling)
[GRANDPA]
Let your feelings
burn like fire!
Cry out with
all your desire!
(Twinkling)
(Low growl)
(Gasp)
[HESTIA]
That's Limit Off!
(Loud roar)
Don't let him
get away!
(Battlecries)
[RYU]
"At this moment, in the silent
skies of the distant forest...
To the infinite stars
that dance upon
the night's eternal firmament...
[ASFI] She's casting a spell
at a time like this?!
[RYU] This mortal begs for
divine protection."
[MIKOTO] That thing's huge.
Hmm.
"Almighty god of the art of
combat, grant me your guidance!
I ask you to bestow
your sublime power
upon this humble form!"
Hah!
[WELF, THINKING]
I know this is selfish of me,
but there's somebody
I want to save!
Please give me the
strength to do this!
HYAH!
[RYU]
"Vagabond winds, come forth.
Across the empty wilderness."
[ASFI]
I suppose I'd better pull out
all the stops as well.
(Electric crackling)
Hyah!
(Pained roar)
[RYU]
"Fill me with the
light of the stars...
...and strike!"
LUMINOUS WIND!
(Roaring)
[ASFI]
AHH!
[RYU]
AAHHH!
[MIKOTO]
"Descend from Heaven
and possess the earth!"
Jinmu Tousei!
Ah!
[MIKOTO]
Futsu‐no‐Mitama!
(Long roar)
(Mikoto straining)
(Growling)
It's a seal...
(Angry growling)
(Mikoto grunting)
I can't hold on...!
AH!
[WELF]
Outta my way!
Kazuki!
Nhg!
(Long roar)
[RYU]
That's a Crozzo magic sword!
Kazuki... it surpasses
the originals!
[HEPHAISTOS, FLASHBACK]
Please, don't make
your companions
pay for your stubbornness.
[WELF, THINKING]
She's right, I was just
being stubborn!
(Cracking and shattering)
I'm sorry.
(Low growl)
(Deep resonance)
Ngh!
[HESTIA, FLASHBACK]
Whenever you find yourself with
the odds all stacked against you
you can still be able to win
with the small bit of power
you have left.
That's what we like
to call a Hero Shot.
Ngh!
(Angry roar)
(Grunt)
YAAAAGH!
(Goliath roaring)
(Roar continues)
(Panting)
(Crumbling)
(Gasp)
[RYU]
It's happening again.
[WELF]
No, no, no, NO!
[HESTIA, THINKING]
Our Bell is different now.
He's faster!
And stronger!
And he can leap
even higher!
(Extended battlecry)
NGH!
(Shattering crystal)
(Echoing boom)
(Wild cheering)
Master Bell! You actually
defeated Goliath!
(Amazed sigh)
(Gasp)
(Weak laugh)
[CHIGUSA]
Ouka!
(Crying)
[MORD]
Not too bad...
For a Little Rookie.
(Hermes laughs blissfully)
[HERMES]
I did it. I saw it!
I saw it with
my own eyes!
[HERMES]
Oh Zeus, you said
he had no potential!
But your grandson truly
carries your blessing!
In fact, he's the Last Hero
bequeathed of your Familia!
I can feel the age
beginning to move forward!
I'd hoped I'd be able
to witness this...
Today, in the land of Orario,
a new chapter
in our history begins!
The future of these heroes,
through their lives
and beyond their deaths!
It is an epic story
of family...
woven by our children!
It's the Familia Myth!
(Ending Song)
(Bar chatter)
That was a hell of a shot!
(Both chugging)
[RIVERIA]
I think she's had enough.
[TIONE]
Omigod. You had to
see it to believe it!
(Take laughs)
[MIKOTO]
Drink, drink, drink!
Thank you, Bell.
(Choking)
(Girls growling)
(Loki screaming)
(All laugh)
(Birds chirping)
[HESTIA, THINKING]
You did it, Bell.
You did it.