(Operatic Music)
[HESTIA]
I'm certain that
Bell is still alive.
The blessing that I gave
him hasn't faded yet.
(Bell grunts)
(Sword slice)
Haaah!
(Growling)
Gah!
(Snarling)
[WELF]
Ignite! Heretic Spell!
Will o' the Wisp!
Ngh...
(Panting)
(All breathing heavily)
(Focused breath)
(Opening Song)
[RYU] Hm!
(Sword slice)
Hyah!
Hah! Hyah!
Hm!
(Loud crack)
(Sheen)
Hah!
(Pained roar)
[CHIGUSA]
That was amazing...
Finished them off
in mere seconds...
[OUKA]
I don't believe it.
Let's go.
[OUKA]
Asfi Al Andromeda...
a gifted
Item Creator.
Her second name is
"Almighty Perseus".
[CHIGUSA]
Is she that good?
[MIKOTO]
She's like... the wind.
(Footsteps)
What happened here?
Hm?
[OUKA]
Well that's
not good.
Oh!
(Gasp)
No. No, this is...
this is Bell's...
I don't see them
over here.
If they were defeated
in this area,
then it's highly unlikely
that they'd get too far
if they lost their equipment.
[ASFI]
A party who'd do
something that foolish
wouldn't have made it
to this point.
[ASFI]
So, the logical
conclusion must be...
...that they gave up on
returning to the surface.
Instead, they decided they
would try to reach the safe
zone on Floor 18.
(Chigusa and Mikoto gasp)
The dungeon floors have
several vertical shafts.
They must've realized
going down would be
wiser than climbing up.
[OUKA]
What? Did you just say
they went further DOWN?
Why would they do
something like that?
[RYU]
That's what I would do.
[GROUP] Hm?
And besides, they were...
Rather, HE...
just finished his
first adventure,
so I'm sure he wanted
to move forward.
Oh, I can see where
you're coming from.
So do I. Bell went
in further inside.
I can feel it!
[ASFI]
Then that settles it.
We are going to
Floor 18.
[HESTIA, THINKING]
Oh, Bell... please,
please be okay!
(Loud explosion)
(Straining)
Ah! Welf?
[BELL]
Welf!
He's gone Mind Down!
What d'you think
should we do? Huh?!
[BELL]
Lili!
(Nervous gasp)
(Distant growls and snarls)
Ngh...
(Determined grunt)
(Uneasy footsteps)
(Bell straining)
(Scraping)
(Continued straining)
(Heavy panting)
(Whistling wind)
Hm?
(Nervous breath)
Hm.
Ngh!
AAH!
(Loud clattering)
(Bell grunting)
AH!
(Heavy thud)
[BELL]
Gah!
(Crumbling rock)
Don't you think it's about
time you explained yourself?
I still don't quite
understand exactly why
you would want to
help Bell so much.
I already told you,
silly girl,
I'm just wanting to lend
a hand to an old friend‐
I'm not stupid, okay!
Uh!
(Chuckle)
Alright, you win.
There's a certain
someone out there
who's requested that
I help keep an eye
on your Bell for
a little while.
"A certain someone"?
[HERMES]
Precisely! But of
course I didn't come
all the way down here
just for the sake
of following orders.
I too have a personal interest
in the boy as well.
[HERMES]
I would like to witness his
strength with my own eyes,
Hestia.
(Labored breathing)
[HERMES]
I want to find out
if he can truly
carry the burden of the age.
[BELL]
NGH!
You're kidding?!
(Echoing footsteps)
Ah...?
Huh?
[BELL]
That's...
That's the Great Wall
of Lamentation.
(Shocked gasp)
Uh?
[LILI, FLASHBACK]
That's Goliath.
But the Loki Familia should
have already beaten him.
(Bell panting)
[LILI, FLASHBACK]
And when you consider his
average recovery time,
we should just
barely make it.
(Crumbling stones)
Huh?
(Loud crack)
AAHH!
AH!
(Deep roar)
(Panting)
(Roaring continues)
(Low growl)
[BELL]
Keep running!
(Growl)
[BELL]
Whatever you do,
don't give up!
C'mon!
(Roar)
[BELL]
G‐go... go... go...
Go! Go! GO!
D‐Don't stop running!
AAHHH!
(Roar)
Ngh! Gah!
AAAAH!
Hng...
[BELL, THINKING]
Lili... Welf...
Goddess...
Guh!
(Grunts)
[BELL]
Huh?
My friends...
need... help...
Ugh...
[BELL]
Please...
(Bell grunting)
Huh?
Wha‐?
Welf! L‐Lili! Ugh!
[AIS]
Are you all right?
Huh?
[BELL] Huh?
WHAA‐?!
Easy, Bell.
Miss Ais! Uh, where
did you come from?!
My group is on the way back
from our latest mission.
We've been camping here
on Floor 18.
What? Floor 18?
Are my friends
here too?!
Guh!
Uuhhhhhhh!
AH!
(Panicked cries)
Huh?
[BELL]
Welf... Lili...
(Relieved sigh)
(Light snoring)
[AIS]
They're doing fine.
Riveria and the others
treated their wounds.
(Light snoring)
Your injuries were just
as bad as theirs.
Ah! Uh, thanks for saving us.
I owe you one... again.
Mm‐mm.
You think you
can stand up?
Uh, yeah.
Then you might as well
come with me
so you can give a report
to the party leader.
Okay?
(Gareth laughs)
[GARETH]
So you got all the
way to Floor 18
on your first trip
to the middle floors...
and then you were able to run
right past the floor boss?
[BELL]
Not exactly, sir... I guess
you could say I got lucky.
Anyway, I want you to know
I'm really grateful to you
guys for helping us!
You have no idea.
You've been through
quite a lot.
You may feel free to
stay here as our guests.
[BELL]
Thank you! I'll do whatever
I can to pay you back.
Well, I could never abandon
someone Ais cares about.
She would never
speak to me again!
(All chuckle)
(Happy sigh)
[FINN]
Actually, there are several
members of our group
who've been badly poisoned
by the monsters.
We've sent some of
our best runners to
the surface to get a remedy.
So until they return, we've
decided to camp out on Floor 18.
[TIONA]
Oh! It's
Mr. Argonaut!
AH!
[TIONE]
It's good to see
you too, Ais.
[BELL] Ah. Uh.
[AIS] Tiona, Tione.
You finally woke up!
So happy you're alright,
Mr. Argonaut!
Thanks, but... why do you
keep calling me that?
(Girls both laugh)
[TIONE]
This goofball.
He doesn't even know
that's his nickname now.
Mr. Argonaut,
you were really somethin'!
We all saw the way you kicked
that minotaur's butt back there!
It totally reminded me of one
of my favorite fairy tales
from back when
I was a little girl!
You're, like, my hero!
GAH!
(Giggles)
So I guess
you're level 2 ...
Going down to the middle floors
is much more impressive
than defeating some
silly little minotaur.
(Boing)
Uh... Th‐thank you.
[TIONA]
Aww, look at him blush!
He's adorable!
[BELL]
I‐I... No... I, uh...
It was nothing really...
Aah...
[COOK]
Oh don't worry,
I've cooked for groups
a lot larger
than this before.
(Slam slam)
Huh...
What's the matter?
So we, uh...
We ARE still in the
dungeon, aren't we?
How is it so bright
down here?
Ngh.
(Gasp)
[BELL]
Whoa!
Is that a...?
Yes. It's completely
made of crystal.
[AIS]
The light fades in and
out periodically,
making it day and night.
(Breathless)
[AIS]
Under Resort... that's
what some people call it.
Or The Labyrinth
Paradise.
[BELL]
Well, she was right.
(Groan)
Huh?
(Both stirring)
Huh?!
Where in the hell
are we?
I don't have
any idea.
You guys remember
anything?!
It's me.
It's me Bell!
There's nothing that could
ever make me forget who
YOU are, Master Bell.
I promise.
Yeah, and I remember that
squeaky little rat voice...
so I guess I'm okay.
(Laugh)
[LILI]
I'm sorry I
wasn't stronger.
Yeah and I must've
been a huge burden...
My apologies.
No, you don't need
to apologize!
If it wasn't for Lili,
we wouldn't have even known
we needed to go to floor 18!
And if we didn't have you, those
Hell Hounds would've fried us!
This party wouldn't stand a
chance on the middle floors
without you two!
Don't you realize that?
(Chuckle)
True.
So in other words, we
couldn't have really done
it without all of us!
(All laugh)
[AIS]
Okay then, the food
is ready now.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Are you all right?
Ah... Sword Princess?!
You're Ais Wallenstein?!
[FINN]
Our guests this evening are
three brave adventurers.
They have risked their lives
in order to help each other
in the dungeon.
Please make our fellow
adventurers feel welcome.
(Fiddle music)
Here.
Oh, thanks.
What is it?
[AIS]
It's some 18th Floor fruit.
Huh? Fruit can
grow down here?
(Squish)
Ah. Mm.
AH! Ugh!
What, you don't like it?
Well if it's too sweet
for you, I'll eat it!
AHHH!
[BELL]
Sure.
Hm? Tch. Grr...
[WELF]
Ugh, way too
sweet for me.
[LILI]
Nah! Nah! Nah!
(Happy chewing)
Hey, Mr. Argonaut!
Huh...?
You've got to tell us how
you got your abilities
to be all level S!
[TIONE]
Yeah, give us all
the juicy details.
Ah... Uh...
Hm.
(Nervous whimpers)
[FEMALE VOICE]
Ah! W‐w‐waaah!
Huh?
[GROUP]
(Screaming continues)
Huh?!
(Dizzy screaming)
Oof! AH!
[HESTIA]
Why did nobody think to tell me
that stupid giant was up there?!
Oh, man...
(Gasp)
Is that you,
Goddess...?
(Screams)
Wha!
AH!
Oh, Bell!
Oh, my sweet, wonderful,
precious Bell!
Oh, thank the gods
you're alright!
Hmm. Oh, Goddess.
[HESTIA]
It's you!
It IS you, isn't it?!
(Stretching sound)
Uh, yeah I think so.
(Whimpering)
[HESTIA]
I'm so happy
right now.
And I'm happy too.
Hm?
(Happy crying)
(Light laugh)
(Gasp)
Hm.
I made you worry... I'm sorry.
(Sniffling)
So‐ WHOOOAA!
[LILI]
Please step aside,
Goddess Hestia!
(Chuckle)
[HESTIA]
How dare you interrupt our
beautiful, touching reunion?!
[LILI]
He got hurt really
badly when he saved us!
He needs to rest, okay?!
[HESTIA]
HUH?! Wallen‐whatserface
is here too?!
[HESTIA]
Who invited her here?!
[LILI] That doesn't matter!
[RYU]
Mr. Cranel.
Huh?
[LILI]
Why are you here anyway?
Are you injured?
[HESTIA] What am I doing here?!
[BELL]
Miss Ryu?!
Shh.
[HESTIA] I came here
to rescue MY Bell...
(Arguing continues)
[HERMES]
Ah, the famous Bell Cranel.
[BELL]
Yeah.
(Arguing continues)
Ah, so it is you then!
I couldn't wait to meet you!
You can call me Hermes!
[HERMES]
Pleasure's all mine.
Thank you for coming, sir.
[HESTIA]
No problem. Anything
for my pal Hestia.
Besides, I think you should
direct your gratitude
over in that direction.
Huh?
[HERMES]
They are the reason
we're here, after all.
(Grunt)
Hmph.
[MIKOTO]
We beg for your forgiveness!
[BELL]
Listen, you don't have
to do that...
[LILI]
You can say sorry, but you can't
expect us to just forgive you.
I mean, you guys almost
got all of us killed!
[WELF]
She's right. I can't just
turn a blind eye
to something like that.
[CHIGUSA]
It was inexcusable...
We're very sorry.
[MIKOTO]
We understand you
have every right
to be angry with us.
[MIKOTO]
I take full responsibility‐
If anyone here is
taking the blame...
I'd be the one
who deserves it.
I chose this.
And honestly, I still
don't believe it was
the wrong decision.
Oh, you got a lot of nerve
sayin' somethin' like that
to my face, buddy.
Watch yourself.
(Groan)
(Grunt)
[BELL]
Wait...
[OTHERS] Huh?
I mean...
if it were me...
If Welf and Lili
were in danger...
I think I might've
done the same thing.
(Troubled sighs)
I guess if it'll
make you happy...
Maybe I can let it go.
But in no way does that mean
I accept it!
Sure. That'll be
just fine with me.
(Bell and Hestia laugh)
Good.
Alright then, why don't we
all discuss our next move?
Asfi?
We need to get back up
to the surface.
Although, we should wait
until the Loki Familia
defeats Goliath.
[ASFI]
It looks like they'll be
ready to move out again
in about two days
at the earliest.
So in other words,
we've got a full day to kill!
[HERMES]
That's a rare opportunity,
so let's get some
rest tomorrow.
(All agreeing)
[LILI]
Goodnight, Master Bell!
[BELL]
Good night, Lili.
[HESTIA]
Hey, Welf?
[WELF]
Huh?
Hephaistos said that she
wanted me to make sure I
got this to you.
Uh...
Along with a message.
(Concerned sigh)
[BELL]
I can't believe this is
really the dungeon.
[AIS]
Everything okay?
[BELL]
Oh?
Oh, I just...
couldn't sleep.
[BELL]
What are you doing
out here, Miss Ais?
[AIS]
I saw you
walking around.
Hm. I... I was worried
about you, Bell.
(Gasp)
Sorry if that
bugs you.
What?! No way!
Not at all!
I'm glad you were‐
I mean‐ No!
Uh! I'm not glad you were
WORRIED, I just... oh no...
You know Bell, you always
seem to be so stressed.
Ugghhh!
(Long gasp)
(Stammering)
(Sigh)
[AIS]
When are you
heading out?
[BELL]
Not until after
you guys leave.
We're taking it easy tomorrow
since we're still pretty tired.
Okay. So then you'll
get to see the city.
What?! You mean there's a city
down here in the dungeon too?!
Mm‐hmm. So you're
looking forward to it?
Well, of course!
A city, huh?
I wonder what kind
of place it is!
[HESTIA]
Hmm, I wonder...
Huh?
I think you've been holding
out on me, haven't you, Bell?
GAH!
[HESTIA]
I cannot imagine why you
wouldn't invite ME first!
I mean, who‐is‐your‐
number‐one‐girl...
REMEMBER?!
AAHH! Okay! Okay!
(Hestia growls)
(Bell whimpers)
[HESTIA]
And as for you,
Wallen‐blabitty‐bla!
You can forget about
that city trip
because I will never
ever EVER allow you to
go on a date with Bell!
DO YOU HEAR ME?!
(Fuming)
[AIS]
On a date?
[BELL]
No, no, no!
She didn't mean it
like that! Goddess!
[LILI]
Master Bell's got a date?!
[HESTIA]
You stay out of this,
you little worm!
(Ending Song)
(Crickets chirping)
I refuse.
Never again.
Alright then.
So no more magic swords.
But Welf... you'll end
up regretting this.
Believe me.
You'll wish you had when there's
someone out there you care for.
[HEPHAISTOS, FLASHBACK]
Please...
Don't make your companions
pay for your stubbornness.
Ngh...
[WELF]
Ah, hell...
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Show"