(Bar revelry)
[HESTIA]
Agh! Can you
believe that, Miach?!
All this time...
my Bell was...
He was cheating on me!
(Crunch crunch)
What's wrong
with him, dammit?!
(Crunch crunch)
He belongs to ME!
Oh come on now,
Hestia.
The boy doesn't
"belong" to anyone.
Hmph! Oh don't you
think I know that?
It's just an expression!
Gah!
He just doesn't
get it! UGH!
Argh!
Hmph!
(Monstrous burp)
Why?! Tell me!
I'm begging you not
to leave me, Bell,
I'll do anything!
Please not so loud.
You're making a scene.
I love you, Bell...
(Loud sobbing)
I LOVE YOU!
(Opening Song)
(Hestia screams
and cries loudly)
[HESTIA]
Ugghhhh...
AH!
(Whimper)
(Sobbing)
[BELL]
Um are you okay,
Goddess Hestia?
Uh!
(Loud gulping)
Uh... Um...
Hmph.
Is something
wrong?
You're acting
kinda weird.
[HESTIA]
Hmph. I'm fine.
[HESTIA, THINKING]
Whatever...
Who cares what you think,
dirty cheater...
Hm?
Oh, uh, Goddess?
This might be
a bad time,
but when's the next day
you have time off?
Time off?
What d'ya mean?
Well, it's just that, uh...
I've been making a lot of money
in the dungeon recently...
and I want to repay you for
everything you've done for me.
[BELL]
Would you maybe want to go out
for a fancy dinner sometime?
Just the two of us?
Like... a date?!
How's today?
[BELL] Huh?
Yeah, today!
[BELL]
Whoa, hold on...
WE'RE GOING TODAY!
I thought you
were sick.
Nope! All better!
Huh?
(Giggling)
Oh!
(Sniffing)
'Kay Bell!
Meet me at 6 o'clock sharp
tonight in the southwest
Main Street Amour Plaza, okay?
(Laughs)
(Viscous bubbling)
[HESTIA]
I got a date with Bell...
And I don't wanna smell...
(Chuckles)
[DEMETER]
Hello, Hestia.
Huh?
[DEMETER]
Fancy seeing
you here.
(giggle)
[HESTIA]
Demeter!
Long time no see!
Ah. Oh!
[DEMETER]
Well aren't you looking
just as busty as ever?
Oh!
Oh. Uh, yeah, well,
you sure are one to talk.
Don't see you here
very often.
I assume there must be some
sort of special occasion
to bring YOU out to visit
the temple baths.
Mhm! I've got a little
rendezvous in town tonight.
So I want to
look my very best.
Ah! You wha‐?!
You positively
must tell me!
I most certainly
do not.
Oh! This is too good!
I can't believe it!
D'you hear
that, ladies?!
Ah!
[GODDESS 1]
Hestia got
herself a man?!
[GODDESS 2]
The same Hestia that couldn't
get a guy in Heaven?
[GODDESS 3]
You mean the shorty
with the big boobs?!
[GODDESS 1]
Like, tell us
who it is!
Uh!
[GODDESSES]
Yeah, spill!
Hm...
Okay, so he is a member
of my Familia.
He's a human.
[ALL]
Ooooohh!
(Hestia growls)
(Goddesses giggle)
[HESTIA]
Hey, shut your
nosey traps!
I'm so done
with you guys!
[GODDESS 1]
Ooh la la!
So do tell me,
Hestia.
[DEMETER]
What's so special about
this boy anyway?
Hm?
Oh, everything!
(Giggles)
(Couple laughs)
(Awkward sigh)
(Oohing and aahing)
[HESTIA]
Bell!
Hm. Huh?
(Hestia panting)
I'm so sorry...
Um...did I keep
you waiting?
No! Not at all!
I actually only got here
just a minute ago.
(Laughs)
[GODDESS 1]
Ooh, is that him?
[HESTIA AND BELL] Uh!
[GODDESS 2]
Hestia's boyfriend?
UGH! AH!
(Goddesses chattering)
[BELL] What are
you ladies doing?!
[BELL]
AH! UH...!
Uh...
I gotcha! Oh!
G‐geh!
(Stammering)
(Bell Struggling)
[DEMETER]
Oh Hestia, we just
couldn't resist.
[HESTIA] UH!
I'm so sorry...
but this is all too much.
[BELL]
Let go...!
OH!
Well, isn't he
simply adorable?!
Mff... Mff!
[HESTIA]
AHHH!
(Demeter laughs)
(Muffled screaming)
Get your... boobs...
off of him!
Oh? Ah?
[HESTIA]
AHWHAAA!
[GODDESS 4]
She's taking him away!
(Goddesses yelling)
Get back here!
Hmm...
Hm?
[GODDESS 2]
I think they went
that way!
(Bell and Hestia straining)
(Panting)
(Straining)
(Bell and Hestia panting)
[BOTH]
Ahh!
(Both panting)
[BELL]
Oh god... Looks like
we finally lost 'em.
[HESTIA]
The other goddesses
always act like that!
Ya bunch of
drooling hyenas!
They kept us running
around the whole day!
So much for
our date, huh?
Ah... I dunno, it was
still pretty fun.
Huh?
Just look out there.
It's not all
that bad, is it?
[HESTIA]
Huh...
(Hestia laughs)
Wow...
It's beautiful.
Mhm.
Hey, Goddess,
let's do this again.
But next time we might
wanna get dinner first.
(Laughs)
[HESTIA]
Yeah.
Hm.
[HESTIA]
I'll be looking
forward to it, Bell.
(Scared gasp)
[GARNEAU]
Ooh, that for me?
Ah!
So then, you say you
got more than usual.
(Coins jingle)
Well sorry, but it still ain't
quite enough though, is it?
(Garneau laughs)
(Scared gasp)
[GARNEAU]
You're lucky!
A twerp like you
wouldn't have a chance
to join the
Soma Familia.
You know who you have
to thank, don'tcha?
[LILI](Pained)
It's... it's all because
of the adventurers...
Damn right, little lady.
Don't you forget that...
And keep bringin' in that cash!
[LILI]
AH!
(Goons laugh)
[GARNEAU]
She hit the ground
pretty good that time!
(Continued laughter)
(Lili sighs)
Who cares about those
stupid adventurers?
Seriously.
Doesn't matter anymore.
I've almost got enough money
saved up at this point.
[LILI]
And I swear, I will get
that knife back, too.
[BELL, FLASHBACK]
You were a huge help, Lili.
Thank you.
(Sigh)
That guy's... so weird.
[MISHA]
So uh did you hear about
what happened, Eina?
Another adventurer from
the Soma Familia
was able to rake in a ton
of valis out of nowhere!
Hmm... Why are they always so
preoccupied with making money?
No idea.
I mean, they've been
selling so much alcohol,
I don't see how their
Familia could be possibly
hurting for cash.
Hm...
(Monsters chitter and screech)
NGH!
HN! HAH!
[LILI]
AH! Master Bell!
Look out!
YAH! AHH!
Hng... Guh...
(Monster screeches)
Leave him alone!
HYAH!
(Battle cry)
[BELL]
Guh! Yah!
(Sigh)
Huh?!
[LILI, THINKING]
Shoot, I wasn't
supposed to use this!
[BELL]
AH! HYAH!
UGH!
(Sigh)
[LILI]
Are you okay,
Master Bell?
Uh‐huh... you saved me.
Thank you.
[LILI]
S‐sure thing.
Hang on...
did you just use magic?
Oh, no!
I have a
magic knife.
[BELL]
Really?! You chose to use
something that valuable for me?
Thanks a lot!
Uh... don't mention it.
I wanted to help
you out, so...
Wow, magic really
is something, huh?
Here.
Huh?
I thought you might
be hungry.
Uh. Thank you
very much.
Hey, Master Bell...
Ahh‐ Huh?
Would it be okay...
if I took a day
off tomorrow?
That's cool. You got
something planned?
[LILI]
There's this big
Familia meeting.
And I sorta have
to be there.
But I know it's
a breach of contract...
so I'm prepared
to pay the price.
No, no! You don't
have to do that!
I should've said
this before, but...
Huh?
I'm not like that, okay?
If you ever wanna take a
day off, just let me know.
(Crunch)
Ah?
(Bell gulping)
(Sigh)
(Crunch)
[BELL]
All finished.
You're taking a little
break today, huh?
I am. So now I've
got some free time.
What do you like to do on
your days off, Miss Syr?
Uh, let me see...
Read books, I guess.
Reading, huh?
Well, I would,
but Goddess Hestia's books
all look too complicated.
Hm?
[BELL]
"Modern Magic Even
a Goblin Can Do"?
That something
you'd like?
A customer left it here
awhile ago, and I doubt
they'll ever be back.
I'd be glad to let you borrow
it if you're interested.
[BELL]
Wow, are you sure?
[SYR]
It's no trouble at all.
Just be sure to return
it whenever you're
finished reading it.
(Bell straining)
Magic, huh...
Let's see... "There are
two types of magic:
Inherited magic,
depends on your race
and 'Acquired' is
determined by a Farna...
or blessing from a God.
Acquired magic must be
self‐actualized.
What interests you?
What do you love? Hate?
Desire? Grieve? Respect?
(Mystical twinkling)
Where does your devotion lie?
The trigger always
manifests from within."
[GRAY BELL]
Shall we get started?
What does the word
"magic" mean to me?
(Sounds of nature)
Great power.
A weapon against
weakness...
my OWN weakness.
[BLUE BELL]
What does magic
look like to me?
[BELL]
Fire... blazing hot.
The opposite of the
weak person I am.
Red fire.
And what is it
you seek to become?
As quick as lightning.
So I can... be...
closer to her side.
[YELLOW BELL]
Is that all?
[BELL]
Well I...
I'd like...
to be a hero.
Like the stories
I used to read.
[BELL]
And for him to
CALL me a hero.
Just once.
[BELLS]
How childish.
Sorry.
But... that's just me!
(Echoing)
That's just me!
[HESTIA]
Bell? Bell!
Huh?
What's with you?
Huh? Ah. G‐Goddess?
[BELL]
Wh‐what happened?
(Mystical humming)
[HESTIA]
So you were reading
some weird book
and then you
suddenly fell asleep?
[BELL]
I... guess so...
(Laughs)
You're so cute.
Huh?!
[BELL]
What's the matter?
[HESTIA]
Magic...
Huh?
You can...
use magic.
[BELL]
WHAT?!
Agh!
Ah! Sorry
about that.
Guh... Ugh.
(Shocked gasps)
[HESTIA]
It's Fire Bolt.
I really never thought you'd
pick up a magic ability.
(Continued shock)
Must be because
of that Skill.
[BELL]
Goddess!
Hm?
It's magic!
I can use magic!
Wow, I can't believe I can
actually use magic now!
(Laughing)
(Annoyed sigh)
Ah! Huh?
Look, Bell.
I assume you've heard that
the only way to make magic work
is by reciting a
spell, right?
Hm.
Usually...
when you first gain
a magic ability...
a spell will appear
with your Status.
However, somehow...
your Status isn't
telling me anything...
'cept for
"Quick Attack Magic."
Yeah?
I'm just guessing here,
but I think that might
mean your magic doesn't
require a spell after all.
Huh?!
Well, you should
probably test it out
when you go down to the
dungeon tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Don't you worry.
It's your magic.
It's not going anywhere.
There's no need to rush.
Ah...
I hope you can
forgive me Goddess.
(Panting)
[BELL]
But there's no way
I can wait to try it out!
[HESTIA]
Please forgive me,
potato croquettes...
(Groan)
I'm gonna eat
you all up! Ah...
(Panting)
Huh?
(Goblin snarls)
Hah...
(Inhale)
Fire Bolt! Ah!
(Screech)
Hng. Huh?
Oh yeah...
SWEET!
Fire Bolt!
(Loud explosion)
Fire Bolt! Fire Bolt!
Fire Bolt!
(Panting)
That was pretty dumb...
I wound up pretty far in.
I guess I should probably
head back out now‐
(Faint)
[RIVERIA]
Wait until they hear this.
You defeated a floor boss
all by yourself.
(Armor and gear jingling)
(Sizzling and bubbling)
[RIVERIA]
Huh?
It looks like Mind Down.
He must've used magic
without actually knowing
what would happen
to him.
It's... him.
What's the matter, Ais?
Do you know this guy?
[AIS]
Well, we haven't
exactly spoken...
But... I've seen him
down here...
I see.
He's the poor soul who paid
for our unfortunate mistake.
That's correct.
So I...
I would like to make it
up to him.
(Water churning)
[RIVERIA](Muffled)
Well then, why don't you
tell him what you told me?
I'm sure that'll
be more than enough.
[AIS]
Hm? You really
think so?
[RIVERIA]
Trust me, it will.
I'll go on ahead.
(Light exhale)
[BELL]
Mom?
No. Sorry, I'm afraid
I am not your mother.
Am I dreaming...?
Mph... This isn't
a dream either.
Hm.
Huh?
(Startled squeak)
(Bell screams)
Uh!
[BELL]
AHHH!
Why does he always
end up running away?
(Bell sobbing)
Aaggghh...
I‐I ran away again!
[BELL]
I'm such an idiot!
(Yawn)
(Continued sobbing)
Hm?
[HESTIA]
What's wrong, Bell?
You have a
bad dream again?
Huh?
(Still sobbing)
Is this because of that
book you read yesterday?
Ah!
Huh?
[BELL]
A Grimoire?
[HESTIA]
Yeah. It's a book that
makes you able to use
magic just by reading it,
so it's super powerful.
How did you get your
hands on this thing?
It was at
the tavern.
Somebody left it,
so they said I could borrow it.
Somebody left this?!
(Sigh)
Ah! Wait, what's the
matter, Goddess Hestia?
Okay... Here's the thing, Bell.
Now listen up...
Once the first person reads it
all the power disappears
without a trace!
(Frantic gasp)
Guh! Ah!
(Quiet panic)
AHH... AH!
Uh... And just where do
you think you're going?
(Clattering)
Hng... I have to go apologize
and find a way to‐
[HESTIA]
Forget it!
Huh?!
Obviously you
have no idea
how much a grimoire
is worth.
It's practically the same
as a top‐class item
from Hephaistos herself!
Maybe MORE!
AHH!
(Extended screaming)
Listen carefully, Bell.
You didn't read
this book, understand?
Not one chapter.
I'll take care of
this mess somehow.
[HESTIA]
Just leave it to me.
[BELL]
Ah! Hang on, what
are you gonna do?!
(Both straining)
Don't try to stop me!
[HESTIA]
There's too many bad things
in the lower world
you can't take back!
This world's a fickle place!
More so than the Gods'!
[BELL]
What? What's that
even supposed to mean?!
(Boing)
[BELL]
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
[SYR]
Oh dear, Bell, you've done
a seriously terrible thing.
[BELL]
Wait a second!
Why are you talking like you
weren't a part of this too?!
Don't do this me.
[MIA]
(Sigh)
I'm sorry,
is there a problem?
You're very cute,
but yeah, there is.
(Giggle)
[MIA]
Ugh...
[BELL]
Uh, Mama Mia?
[MIA]
Oh, save it.
[BELL] B‐but...
[MIA]
The damage has already
been done, okay?
Whoever was dumb enough to
just leave it laying around
is to blame here.
Yeah, but don't
you think I
(Grunt)
(Bell squeaks)
[BELL]
Uh... off to
the dungeon!
(Chuckles)
(Annoyed sigh)
[EINA]
Let's see...
Where could it be?
[LOKI]
Aha! Check it
out, Riveria.
Ah. Huh?
Wine from the
Soma Familia!
C'mon, let's
get us some!
Pretty please,
Mama?
Don't call me that.
[LOKI]
Guh!
I came to restock
our supplies...
not to buy you
a bunch of alcohol.
[EINA]
Lady Riveria!
Oh!
Hmm...
Eina... what are
you doing here?
Hm?
(Loki marvelling)
(Wicked laugh)
[EINA]
Thank you so much
for buying her that.
I didn't know how else
I was going to get her
attention.
[RIVERIA]
I would've been forced
to do so anyway.
At least this way I can take
comfort in knowing that it
will be useful to you.
Okay, you promised.
Answer her
question, please.
(Extended aahing)
[LOKI]
Okay, okay!
So you wanna know
what the Soma Familia
is all about, right?
[EINA]
Yes, please.
Well... how should
I explain this?
I know what those guys worship
and it sure ain't Soma.
It's wine.
Huh?
Master Bell must
be running late.
Uh. AH!
Hm? Shouldn't Lili
be here by now?
Ah? Ah‐
[BELL]
Oh, there she is!
Huh?! Lili!
Hey, there.
Uh! You're that guy from
the other night.
(Tense breath)
[GEDO]
So you hired the little
street meat, did ya?
I guess you must have figured
out what's going on then, huh?
What are you
talking about?
Oh, don't even.
But okay, check this out.
I can help you
get back at her.
Huh?!
C'mon, what's
that look for?
I mean you do want a
piece of everything
she's been stashin'
away, don't ya?
Think about it.
It's just a couple o' guys
makin' a few bucks off of
some skeezin' little
pack‐mule, am I right?
(Seething)
No way.
[GEDO]
Ahh?
No! Never!
Fine.
Suit yourself, kid.
Moron.
(Tense breathing)
[LILI]
Master Bell.
Huh?
Were you there
this whole time?
So that adventurer guy...
What were to two of you
talking about?
Oh no, don't worry.
It wasn't
anything important.
He just wanted
to chat... yeah...
Anyway, what about you?
[BELL]
That looked
pretty serious.
You okay?
I'm fine.
It was nothing.
[LILI]
Ready to go?
Ah... Hm...
Well, looks like it's
about that time, huh?
(Ending Song)
[HESTIA]
Next Time:
"Liliruca Arde"