[BELL]
Well, I'm off,
Goddess Hestia.
Hm. You know what, Bell...
That salamander wool
is a lot more conspicuous
than I thought
it would be.
Well I'm gonna have to
be extra‐prepared
for the middle floors.
Miss Eina would
have it no other way.
You're right, though,
it is a little bit flashy.
Yeah, well, if your advisor
suggested it to you...
then I guess you should
probably listen.
And don't start pushing
yourself too hard
just because you're
level 2 now, okay?
Right!
Wish me luck!
(Sigh)
Ah.
(Opening Song)
(Street chatter)
[TAKE]
Above all else, come back
in one piece,
Hm? Ah.
you understand me?
[GROUP] Right!
[TAKE]
And Mikoto,
don't go crazy
just because
you've ranked up.
Sir!
[OUKA]
Thank you, Lord Takemikazuchi.
We're off then.
Hm.
[HESTIA]
Take?
Oh?
I take it those are the
children of your Familia?
That's right,
they're mine.
[HESTIA]
Are they for
the middle floors?
[TAKE]
Yeah. Your Little Rookie's
on his way down there
as well, isn't he?
Yes, that he is.
He's just
starting today.
Huh?
He took off pretty
early this morning.
[TAKE]
Well, worrying about it
won't help anything.
Uh!
All we can do is
have faith in them.
Hm.
(Rumbling)
Oh?
[HESTIA]
That an earthquake?
(Birds chirp wildly)
[TAKE]
Yes. We've had several lately.
[HESTIA]
Yes, we have.
And they seem to last longer
than they used to.
[HESTIA, THINKING]
You'll be okay. Right, Bell?
Hmm...
(Gnarly howl)
Guh! Hng...
(Bell grunts)
(Welf yells)
(Wolf growling)
Now take him out!
(Pained roar)
YAAAH!
Whoa!
(Laughs)
Well, we survived our first
middle‐floor fight.
Not bad, huh?
[BELL]
Yeah! That wasn't
all that hard.
Even the fire attacks from
those Hell Hounds were
pretty easy to handle.
Uh‐huh.
[LILI]
We need to find an open area.
This isn't a good place to be
surrounded by monste‐
(Squeak)
Ah! Uh?
(Squeaking)
[LILI]
They look like you.
[WELF]
Hm. Little Bell‐bunnies.
[BELL]
They're called
Al‐Mi'raj!
(Hissing)
(Screeching)
Bell's angry!
Can you calm down
your little friends?
Agh! They have nothing
to do with me!
(Humming)
[ASFI]
You know, the other adventurers
are beginning to say
some very nasty things about
that "Little Rookie" person.
Hm? Hm...
[ASFI]
Well, he did kill a minotaur
single‐handed...
but they say that
he was using magic.
And that the Loki Familia
left it there for him.
Even if he received
a blessing from a god...
S'no way he could've possibly
leveled up that easily.
[ASFI]
Some have speculated
that he lied about
how long it took
to rank up.
[ASFI]
They don't believe he did it
faster than the Sword Princess.
They're so sensitive. Hm!
Still, the more I hear about
him, the more curious I get.
I can't wait
to meet this kid.
What exactly do you have
planned, Master Hermes?
Why are you so interested
in that boy anyway?
C'mon, what's wrong, Asfi?
You jealous?
(Annoyed grunt)
[ASFI]
What?! Look, I just
don't want to get into
any trouble, alright?
Think of MY position
for once!
Mph!
All the members
appreciate you, Asfi.
You're the best leader a
Familia could ever ask for.
You're so perfect, even your own
god depends on you, right?
(Chuckle)
Uh, yeah... thanks...
(Pop pop)
Good to see you,
FUR‐ends! Huh?
[CHLOE]
Lord Hermes?
Miss Chloe.
And Miss Syr!
[BOTH]
Oh!
(Chuckle)
(Panting)
Uh!
Hah!
(Grunt)
Hyah!
(Boom and fizzle)
[OUKA]
Mikoto! Come on,
don't fall behind!
[MIKOTO]
Right!
(Panting)
I'm sorry, but we can't
afford to lose anybody.
There is no need for you
to apologize, Sir Ouka!
A party needs to
stick together!
[CHIGUSA]
Mikoto...
[OUKA]
I know, but...
[PARTY MEMBER]
Look out!
Hell Hounds!
[OUKA]
There's a room up ahead!
Let's see if we can
hide in there!
YAAAGH!
[BELL]
Hyah!
[WELF]
They keep comin'!
Can't catch
my breath!
Then maybe you shouldn't
waste it by talking so much!
[BELL, THINKING]
This is crazy.
The enemies are tougher,
and there's way more of them!
Huh?
Sir Ouka!
They're starting
to catch up to us.
We need to retreat and come
up with a new strategy.
Huh?
We're gonna have to run
through them, Mikoto.
Ugh! We can't do that!
They're in trouble‐
I'm much more concerned about
the lives of my own team members
than a bunch of strangers.
Ugh!
(Uncomfortable sighs)
(Weak grunt)
[OUKA]
Look, I know you don't
agree with this,
but you can yell at me
all you want later!
(Howling intensifies)
[BELL]
Hng!
Hyah!
(Screeching)
Hng! AH!
Ngh! Hah!
Huh?
[LILI]
Uh‐oh...
Huh?!
It's not over yet!
Gah!
Uh!
Huh?!
[LILI]
They Pass‐Paraded us!
(Gnarly howling)
Hah...
[WELF]
Are you serious?!
[LILI]
Let's retreat!
Head for that passage!
(Growling)
(Screeches and growls)
(Sigh)
(Panting)
They're coming!
They're gonna catch us!
[BELL]
Lili! Keep running!
Master Bell!
Fire Bolt!
(Fiery explosion)
(Pained howls)
(Growling)
NGH!
Huh?
Look out!
Hng!
Have some of THIS!
Hyah!
Ah!
YAHH!
[BELL]
HYAH!
Gah!
(Magic Stone thuds)
(Sigh of relief)
Lili, you're not
hurt, are you?
I'm fine...
You okay, Welf?
(Strainig)
Uh‐yeah. I think so.
(Worried sigh)
(Distant howling)
Ah! Huh?
[LILI]
There's more?!
That's not all,
either.
(Nervous gasp)
(Loud shrieks)
[BELL]
Looks like
we're surrounded.
[WELF]
Why do the monsters on
these middle floors
always catch up
to us so fast?!
[LILI]
Yeah, that's just
how it works down here.
[RYU, FLASHBACK]
Mr. Cranel...
The dungeon is
a cruel place.
It'll overwhelm you with
small challenges.
Until, eventually,
you're left with an
impossible and painful burden.
Huh...
(Sigh)
And then...
HAAAH!
you buckle.
YAAGH!
[RYU]
You give in and you collapse
NGH!
like a castle made
of sand.
(Panting)
[RYU]
You don't have time
to rethink your strategy.
[RYU]
So once its prey
cries out in anguish,
weakened to the point
of exhaustion...
(Rocks crumble)
Huh?
[RYU]
...the dungeon finally
bares its true fangs.
(Slow gasp)
[BELL, THINKING]
No...
There's more?!
(Shrieks and screeches)
(Thunderous boom)
(Bell and Welf grunting)
Uh?!
(Pained grunts)
Ngh... Ngh...!
[WELF]
Ngh! Ah!
(Gasp)
(Lili gasps)
Huh?!
(Soft crying)
(Tense breath)
(Monsters snarl)
Uh!
(Screeches and howls)
(Flaming roar)
[LILI, THINKING]
This is it...
[WELF, THINKING]
Ngh. He's not gonna make it...
(Fiery explosion)
[BELL, THINKING]
So these...
...are the
middle floors.
(Hestia panting)
[EINA]
What?
That is just awful!
Are they still down there?
[HESTIA]
Mm‐hmm.
I can only assume so.
I mean, obviously they
haven't stopped by here.
[EINA]
No, they haven't.
At least I haven't seen them...
What about you two?
Okay then...
Hm.
Then I shall order a Quest!
To go in the dungeon and
find Bell and the others!
Hm.
[TAKE]
Hestia!
Huh?
Uh. Take?
(Welf groaning)
Ah!
[BELL]
Still hurts?
Uh yeah...
pretty bad.
Hey, how awesome
are we?
As soon as we tried to make
our way back upstairs...
we end up falling
down two floors.
The floor caved in so fast,
it's a miracle the three of us
were able to make it out.
[BELL]
And if I wasn't wearing this
Salamander Wool,
those Hell Hounds would've
burnt me to a crisp.
[WELF]
Your fashion advisor's
pretty smart.
[BELL]
No kidding. Huh?
(Troubled sighs)
[LILI]
Again?
[BELL]
Another dead end.
Hm...
(Distant growls)
Ah?
(Echoing howls)
(Chuckle)
Listen...
you need to leave me behind
if things get too
bad, alright?
[BOTH] Huh?
What are you
talking about?!
Admit it.
[WELF]
I'm just gonna slow
you guys down.
[BELL]
There's no way we're gonna leave
you just because you're hurt!
(Tense sigh)
There's no
other choice.
[LILI]
Wait...
Huh?
I think I might know a way.
We may be able to
get out alive...
if we can somehow make it
down to Floor 18.
But that doesn't
make any sense.
What's the point of us
going further DOWN?
The monsters are
gonna be stronger!
[LILI]
Just hear me out, guys.
Floor 18 is actually
a dungeon safe zone.
Which means monsters
don't spawn down there.
[LILI]
If we can meet up with some
higher‐level adventurers
who might be on their
way out of the dungeon,
it will give us a much better
chance of surviving this.
Yeah, but... how
do we get there?
[LILI]
We'll use a pit.
[BELL and WELF]
Huh?
[LILI]
The middle floors
are full of pits
like that one there.
Going straight down
through the floors
would get us
there a lot faster
than searching for
the stairs.
It's the most
efficient way down.
But what about
the Floor Boss?
Some of 'em are huge.
Like the one on 17.
[LILI]
That's Goliath.
But the Loki Familia should
have already beaten him.
And when you consider
his average recovery time...
we should just
barely make it.
[WELF]
Have you lost your mind?
I'm afraid it's the
only option we have left.
Master Bell, you're
the party leader.
It's up to you.
Up to me?
Go on... decide.
Hm.
Ah, don't be
afraid, Bell.
We won't blame you
for whatever happens.
Mm‐hmm.
Let's go.
[TAKE]
I'm sorry, Hestia!
[MIACH]
So you're saying
they purposefully lured
a pack of monsters
toward Bell's party?
[TAKE]
Even if they were desperate,
it was still unacceptable.
(All sigh)
[HESTIA]
If Bell doesn't make it
out of there alive...
Ah...
I will blame you
until the day I die.
That being said...
I'm not going to
hate you. I promise.
So, will you please help
bring my Bell back home?
(Speechless gasps)
[ALL]
As you command!
Oh...!
[HEPHAISTOS]
You see, the thing is...
I really can't help you
much with a search party.
I don't have any of
my best members.
They're currently down in the
dungeon with the Loki Familia.
I don't mind sending
Mikoto and Ouka down
to the middle floors.
[TAKE]
And Chigusa would probably
be fine as their supporter.
I'm afraid the others
would just slow you down.
(Collective sigh)
[TAKE]
But three probably
won't be enough...
[HERMES]
I'll help you
out, Hestia.
Ah!
Oh, hello, Hermes!
[TAKE]
What are you doing here?
What about your journey?
[HERMES]
I came running
as soon as I heard
my sweet friend Hestia
was in a tight spot.
Why don't you take
a look at this:
I even put in a little
request for a search.
(Hestia gasps)
[HEPHAISTOS]
You say that she's
your friend...
[OTHERS] Huh?
and yet you've had absolutely
nothing to do with her
since you got
to the lower world.
[TAKE]
Well she does
have a point.
[MIACH]
You've never seemed like
a very devoted friend of hers.
[HERMES]
Aw, come on now...
Man, you guys are
a tough crowd!
(Grumbles)
But still, I genuinely do
want to help Hestia.
[HESTIA]
And I'd like to
save Bell,
if I may.
(Pop)
[HERMES]
So I've decide to let
Asfi here tag along.
Huh?!
She's my top dog,
so we'll be just fine.
(Sigh)
(Sad grunt)
[TAKE]
Well, it's
your call.
Rescuing Bell is my
number one priority.
And the more help I get,
the better.
I accept your
offer, Hermes.
Good! You can
count on me.
(Groan)
[HEPHAISTOS]
We'll leave as soon as
everyone is ready.
[MIACH]
Let's aim for this
evening, shall we?
[TAKE]
You three, make sure
you're prepared.
[GROUP]
Sir!
Okay Asfi,
what's wrong?
Tell me the truth.
When you told everyone
"we'll be just fine" earlier...
Don't tell me...
[HERMES]
That's right...
I'm going with you.
UH! Hermes, gods are not
permitted inside the dungeon!
Look nobody needs to know.
Just be sure not to make any
mistakes... it'll work out.
(Sigh)
Oh?
You planned this
from the start,
didn't you?
(Pop)
(Laughs)
(Pop pop)
You just focus on
protecting me, okay?
[HESTIA]
You're taking me
with you!
[BOTH]
Hestia?!
[HERMES]
Don't be absurd!
(Whistle)
Gods aren't allowed
inside the dungeon.
You know that...
That's preposterous!
We'll have to
keep it a secret!
Uuhh!
I am going in with you
to save Bell.
There's something not right just
leaving it up to somebody else.
So I'm going to help too!
You understand?
Ugh...
[HEPHAISTOS]
Um... Hestia...
[ALL] Huh?
[TAKE]
Forgive me. We are
to blame for this.
[HESTIA]
Oh, forget about that.
I can sense him.
[HESTIA]
I'm certain that
Bell is still alive.
The blessing that I
gave him hasn't faded yet.
(Collective chuckle)
[HEPHAISTOS]
Hestia?
Oh?
If you happen to
run into Welf...
could you give him
something for me?
[HEPHAISTOS]
Along with a little message.
If you don't mind.
[HESTIA]
Of course I can.
[HERMES]
Asfi, I'm afraid
I have to ask.
Can you protect both
me AND Hestia?
Well, I can't
guarantee anything.
That's a problem.
[HERMES]
Shall we enlist
one more, then?
(Heavy sigh)
Ugh!
(Coughs)
(Forcefully clearing throat)
(Lili sighs)
[WELF]
Please, Little Bit!
Can you please do
something about that smell?
[LILI]
Oh, just shut up!
How do you think I feel,
you jerk?!
I'm the one
who's holding it!
[BOTH] GAH!
[LILI]
Why don't you try carrying
it, Master Welf?!
I'm sorry!
[BELL] Please, have mercy on us.
[LILI] You think you're the
only one who doesn't like it?!
How dare you complain to me!
AH!
This stink‐bag is our
last hope for survival.
As long as it keeps on
smelling disgusting,
hopefully it'll keep
the monsters from
trying to attack us.
[WELF]
I understand that,
but... Guh...
We just have to
deal with it.
Huh?
(Growling)
Let me get
this one.
Ignite, Heretic Spell!
Will o' the Wisp!
(Whistling winds)
(Heavy explosion)
[ALL]
Guh!
Wow, that's
a great spell!
I assume it uses the enemy's own
magic to make it self‐destruct.
Yeah, and well, I never
knew when I was going
to have to actually
break it out
and use it.
Are you okay, though?
You've been casting
that same spell a lot.
Don't you worry.
I'll be fine.
(Weak laugh)
(Worried sighs)
[FREYA]
Just what are you plotting?
Ah. 'Tis no matter.
But know this:
The only one who gets
to toy with him...
...is me.
(Rumbling)
[BELL]
Lili...?
[LILI]
Yeah.
we're all outta
the stinky stuff.
(Heavy footsteps)
(Snarling)
(Scared gasps)
You are kidding me.
This isn't
funny anymore!
I mean,
what the hell?!
(Loud roar)
HNG! YAAAH!
YAH! Guh!
HNNGG!
(Minotaur roars in pain)
YAAH!
HAH! HYAH!
AGH!
[WELF]
Jesus H...
(Bell grunts)
(Snarling)
What the...?
Ah!
AAGGHH!
YAAGGHH!
(Loud explosion)
(Rocks crumbling)
(Both grunting)
(Stammering)
[WELF, THINKING]
Damn...
(Panting)
This guy really
did beat a Minotaur
when he was only level 1!
Ugh!
[LILI]
Master Bell!
Omigosh, are
you okay?! Huh?
(Heavy panting)
(Worried gasp)
Hm.
(Ending Song)
Okay.
Everyone ready?
[HERMES]
Uh‐huh!
[GROUP]
Ready!
Good, then let's go find
Bell and his party‐
[MIKOTO]
Wait, who's that?
Why is she here?
No need to
fret, darling.
Huh?
She's here to help.
Hm.
[HESITA]
Alright!
Don't worry, Bell,
we are on the way!
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Under Resort"