[OTTARL, VOICE‐OVER]
Those who do not embrace
adventure
will never be able
to overcome the barrier.
(Minotaur roars)
[BELL, FLASHBACK]
Level... 6...?
[EINA]
She got it on floor 37,
I believe.
She managed to defeat the
Floor Boss all by herself.
[BELL]
Whoa...
[EINA, FLASHBACK]
Defeating a foe that powerful
normally requires
a full party of
high‐skilled adventurers.
Do not try to compare
yourself to her, Bell.
I've never heard of
something like what she can do.
Lady Wallenstein
is very unique.
[BELL]
Hyah! Hah! Gah! Hah!
Guh! Hah?
AH!
Ngh!
Ugh...
[BELL, THINKING]
I want to be
closer to her,
even if just a little bit!
(Exhausted breaths)
[BELL]
Let me try one more time!
Ngh... AAGGHHH!
[AIS, FLASHBACK]
You're exceptionally strong.
How did you manage to
get that way so quickly?
[BELL, THINKING]
Just a little stronger...
A little faster...!
(Opening Song)
(Street chatter and footsteps)
(Choked up)
[SYR]
Bell!
Huh?
(Panting)
Mmm.
Wha... Miss Syr?
I want you!
Huh?!
[BELL]
WHAT?!
So THAT'S what you meant?!
I'm sorry.
Uh...
They piled up while I
was goofing off‐ Uh...
I mean, taking
a short break.
So Mama Mia is
sorta punishing me.
She's angry.
So then you're just
pushing it off on me?!
I know, it's mean of me,
but I know you can do it!
(Giggles)
(Disgruntled sigh)
Oh well... maybe this'll help
get my mind off of things.
Huh?
This is way too much for you.
Please let me help.
Thank you...
(Dishes rattle and clank)
[BELL]
Were you ever an
adventurer, Miss Ryu?
[RYU]
Well... I was once.
Why do you ask?
[BELL]
I was wondering, what should I
be doing to make my level go up?
Do I just need to keep
fighting monsters?
No, that's not going
to be enough.
There's a lot more to it.
And actually, you'll need
to conquer one of the
more powerful enemies.
Huh? Do you really
think I can do that?
[RYU]
It's not going
to be easy.
But you'll have better luck
with the right skills
and a proper strategy.
Huh?
Combine skill AND strategy.
Right now you're lacking
a little something in both.
Hrm...
[RYU]
Although, that alone won't
be enough to defeat one.
You need to join up
with a Party.
If you seriously
hope to improve,
you'll have to find
one eventually anyway.
[RYU]
Find someone whose strengths
compensate for your weaknesses,
and you'll have no trouble
defeating the tougher enemies.
[RYU]
Now, to answer your
question, Mr. Cranel,
the main condition
for leveling up is simple ‐
to go on adventures.
[RYU]
And a journey is more
meaningful with multiple people.
I don't know what sort
of adventures you've had
to this point, but please,
don't ever forget what
you've learned from them.
Uh. Huh?
Cause in the end...
what I believe...
...is that if you
want something...
the only way to get it
is to step up and take it.
[RYU]
But, that said, I have
been wrong in the past.
Ah? Hrm...
(Bell grunting)
(Blades clashing)
Yaaah!
Hyaaaaahhh!
Agh!
(Bell yelps)
(Grunt)
You just countered.
You hadn't done that yet.
I guess... Yeah.
[AIS]
That's it for
your training then.
Huh?
Thank you, Miss Ais, for
all your help this week.
Thank you, Bell.
That was fun.
Hah...
[AIS]
Do your best
out there, alright?
Hm? Uh...
Right. You too...
um... do your best.
(Light chuckle)
[BELL, THINKING]
I don't know if
I'll ever catch up.
But I'll try.
I'll chase after you as if
you're within my reach.
And then...
(Birds chirping)
[HESTIA]
So, did you finish your special
training
with Wallen‐what'serdealy
this morning?
[BELL]
Yep, right on schedule.
The Loki Familia starts
their expedition today.
Oh, good.
All done, huh?
Hm...
[HESTIA, THINKING]
But still, these abilities...
[BELL]
Well, see ya later,
Goddess Hestia.
Wait just a minute!
Your Status!
We can do it
when I get back.
Huh? B‐Bell! Bell!
Ah...
Bell...
[HESTIA]
What is with you anyway?
(Chatter and footsteps)
[FINN]
Everyone... we're going to
descend to the lower floors.
[FINN]
Just as before, we'll split into
two groups to avoid crowding.
Group one will go with me,
and Gareth will lead group two.
The Hephaistos Familia smiths
are joining us as well.
The plan is to meet on floor 18
and head straight to floor 50.
[FINN]
We have only one objective:
To be the first party
to ever reach floor 59!
[OTTARL]
Everything is prepared.
Although one voracious
little adventurer decided
to sneak a peek already.
[FREYA]
Oh?
Well I hope he is about
to show me something...
exhilarating.
(Laugh)
(Echoing footsteps)
Is something wrong,
Master Bell?
Don't tell me
you don't feel that.
[BELL]
Almost like somebody's
watching us.
No.
But I get it though...
this floor is totally
giving me the creeps.
[BELL]
Uh‐huh.
Where are all
those monsters?
And where did
the people go?
[BELL, THINKING]
It's just like... before.
Hm...
Let's go.
O‐okay.
(Distant roar)
[BELL]
Huh?
What was that?
(Scared whimpering)
(Snarling)
(Snarl)
(Heavy footsteps)
(Grinding metal)
(Growling)
(Lili gasps)
[LILI]
Why is there a minotaur
on Floor 9?
Let's run, Master Bell!
It's too dangerous
with a longsword!
C'mon!
(Anxious breathing)
Master Bell?
(Minotaur snarls)
Huh?
(Grunt)
(Growling)
[LILI]
What's the matter
with you?!
(Growling)
(Loud roar)
(Scared gasp)
[LILI]
Snap out of it!
[BELL]
AH!
Ngh... Guh...
Ah!
(Startled gasp)
Lili, you okay?
(Growl)
(Strained breath)
(Loud growl)
Hng.
Lili...
[BELL]
forgive me!
Fire Bolt!
Fire Bolt! Fire Bolt!
FIRE BOLT!
(Heavy panting)
(Minotaur roars)
Guh! Ngh!
GAH!
(Bell coughing)
(Minotaur growling)
(Weak breathing)
(Snort)
(Long roar)
(Panting)
(Weak grunt)
[BETE]
You mean you actually saw
a minotaur down here?
Huh?
[MAN]
Yeah, I saw it with my own eyes.
It was roaming around on Floor 9
and it's carrying a giant sword.
[TIONA]
Is it a survivor
from last time?
[RIVERIA]
That's impossible.
It's been almost
an entire month,
and no one's seen a
minotaur down here.
Regardless, I'm glad that you
were able to make it out.
[FINN]
Did you see anyone else?
Yeah, it attacked
this other guy.
He was all by himself.
It was that white‐haired kid...
the one from before...
Wait! Ais!
Alright, we're
on a mission!
Uh!
[BETE] Dammit...
[TIONE]
Bete! Tiona!
Apologies, Raul.
Feel free to take over.
[RAUL]
Ah, right!
(Stone crumbling)
[BELL]
NGH! AH!
(Grunt)
(Bell grunts)
Ah!
[BELL,THINKING]
It's the same as last time!
[AIS, FLASHBACK]
You feel afraid, don't you?
AH!
Guh!
(Grunt)
(Loud roar)
(Bell grunting)
(Metal clashes)
AHH!
(Heavy panting)
[BELL, THINKING]
It's only a matter of
time before he gets me.
I've gotta make
a break for it!
(Groan)
Huh?
[LILI]
Master... Bell?
Lili!
[BELL]
Get outta here, now!
Hurry up!
I can't...
I SAID RUN!
I won't leave you!
Ghh!
GET OUT OF HERE!
Ah!
(Crying)
(Lili screams)
(Minotaur grunts)
[BELL, THINKING]
Good... now I can run too.
Huh?
Wait, no!
If I run away,
he'll go after Lili!
He'll kill her!
Damn you!
(Raging growl)
(Bell grunting)
(Minotaur roaring)
GYAH!
[BELL, THINKING]
If I dodge, we're just about
evenly matched in speed.
[BELL, THINKING]
Okay, that's what I'll do.
It's pretty pathetic, but I just
need to hold him off for now!
(Growls)
Hng!
Geh!
Guh! Ah!
(Bell whinces)
(Gasp)
(Minotaur roars)
(Armor shattering)
[BELL]
HNNNG!
(Minotaur roars)
Agh!
AAGGHHH!
(Minotaur grunts)
AH!
(Heavy thud)
AH! Ugh!
(Pained breaths)
(Wheezing)
Guh! Ah!
(Growling)
(Gasp)
[AIS]
Are you all right?
(Gasp)
[AIS, FLASHBACK]
Are you all right?
(Speechless)
[AIS]
You did very well,
but I'll save you now.
(Sword clanks)
(Shocked gasp)
[BELL, THINKING]
Save me?
Again?
How many times am I gonna
let Ais Wallenstein
swoop in and
fix my problems?
Do I ALWAYS need
to be rescued?!
Ghh...
(Whimper)
No, not again.
[BELL, THINKING]
If I don't overcome this now,
I'll always be weaker than her!
[TIONA]
There you are!
What exactly are
you thinking, Ais?
(Minotaur growls)
[AIS]
Uh!
[BELL]
I won't do it.
I will not let Ais Wallenstein
rescue me anymore!
Never again!
Uh! Ah...
(Minotaur growls)
(Angry grunt)
[BELL, THINKING]
It starts today.
This is MY first adventure.
(Echoing footsteps)
[BELL]
HAAAGH!
GUH! Ah!
[BETE]
Ain't there s'posed
to be some kinda rule
about takin'
someone else's target?
Wait... Holy crap!
Is that the Tomato Dude?!
(Laughs)
Man, what is it
with this freakshow asshole
and these
damn minotaurs?!
[TIONA]
He's the one Ais saved?
Yeah, and apparently these
big smelly things love
Tomato Head so much
they keep comin' all the
way up here to hang with him!
[TIONE]
Don't be like that, Bete.
Tch... What?
You heard the guy...
he doesn't want our help.
He's probably too embarassed
after making an ass of himself
in front of the girl
of his dreams, remember?
Hey, Ais... you
sure about this?
He's gonna die.
[BETE]
So?!
Huh? Hm.
[BETE]
Seriously, just let him go!
Maybe this time he'll
actually be a man about it.
I mean I think I'd
rather die than get
saved by a girl again.
(Lili gasps)
[BETE]
Ah! Huh?
[LILI]
I'm begging you, sir...
Please help him!
I don't want
Master Bell to die!
[BETE]
Hey, get off me,
you little squirt!
I'll do anything!
[TIONA]
She's in bad shape.
Not sure how she's standing.
It must've taken
everything she had
just to bring us here!
[LILI]
Whatever it takes,
I'll pay you back!
I swear, okay?
Just help him fight!
Please don't let him die.
[BETE]
Ugh...
(Mystical resonating)
[LILI]
You have to help him...
Help Master Bell...
I beg of you...
Tch...
[RIVERIA]
Uh! Where are
you going?
Okay, now listen.
I don't normally help out
little punks like him.
But I'd rather do that
than look like the guy
who enjoys picking on
all the wimps and
the weaklings.
Outta the way.
I'll do it.
Huh?
(Minotaur roars)
(Bell grunts)
HYAAAH!
Is that guy...
really a level 1?
Only a month ago...
you were very quick to
write him off as nothing more
than a reckless amateur.
[FINN]
Right, Bete?
What the hell happened
to him since then?
(Minotaur roars)
Hng! Gah!
Hah! HYAH!
(Grunt)
[BELL, THINKING]
This is MY adventure.
I WILL succeed!
I will be a hero!
YAAAHH!
[TIONE]
He's like the Argonaut.
[FINN]
The legend about the boy
who wanted to be a hero.
[TIONA]
I always liked that story.
(Minotaur roars)
(Bell yells)
(Roar)
HNG!
HYAAGGH!
(Freya laughs)
(Overjoyed laugh)
Ah... Incredible...
Such a beautiful sight!
(Laughs)
(Bell grunts)
Guh! Ngh!
Now that is
one tough knife.
It's just a simple blade.
How is he doing that?
Perhaps his technique...
[TIONE]
He's really going all out.
[TIONA]
But he's not
getting through.
[AIS]
A minotaur's skin
is extremely thick.
(Wincing)
Oh, Master Bell...
Guh! Hyah! Hng!
HNG! AH!
Hnng! Fire Bolt!
(Minotaur roars)
[TIONE]
He can do magic
without spells?!
It would appear so, but this
foe is awfully strong.
It's not THAT strong.
[TIONE]
Is it a stalemate?
HUH!
HYAAA!
(Metal shattering)
HYYAAAAAH!
(Minotuar roars in pain)
(Bell grunts)
(Pained roar)
Hng!
(Minotaur roars)
(Bell yells)
HYYAAAA! HYAH!
GUH!
HNG! GUH!
(Bell panting)
(Minotaur roars)
YAAGH! GAH!
(Pained growl)
(Strained roar)
YAAAAGH!
Bad idea.
Gah! Dumbass!
BELL, NO!
[AIS]
He'll be fine.
YAAARGH!
(Metal shattering)
Guh!
Hng... HYAH!
(Bell grunts)
Fire Bolt!
(Pained grunt)
(Blood splatters)
(Bell panting)
What, you want some more?!
FIRE BOLT!
(Minotaur cries in agony)
(Grunt)
(Gasp)
AGH! FIRE BOLT!
(Loud, pained roar)
(Thunderous explosion)
(Sizzling)
(Boom)
[LILI]
Master Bell...
[BETE]
The kid actually
pulled it off.
[TIONA]
I think he passed out
standing up.
[TIONE]
It's... Mind Zero...
(Thud)
[LILI]
Master Bell! Wake up!
(Panting)
(Worried sigh)
Ah...
[BETE]
Hang on, check
his Status.
[RIVERIA]
I don't think he wants us
all just staring at him.
Well it's not like
he's in any condition
to tell us not to.
(Sigh)
Riveria!
So, what's he got?
(Light chuckle)
Well, his abilities
are all level S.
[ALL]
Huh?!
What's this
guy's name?
It's Bell.
Bell Cranel.
I'm so proud of you.
You did it.
[BELL, FLASHBACK]
Hey, Goddess...
I want... to be strong.
[HESTIA, THINKING]
This is it.
The first page
of our story.
(Ending Song)
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Welf Crozzo"