[BELL, VOICE‐OVER]
That's right...
it was a clear day...
just like this one.
[MAN]
Bell! Something's
happened...
[BELL, VOICE‐OVER]
My grandfather was attacked
and killed by a monster
up in the mountains.
They said he fell
into a chasm.
I couldn't even
go look for him.
Grandfather,
I'm going... to be...
an adventurer.
[BELL, VOICE‐OVER]
The problem was,
it was impossible to find
a Familia out there...
(People laughing)
that would accept an
adventurer as weak as me.
[GATEKEEPER 1]
Forget it, kid. Get outta
here! Take a hike!
(Bell grimacing)
[GATEKEEPER 2]
Maybe we could hire you
to sweep the floor.
(People laughing)
[GATEKEEPER 3]
You'll have to pay
us to work here!
[BELL]
Please, sir!
I just want to help.
Please let me join your‐
[GATEKEEPER]
I said, no!
Come back when you're
stronger, squirt.
Now take off!
(Bell sighs)
[HESTIA]
Hello there.
You're looking
for a Familia?
[BELL, VOICE‐OVER]
And there she was...
A goddess.
(Laughs)
[BELL, VOICE‐OVER]
My goddess.
(Roaring)
I'm buying you
some time, Goddess.
So get out of here
and save yourself.
Bell, what are you
talking about?!
Open this door,
right now!
Listen to me...
Whatever happens, I'm not
losing any more family.
Bell, please!
Come back!
(Bell panting)
BELL!
(Opening song begins)
(Wrangler grunting)
The monsters escaped?!
How did this happen?
[ATTENDANT 1]
There's something wrong
with all the guards.
It looks like their spirits
have been drained somehow.
We have reason to
suspect that an outsider
could have been
responsible for this.
We'll have to figure
that out later!
Tell me, how many
did we lose?
We've lost nine,
my lord.
And a suppression force has
already been assembled
and begun searching
the area.
They're not going
to be fast enough!
We'll need assistance
from other Familias.
[GANESHA]
Now go forth and request aid
from the other deusdea!
Uh yes, but,
my lord...
Our Familia is
the one at fault
for letting them get out
in the first place!
Asking for help from other
sources would be a great
dishonor to us!
[GANESHA]
I am Ganesha,
leader of this Familia.
Our concern is for the
happiness of our children,
not petty status
or prestige!
The safety of our beloved
citizens comes first!
[ATTENDANTS]
Yes, Lord Ganesha!
[GANESHA]
Now, in the meantime...
try to keep the
chaos contained.
The festival shall
proceed as planned.
Begone!
[ATTENDANTS]
Right!
(Receding footsteps)
[GANESHA, THINKING]
What is it they're after?
(Crowd cheering)
[GANESHA]
Are they trying to
create a diversion?
Or maybe...
something else.
(Bell panting)
(Silverback roars)
Ah!
(Heavy breathing)
(Shattering)
[BELL]
Goddess Hestia...
I'm sorry.
AH! O‐ow...
Ow...
(Sighs)
[HEPHAISTOS]
Alright, Hestia.
Now listen to me carefully.
That knife generates a
Status that accompanies
whatever hieroglyphs you
happen to engrave into it.
So what I'm telling you is...
the knife is alive.
It's alive?
[HEPHAISTOS]
As soon as Bell Cranel
receives this weapon,
it will draw its first
breath and start growing
along with him.
[HESTIA, THINKING]
I'm coming, Bell!
[EINA]
Sure, that'd be great.
[MISHA]
Eina! Eina!
[BOY]
Thank you!
(Eina giggles)
(Whispering)
What, are
you sure?!
Yeah. I just heard
it straight from
the Ganesha Familia!
They said several monsters
escaped from the west gate!
[EINA]
Shhh! Please, Misha...
Mm!
don't be so loud!
We don't want
to cause a panic.
Right. Right!
So anyway... they said
to ask for help
from any adventurers
I could find,
regardless of what Familia
they happen to be from.
Oh great, not sure we want
the ones around here.
[LOKI] Whoo,
smells like money!
[BOTH] Huh?
YEOW!
Excuse me what's
going on?
[MISHA] Whoa.
The Sword Princess!
[LOKI](Continued agony)
It's you.
Ais Wallenstein.
(Silverback roaring)
(Bell panting)
[BELL]
Ngh!
(Bell panting)
(Chains rattle)
Ah!
(Roars)
(Bell screams)
AHH!
(Exhales)
[BELL, THINKING]
I hope... Goddess Hestia
was able to get away...
(Heavy footsteps)
(Bell gasps)
[BELL]
Ngh!
(Silverback growling)
Miss Ais isn't gonna save me.
Not this time anyway.
(Snarling)
[BELL, THINKING]
I wanted to meet her...
at least one more time.
But I guess this
is for the best.
I can't let her see me
like this again.
(Roars)
(Sword slicing)
(Agonizing cry)
(Boom and fizzle)
[LOKI]
Heh.
That's my girl!
Kickin' mad
monster booty!
[LOKI]
Ooh, speaking
of booty... Ah!
[AIS]
Okay. How many more are
still out there?
[LOKI] (In pain)
That's okay,
I know you love me.
Well, the other adventurers
are keeping them contained
for the time being...
but there should be
about three or four.
Hm.
(Guildmen panting)
[LOKI]
Ugh...
Hey, wait for me!
[MISHA]
Wow.
The Sword Princess sure
is something, huh?
Right? I can certainly see
why Bell's become
so attracted to her.
[EINA, THINKING]
Hopefully....
he's not caught
up in this mess too.
(Silverback snarling)
[BELL, THINKING]
Goodbye, Goddess...
[HESTIA]
Bell!
Huh?
[BELL, THINKING]
Oh, no...
Why are you here...?
(Hestia laughs)
You weren't supposed
to follow me!
(Silverback growls)
(Bell panting)
(Chains rattle)
AH!
(Hestia screams)
[BOTH]
NGH! AH!
AH!
[HESTIA]
Ah...
Ngh... Are you okay,
Goddess Hestia?
Uh... uh‐huh!
I think I am.
What were you thinking
coming here?!
I asked you to
save yourself!
So, why?
You still haven't figured
it out yet have you?
There's nothing
in this world
that could make
me leave you, Bell.
(Gasps)
[HESTIA]
You want to protect
me, don't you?
Well, that's exactly how
I feel about you!
And besides... you made
me a promise, remember?
[HESTIA, FLASHBACK]
I'm begging you Bell,
do not leave me all alone.
Ngh!
(Silverback roars)
Yeah, but... now the
both of us are going to be‐
(Bell grimacing)
It's too early
to surrender.
Ah!
C'mon!
We can't give up
just yet, okay?
(Distant rumbling)
(Snarls)
(Man and woman screaming)
[BELL]
Tch... Forgive me,
Goddess!
[HESTIA]
Wha... Ah!
(Snarling)
(Bell panting)
I'm sorry, Bell.
This might be a bad time,
but I just wanted
to let you know
you're making me
really happy!
[BELL]
What the heck are
you talking about?!
(Silverback snarling)
(Panting)
[BELL]
Ah!
Huh?
[BELL]
Thank the gods...
Hyah!
(Grinding stone)
(Snarling)
(Chains rattle)
(Rumbling and growling lessens)
(Sigh of relief)
Well...
it looks like it's
definitely after you.
It won't be long
'til it finds us.
[HESTIA]
Then we'll have to change
our strategy!
You're gonna have to defeat that
big ugly gorilla yourself!
Huh?
I'm gonna update your
Status right now.
That way you'll have
more than enough power
to kill that thing
for sure!
I can't do it...
I may have just had a huge
increase in my stats, but...
but my attacks weren't
even strong enough
to put a scratch on him.
Sorry.
[BELL]
there's just no way
I can win.
It's impossible.
Oh, please.
Since when did
you ever think
you couldn't do
something?
I've always believed
in you, you know.
And I always will.
The Bell Cranel
I know is so busy
drooling over that
Wallen‐whatserface girl...
He doesn't have time
to worry about nonsense.
He knows he can defeat
some stupid old monster!
But, Goddess...
I brought
something for you.
Huh?
(Shink)
This is... uh...
[HESTIA]
It's your‐
no... OUR weapon.
Huh?
It's called...
Hestia Knife!
(Gasps)
It's the key to
winning this fight.
So just go win it!
Have faith in me, Bell.
(Sniffling)
Right!
(Monster roars in pain)
Ngh!
(Crowd cheers)
[LOKI]
Well, that oughta
wrap things up I guess.
Now that we've bailed out
the Ganesha Familia.
(GUILDMAN 1)
Excuse me.
There's one Silverback
still unaccounted for.
And according to the report
of some witnesses,
it chased a young adventurer
down to Daedalus Street.
Oh, Daedalus
Street, huh?
That's a sketchy
part of town.
[GUILDMAN 2]
That's true. The Ganesha
Familia's already sent
their suppression team,
but as you might have guessed,
(Distant roaring)
they haven't been able
to locate it yet.
(Roaring continues)
[LOKI]
Hm? Ah! Hey, can't we
take a breather first?!
Ugh!
(Sniffing)
(Roars)
(Blade unsheathing)
(Resonating)
[HESTIA]
Is this knife
really that powerful?
It is. You can think of it
as a top‐of‐the‐line weapon
meant for adventurers who
are just starting out.
That's amazing!
Just what I would expect
from the Divine Artisan!
Don't think you're getting
some sort of discount
for sweet‐talking me.
Boo...
[HEPHAISTOS]
Look, as a
master weaponsmith,
making something like
this is kinda heresy.
So please don't ask me
for another one.
(Giggling)
Okay!
(Mystical humming)
[HESTIA, THINKING]
Thanks, Hephaistos.
Now...
to find out how much his
Status has increased.
(Chains rattling)
(Rumbling and snarling)
(Sniffing)
(Growling)
(Loud roar)
(Fabric blowing)
(Distant roar)
Hm.
(Mystical whirring)
[HESTIA, THINKING]
Woah!
His total Skill level
is above 600?!
This might work!
[BELL]
Look out,
here it comes!
(Growling)
[HESTIA]
There you go.
(Roars)
(Heavy breathing)
[HESTIA]
It's okay, Bell.
Ah. Huh?
It's like I said before...
I've given you
the key to victory.
(Exhales)
All right.
You believe in me,
right?
Yeah!
[HESTIA]
Then get out there!
Hyah!
(Panting)
[BELL]
Hyah!
Ngh!
(Chains rattle and clang)
[BELL, THINKING]
Wait a second...
[HESTIA]
This is the kind of power
you're capable of!
Use it!
[HESTIA]
That knife I gave you...
it's alive!
And as long as you keep
getting stronger,
it'll grow with you!
Is that... true?
(Growling)
[BELL]
AH!
[HESTIA]
Believe!
Hyah!
[HESTIA]
Believe in your knife!
Believe in
your Goddess!
Hup! Ah!
[HESTIA]
And believe in
yourself, Bell!
Hm...
(Growling)
(Roars)
(Chains rattle)
[BELL]
NGH!
WOAH!
[BELL, THINKING]
I believe.
(Thread straining)
I believe!
I believe.
I BELIEVE!
[BELL]
HYAH!
(Silverback roars)
Hmph.
[BELL, THINKING]
For the sake
of my Goddess!
(Battle scream)
(Roaring)
(Quick breathing)
(Roars)
HYAH!
(Snarling)
(Excited gasp)
Hm.
(Loud boom and fizzle)
(Heavy clank)
Was that me?
YEAH!
(Applause and cheers)
Oh, wow! Did you
see that, son?
[HESTIA]
Oh, Bell! You
really did it!
[BELL]
Ah!
(Both laugh)
Yeah I guess I did,
didn't I?
But I couldn't have done it
without you, Goddess!
Hey, I'M the one who should be
thanking YOU, you goof!
(Bell laughs)
(Bell and Hestia laugh)
Guh!
Aw man, is the
show over already?
[LOKI]
I ran so fast trying
to stay on your tail.
Seems like such
a waste, doesn't it?
(Malicious laugh)
[LOKI]
AH! Guh!
OW! Wait, are
you leaving?!
Come on, we should
celebrate, right?
Maybe go for a drink?
Wow this kinda turned into
a pretty big deal didn't it?
[HESTIA] (Strained)
Yeah... sure did...
Huh?
Are you okay?
You know...
you did...
a really great job...
(Bell gasps)
GODDESS HESTIA!
I suppose I might have
done something
to put Hestia
in harm's way.
[FREYA]
But we'll play again soon.
Won't we?
(Freya chuckles)
It was tough...
but everyone did well!
Lord Ganesha is pleased!
And by the way,
my name is Lord Ganesha!
[ATTENDANT]
We know, Sir...
[EINA]
...however, there have
been no casualties
nor serious injuries to report.
Hmm.
[EINA, THINKING]
But who could have
been responsible
for causing
something like this?
What were they trying
to accomplish?
(Street revelry)
(Footsteps)
Huh?
[SYR]
Hey Bell.
Is the Goddess
feeling alright?
[BELL]
Looks like she was
just exhausted.
Thanks for lending her
a bed and everything,
I'm sorry to be a bother.
[SYR]
Oh no, I'm happy
to help.
And Mama Mia doesn't mind,
so no rush.
You can stay
as long as you like!
Besides, I feel
kinda guilty.
If I hadn't
forgotten my wallet,
then you and your Goddess
wouldn't've had to get involved
in any of this stuff
in the first place.
I'm sorry.
[BELL]
N‐no, it's not
your fault!
Ah! You know what?
Ah?
Everybody's been
talking about you, Bell.
It's because you were
so brave and strong
when you fought
that monster.
Oh, I'm not brave.
I did a lot of
running away...
No, that isn't
true at all!
And, uh,
well actually...
I got to see a little bit
of the battle...
...and I liked
what I saw.
Eh?!
(Syr giggles)
Welp. I'd better get
back to work.
I'll check on
you later, Bell!
I... I think she might've
been messing with me...
(Hestia moans)
[HESTIA]
Bell? Bell?
She's okay!
[BELL]
You have no idea how worried
I was when I saw you collapse.
[HESTIA]
Uh yeah... I guess
I was more tired out
than I thought I was.
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to scare you.
So I talked to
Miss Syr earlier.
And she told me all the
other monsters that escaped
have already been
taken care of.
And I heard
Miss Ais Wallenstein...
she helped out with them too.
(Sarcastic)
Wow... How
'bout that?
Oh, I was
wondering...
Huh?
[BELL]
I was looking
at the knife...
Does that really say
"Hephaistos"... as in...?
Huh!
As in THE Hephaistos!
The one and only.
(Squeals)
Oh...
Oh come on...
I've noticed the way
you've always got your face
all squished up
against her shop window.
[HESTIA]
Now, it may not be exactly
what you were looking for...
But Bell, it's the
only one of its kind
in the entire world.
That's pretty neat, right?
(Breathless)
Listen...
I don't want to just
sit and watch.
I never liked being...
taken care of, y'know?
Or fussed over.
How'd you get this?
Hephaistos Familia weapons
are insanely expensive!
It's all been
handled!
Huh?
You want to
be stronger.
And I want
to help you!
I know it's
not much...
but at least let
me do this, okay?
(Sobbing)
[HESTIA]
There's nothing I want
more than to be the source
of your strength, Bell.
I love you with
all my heart.
Always!
(Still sobbing)
[BELL]
G‐Goddess...
Oh!
Oh, Goddess!
[HESTIA]
Please put your faith
in me forever.
Because I'm
your goddess.
(Cracking rock)
[GEDO]
Hey! Hurry up now,
I don't have all day.
Come on, quit draggin'
your feet.
I swear, why do I
even put up with you.
You haven't accomplished
anything in your
whole life, have you?
I know you haven't
made me any money.
(Thud)
[GEDO]
That's for
damn sure.
Well, if we end up getting
attacked by a monster...
at least I can
use you as a decoy.
So maybe you're not
completely worthless.
(Chuckle)
(Ending Song)
(Jiggle jiggle)
(Bam)
(Snicker)
[HESTIA]
Ugh... are you sure
about this, Hephaistos?
(Groan)
(Hephaistos laughs)
Well of course
I am!
(Stifled laughter)
(Panic)
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Supporter"