(Street chatter)
[EINA]
SERIOUSLY? FLOOR SEVEN?!
But it was only just
the other day
you almost got yourself
killed on level five!
What in the world makes you
think you're ready for seven?!
How insane can
you possibly be?!
Aw! Please, Miss Eina?
I've really grown
a lot since then.
I mean did I tell you my Status
is all the way up to E already?
C'mon...
[EINA]
E?
But, no, that's not...
even possible...
Hmm...
Let's see...
Strength and endurance
are both E.
And agility... D?!
Huh?
[EINA]
You weren't kidding, Bell!
You've been advancing
extremely quickly!
I‐I'm not able to read the whole
thing, but...
Well, your abilities do
appear to be genuine.
So I guess that means
it'll be okay with you
if I go down to floor
seven starting today.
On the one hand, if your Status
is really that impressive,
I have no reason not to clear
you for floor seven, but, um...
[EINA]
On the other hand,
your armor...
Ugh...
Tell you what...
do you have any
plans for tomorrow?
Huh?
(Opening Song)
[EINA]
Bell!
Over here!
Ah. Oh, Miss Eina!
Huh?!
(Eina giggling)
(Bell speechless)
Ah... Um...
Morning.
Wow you got here
pretty early.
Were you looking forward
to spending the day
shopping with me that much?
Ah! Uh!
Uh, no, I'm just...
It's okay, I must admit I was
pretty excited to see you, too.
(Shy exhale)
[EINA]
That's why I got
all dressed up.
O‐oh?
(Giggles)
[EINA]
Uh, Bell?
(Panicked breath)
This is the part where
you compliment my outfit.
Go ahead.
OH! Oh, uh...
it's nice...
You, uh... you look
a lot younger!
Ah!
What?!
Hey, I'm not that old
to begin with, you know!
(Struggling)
[EINA]
You'd better apologize
to me right now, mister!
(Laughing)
Could you please
let go of me?!
(Groan) So, where are
we going today, Miss Eina?
(Giggle)
In there.
Huh?
[BELL]
Babel?
[EINA]
Right. To the
Hephaistos Familia shop.
[BELL]
Wait...
WHAAA‐?!
No way! Their stuff is
so freaking expensive
I can't even afford to THINK
about buying something there!
Would you stop yelling?
You really should
loosen up a little.
Uh! Uh!
M‐Miss Eina!
[EINA](Giggling)
Let's get shopping!
(Elevator dings)
(Doors scrape open)
[BELL]
Hm? Huh?
Ah!
(Amazed laughter)
[BELL]
I had no idea there was a
shop like this in Babel.
This is incredible!
Of course the top of it
attracts the most attention...
but it also happens to be one
of the Hephaistos storefronts.
Let's look around.
Huh? Oh...
WHOA! That says it's
30 million valis!
(Door creaks)
[HESTIA]
Welcome!
[BOTH]
Hm?
What can I do
for you today,
valued customers?
Huh?
Oh!
Bell!
Goddess!
What are you
doing here?!
I know you've been
kinda busy lately,
(Giggles)
but you never told
me anything
about having two jobs!
Uh, well first,
I'd like to know
what YOU'RE doing here!
(Grunts)
AFTER you tell me who
this half‐elf is!
Oh right.
Goddess Hestia,
I'd like you
to meet, uh‐
It is a pleasure to meet
you, Goddess Hestia.
I am Guildswoman
Eina Tulle.
But more specifically...
I am also the labyrinth search
advisor for Mr. Bell Cranel.
Ohh... Is that so?
Uh...
Looky here,
Miss Advisor.
You wouldn't be abusing
your position to try and
seduce my precious Bell,
now would you? Hmm?
Huh?!
(Seething)
[EINA]
Um... I‐I like to
keep business
and pleasure
separate.
[BELL]
Uh...
[EINA]
She's a ... character,
isn't she?
(Awkward sigh)
(Crowd chatter)
[EINA]
Well okay,
here we are.
Now I assume...
you think that all these
high‐quality Hephaistos items
are going to be way out of
your price range, right?
Uh... Well, yeah...
Well, you might
be surprised.
[EINA]
See? Look
at this one.
[BELL]
W‐wow. That's not
that expensive.
(Laughs)
Pretty good, right?
[EINA]
Everything sold
here is made
by novice craftsmen.
It can be sold for cheap,
way below standard prices.
Plus, good reviews
are a big help
for all the beginner
blacksmiths.
Sometimes you can find
a real bargain if you
know where look!
Shall we move on?
(Excited gasp)
[BELL]
Wow!
Woah!
(Both laugh)
I'm gonna go take a look
over there, okay?
Woo!
Oh, Bell‐!
(Bell laughs)
There he goes...
Aha!
Huh?
Oh? Hm.
(Metal clanking)
Ooh...
Hm?
Looks like there's
a signature here.
"Welf Crozzo"...
Let's see... it's...
Huh?! 9,900 valis?!
That's about all
I've got on me.
But still...
(Footsteps)
Ah, I thought you might
find your way back here.
Huh?
I found a couple of good
pieces over by the‐
Uh... Huh?
Check this out!
I think I'm
gonna buy it!
Oh, Bell...
Hm?
I should've known
you'd end up
picking another piece
of light armor.
I‐is that a
bad thing?
It's fine. If that's
what you're looking for.
And if your heart's set
on that particular one,
I think you
should get it.
Hah!
I think so too.
[EINA]
Are you going into
the dungeon tomorrow?
Yeah!
Well, I would really
like it if you would
team up with someone
if you can.
You could at least find
a supporter for me.
Do you think I
should hire one?
Yes! I think it would make you
a more effecient adventurer.
I'd be happy to help you
find one if you want.
Ohh... Well let me
think about it, okay?
Thanks a lot for all
your help today.
Oh, one
more thing...
Hm?
[EINA]
I want you to
have this.
Oh, thank you.
What is it?
It's a present
from me to you.
And don't you
forget to use it.
Huh?! But I can't
accept this!
No, you are going
to take it.
Not just for my sake,
Bell, but for your own.
Huh?
It's a hard life.
Adventurers have no
way of knowing
what day might
be their last.
Huh...
[EINA]
I've known several
who didn't
make it back alive.
Hm...
I don't want to lose
you, too, Bell...
I can't do it.
(Laughs)
I guess maybe it is for
my sake then, isn't it?
Huh? Ah!
Well besides, when I see
how hard you work at this,
I really just want to do
whatever I can to help you out.
Please accept it, Bell.
Please take it.
[EINA]
For me?
(Shy gasp)
Okay, I will...
thank you, Eina.
Well you are
very welcome.
[BELL]
It's getting
kinda late.
[BOTH]
AH!
[BELL]
You okay?
(Weak struggle)
[GEDO]
Just where do you
think you're going,
[BELL] Huh?
you stupid,
pathetic Prum!
Ahh!
(Mystical humming)
(Gasp)
(Bell and Gedo struggling)
[GEDO]
You got a problem?
This mongrel a
friend of yours?
N‐no! I've never
met her before!
[GEDO]
Then why are you
trying to help her?
Huh? Uh, because
she's a girl.
Well...
That's a ridiculous
reason to die.
[RYU]
That's enough.
Huh?!
Please.
Crossing swords within
the city limits...
you two ought
to be ashamed.
And you oughtta keep
your fat mouth shut!
Now beat it
before I have to‐
[RYU]
Be quiet.
Uh...
[RYU]
We should avoid
resorting to violence.
I tend to get carried
away sometimes.
(Angered grunt)
[GEDO]
Skank...
(Sigh)
Now that was
pretty awesome.
Thank you
for saving me.
I probably shouldn't
have interfered.
[BELL]
Oh? Oh,
that girl...
Where'd she... go?
(Gasp)
[BELL]
Must've gotten
scared and ran off.
(Sly chuckle)
Syr would be
extremely upset
if you got
yourself hurt.
[RYU]
Be careful.
Hm?
Uh... right.
Well, goodbye then,
Mr. Cranel.
Thank you
so much, Miss Ryu!
[RYU]
Mhm. Goodnight.
(Straps rattling)
[BELL]
All set!
Hm.
(Chuckling)
Goddess, I'm
heading out now.
Uh‐huh. Okay, I'll see
ya later...
(Yawn)
(Chuckle)
Huh. Hm.
So a supporter, huh?
[LILI]
Mister! Hey, Mister!
You with the
white hair!
Ah! Huh?
A very good day
to you, sir!
Sorry to bother you, but would
you happen to be in the market
for a supporter?
Huh? Hey, uh...
you're the girl
from last night.
Uh, what? I'm sorry you
must be confused.
But it's not really all
that complicated, sir.
Uh.
[LILI]
I'm just a poor,
lonely supporter
offering her services
to an adventurer
who doesn't have
a partner.
Yeah I kinda gathered that.
But, you are...
the prum I met
yesterday, right?
I'm... not a prum.
I'm a chienthrope.
It's like...
an animal person.
Chienthrope?
Well look at that.
Mmm... AH!
That's not
appropriate!
Ah!
Sorry about that.
You just
surprised me.
(Snicker)
[BELL]
So, uh... Liliruca, was it?
Why did you ask me?
Well, it seemed to me like
you were all by yourself.
I mean you're an
adventurer, right,
and you're carrying
a backpack around, so...
I kind of just
assumed, y'know?
Ah.
So have you decided
yet, Mister?
You want me to be
your supporter or what?
To tell you the truth, I have
thought about getting one.
It sounds like a good idea.
Wow, you think so?!
Does that mean you'll take
me with you, Mister?!
Pretty please!
U‐uh!
I don't have much money...
so I wasn't sure exactly
what I was gonna do...
Besides, you do
kinda owe me...
'Cause you touched my
special spot...
And you didn't
get my permission.
U‐uh...
[LILI]
You need to take responsibility
for such behavior.
(Awkward squeal)
(Laughs)
Y‐you've got
a point.
Ah!
I guess maybe
I will hire you
as my supporter then.
But just for today.
You won't
regret this!
(Slice)
[BELL]
EH!
Hyah!
(Monster chitters)
[BELL]
Hng!
Ahh!
(Monster screeches)
[LILI]
Master Bell!
Hng.
(Monster chitters)
[BELL]
Hyah!
Hey, that was
really good!
(Bell sighs)
It's good to have you
here with me, Lili,
now I can concentrate
more on fighting.
[LILI]
Oh, no!
You taking out all
those monsters alone
was way more impressive than
anything I did, Master Bell!
Although, I'm guessing most
of your power
probably comes from that weapon
you're using, doesn't it?
Yeah, you can say
that again.
[BELL]
I'm starting to wonder if
I'm depending on it too much.
Hm...
[LILI]
So, where did you get a
knife like that anyway?
Huh?
Where'd I get it?
Well, the Goddess of my
Familia gave it to me.
Oh, that reminds me, are you a
member of a Familia too, Lili?
[LILI]
Yep. The Soma Familia.
Yeah? That's pretty cool.
Hey, Master Bell.
That one still has
its magic stone.
[LILI]
It shouldn't be
too deep inside.
I'll get the ones that
fell on the ground.
[LILI]
Wanna call it a
day after that?
[BELL]
Sure.
(Struggling)
It's kinda hard
to cut.
(Struggling continues)
[EINA]
Hm...
Wait, you said that your
supporter's in the Soma Familia?
Uh‐huh.
What's wrong with that?
Uh, the Somas mainly focus
on exploration.
And they sell a lot of
booze as well.
[EINA]
Which is fine, but... Uh...
The whole group always
seems to be so desperate.
Like they're always in
a panic about something.
But besides that,
what'd you think of Liliruca?
Did the two of you
end up getting along?
Yeah, she was nice!
[BELL]
We got a good
haul today, too.
Well, that's great.
I won't suggest
otherwise then.
Do whatever you
think is best.
I mean, it's your own decision
to make after all.
Thanks a lot,
Miss Eina.
See ya!
[EINA]
Huh? Bell?
Yeah?
Your knife...
it's gone!
What?
[BELL]
U‐uh? Wha‐?! Uh!
(Panicking)
[BELL]
I DROPPED MY KNIFE!
[GNOME]
Hmm...
I can give you
30 valis.
[LILI]
Ah!
[GNOME]
It's not very sharp.
And it...
won't cut anything.
[GNOME]
The blade's gone
completely dull.
[LILI, THINKING]
You're kidding me!
It cut down all those monsters
without even getting scratched
and he offers me 30 valis?!
That's ridiculous!
Ah!
(Blade resonates)
[RYU]
Wait a second.
You, little prum.
Uh.
[RYU]
Let me see that knife
you're hiding in your cloak.
[SYR]
Ryu?
I want to find out
if it belongs
to someone I know...
who lost theirs.
[LILI]
Uh! Uh, you must
be mistaken...
this is mine.
I'm sorry...
but I can't help you.
Give it to me.
I only know of one knife that's
covered in markings like that.
(Coin rings)
[LILI]
Ah!
And it's not yours!
(Loud thud)
Ah!
(Lili begins running)
(Bell panting)
Ugh... where did I‐?
[BOTH]
AH!
Ow...
Huh? L‐Lili?!
M‐Master Bell?
(Grunt)
[LILI]
Tch.
Hm...
She's a chienthrope?
[BELL]
Miss Ryu?
(Syr Panting)
And you too, Miss Syr?
Oh, hey, uh!
Have either of you guys found
a knife around here?!
It's jet black from
top to bottom
and it's really, really,
REALLY important to me!
(Knife resonates)
[RYU]
Looks like this?
That's it...
My knife...
(Sniffling)
AHAHA!
You found it!
Uh!
Oh thank you so
much, Miss Ryu!
You're the best!
[RYU]
Mr. Cranel,
please...
could you, uh,
stop that?
(Bell awing)
I understand that
you're excited...
Why don't you take
Syr's hand instead?
[SYR]
Ryu, what...
What are you doing?!
[RYU]
Here, take it.
[BELL]
Oh, thank the gods!
(Mystical hum)
Huh?
Please forgive
me, Goddess.
I swear that I will
never drop it again!
You dropped it?
Sure did.
[LILI] Uh.
Where'd you find
it, anyway?
[RYU]
Well, to be precise...
I took it from a prum
who said that she found it.
[BELL]
A Prum?
[SYR]
Ah!
(Chuckle)
[RYU]
Anyway, we should
really be going.
[BELL]
Okay, thanks again!
You shouldn't be such
a naughty little girl.
Ah!
[BELL]
Man! Talk about
great timing!
I was afraid I wouldn't
be able to find you!
Uh!
So uh, Lili...
do you want to go back to the
dungeon with me tomorrow?
(Surprised gasp)
Hm.
(Birds chirping)
[LILI]
Master Bell?
[BELL]
Hm?
Thank you for officially
hiring me.
It really means a lot.
Huh?
Where's your
weapon today?
Don't you usually carry it
right there on your belt?
Yeah! I'm gonna start
keeping it in here now.
That way I won't drop it.
Really?
Anyway, you sure you don't
want a down‐payment first?
Nah. There's only you
and me down here, so...
it won't be too hard to
figure out who gets what.
Besides...
Besides?
I want to do whatever makes
things easier for you,
Master Bell.
Huh?
Are you ready to go?
As long as you
do your best,
I'm sure there won't be
any problems at all!
Uh, right.
[LILI]
I wonder how much loot
we'll get today.
[BELL]
Yeah.
(Cash register rings)
[BOTH]
Twenty‐six thousand?!
I‐I'm not dreaming,
am I?
W‐we really got
this much?!
You're amazing!
Thanks to you,
we made more than
a whole party of five
level‐1 adventurers
would've made combined!
Well, it's like the
old saying goes,
even rabbits can climb trees,
if you flatter them enough!
I have no idea what
that means, but sure,
if you say so,
Master Bell!
Oh, wow!
[LILI]
Let's try to get
even more tomorrow!
Now we just have to decide how
we're gonna split the money...
[BELL]
Oh, here.
Uh.
(Laughs)
I bet I can buy
Goddess Hestia
lots of nice dinners
with all of this.
Huh? Wha‐?
[BELL]
Hey, speaking
of which!
W‐w‐w‐w...
Wanna get something
to eat right now?
Wait... Wait a second!
Hm?
Um... this looks
like it's half.
I don't understand.
I mean, shouldn't you
get a bigger share?
Huh? But why?
I couldn't have made
this much by myself, right?
I mean, you're half
of the team.
Ah!
You were a huge help,
Lili. Thank you.
It's good to
have you on board.
Uh...
(Chuckling)
You're a weirdo.
(Clang)
[SOMA GUILDSMAN]
It's only worth 12,000 valis?!
Are you blind?!
Please tell me this is a joke!
(Sobbing)
[MISHA]
Ugh, not this again.
There's another one of the
Soma Familia members.
God... It's not
gonna be enough!
Just as unstable
as ever.
Bell, please do try to
be careful in there.
(Rumbling)
(Crumbling rock)
Here it comes.
Riveria, please,
allow me to handle this.
Hm.
Ahh...
(Swoon)
Oh, goodness.
I was going to sit back
and just watch for
a little while...
but I simply cannot
help myself.
I must see
it emerge...
The power that now sleeps
so deeply within you...
(Ending Song)
(Street noise and footsteps)
[HESTIA](Sigh)
Another day,
another valis...
I mean, yeah, yeah I know
I owe her money and everything,
but why does she have to work
a poor little Goddess so hard?
Hm... I sure wish Bell
was here with me.
(Bell and Lili laugh)
Huh?
(Hestia laughs)
(Lili laughs)
It is Bell!
Ugh!
(Bell and Lili laugh)
AWHAAAAA!
[HESTIA]
How could he
cheat on me?!
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Grimoire"