[LILI, VOICE‐OVER]
When I awoke... there I was.
Just me, completely alone.
(Bar chatter)
My parents had gone into the
dungeon looking for money,
but they didn't survive
for long.
My entire life has been
one big struggle to survive.
(Gasping)
AH!
[MAN]
Hey!
(Lili whimpers)
[MAN]
You want me to dock your pay?!
Hurry it up! Let's go!
(Weak breath)
(Bar revelry)
[MAN]
Aw. Poor thing.
[MAN] Hyah!
[LILI] AH!
(Man laughs)
Agh...
[MAN]
Just kiddin',
here ya go.
(Gasp)
(Man laughs)
[LILI, VOICE‐OVER]
I was constantly abused,
beaten, and ripped off...
(Quick footsteps)
Whenever I'd run away
or try to hide...
(Lili and clerks chuckle)
Somehow, they always
found me.
(Maniacal laugh)
(Pained breathing)
Uh!
[LILI]
Ah!
(Gasp)
(Flower lady grunts)
[LILI, VOICE‐OVER]
I finally found a place
where I belonged,
and they took it away.
That's why
I hate adventurers.
I really... really... hate them
And I always will.
(Opening Song)
(Flowing liquid)
(Giddy laughter)
MMmmm...
Ahahaha!
Oh man!
I haven't had Soma wine in,
like, FOREVER!
So now then, Goddess,
did I understand correctly that
the members of the Soma Familia
are worshipping wine
instead of the Gods?
[LOKI]
Uh‐huh. That's about the
gist of it, yeah.
And this stupidly
expensive cask...
is actually a
reject batch.
[LOKI]
So the one that
they worship,
is the finished masterpiece
you can't find on
the market anywhere.
Masterpiece?
Uh‐huh.
Now that stuff's
hardcore. Hehe.
One sip, and you're drunk
right down to your soul.
In fact, some people became
part of the Soma Familia
just to get a
little taste of it.
[LOKI]
It's all about
el vino primo.
Really? That's it?
That's the only thing holding
the whole group together?
Exactly.
But in order to make wine,
you need to make money first.
So they offer a little sample
to the adventurers who
rake in the most cash.
[LOKI]
After they try it once,
it's easy to entice them
to work for one more sip.
(Gulp)
Hah...
[LOKI]
They get desperate
for more.
Enough to betray
their friends.
And even sacrifice
each other.
Uh...
[LOKI]
Anyway, that's
all I know about it.
So does that help
you out, Eina baby?
[EINA]
Yes! Thank you!
Thank you, Goddess.
[LOKI]
Hah!
Now come on, Ais!
[LOKI]
How long do you plan on
pouting over some dude
running away from you?
[LOKI]
Let's go update your Status,
shall we?
It'll do you some good.
Fine, if you say so.
(Loki giggles)
[LOKI]
And if you're lucky,
you might get a massage too.
[AIS]
If you try anything,
I WILL cut you.
[LOKI]
Aww, c'mon!
She's certainly is
an interesting one.
Goddess Loki can be
a bit eccentric...
but she is quite clever...
and we have a great
deal of trust in her.
Hm...
Even sacrifice other
people... huh...
[LOKI]
You're at level 6 now?!
Pfffft!
(Thick bubbling)
(Bubbling and boiling)
(Sigh)
[HESTIA]
So then... you're worried about
that supporter of yours?
That's right.
There's this adventurer
who's after Lili
and it looks like
he's pretty bad news.
[BELL]
I thought if we gave her
a place to hide for a bit...
maybe...
It's just that...
[BELL]
Yeah?
I hate to say this,
but, uh...
Are you sure that we can
trust this girl, Bell?
Huh?
I'm sorry,
that wasn't the
nicest way to put it.
But judging by everything
you've told me so far,
there's something awfully
suspicious about her.
[HESTIA]
Think about it, Bell.
Did you really "drop"
the knife?
(Sigh)
And why would there be an
adventurer out to get her?
You see what
I mean, right?
She's hiding
something from you.
I, uh...
Hmm.
[BELL]
Thanks for looking
out for me...
(Street chatter)
[BELL]
Huh? Floor 10?
Yeah! I think you're good
enough to make it down there.
You're tough, so I'm sure
it'll be just fine.
But uh...
you had to save me.
You used your magic knife
back on floor 7,
don't you remember that?
Besides, once you get
that far down...
(Boom)
...then you start to run
into the bigger monsters.
[LILI]
Yeah, but that's not gonna be a
problem for you, Master Bell!
'Cause now you've
got magic firepower!
(Nervous laugh)
Don't worry,
I know you can do it!
And I've been all
the way down to floor 11
so you can take
my word for it!
(Awkward sigh)
(Gleeful laugh)
(Thud)
[EINA, THINKING]
I was planning
to have a talk
with Goddess Hestia
anyway, but...
I had no idea it would be
during my inspection of Babel.
I guess I'll need to do it...
Mix business and pleasure.
But I absolutely must warn her
about Bell's supporter.
Huh?
Hm.
[LILI]
I wanna thank you for taking my
suggestion, Master Bell.
Becoming your supporter
really turned out to be
quite a stroke
of good luck for me.
[BELL]
Yeah, well...
All that aside...
I had to come down
sometime.
[LILI]
Oh, and...
Hm?
I hope you don't think it's
too forward of me, but...
(Sword unsheathing)
[LILI]
I suggest you try fighting
with this from here on out.
You think so?
[LILI]
Yeah.
The weapon you've been
using is gonna be
a little too short
for big monsters..
So this baselard
should work better for you.
[BELL]
Got it.
I'll borrow it Huh?
Hm.
(Tense sigh)
[LILI]
Master Bell?
Ah.
Hm. Hm.
(Clang)
[BELL]
There. We're all set...
You ready to go?
You know it!
You're telling me that I saved
one of your adventurers?
[EINA]
Yes. I'm so glad I got
a chance to thank you.
You see, he was about to be
killed by a minotaur on the
fifth floor,
but then, suddenly,
you came to the rescue.
[AIS]
A Minotaur?
That's right.
Uh, his name is Bell Cranel.
(Ais gasps)
(Speechless)
[EINA]
Uh... Lady Wallenstein?
I, uh... I hope I didn't
scare him, did I?
[EINA]
Uh, n‐no! No!
He's fine!
A‐actually, Mr. Cranel has
been exceedingly appreciative
of everything you did for him!
Ah! Is that true?
Positively!
Oh, well thank
goodness.
[GARNEAU]
So, the twerp's just about
ready to scam that punk kid.
Hm.
The one with the
white hair, huh?
[GEDO]
Yeah. And I'm sure you can
figure out where this is going.
Don't screw this up, fellas.
[GARNEAU]
Yeah, yeah, we got it.
(Laughs)
Hm... So does
that mean...?
[AIS]
Is there
something wrong?
[EINA]
Ah... Hm...
Okay, Your Ladyship.
Please forgive me, but I'm
afraid I need to ask you
for a very important favor.
Hm?
Is this really
the tenth floor?
Yeah... this is
our mission today.
Oh... Hmph.
[BELL]
Stay close to me, Lili.
[LILI]
I will. Thank you.
Hang on,
isn't this...?
Yep. It's a Landform, but...
...I'm afraid we've got
bigger problems right now.
Huh? Ah...
(Heavy footsteps)
(Growling)
(Hearty roar)
That's pretty big,
alright.
Don't turn back now,
Master Bell.
You're absolutely right, Lili.
If I can't defeat an orc,
then I'll be no match for the
monsters we'll face later on.
[BELL, THINKING]
Not even a Minotaur!
(Growling)
(Throaty roar)
[BELL]
That landform!
He's using it as a weapon!
He's coming
this way!
(Roaring)
(Quick breathing)
[HESTIA]
What do you want,
Miss Advisor?
[HESTIA]
You're here on
Guild business, right?
Or are you just talking
to me 'cause you're bored?
This is very important.
It's about Bell's
new supporter.
Hm.
[EINA]
I think she...
I think she's dangerous.
Guh! HAH!
(Orc grunts and roars)
Hyah!
NGH!
(Bones breaking)
[BELL]
HAH! HYAH!
(Orc grunts)
Done!
[LILI]
Master Bell, there's
another one!
Ah? Huh?
[BELL]
Fire Bolt!
(Heavy explosion)
(Orc growls)
(Chuckle)
[BELL]
Fire Bolt!
(Confused grunt)
[BELL]
Whew! Got him!
Looks like we're good!
Ah? Ah...
Lili? Oh don't tell me
they got her!
(Squish)
Huh? Ah‐
(Squishy bounce)
[BELL]
Huh?
Are those Monster Lures?
Why would those
be here?!
(Heavy footsteps)
Huh?
(Growling)
(Roars)
Ngh...
Where'd she go?!
(Roaring)
Ah! Uh!
Fire Bo‐ AH!
Ngh!
Guh... Huh?
(Growling)
GAH!
(Heavy crunch)
Lili! Lili,
where are you?!
(Arrows whistle)
HUH?!
Ah!
[BELL]
Lili?!
What the hell
are you doing?!
Sorry, Master Bell...
I really am.
But this is it for you.
[BELL]
Huh?!
(Orcs grunt)
Ngh!
He told you all about me,
didn't he?
Huh?!
Wh‐what are you...?!
(Orcs growl)
When you get a chance,
do what you can to get away.
Best of luck to you,
Master Bell.
Gah!
(Orc grunts)
Wait! Lili!
(Orcs growling)
[BELL]
Guh! Ngh!
LILI!
[LILI]
He was far
too trusting.
"The clock strikes midnight.
Cinderella."
(Magical humming)
It's your fault, Master Bell.
[LILI]
If only you'd never
run into him.
No, it's better this way.
He's an adventurer, after all.
And adventurers will reap
what they have sewn.
[LILI]
This is a
Hephaistos weapon.
I'll be able to sell it
just about anywhere!
Maybe I'll even get enough to
cover everything else I need.
I am doing this
to free myself.
(Panting)
[LILI, THINKING]
I have got to get out of
this awful Familia!
I don't care
what it takes!
(Goblin grunts and screeches)
(Rapid breathing)
(Footsteps and flowing fabric)
[LILI]
Guh‐ AH!
Huh?!
[GEDO]
Well, well.
(Gasp)
Aren't I the
lucky one?
[GEDO]
Ngh!
[LILI]
Gah!
Ahh!
You're a serious
pain in my ass...
You filthy,
disgusting prum!
Ahh!
[GEDO]
Hmph!
You know you
deserve this, right?
[LILI]
Ngh! Ahh!
(Pained scream)
[GEDO]
I kinda figured
you'd be letting
that kid loose
(Whimpering)
right about now.
All I had to do was wait and
throw out a little net.
[LILI]
A net...?
I mean, there's only
so many paths you can
take on this floor, y'know?
So I only needed to
bring along four men.
(Laughs) But you just
came straight to me,
didn't you, little lady?!
[GEDO]
Now let's see
whatcha got!
(Lili screams)
Argh!
Ah!
Heh heh!
[GEDO] (Laughs)
Alright... this is some
good stuff here!
[GEDO] Hng!
[LILI] Ahh!
You even managed
to grab a magic knife!
[GARNEAU]
Gettin' ready to
take off, buddy?
Oh, back so soon?
You made some good time.
(Quiet shock)
[GEDO]
You believe this worm?
She even got her hands
on a magic knife.
You guys were right
all along. Ha!
She really has been piling
up the goods, hasn't she?
[GARNEAU]
How 'bout that?
That reminds me.
Think you can do me
one favor, Pal?
(Gasp)
I'm gonna need
you to give me
Huh?
everything that
little brat's got!
AH!
Could ya now?
(Monster screeches)
AHH!
What the hell, you idiot?!
[GEDO]
Do you have any idea
what you've done?!
[GARNEAU]
Yep. A wounded killer ant
always sends out
(Ant screeches weakly)
a signal to its kind.
[GARNEAU]
Any good adventurer
should know that.
Heh heh.
(Gasp)
[GEDO]
Unbelievable.
Are you guys freakin' crazy?!
[GARNEAU]
C'mon...
You don't wanna end up dinner
because you were too busy
fightin' with us, now do ya?
(Ants screech)
[LILI and GEDO]
Ah!
[GARNEAU]
Supper time...
[GEDO]
Argh! You bastards!
(Panting)
[GEDO]
AHHHHH!
Eh?!
Hah? Ah!
(Chittering)
(Ants screech)
[GARNEAU]
Uh‐oh.
In trouble again, aren't ya?
But we're all in
the same Familia.
So just gimme what you got...
and you'll be free to go.
Uh!
Unless!
You think you can cheat us
like you did yesterday.
'Cuz if you do... Heh heh...
(Ant head chitters)
AH!
[LILI]
Okay, fine!
You can have it okay?
Hm.
[GARNEAU]
That's a good girl.
[LILI]
My gnome safe
deposit box...
I traded the money for jewels
and locked them in there.
[GARNEAU]
So, that's
pretty clever!
AH!
Hahaha!
[LILI]
Ah! Mr. Garneau...
Have yourself a
little look around.
(Weak whimper)
(Ants chittering)
[GARNEAU]
Not too pretty,
now is it?
Ahahaha!
You know...
you'd make good bait!
NO!
[GARNEAU]
Yeah... Hehehe.
But... but
you said‐
Recognize any
adventurers around here
you made a formal
contract with, kid?
Time you did somethin'
worthwhile.
How 'bout you be a good little
supporter
and support
our asses outta here!
(Lili screams)
(Garneau laughs)
[LILI]
UH!
(Ants screech)
Yeah... well...
[LILI]
What else would I expect
from adventurers?
I guess this is fair,
isn't it?
I mean, it's what I get
for deceiving Master Bell.
But either way...
I don't want to
just give up...
Please, Gods... tell me...
Tell me... why I was
made to be this way.
I wish I didn't have to be
so tiny and so pathetic.
But everything's always
been like that for me.
[LILI, VOICE‐OVER]
I was so lonely.
I just wanted to be
needed by someone.
But it's over now.
I'm finally
going to die.
After a lifetime of
helplessness...
weakness...
worthlessness...
and loneliness.
It's all coming to an end.
Finally, I'm going to die.
[BELL, FLASHBACK]
Lili?
[LILI]
I'm going to die!
[BELL]
FIRE BOLT!
(Concussive explosion)
(Sizzling)
[EINA]
Goddess Hestia,
please understand something.
I strongly implore you to get
that supporter away from Bell!
[HESTIA]
Can't do it.
I‐I'm sorry...?
I'm afraid Bell has
already made up his mind.
(Bell grunts)
Fire Bolt!
[HESTIA]
He said he wouldn't
abandon that girl...
no matter what.
[BELL]
Ngh!
(Whimper)
[BELL, THINKING]
Goddess Hestia...
Despite everything...
If that girl's in danger,
then I want to help her!
(Bell screams)
Hyah!
[BELL]
I can tell she's
really lonely.
GAAHH!
[BELL, THINKING]
Just like I was
before I met you.
(Boom and fizzle)
(Panting)
Hey! That was a close one.
Are you alright?
(Insert Song Begins)
Master Bell...
How did you...
get back here?
Well, it was hard to see
through all that fog...
But it looked like another
adventurer showed up.
After that,
the orcs disappeared.
So I ran straight
for you.
I'm glad I made it
in time.
[LILI]
Why?
Huh?
I want to
know WHY!
Why did you come back and save
me when you know good and well
you should've left me
to die, Master Bell?!
Wh‐wha...?
Oh please, don't tell me
you didn't realize
I was trying to
steal from you!
I tricked you! I led you into
a trap and took your knife
just so I could sell it
and make a little money!
[BELL]
Guh!
What is wrong with
you, Master Bell?!
Huh?
I don't understand!
Are you stupid
or something?!
Are you really
that blind?!
Look. Just calm
down, okay?
I can't!
Huh?
How did you not notice
any of it?!
I pocketed tons of money that
should have been going to you!
You were nice enough to offer it
50/50, but I split it 60/40!
Sometimes I even made it 70/30!
And whenever you would
asked me for items...
I would always tell you
they cost double!
Plus I've said awful and
hurtful things about you
behind your back!
Don't you understand?!
I'm a terrible person!
I'm a thief!
[LILI]I'm a wretched little prum
who's only ever lied to you!
But you... in spite of all of
that you still saved my life!
Mhm.
Why?!
Uh! Uh...
because you're a girl.
My God!
Uh!
I can't believe
you'd say that!
You're telling me
you would save anybody
as long as they
were a girl?!
Now you're nothing
but a philanderer!
A playboy!
Pervert! Creeper!
(Sobs)
[BELL]
Actually... it's 'cause
it was you.
(Gasp)
Really.
That's why I
wanted to do it.
I only did it because
it was you, Lili.
(Crying and sniffling)
[BELL] I didn't
want to lose you.
That's all
there is to it.
You're reason enough.
(Sobbing)
Lili, if you're ever in
trouble, just tell me.
I never told you this...
and I probably
already should have...
[BELL] ...but I will
always be here for you.
(Sobbing)
Oh!
Hm.
[BELL]
It's okay.
(Continued crying)
[BELL]
I'm sorry, Miss Eina.
I didn't mean to make
you worry about me.
And I lost...
that protector.
You mad at me?
No. Just as long
as you're safe.
At any rate,
what's next?
Hm.
Mm...
[BELL]
Excuse me,
Miss Supporter.
(Gasp)
Are you looking
for an adventurer?
Huh? Uh.
Huh?!
You seem to be
a bit confused.
But it isn't really all
that complicated, Miss.
'Cause I'm just a
rookie adventurer
who's looking to find
a supporter.
And I think that you
would make a great one.
Master Bell...
[BELL]
Would you please go into the
dungeon with me again soon...
Lili?
Sure... I'd love to!
(Clang)
I forgot to
apologize again.
Oh?
[AIS]
Isn't that...?
[HESTIA]
Next time:
"Ais Wallenwhatever"