[IZUKU]
It's been two days since Hosu,
and five days since Class 1-A
started our internships.
Because my injuries from Stain
aren't fully healed yet,
I'm stuck at the hospital.
[IZUKU] Everyone on the news is
obsessed with the Hero Killer.
The story being reported
is that seven pro heroes
and three high school
students stumbled upon him.
Then Endeavor rushed in and
took care of the situation
all by himself.
[IZUKU] Of course, that's
just the official cover
from the police department.
[IZUKU]
The chief was true to his word.
Me, Iida, and Todoroki were
never named in connection
to the Hero Killer.
Our injuries were
explained as being caused
by accidents that happened
during our internships.
The day Iida got his
exam results and realized
one of his arms was
seriously damaged,
he ended up going back home
to his parents' house.
so his mom could
take care of him.
Todoroki's injuries
weren't all that bad.
I'm returning to my internship.
Back to your dad's agency?
[TODOROKI] I still wanna learn
everything I can from him.
Besides, they're
saying he defeated
the Hero Killer, even
though it was actually
his son who helped out.
I wanna see if there's
any shame on his face.
[IZUKU] Just when I think you
can't get any more intense,
your dad comes up.
[IZUKU]
Huh.
I wonder how everyone
else is doing.
[BEST JEANIST] It's possible
some villains were inspired
by what happened in Hosu.
That means they could
be feeling bolder.
This may just be a patrol,
but keep your guard up.
Yeah, yeah.
[BEST JEANIST]
Here's a question for you.
Patrols are mainly
meant to deter villains
from committing any crimes.
But they also have
a secondary purpose.
What is it?
If we see some bad guys,
we can beat 'em up on the spot.
[BEST JEANIST]
Incorrect.
Hey, it's Best Jeanist!
Thank you so much
for keeping us safe!
[STUDENTS squeal]
[BEST JEANIST] The answer is:
to remind people who we are.
Our presence gives the
public a peace of mind.
[KATSUKI growls]
[BEST JEANIST] This helps
weave a tapestry of trust
between the protectors
and the protected.
I think you just like
getting recognized.
[BOY 32A]
Hey!
I've seen that
blond guy on TV before!
[KATSUKI] Another fan
from the sports festival.
Yeah, an ooze villain caught him
and he almost cried like a baby!
[KATSUKI]
What did you say?!
[BOYS whimper]
[BEST JEANIST] Have you
really forgotten everything
I've taught you?
Talk with them like a pro.
Yeah. Fine.
Listen up! I wasn't helpless.
I was just coming up
with ways to fight him.
Sometimes a hero has to
pretend he's been caught.
You really think I would lose?
You'll eat those words when
I'm the new number one hero!
You dumb kids'll
never laugh at me again
if you know what's good for you.
[BOYS scream]
[BEST JEANIST sighs]
He has too much pride.
It would be one thing if he
channeled all that passion
toward becoming a hero,
but at this rate,
he could turn out quite poorly.
[BEST JEANIST]
So, then, what do I do with him?
[GUNHEAD] Let's start with
how you'd fight against
someone wielding a blade.
Uravity. Try attacking me.
Are you sure?
[GUNHEAD]
There's no need to hold back.
All right. Here I come!
[yells]
[GUNHEAD] When someone's
waving a knife around,
your best bet's to
keep your distance.
If they attack directly,
plant one leg
and use it to pivot and dodge.
Then, grab their wrist
and back at the same time.
Now you can take 'em down!
See how I did that?
[OCHACO grunts]
[GUNHEAD]
Twist your attacker's wrist
to make them drop their knife.
Make sure you kick it
away for your own safety.
So, easy peazy, right?
[OCHACO grunts]
[OCHACO]
His movements were so fluid.
These Gunhead Martial
Arts are amazing!
He acts cute, but he's fierce!
[GUNHEAD] This time,
how 'bout I hold the knife.
We'll keep on repeating
this until it's second nature.
Sound good?
Yes, sir!
[FANS squealing]
[MAN 32A]
Look over here!
[YAOYOROZU]
Um--
If you work as diligently as me,
maybe you can have
a rabid fanbase, too.
They just love getting
to meet a famous pro.
This is working diligently?
I think she's a little
out of touch.
Giving back to the community
is a big part of bein' a hero.
So don't let me see
you drag your feet!
Understand me?
[TETSUTETSU, KIRISHIMA]
Got it, Mr. Fourth Kind, sir.
I can't hear you!
[BOTH]
Got it, Mr. Fourth Kind, sir!
[DEATH ARMS]
How many hostages?
From what I can hear,
I think only two.
[DEATH ARMS]
'Kay. We're going in.
Earphone Jack, You lead
the hostages to safety.
[JIRO]
Uh, right. Not a problem!
Let's go!
We're pro heroes! Do as we say!
I'll escort you.
Please, come with me!
[HOSTAGE 32A]
Oh, we're saved!
[HOSTAGE 32B]
Thank you, so much, Hero!
[scrubbing]
[splash]
[TSUYU]
Ribbit.
[SIRIUS]
Froppy!
Ribbit?
[SIRIUS]
How's the work going?
I think I'm all done
cleaning the deck.
What now, Sirius?
[SIRIUS] It's kinda
boring having to spend
every day cleaning, isn't it?
[TSUYU]
Eh, a little.
You know, I felt the same way
when I did my internship.
As a kid, I'd always imagined
I knew what it meant
to be a hero.
It turns out, the reality
is very different.
I always figured
being a hero would be
super glamorous,
but then I discovered
it was a lot of patrols
and cleaning up.
I even had to do
laundry, which meant
washing the captain's underwear.
I had to ask myself what
I was even doing here.
So you got tired of it?
At first, yeah.
But, after becoming
the captain's sidekick,
I figured something out.
I realized what was
actually important
when it came to being a hero.
Oh, really? What was it?
Will you tell me?
Oh, it'll be better if you
find it out for yourself!
Don'tcha think?
Ribbit.
[SELKIE]
Hey, Froppy!
Why're you just sittin' there?
Shouldn't a frog be jumpin'
to get her work done?
And I thought I told you to
keep on top of her, Sirius.
Don't you slack, either.
I've finished cleaning
the deck, Captain, sir.
And I'm totally
supervising her properly.
Ribbit.
Oh, is that right?
Guess I jumped to conclusions.
Sorry about that ladies.
I apologize--my bad.
Forgive me?
[SIRIUS, TSUYU]
Uh...
[laughing]
I'm too cute for words,
aren't I, Froppy?
[SIRIUS]
Yeah, she's dumbfounded.
I know I always say this,
but trying to look cute
like that doesn't work.
The rest of your physique
is just too macho!
[SIRIUS]
Your face is pretty rugged, too.
What did you say?!
When I make that sweet face
for kids, they eat it up!
[SIRIUS]
Of course.
Because they're actually
making fun of you.
Trust me--there's
nothing cute about it.
[SELKIE whines]
[TSUYU]
Adorable!
Captain Selkie, sir.
An urgent message has just
come in from the Coast Guard!
I hear ya! Comin' now.
Froppy.
Will you help me
unfasten the ropes?
Looks like we're sailing out.
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
Selkie here.
[SIRIUS]
Hey, you're good at this!
[BOTH grunting]
I see. 'Kay, we're on it.
[SIRIUS]
The ropes are pulled in!
Hear that, sailors?
Emergency departure!
[SUBORDINATES, SIRIUS, TSUYU]
Aye, aye, sir!
[SELKIE]
Full speed ahead!
Good work!
The Oki Mariner is on the move!
[SIRIUS]
So, what are we dealing with?
[SELKIE] The Coast Guard
got a tip that there were
stowaways on the
trade ship, Nysan ,
but things may not
be what they seem.
Officials inspected
the ship, but they didn't
find any stowaways
hiding on the vessel.
Upon further investigation,
though, they discovered
that important cargo from the
ship's freight list was missing.
I'm sure you all know
what that means.
What do you think, Froppy?
It's likely that, before
the Coast Guard arrived,
the stowaways moved the
cargo to another ship
somewhere close by and fled
the scene of the crime.
In fact, it's possible
that the stowaways
had plants on the ship.
Correct!
[SUBORDINATES, SIRIUS]
So embarrassing.
[TSUYU]
Adorable!
It's our job to
find these criminals.
Based on the information
we have, they probably
escaped on a small boat.
We will deliver them
to the Coast Guard!
Considering the
Nysan's position,
this is the general
location that would make
the most sense as
an escape route.
Authorities and other
sea rescue heroes
are also searching for them.
We'll be focusing on
this area. Take note.
[SELKIE]
The sun will set soon.
That means you'll be searching
for the boat via radar.
I'll take to the ocean
and look for them myself.
That's all.
Got it? Let me
hear ya, sailors!
--[SUBORDINATES] Aye, aye, sir!
--[TSUYU] Ribbit!
[PRESENT MIC]
Sea Rescue Hero, Selkie!
His Quirk: Spotted Seal!
He can do pretty much
anything a spotted seal can.
That includes making a
sonar-like sound and using
its echo to determine the
position of his opponent.
He's also very strong!
[SELKIE] They aren't
anywhere around here.
Guess I'll have to
widen my search!
[TSUYU] As expected, I can't
see anything in the darkness.
And we haven't seen anything
on the radar yet, either.
[SIRIUS]
Never fear.
Huh?
Don't forget: the captain's
looking for them, too!
[SUBORDINATE 32B] Incoming
message from the Coast Guard!
A fishing boat thought
to belong to the stowaways
has shaken off a hero
agency patrol boat.
It was last seen
headed toward the area
that we're in charge
of searching.
Captain!
I've confirmed the location
of the missing fishing boat
we've been looking for.
This is our chance.
Turn off the lights
and get close without
letting them know where we are!
--[SUBORDINATES] Aye, aye, sir!
--[TSUYU] Ribbit!
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
Captain. We found the boat.
I don't think
they've spotted us.
[SELKIE]
Good.
I want you to block their
course with the Oki Mariner
then board their vessel
while setting off a flair.
[SUBORDINATES]
Aye, aye, sir!
[TSUYU]
What should I do?
You stay here.
Ribbit?
[SELKIE]
Sirius. You're with her.
[SIRIUS]
Yes, sir!
But how can I learn if I
don't get any experience?
Just be quiet and do as
I say, intern. Let's go.
[SUBORDINATES]
Aye, aye, sir!
Ribbit...
You wanna go with them,
Froppy, I know.
I get it. But you
know something?
Thing is, even though
we're only up against
some stowaways, this
could still be dangerous.
So we have to follow
the captain's orders.
We'll support them together!
Ribbit.
Captain.
We've impeded their
intended course as ordered.
[SELKIE] All right. Then you
can leave the rest to me.
[SELKIE] This is a
pro hero. Stop your ship!
We're here on behalf
of the Coast Guard.
We will now inspect your vessel!
[SUBORDINATE 32A]
Captain!
I looked for the missing cargo,
but I didn't find anything.
Yeah, same here.
See, what'd I tell ya?
You'll find nothin' but
humble fishermen aboard.
[thud]
[SELKIE] Then, you can show us
what's inside this, too.
Can't you?
[FISHING BOAT CAPTAIN 32A] It's
just a bunch of fish down there.
Then open the hatch
and let's see.
[KARASU]
What a pain.
[TONBI]
This is pointless.
It's too dark to see
anything clearly.
Can't you turn on the lights?
[ALL yell]
I did exactly what you said.
So please. There's no
reason to kill me.
Oh, we won't kill ya.
Don't worry!
[splash]
I think we bought some time.
It'll be easier
for Boss Innsmouth
to do what he needs to do now.
I think this means our
job here is complete.
[BOTH]
See ya!
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
Captain!
Captain, please respond!
It's no use--we've lost contact.
I'm going over there!
Hold on!
[PRESENT MIC]
Sirius! Her Quirk: Good Ear.
She can hear high frequencies
that normal people can't detect!
[SELKIE clicking]
"The stowaways."
"Different boat"!
[BOTH gasp]
[SIRIUS]
"We're fine. Find them!"
Go. Start the ship!
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
Right!
Ribbit.
[SIRIUS] If that boat was
a decoy, then the stowaways
are probably heading
toward the shore.
Hurry!
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
We're going full speed!
Shouldn't we rescue the
captain and the others?
The captain is relying on us
to follow his orders.
If we believe in him, then we
trust in his course of action.
Do you have faith, Froppy?
In the captain and in us?
Right there!
Hiding in the shadow
of those rocks!
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
Damn it.
This won't be easy.
Cut the engines and
approach their blindspot.
Yes, ma'am!
Whaddaya say--
you in this with us?
Ribbit!
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
There's someone keepin' watch.
[SIRIUS]
Froppy.
Can you bring the
guard over to us?
[TSUYU]
Leave it to me.
[yelps] What's happening?
No, no, no!
You guys, we're--
If you answer our questions,
then we won't have to
get rough with you.
[TSUYU]
Ready.
[SIRIUS]
Do it.
[SIRIUS] There's only one
other person on this cruiser.
He's hiding out
in the main cabin.
[SUBORDINATE 32B]
I can take care of him.
[yells] My eyes!
Watch out!
[SUBORDINATE 32B groans]
[SIRIUS]
Froppy!
[yelps]
Sirius!
[INNSMOUTH cackles]
I've got you now.
A villain!
And here I thought
I'd gotten away with it.
But you idiots just won't
give up, now will you?
Ribbit.
How sad.
A girl and some kid are all
that's left to stop me?
[yells]
[grunting]
[INNSMOUTH]
Uh-uh, not so fast.
I'll give her back just as soon
as the Coast Guard
calls off their search.
But first, you're gonna help
me unload the cargo, got it?
[SUBORDINATE 32A]
Sorry.
[INNSMOUTH]
Huh?
[SUBORDINATE 32A]
Our transmission was blocked,
and we're still stuck
on the fishing boat.
The captain made it out.
How're things on your end?
Tell me your status.
Please respond!
So this is actually
a radio, huh?
Here you go, kid.
If you value this woman's life,
then repeat after me.
"Unfortunately, we weren't able
to track down the stowaways."
[gasps]
Froppy! Don't do--
Sirius!
[INNSMOUTH]
Hurry up, now!
Oh, I see. You don't care
what happens to
your friend here.
Come on. Get to it.
Well?
[SIRIUS] I realized what
was actually important
when it came to being a hero.
The captain is relying on us
to follow his orders.
If we believe in him, then we
trust in his course of action.
Do you have faith, Froppy?
[TSUYU]
I get it now.
[INNSMOUTH cackles]
[SIRIUS grunts]
The stowaways are
at the double rocks!
[SIRIUS]
Thank you, Tsu.
[INNSMOUTH]
You stupid little brat!
I'll kill you!
Stop jumping around
and stay still, dammit!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
[INNSMOUTH]
Oh, yes! I've got you.
[TSUYU grunting]
[TSUYU]
Ri...
[INNSMOUTH]
This is the end, Froggy.
[INNSMOUTH cackles]
You're just a helpless child.
But since you came
here uninvited,
I'll have to teach
both of you a lesson.
[TSUYU]
Ribbit...
[INNSMOUTH yelps]
[TONBI, KARASU grunt]
Boss!
My brothers!
[INNSMOUTH gasps]
Ribbit!
[TSUYU]
Captain!
Sorry for being late.
Leave the rest to me!
[INNSMOUTH]
Think again!
[clicking]
[SELKIE]
Even if I can't see...
...I know where you are.
You can't hide, villain!
[INNSMOUTH]
You bastard!
Captain!
[INNSMOUTH groans]
It's over!
The captain's amazing!
[SIRIUS]
Froppy!
Ribbit.
Are you all right?
Did he hurt you?
I'm okay. But what about you?
Well, thanks to you,
I'm still here.
You two did a great job here.
Thanks to you,
we caught the stowaways.
[groans]
Captain.
Thanks so much!
You really are hopeless.
[TSUYU] Sirius, I'm really
glad I had the chance
to come to this internship.
[SIRIUS]
Huh?
I think I get it now.
What's important when
it comes to being a hero.
And it'll definitely
help me become a pro!
Well, that's nice.
[COAST GUARD 32A]
Arrest all the stowaways.
We were able to recover
all the illegal drugs
they were trying to bring in.
It was a big haul.
By the way.
You didn't tell me that you
got a new sidekick, Selkie.
Ribbit?
She's a UA student.
Here for an internship.
Well, you don't say.
We put you through
something scary today, huh?
I'm sorry.
[SELKIE] Hey, now.
Don't treat her like a kid.
Froppy may not have
her license yet,
but she's an excellent hero.
I'd stake my name on that.
Well, then, I guess
I can look forward
to working with you again.
Hope to see you soon, Froppy.
[TSUYU]
Ribbit, ribbit.
[IZUKU]
All Might!
I'm finally back
from my internship!
[ALL MIGHT]
You went through a lot
in the Hosu incident, huh?
I'm sorry I wasn't
there for you.
[IZUKU] All Might,
what do you have to tell me?
[ALL MIGHT]
The time has come for me
to be completely honest.
About myself, One For All,
and the mission
entrusted to you.
[IZUKU]
Next time:
"Listen Up!
A Tale from the Past."
[ALL MIGHT]
It's a super important episode
you're not allowed to miss!
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Plus Ultra!