[IZUKU] We'll pass Hosu City.
I wonder how Iida's doing there.
[BOTH gasp]
[PASSENGERS screaming]
Nomu!
I want ya to stay
back, you hear me?!
[IZUKU]
Gran Torino!
[TRAIN CONDUCTOR]
Everyone, please! Remain calm!
Return to your seats!
The villain is no longer here!
More heroes will
arrive soon, I'm sure!
[IZUKU]
Keep them calm.
I'm going after him!
[TRAIN CONDUCTOR]
Hey, are you nuts?!
It's way too
dangerous out there!
[IZUKU] He looked different, but
there can't be that many people
with wild eyes and
brains spilling out.
Maybe Nomu's brother?
What is he doing in the city?
No time for detours or stairs.
Gotta put my training
to the test.
[IZUKU]
One For All... Full Cowling!
I've totally got this.
[IZUKU]
Gran Torino. Please be okay!
[MAN A]
A villain! Run!
Where are all the pros?
[howling]
[WOMAN screams]
I haven't fought this
earnestly in years.
Picked a fine time to patrol.
That's right! Bring it on, ugly!
[GRAN TORINO] He's fast.
But not faster than me.
[MAN A]
No, stay away! Ah!
[GRAN TORINO]
He's attacking at random.
Stop it, you stupid beast!
[ENDEAVOR] I was looking for
the elusive Hero Killer,
but this thing will have to do.
Thanks, old timer.
I'm afraid I don't know you,
but I can handle this
from here on out.
[GRAN TORINO]
It's you.
Whoa, look!
Why's he in Hosu?
[ENDEAVOR]
Hmph.
Isn't it obvious?
I came because I'm a hero.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[IZUKU] They're probably at
the center of this craziness.
I don't get it. Why did
that guy look like Nomu?
If he's got insane
power like the one
All Might fought at the USJ,
this could be really bad.
It won't just be Gran Torino
in trouble, but the entire city!
That includes Iida.
He's interning here!
Crap, what do I do?
Come on, think.
How do I be the best
possible hero right now?
[MANUAL]
Tenya!
[gasps]
[MANUAL]
Where are you, Tenya?
[crash]
[GIANT NOMU roars]
[IZUKU]
Oh, no. What are these things?
Manual! Stop the fire!
[MANUAL]
Yeah. Got it!
[IZUKU]
That's Manual. The Normal Hero!
Iida's at his agency!
Why'd run off by yourself?
Where the hell are you,
Tenya? Dammit.
[IZUKU] Wait, he went off alone?
Despite what's happening?
That doesn't sound like
something he'd do.
You're in the way, kid.
Get out of here.
Right. I'm so sorry!
[HERO A] We can hold these
things back on our own.
Evacuate with everyone else.
[MANUAL]
I could've used the extra hands!
[IZUKU] I can't believe
Tenya would run off
with such a huge disaster
right in front of him.
Hosu City... Guys who
look like Nomu...
Iida... Hosu...
Where the Hero
Killer attacked...
Don't tell me...
[HERO A] Dammit.
What are these things?
They're way too powerful!
[HERO G]
Watch out, Fly!
Crap! What do we do now?
[HERO G]
Are these really men?
Or are they actual monsters?
[SHIGARAKI] The Nomu make
such great play things.
[KUROGIRI] Are you not going
to participate in the fight?
[SHIGARAKI] Don't be stupid.
I'm still injured.
That's why I brought
those pets with us.
Master, how many
Nomu are completed?
[MASTER] I've finished adjusting
the behavior of six of them.
Though, they are not as strong
as the one from the USJ attack.
[SHIGARAKI]
Give them to me.
[MASTER]
Why?
[SHIGARAKI] Because I
don't like that arrogant
Hero Killer you brought in.
And it's my right
to destroy anything
that I don't like,
right, Master?
[MASTER] Very well. However,
you may only have three.
Try to use this as a
learning experience.
[SHIGARAKI laughs]
[SHIGARAKI]
Once this night is over,
the world will have forgotten
you ever existed, Hero Killer.
[STAIN]
A child wearing a suit.
Who are you?
[TENYA] I am the brother
of an incredible hero
who you attacked.
He's the best older brother
that anyone could hope for.
I have come to stop you.
Because he can't anymore.
[INGENIUM] I want you to take
the name. For me, Tenya.
You're going to remember my
name for as long as you live.
I am Ingenium, and I will
defeat you. That, I promise!
[STAIN]
Then so be it. Die.
For Tensei!
[STAIN]
Ingenium. So you're brothers.
I let him live so he could
spread the good word.
Word of me.
You're a weakling.
Just like he was.
You aren't heroes. You have
no right to be called that.
Both of you are
nothing but fakes.
[TENYA]
Shut up, villain.
You damaged his spine
and paralyzed him
from the waist down.
He's never gonna be able
to work as a pro hero again.
My brother was incredible.
A caring person who
saved many lives.
Someone people looked up to.
You had no right to take
that all away from him!
[TENYA'S DAD]
Tensei. I'm so proud of you.
You've become independent
at a very young age,
with many sidekicks
following you.
That's no easy feat
in these times.
Nah, they're not followers.
It's the opposite, Dad.
They support me 'cause
I'm not great on my own.
They're just looking out for me.
I honestly couldn't do
anything without them.
I need their support.
Of course, I'm working hard
so I can return the favor.
I'm not super
talented or anything,
but if I'm going to
call myself a hero,
then I have to live up to
that title and help people.
[TENYA]
He is my hero.
My older brother
inspired my dream
that one day I could
be a pro, too!
I won't forgive you.
I'll kill you!
Shouldn't you be worried
about saving that guy?
[STAIN] So busy with your
grudge you forgot about him.
You plan on using your
Quirk only for yourself.
You're completely blinded by
a selfish desire for revenge.
You're about as far away from
being a hero as I can imagine.
And that's why
you'll die tonight.
[TENYA]
My body... won't move!
[STAIN]
Goodbye, child.
May your death bring
about a better world.
No, please! Not like this!
Knowing you look up
to me makes me better.
I have to be sure
I make you proud.
[laughs]
Say whatever you
want to about me!
You're still just a criminal
who hurt my brother!
[grunts]
[IZUKU]
Smash!
Who's there?
Midoriya? How?
Don't you worry, Iida.
I'm gonna save you.
[IZUKU]
I might be overthinking things.
I don't exactly have any proof.
But I can't just stand by.
I have to do something!
Guys like Nomu
are running wild.
The same place the
Hero Killer appeared.
I don't want to even imagine it,
but I'm afraid I might be right.
The League of Villains
and the Hero Killer
are connected somehow!
That means...
The Hero Killer is probably
somewhere in the city
this very moment.
Since Iida wasn't
at the fight earlier,
he may've stumbled upon the guy
who hurt his brother himself!
[gasps]
[yells]
Guess I was right!
[STAIN] It's him. The one
from Shigaraki's picture.
You found him, too? But how?
I saw it on TV.
They had some stats
about the Hero Killer.
Most his victims were found
where there weren't many people.
So in order to find you,
I needed to search far
away from the panic.
In the back alleys of Hosu City.
Let's go.
Back toward the street.
We have to get
help from the pros.
Ugh. I can't move my body.
[IZUKU]
Huh?
It must be his Quirk.
Since he cut me,
I've been paralyzed.
That's the kind of
Quirk people on TV
said the Hero Killer might have.
So cutting somehow
activates his power, huh?
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU]
There's someone else!
If it had just been Iida,
I could've picked him up
and carried him away myself.
[TENYA] Midoriya, please!
Don't get involved.
This doesn't have
anything to do with you!
Iida, what are you saying?
You showed up to save
your friend's life.
You even made a big entrance.
But I have a duty to kill him
and this so-called pro.
When your friend
chose to fight me,
it guaranteed that the weaker
of us would be culled.
So what will you do?
Criminals like you--
You always try and make
your actions sound noble.
[IZUKU] He's different from the
villains who attacked us before.
Those are the eyes of a fanatic.
[IZUKU] Even though
it was just a guess,
and I didn't have any proof,
I should've made sure that a
pro came with me to find him.
I'll just have to protect
these two who can't move
and stall for time...
all by myself.
Maybe I can even force
the Hero Killer to run.
[TENYA]
Listen to me!
Stand down. Run away.
I told you, this has
nothing to do with you.
[IZUKU]
If you really believe that,
then why are you trying
to become a hero
in the first place?!
There are plenty of
things I'd like to say,
but they'll have to wait.
All Might was right, though.
Meddling when you don't need to
is the essence of being a hero!
Heh.
[STAIN]
Good.
[IZUKU]
Gotta get past the sword.
[STAIN] Trying to get in close
so I can't strike him.
Smart move.
[TENYA]
No! If you get cut--!
[IZUKU]
Watch the blades!
[STAIN]
He's gone?
No.
A five percent...
Detroit... Smash!
[TENYA]
What? These movements.
He's flying around,
like Bakugo does.
[IZUKU]
Did I get him?
Did Full Cowling work?
Yes, I really can fight!
[IZUKU]
My body!
[IZUKU] Did he cut me and
I didn't even notice?
One graze is all it took?
[IZUKU]
No. It's... the blood!
[STAIN]
You're not powerful enough.
It's not that you
predicted my movements.
You just left my
field of vision,
and maneuvered so that you'd
be able to get in a clean shot.
But I saw through your plan.
There are countless false heroes
around here who are all talk,
but I think you're worthy
of staying alive.
You're different from these two.
Wait, don't. Stop it!
Get away!
Someone else to get in my way.
Today's been full
of distractions.
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya,
you need to give more
details in times like this.
I was almost too
late to stop this guy.
[TENYA]
You, too, Todoroki?
[IZUKU]
How'd you get here?
Hold on, you're using
your left side?
[TODOROKI]
How'd I get here? Good question.
Your message took me
a while to figure out.
Next time, try to send more than
just your specific location.
But you're not really one
to send cryptic messages
without a reason, are you?
[TODOROKI] So I figured you were
in trouble and asking for help.
Everything's okay. The pro
heroes will be here any minute!
[STAIN] The time will be up
for one of them soon.
[TODOROKI] You're just
what they said you were.
But you won't be taking
any more lives, Hero Killer.
[IZUKU] Todoroki! You can't
let that guy get your blood.
I-I think he controls
his enemy's actions
by swallowing it.
That's how he got us!
He ingests blood to keep
people from moving.
That explains the blades.
All I've gotta do
is keep my distance.
[STAIN]
Ya have good friends, Ingenium.
Or you did!
[TODOROKI]
His sword!
He threw it at the same
time as the knife!
[TODOROKI]
He's strong.
Just stop it.
Why are you doing this?
His fight is with me!
I inherited my brother's name.
I'm the one that should stop
him. The Hero Killer is mine!
[TODOROKI]
You're Ingenium now? Strange.
The Ingenium I knew before
never had that look on his face.
You've got a dark side.
Guess my family
isn't the only one.
[grunts] Careful, Todoroki!
Uh. Huh?
[STAIN] Ya blocked your
own field of vision
against an opponent
who's faster than you.
Rookie mistake.
Come get me then!
[STAIN]
You're good, kid.
Unlike him.
[TODOROKI]
Watch out!
Midoriya!
I'm not sure why,
but I'm able to move now!
So he has a time limit.
[NATIVE]
No.
That kid shoulda been
the last one to be freed.
I still can't move a muscle.
[STAIN]
He must be type O.
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya, dodge!
[IZUKU coughing]
He swallows a person's
blood to freeze them,
but I was the one freed first.
I've got three
different guesses why.
His Quirk could
be less effective
the more people he uses it on.
The amount ingested could
play into how long it works.
Or there could even
be a difference
based on a person's blood type.
If it's the last one,
my blood type is B.
[TENYA]
I'm type A.
So you figured it out.
Bravo. Very impressive.
[PRESENT MIC] Hero Killer Stain!
His Quirk, Bloodcurdle!
By tasting someone's blood,
he can freeze them for
up to eight minutes,
depending on their blood type!
From shortest to longest time,
it's O, A, AB, and B!
It doesn't really
help us that much
to know how his
Quirk works, though.
I thought we could hurry and
carry those two out of here,
but it's no good.
He's too fast. He can
dodge ice and fire.
I'd have to leave
myself unguarded.
Our best option is to hold
until the pros arrive
and avoid close combat.
No, you know you've already
lost way too much blood.
I'll distract him while you
support me from behind.
Sound like a plan?
You want us to take
a pretty big risk.
Okay.
We can protect them!
Two against one, huh?
This fight won't be easy.
[TODOROKI]
Iida.
I've been worried about you
ever since your
brother was attacked.
I recognize the face of someone
who's drowning in resentment.
[TODOROKI]
And I know just how narrow
your field of vision can get
when you long for justice.
That day, I told her about
my life with Father,
and about who I have become.
She cried and apologized.
She forgave me.
Faster than I ever imagined.
She told me to move forward.
That nothing was
holding me back,
and that doing so
would be her salvation.
If I hadn't spoken to her,
I would never have been able
to choose my old man's agency
for my internship.
I couldn't bare being near him.
I haven't forgiven him.
I doubt I ever truly will.
But I chose him,
so I could learn what it takes
to be the number two hero
with my own eyes and ears.
I had to know.
[ENDEAVOR]
Get ready. We're going out.
Yeah, okay. Where to?
[ENDEAVOR] If the Hero Killer
is following his pattern,
we know where
he'll show up next,
and we'll be there to stop him.
We're taking a
work trip to Hosu.
[ENDEAVOR SIDEKICKS]
Yes, sir!
[TODOROKI]
My old man is a scumbag.
But a scumbag with the
judgment and instincts
of a number two hero.
And I can acknowledge that.
It's so simple.
But I still needed
someone to show me.
It's yours! Your Quirk, not his!
[TODOROKI] Just a few words.
Two short sentences.
Shouldn't you be worried
about saving that guy?
Don't you worry, Iida.
I'm gonna save you.
[TODOROKI]
We can protect them!
[TENYA]
I'll kill you!
[STAIN grunts]
[IZUKU]
No good.
His fighting style has
completely changed!
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya!
[TENYA]
You have to run.
I can't watch this.
You wanna make
your brother proud?!
[TODOROKI]
Then stand up and be Ingenium!
Become the hero he
wanted you to be!
[TENYA] I am Ingenium,
and I will defeat you.
That, I promise!
[IZUKU]
Now, the preview!
[TENYA]
Stand down!
I told you, this has
nothing to do with you.
[IZUKU]
If you really believe that,
then why are you trying
to become a hero
in the first place?
[TODOROKI]
I've been worried about you
ever since your
brother was attacked.
[IZUKU]
All Might was right, though.
[TODOROKI]
And I know just how narrow
your field of vision can get
when you long for justice.
[IZUKU]
Meddling when you don't need to
is the essence of being a hero!
[TENYA] I have no right
to call myself a hero.
Even so, there's no
way I can back down.
If I give up now, then
the name Ingenium will die.
[IZUKU]
Next time: "Climax."