[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
with 80 percent of us possessing
some uncanny ability.
Cities swirled with
chaos and confusion
following the appearance
of these powers,
and a new profession emerged.
We call those who
fight for justice
and help other
in need, "heroes."
Oh, by the way,
this is the story
of how I became
the world's greatest hero!
[PRESENT MIC]
Welcome to the first match
of the finals tournament.
It's Izuku Midoriya from
the hero course, versus,
Hitoshi Shinso from
general studies!
The rules are simple:
Immobilize your opponent
or force them outta the ring!
You can also win by getting
the other person to cry uncle.
[sighs]
[SHINSO]
So you can just give up, huh?
[gasps]
[SHINSO]
In a way, this is a test
of how strong your spirit is.
If you know what you want
your future to hold,
you can't worry about
what other people think.
[PRESENT MIC]
Ready?
That monkey was going on
about his pride earlier.
[PRESENT MIC]
Begin!
[SHINSO]
But I just think he's an idiot
for throwing away
his chance like that.
[gasps]
[growls]
Don't you talk about Ojiro
that way, you hear me?
[SHINSO]
That's it. I win.
[groans] I warned him
not to say anything!
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
[PRESENT MIC]
Huh?! Hey, hey...
Come on, Deku!
Why in the world
isn't he moving?
[PRESENT MIC] It should
start out with a bang!
[PRESENT MIC]
The fight has just begun
and Izuku Midoriya is...
completely frozen?
He's not moving a muscle!
And what's with that
look on his face?
Could this be a Quirk at work?
Hitoshi Shinso seems
to have Izuku Midoriya
completely stunned!
[PRESENT MIC] He didn't stand
out in the first rounds at all,
but it's possible
Shinso's crazy powerful!
Who could've imagined
this turn of events?
That's the Festival
for ya! [laughs]
[AIZAWA]
This is a perfect example of why
the entrance exam
isn't rational.
[PRESENT MIC]
Huh? Why's that?
[AIZAWA] Since we're on
to the individual matches,
I had some information compiled
about our final competitors.
Shinso failed the practical exam
to get into the hero course.
Since he also applied
for general studies,
he probably figured
that would happen.
His Quirk is incredibly strong,
but that entrance test consisted
of fighting faux villains.
Robots.
It gave a huge
advantage to those
who had physical superpowers
they could show off.
[AIZAWA] Despite his
abilities, Shinso never
stood a chance at passing.
[SHINSO]
So here we are.
You're lucky to have been
so blessed, Izuku Midoriya.
Now turn around and
walk out of bounds
like a good little hero.
[PRESENT MIC] Uh-- What?!
Ah! Midoriya's obeying him!
Oh, no, Deku,
what are you doing?
He can't walk out of the ring!
He'll lose the match if he does!
[ALL MIGHT]
What is this power?
[PRESENT MIC] Hitoshi Shinso!
His Quirk: Brainwashing!
When an opponent
answers his question,
it flips a switch
in their minds,
forcing them to do
whatever he says.
Not every question
does it, though.
He only brainwashes
when he wants to.
Not very flashy...
[AIZAWA] In the fitness test
on the first day of school,
Midoriya scored pretty
low for a student
who'd been accepted
into the hero course.
Still, even in tests where
he didn't use his Quirk,
he outperformed Shinso.
If they fought without powers,
Midoriya would almost
certainly win.
But he'd have to overcome
Shinso's Brainwashing
to do that.
Either way, this match
will be over quickly.
[ALL MIGHT gasps, yelps]
What are you doing, kid?
Get back in there and show
'im what you're made of!
[IZUKU]
What's happening?
My body's moving on its own.
I feel like my brain
is full of fog.
I can't concentrate.
No! Not like this.
Gotta stop! Dammit!
I fell for it,
even after Ojiro warned me
about his power. I'm an idiot.
This is all my fault!
[gulps] So his Quirk is that
he can control other people?
Can I beat something like that?
Yes. By not giving him
a chance to use it.
He didn't get into
my head until I answered
a question he asked me
before the second round.
I think that's the
secret behind his power.
So I have to be careful
not to say anything
or I'll lose for sure.
[OJIRO]
Not exactly.
Even if he gets you,
there's still a chance.
For round two,
I don't remember anything at all
except the very end
of the battle.
[OJIRO] I think we were
running away after Shinso
took Tetsutetsu's headband.
I bumped into another person,
and it was like I woke up.
[gasps]
[OJIRO]
I was me again.
And suddenly I was
able to think clearly.
So that bump broke his hold?
[OJIRO]
Maybe. It's only a guess.
Still...
I don't know how much
of a shock it would take
to break his spell.
And in a one-on-one
match, you can't count
on an outside force
intervening to help you.
Anyway, man, I hope
that's helpful,
'cause it's all I know.
Thank you so much.
You're a good guy, Ojiro!
I know this sounds selfish,
but I'll say it anyway.
Beat this guy for
you and me, all right?
I'll do my best!
[IZUKU]
I can't stop it.
[IZUKU] I'm going to lose.
It's all over.
[IZUKU]
Even though...
...so many people
are counting on me...
Everyone is watching...
Everyone!
[IZUKU]
What... is... that?
Wait.
[SHINSO]
Even with a Quirk like this,
I have my own dreams
of becoming a great hero.
[SHINSO]
So, lose for me.
[gasps, pants]
[PRESENT MIC] What's this?
Midoriya stopped just in time!
[CROWD cheers]
That's the way to do it!
Whoa. I was about to freak out!
[AIZAWA gasps]
His fingers.
He broke them in order
to stop Shinso.
Whew, that just
about killed me.
No. Impossible.
You're not supposed to
be able to fight back!
What did you do?
[IZUKU] I'm the one
who used One For All.
But I'm not the one who
moved my fingers just now.
It was like people I didn't
know came into my mind.
And for a second,
it was clear.
Could it be--
[ALL MIGHT]
One For All.
A sacred torch that's been
passed on from person to person.
[IZUKU]
Those people.
Were they the ones
who cultivated this power?
Did they save me?
Is that even possible?
How'd you do that?
[IZUKU]
Later.
I don't have time to
figure things out right now.
I have to focus.
[SHINSO]
He won't answer.
Did he figure it out?
No. He's known.
That monkey must have told him.
I have to get him to talk again.
Come on, say something.
I didn't know you
had so much power
in your fingers. I'm
kind of jealous of you.
[IZUKU] I know what
that jealousy feels like.
I've been there.
Thanks to the way
my Quirk works,
I've always been at
a big disadvantage.
But someone as blessed as you
wouldn't understand that.
[IZUKU]
I get it.
Even though he's right.
I have been blessed.
You're lucky enough
to have a heroic Quirk!
It'll be so easy for you
to reach your goal!
[IZUKU]
I've been blessed by others.
That's why I'm here!
Say something, dammit!
[IZUKU]
I can't lose this.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
I'll do it for them!
[SHINSO]
He's pushing me out.
[groans]
[SHINSO]
You've gotta be kidding me!
Get out of this ring,
you lucky brat!
[yells]
[IZUKU] No. I refuse
to let this be the end!
[MIDNIGHT]
Shinso is out of bounds!
Midoriya advances
to the next match!
[CROWD cheers]
Whoa!
Your Quirk is brainwashing?
That's so cool!
[STUDENT 20B]
Seriously!
I can't think of anyone
who's had that power!
I'm so jealous, Shinso.
Imagine all the cool stuff
you could do controlling people.
Yeah, you can do any
bad thing you want.
And no one would
ever know it was you.
Just promise you won't
make us your slaves, okay?
[SHINSO] Heh... Everyone
always says that.
[SHINSO]
Of course.
I'd probably think
anyone with my power
would use it for evil, too.
"Sounds criminal, Shinso."
"It's the perfect power
for a villain to have."
I'm used to people looking
at me like I'm the bad guy.
But you know what?
[SHINSO]
I'm not.
[PRESENT MIC] And with that
expertly performed throw,
we have our first
victor of the finals!
Class 1-A's Izuku Midoriya!
[CROWD cheers]
[sighs] Ugh, that was
so nerve-wracking!
[TENYA] Turning the tables
at the last moment--
a classic Midoriya maneuver!
He's pulled that shoulder
throw on you before, huh?
Shut your damn face, Sparky.
[KATSUKI]
That jerkwad.
He's definitely
aiming for the top.
And that purple-haired
guy fell for his trap!
[AIZAWA]
He focused his power like he did
in the fitness test, and used
the throw from combat training.
It's not just that he's
learning from his experiences:
he's using every trick he's
picked up to improve his odds.
[PRESENT MIC]
Oh, yeah!
That was actually kind of
a boring first match, kids.
But both of you fought bravely.
Let's show them
some love, everyone!
[applause]
[SHINSO]
Someone as blessed as you
could never understand!
It'll be so easy for you
to reach your goal!
Why do you wanna be a hero?
What's driving you?
[SHINSO grunts]
I'll be a hero.
[SHINSO] You can't help the
things your heart longs for.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
I felt the same way.
Before I inherited One For All,
I was just like him.
[IZUKU] But, nothing I say is
going to make him feel better.
[STUDENT 15A] You were
awesome out there, Shinso!
[gasps]
We're proud a' you!
You didn't tell us
you were that good!
Yeah, you're the star
of our program!
I can't believe you
put up such a great fight
against the dude who was
in first place earlier!
[STUDENT 15A]
Listen to them!
With a Quirk like that,
it would be very simple
to capture dangerous villains.
Wish I had it.
[HERO 20B]
I can't believe they stuck him
in General Studies.
Those idiots.
Well, there are a ton
of applicants each year.
Guess sometimes people
slip through the cracks.
[HERO 20E] If only he had
more combat experience.
[HERO 20D] Yeah, I bet
he would've dominated.
[HERO 20E]
What a waste.
Shinso, you hear that?
It's great! They think
you're incredible!
[SHINSO]
Depending on the results,
they might transfer people
into the hero course.
Remember that.
Even if it didn't
work out this time,
I'm not giving up.
I'll get onto the hero track,
get certified, and then,
I'll become a better
pro than any of you.
[IZUKU inhales]
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU gasps]
He got me again!
But why? The match is over!
[SHINSO chuckles] You know,
usually people tense up
whenever they talk to me.
If you're not on guard,
someone's going to defeat you.
So be careful.
[gasps]
[SHINSO] You better not lose
and make me look bad.
[IZUKU]
Shinso...
I won't!
[IZUKU gasps]
[RECOVERY GIRL]
Mmmmwah! That should do it.
[IZUKU]
That match with Shinso--
I couldn't smile
through it like you would.
[sighs] I heard some of
the things he said to you.
It must've been painful,
knowing how much you
could relate to him.
Yeah. But I still
couldn't go easy on him.
I have to keep
my eye on the prize.
Aiming for the top.
Just like you've said.
[sighs] You poor little darling.
Have you been putting too
much pressure on him again?
[ALL MIGHT groans]
It was necessary, and that hurt!
[IZUKU]
Oh, yeah. All Might!
[ALL MIGHT groaning]
[IZUKU] I had... some kind of
vision in the match.
There were... people.
Maybe eight or nine
of them? I'm not sure.
When I was under
Shinso's control,
it felt like my brain was
full of fog or something.
But when the vision appeared,
it completely drove
the fog away.
That's when I was finally
able to move for a second.
Just my fingertips.
[IZUKU]
One of the figures had eyes
just like yours, All Might.
Do you think all
the people who've used
One For All in the past
were there, pushing me on?
Like spirits?
Spooky. I'm a ghost?
Huh?! I thought
you'd have answers!
[ALL MIGHT] Actually, I saw
something like that, too.
In my younger days.
Uh?
It's a clear sign
that you're getting
closer to making One For All
your own power.
What was it?
I think it's like a trace
of the user's spirit
that's left behind in One For
All when it's passed on.
Don't worry.
Whatever you saw,
it won't be interfering
with you or your progress
in the future, I'm sure.
In other words, that vision
wasn't what got rid of
the brainwashing effects.
Regardless of what
you saw out there,
it was your passion that
allowed you to overcome
Shinso's power, even if
it was only long enough
for you to wiggle
your fingertips
and expel some energy.
Man, that explanation
is so not satisfying.
Forget about it!
More importantly,
shouldn't you be worrying
about who you're fighting next?
Huh?
You're right.
Thank you both very much!
[RECOVERY GIRL]
You're welcome.
[IZUKU]
Goodbye!
[RECOVERY GIRL]
So, he saw you there, too.
That's a good thing.
[TODOROKI]
Of course Midoriya won.
What do you want?
You're acting
disgracefully, Shoto.
[ENDEAVOR] If you simply used
the power in your left side,
you would've had an
overwhelming victory
in both of the first rounds.
It's time to stop
this childish rebellion
of yours. You have
a duty to surpass
that imbecile All Might.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
You're different
from your siblings.
You're my greatest masterpiece.
[TODOROKI] Is that all you have
to say to me, you bastard?
I'll win this match and advance
using only Mom's Quirk.
I won't give you the pleasure
of seeing me use yours.
Even if that works for
you in this tournament,
you'll soon find the
limits of that power.
[OCHACO]
Ah! There you are, Deku!
You did good!
Come on down here--
we saved a seat for you!
Ha! Thanks, guys!
[PRESENT MIC]
Enough standing around.
Now welcome to the ring,
our next players.
[PRESENT MIC]
He's got skills!
But at the expense of some
really creepy-looking elbows.
From the hero course,
it's Hanta Sero!
That was uncalled for.
[PRESENT MIC]
Versus, an early frontrunner
in the competition
who's way too strong
for his own good!
Someone who rightfully
got into the hero course
based on recommendations!
It's Shoto Todoroki!
[PRESENT MIC]
And now, for the second match
of the finals.
--[PRESENT MIC] Ready?
--Well, I don't really feel
--Begin!
--like I can win this fight.
But, man--
I don't feel like
losing, either!
[PRESENT MIC] That attack
could throw his opponent
out of bounds!
A brilliant, surprise
opening from the underdog!
Way to start off strong, Sero!
Apologies.
[SERO gasps]
[RECOVERY GIRL]
Is that... an earthquake?
What the heck is goin' on?
Was that--?
[ALL gasping]
[DEATH ARMS]
Holy crap.
[pants]
[ENDEAVOR]
Hmph.
[SERO]
Um...
Don't you think
you went overboard?
Tell the truth, Sero.
Can you move at all?
Are you kidding? Obviously not.
My body is freezing!
[MIDNIGHT]
Sero has been immobilized!
Todoroki advances
to the second round!
Um. Well, nice try!
Nice try!
[AUDIENCE]
[HERO 20H]
Nice try!
[AUDIENCE]
Sorry about that.
It was a bit much.
I was angry, is all.
[IZUKU] As the crowd
shouted, trying to make
Sero feel better,
Todoroki took a moment
to melt his opponent
from the ice prison
he'd created.
[IZUKU] For some reason,
in that moment,
he looked very sad to me.
[ALL MIGHT]
Surprise! The preview is here!
[IZUKU] It's the UA Sports
Festival finals tournament,
where 16 players will clash
in a battle of wits,
Quirks, and pride!
[ALL MIGHT] It's still anyone's
game at this point.
[IZUKU]
Even so--
[ALL MIGHT]
The only ones who can win
are those who train
diligently every day
and cling to their dreams
of becoming heroes!
Come on, kiddoes, show us
what you're made of!
Do your best and act
like real pros!
[IZUKU] Next time:
"Battle on, Challengers!"
[ALL MIGHT] Young Iida
is manipulated by a girl
and ends up humiliated!
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Plus Ultra!