[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
with 80 percent of us possessing
some uncanny ability.
Cities swirled with
chaos and confusion
following the appearance
of these powers,
and a new profession emerged.
We call those who
fight for justice
and help others
in need, "heroes."
Oh, by the way,
this is the story
of how I became
the world's greatest hero!
[MIDNIGHT] Forty-two of you
qualified to move on.
Now, gird your loins and
prepare for a Cavalry Battle!
Izuku Midoriya placed
first in the qualifier.
He'll be worth
ten million points!
[MIDNIGHT] It's survival of
the fittest, with a chance
for those at the bottom
to overthrow the top!
[TENYA] Bakugo and Todoroki
have challenged you already,
but they aren't the only ones
who see you as a rival.
I'll try my best to defeat you.
[IZUKU]
You ready?
Yeah!
[IZUKU]
Hatsume?
[giggles]
[IZUKU]
Tokoyami?
Yes.
Let's do this.
Take this!
Stupid bird!
I told you to call me "Tsu."
[yelps]
[IZUKU]
Kacchan!
[KATSUKI] Don't think for
a second you're safe.
[yelps]
[KATSUKI]
I've got you!
Tokoyami!
--[DARK SHADOW growls]
--[KATSUKI grunts]
[pants]
I'll be taking that, now.
[MINETA whimpers]
Normally, I wouldn't
have teamed up with you,
but this was a good plan.
So, I'm not sure how
you lost your headband.
Where the heck did it go?
This just means there's
nothing left to lose!
Shoji! Full-on attack mode!
[MINETA] We'll use all our
powers to steal the points
from those two teams!
[TOKOYAMI] I didn't think this
confrontation would happen
until later in the contest.
He seems to have it out
for you, Midoriya.
The game's only halfway over.
We can't stop now!
Now, Iida. Forward!
[TENYA]
Right!
[TODOROKI] Yaoyorozu.
Be ready to protect us.
[YAOYOROZU]
On it!
[TODOROKI]
Kaminari--
Oh, I know what I gotta do.
Uh... Watch our surroundings.
It's not just Todoroki.
Everyone's after us!
[KAMINARI] I hope you made
something strong, Yaoyorozu!
[KAMINARI] Indiscriminate Shock.
1.3 million volts!
[yelps]
[DARK SHADOW screams]
[STUDENT COMPETITORS yelling]
[JIRO]
Kaminari!
Less than six minutes left.
It's time to make a move.
[TODOROKI]
Sorry, but there's no other way.
[PRESENT MIC]
Will you look at that!
He's stopped all those
teams cold in their tracks!
[AIZAWA] But only after
Kaminari had immobilized
the students using
his electricity.
In the obstacle course,
he was surprised
by how many people
avoided his attack.
He's adapting his strategy.
[PRESENT MIC]
Nice commentary!
[gasps]
[TODOROKI]
I might as well take these.
[growls] Come back!
[HIRYU]
What? Mine, too?
The jet pack's malfunctioning!
Baby! Guess it needs
some upgrades.
[OCHACO]
Oh, no, they're too fast!
We can't get away!
Take care of them.
Yaoyorozu!
She's too good at
her Creation Quirk.
We have to be careful.
[TOKOYAMI]
No. Kaminari is the one to fear.
If there was any more sunlight,
Kaminari's attack
would have completely
destroyed Dark Shadow.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] So what I want you to do
is devote yourself to defense.
I'm hoping you won't
have to attack at all.
Sound good?
[TOKOYAMI]
Hmph. Interesting.
Ah--
[TOKOYAMI] My Quirk's offensive
ability gets stronger
when I'm in darkness.
But, that makes
Dark Shadow aggressive
and difficult to control.
On the other hand,
the beast is easy
to handle in the sunlight.
That's at the cost of its
attack power, though.
You couldn't have known this,
and yet you've chosen
the correct role for me.
Your proposal seems
like a good one,
under the circumstances.
Very well. I'll
follow your lead.
We're counting on you. Midoriya.
I get it. His lightning
is our big problem.
[TOKOYAMI] As long as he
keeps using his Quirk,
it will be very difficult
for me to attack.
Dark Shadow is too
timid in the light.
[DARK SHADOW whimpers]
Violence solves nothing.
[HATSUME, IZUKU yelp]
[PRESENT MIC] Team Midoriya
has nowhere left to run!
[IZUKU]
Your attack power is low,
but they have no idea
that's the case, right?
[TOKOYAMI]
I don't think so.
The only person I've
mentioned this weakness to
is Koda back at the USJ.
And he's a man
of very few words.
Okay, good deal.
We can use that.
[IZUKU]
This'll work out.
All we have to do is hang on
to the ten million points,
no matter what!
Your class is too
small minded. Think bigger.
He got us!
What'd you say? Come back here!
Oh, hey. You're
kinda famous, huh?
For being attacked
by that sludge villain.
You'll have to tell me
about it sometime.
It must be strange
to always find yourself
in the role of the victim.
Kirishima, we have
a slight change of plans.
[MONOMA]
Hm.
[KAIBARA]
Monoma. Don't provoke him, man.
That's the kinda thing
he would do.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's not very heroic of me.
Besides, you know how
these things work.
Heroes are always being hounded
by moronic villains desperate
for some kind of revenge.
Calm down, Bakugo.
You've gotta keep a level head
or we'll never
get our points back!
[KATSUKI roars]
[KATSUKI]
Shut up! I've never been calmer.
Can't you tell? Now get
after them, Kirishima!
Please don't make
us regret this.
[KATSUKI]
You think you're tough?
Die!
[grunts]
Huh. Wow. I see why
you like this Quirk!
[KIRISHIMA grunts]
My power...
Whoa, weird! That guy
has your Quirk!
[growls] Damn it!
[MONOMA]
You both have impressive powers.
But I think you'll
agree mine's better.
[gasps]
Huh? What? Mine, too?
Bastard.
His Quirk.
He can copy other powers.
Very good.
[PRESENT MIC]
Neito Monoma. His Quirk: Copy.
He can use the Quirks
of whomever he touches,
but only for five minutes.
Plus, he can only
borrow one at a time.
So even an idiot
could figure it out.
[growls]
[KATSUKI yelps]
Nice one. Thanks for
the backup, Bondo.
[KAIBARA]
Monoma.
If we keep those
headbands, we're good.
As long as no one gets near us,
we'll make our class proud.
Stop 'em!
[KIRISHIMA]
It's too sticky! Crap!
I can't move.
[ASHIDO]
No prob!
I'll melt through this
gunk with my Quirk!
Well, hurry! We're sitting
at zero points now!
[MONOMA]
Oh, no hard feelings, right?
After all, you provoked us.
What was it you said in your
little speech before the games?
Uh...
Oh, right. Oof.
I just wanna say I'm gonna win.
[KATSUKI] This isn't over. I'm
still gonna come out on top.
And I won't just make it
to first place--
I'll be the undeniable champion.
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC]
Only one minute left!
Todoroki has cornered
the ten-million-point team
and is poised to seize
the ultimate prize!
At least, that's what
I would have predicted
five minutes ago!
[PRESENT MIC] Unbelievably,
Team Midoriya's been able
to keep away from the ice master
for the last half of the game!
[IZUKU]
Stay back!
[ALL MIGHT]
You're doing good, kid.
He's exploiting your weaknesses.
Don't be a fool.
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya is keeping his distance
and staying on my left side.
That's his strategy.
From this position if I try
to freeze them, I'll hit Iida.
If he keeps moving like this...
There's no way I can get
a clear shot at his team.
[KAMINARI]
I'm not...
--...done yet.
--[TODOROKI] Plus, Tokoyami
[TODOROKI] can defend against
Kaminari's electricity.
There's not much time left.
[TODOROKI]
The bastard!
Everyone, we have
less than 60 seconds.
I'm gonna do something that'll
make me useless to you.
What are you gonna do?
Make sure you get that headband.
Brace yourselves. Hold on tight!
[TENYA]
Torque Over--
[grunts, yelps]
Watch the--
[TENYA]
Reciproburst!
[gasps]
[PRESENT MIC]
Wha-ho-ho! What just happened?
That was one big blur!
Holy smokes, folks!
Why didn't he show off
that super speed
in the preliminaries?
Iida. What was that?
Forced my torque
and RPM into overdrive,
which gave me explosive power!
Unfortunately, the recoil
stalls my engines for a while.
It's a secret move
I've been saving.
No one in the class
knew about it.
I told you, Midoriya...
...that I'd do
my best to beat you.
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC]
Insanity!
This entire game was just
turned completely on its head!
Todoroki's team has
the ten million points,
and Midoriya's team is suddenly
left with nothing at all!
[IZUKU]
Don't let them go!
Kaminari's still
a problem for us.
It'll be smarter for us
to try for other points now.
We can't!
We don't know who's got
the other headbands.
This is our only chance!
[OCHACO]
Then let's go!
We'll get the points
back, Deku. I know it!
Uraraka...
[OCHACO]
I'm gonna become a pro.
I'll sign with a good agency
and make plenty of money.
Then my parents will
have an easy life!
[IZUKU]
That's right.
I'd like to use your fame
to my personal advantage!
[IZUKU]
I'm not alone in this.
We're counting on you, Midoriya.
[IZUKU] All three of them
put their trust in me.
This is my responsibility.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] We all have our
reasons to win this,
and I refuse to let
the others down!
[PRESENT MIC]
With time almost up,
Team Todoroki is in first
place with four headbands.
Despite their best efforts,
Team Midoriya has
fallen to the bottom!
Will these be the top four teams
that move on to the next round?
[MONOMA]
Second place.
We've done pretty
well for ourselves.
Now, we can let
the clock run out.
[KATSUKI]
Losers! Get back here.
[MONOMA groans]
Doesn't he ever give up?
Knowing you've been bested
is an important part
of being a hero.
Hey, don't just
fly off on your own!
Tsuburaba! Stop him!
A'right!
[PRESENT MIC] Kosei Tsuburaba.
His Quirk: Solid Air.
He can harden the air
to form walls or steps.
The bigger the breath,
the stronger the shield!
You look pretty stupid
fighting with air.
[KATSUKI yells]
[MONOMA]
Crap, he snatched some of 'em!
[PRESENT MIC]
Team Bakugo nabs two headbands
and moves into third place!
The final moments of the game
have been full of shakeups!
Oh, to be young again!
[PONY yelling]
[KAMAKIRI]
Tsunotori!
[BONDO grunts]
Damn it!
We're still in
fourth. It's fine.
Kendo's been frozen and
hasn't been a real player.
Yeah.
If we defend this one to
the death, we'll move forward.
I told you to warn us
before you jumped!
[KATSUKI grunts]
Whatever, this means
we're advancing.
We're not done!
[SERO]
Huh?
We're gonna be the indisputable
champions of the game!
[AIZAWA]
Now, look at this.
Class 1-B's strategy
was a reasonable one,
but there's one thing
they forgot to consider.
[KATSUKI] I couldn't brace
myself earlier when I jumped.
Get closer!
We'll get our points
back from this idiot,
then go for the big one!
Heh.
[gasps]
Do it.
Elbow guy. Tape 'im!
My name's Sero!
[MONOMA]
You missed!
[KATSUKI]
Raccoon eyes!
Lay down some acid in
the direction we're going.
It's Mina Ashido!
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Bakugo.
You understand
something crucial,
a truth no one had to teach you.
[ALL MIGHT]
But there's a difference between
those who aim for the top,
and those who will settle.
[ALL MIGHT]
And that difference matters.
[AIZAWA] Class 1-B didn't
take into account Bakugo's
overwhelming tenacity.
[PRESENT MIC]
Bakugo is a merciless force!
What a point hog!
That was a shield break
heard 'round the arena,
and I can't wait
to watch the replay!
Now! We're going after
Deku and Todoroki.
[IZUKU] It was the first
time I used my power
against a person.
[IZUKU]
This'll be fine.
I'm not actually
going to hit him.
I'm just slicing through
the air to take out
my opponent's defenses!
[TODOROKI]
My left side. What am I doing?
[IZUKU] My hand hurts,
but it's not broken!
He's turned the bands around
to hide their point values.
But he put the ten million
one on last, right?
So it must be on top!
[IZUKU]
I've got it!
That's it. I did it!
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC]
With just 11 seconds left,
Team Midoriya's
back in the game!
Uh, wait a minute.
Please tell me I got something
wrong with my eyes.
[IZUKU]
They tricked us.
We mixed the headbands up.
There's no way we'd
leave the prize on top.
You underestimate us.
Todoroki. Better watch yourself.
That was too close!
[PRESENT MIC]
Oh, no!
Team Midoriya didn't get the
ten million points after all!
[IZUKU]
Only 70 points. It's not enough.
The game is almost over!
Time for a countdown!
[buzzer sounds]
Tokoyami!
[TODOROKI]
Kaminari!
Deku!
Bakugo!
Ah...
Uraraka!
Let's go!
Yaoyorozu!
Who's got the points?
Dammit, Icy hot!
[PRESENT MIC]
Time's up!
And with that, the second round
is officially over!
[grunting]
Bakugo!
Are you okay, man?
Damn it.
Now, let's take a look at who
our top four teams are!
In first place, Team Todoroki!
We ended in first place,
but it was too
close for comfort.
I'm sorry. I let
everyone down, didn't I?
That's not true.
You're the reason we won.
Thank goodness for that
special move of yours.
[PRESENT MIC]
In second place, Team Bakugo!
Ugh. We were so
close to first place.
Meh. Sure.
But we're movin' on,
so it's all good.
I don't think our leader
would agree with you.
Like, at all.
[screams]
[PRESENT MIC] In third place
is Testute-- Wait, what?
It's Team Shinso? When did
they come back from the dead?
Thanks for all your help.
[HATSUME whines]
[OCHACO]
Hey, Deku.
[IZUKU]
Guys, I'm... really sorry.
[HATSUME, OCHACO]
Huh?
[TOKOYAMI]
I must apologize.
When Todoroki was shaken
by your first attack...
[TOKOYAMI] I tried to grab the
ten-million-point headband
but things didn't go as planned.
[gasps]
[TOKOYAMI]
Still, I got one.
It was around his head, where
his guard was the weakest.
Midoriya. You're the one who
created the opening for me.
And ensured our advancement.
[PRESENT MIC] And in fourth
place is Team Midoriya!
[IZUKU screams]
[PRESENT MIC] These four
valiant teams will advance on
to the final round!
[sighs]
[IZUKU screaming]
[TODOROKI] I said I'd
never use this to attack.
But as soon as
I was overwhelmed,
I broke my own promise.
At this rate, he'll
win and I'll end up
exactly who he wants me to be.
[PRESENT MIC] Now, let's
take an hour lunch break
before we start the
afternoon festivities!
See ya soon!
Hey, Eraser Head.
Let's grab some food.
[AIZAWA]
I'm taking a nap.
[PRESENT MIC]
Whew.
What the hell just happened?
Suddenly we had zero points
and it was all over.
Maybe it was some
sort of karmic punishment.
For taking the tiny one's
headband. It was so underhanded.
[MINETA] No, what happened?
All my points are gone!
[TETSUTETSU]
No fair! I want a do-over!
How disappointing.
Mina. Congrats.
Thanks, but Bakugo
only asked me to join
because I could
melt Todoroki's ice.
It's not, like, you know,
I really helped that much.
Iida, you were
holding out on us.
I had no idea you could do that!
Rest assured it wasn't
my intention to deceive you,
I was just being strategic.
Uh heh, heh!
I merely wanted to show
that I could
compete with Midoriya.
[OCHACO] You're always trying
to one-up each other.
Oh, speaking of which,
where'd he go?
Has anyone seen Deku?
You brought me here. Now what?
[ALL MIGHT]
Yo! Long time no see!
Let's catch up, Endeavor.
[ENDEAVOR]
All Might.
[TV NEWSCASTER 14A]
And now, updates
from the UA Sports Festival.
The first years have finished
their second round.
That means we know which
16 next-generation heroes
will be moving on to
the final tournament!
Izuku, my baby!
I'm so proud of you!
You worked so hard for this!
But please, son.
Don't get hurt
in the final round!
[IZUKU]
It's the preview!
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya, you've got All Might
in your corner, helping you out.
I don't know what that's all
about, but know this for sure.
I am going to beat you.
[IZUKU] Todoroki, why do
you have it out for me?
[TODOROKI] I don't really care
what you are to All Might.
[IZUKU] Your eyes are
like ice! It's so creepy!
[TODOROKI]
I will go higher than you.
[IZUKU]
You can say that, sure,
but I have my own reasons
for reaching the top!
Next time: "The Boy Born
with Everything."
[TODOROKI] The girls from
our class will cheer
and cheer and cheer some more.
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, TODOROKI]
Plus Ultra!