[buzzer blares]
[ANNOUNCER 34A]
Team Asui and Tokoyami.
Practical Exam: Ready...
Go!
[ECTOPLASM] Maybe you didn't
understand, but we teachers
are trying to crush you
with everything we've got.
No holding back.
[ECTOPLASM]
Steel your nerves...
...and show me your resolve.
Get her.
Dark Shadow!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
Asui. Your turn!
Got you, Tokoyami!
[TOKOYAMI grunts]
I'm glad we made
a plan beforehand.
Yes.
Nice!
An escape only the two
of them could pull off!
[RECOVERY GIRL]
That's good communication.
They're talking to each other.
It may not seem like much,
but it's important.
I don't just mean
having a sidekick
or teammate that you know
you match well with.
Real heroes need to be able
to communicate with anyone.
Um, so...
We were talking about these
finals and how each student
is supposed to be
facing their weaknesses.
That's right.
Okay, so, what do
Tokoyami and Asui
have to work on? I'm
having trouble seeing how
Mr. Ectoplasm's Quirk is a
bad match-up against theirs.
Oh?
Well, it's not good...
for Tokoyami, at least.
Huh? Why do you say that?
[RECOVERY GIRL]
Keep watching, you'll see.
[ECTOPLASM] So you've
chosen to avoid a fight.
Good luck.
[PRESENT MIC]
Ectoplasm. His Quirk: Clones!
He shoots weird
ectoplasm from his mouth
and turns it into
copies of himself.
He's able to produce
30 at one time.
Though, apparently, after
about his second or third
song at karaoke, that
number goes up to 36!
[DARK SHADOW]
Now!
[DARK SHADOW grunts]
[TSUYU]
Gotcha!
Thanks!
[DARK SHADOW grunts]
Dark Shadow!
There's no end to them!
Let's keep moving.
[gasps]
[RECOVERY GIRL]
Tokoyami is quick and can attack
from afar, allowing him
to keep his distance.
Those are all strengths.
But, looking at
that another way,
it means he's weak
at close range.
Wow, I never thought about
his powers like that.
And Mr. Ectoplasm's
clones can appear
anywhere unexpectedly.
On the other hand, there's Asui.
A stellar student with
no clear weaknesses.
She can provide
support to her ally,
as powerful as he may be.
But she's important
in another way, too.
Her level-headedness
and ability
to provide emotional support
are the key to them passing.
Emotional support, huh?
[IZUKU]
Now that I think about it,
having her around
during the USJ attack
really helped us stay focused.
I'm rooting for you,
Asui and Tokoyami.
Beat him!
[TOKOYAMI]
That was clone number 28.
Tokoyami, look. It's the goal.
Which means that's probably
his real body down there.
[ECTOPLASM] Excellent job
getting past the others.
But tell me--what will
you do against this?
[ECTOPLASM]
Just try to escape.
Giant Bite Detention!
[BOTH gasp]
[ECTOPLASM] I can't put
out more clones now.
But as long as I
have you captured,
this one is all I need.
Asui! Look out!
[BOTH gasp]
[ECTOPLASM] Only I can
get rid of this behemoth.
So what is your plan?
This Quirk is way too powerful.
[DARK SHADOW]
Hey, so am I.
Dark Shadow.
You just have to
get through that gate!
[DARK SHADOW]
I'm on it!
[yells]
[DARK SHADOW]
Dammit!
I don't think he has
a chance against a real pro.
[TSUYU]
Well, if he can reach him,
we do have a chance.
Call Dark Shadow back.
I have something
for you to give him.
Asui, what do you mean?
[TSUYU]
Please... Don't watch me.
Mr. Ectoplasm will notice.
And besides, it's...
...really gross
to see me do this.
[TOKOYAMI gasps]
[ECTOPLASM]
Will you keep this up until
time runs out, little bird?
What I want to see is
a student who can do away
with an adversary,
no matter what!
[TOKOYAMI]
Dark Shadow!
Calm down. We've got this.
[TSUYU] Because Tokoyami
and Dark Shadow are heroes!
[DARK SHADOW yells]
[TSUYU] I figured this was
the only way we could win
if he managed to
capture us somehow.
So I swallowed the cuffs.
My Quirk lets me take things
in and out of my stomach.
[ECTOPLASM]
How unexpected.
[OCHACO]
Whoa, they legcuffed him!
Then they passed!
They figured out a way to do it!
Dark Shadow and Frog together--
what a great team!
They're so smart!
[ANNOUNCER 34A]
Team Asui and Tokoyami
have passed the final!
[ECTOPLASM]
That was wonderfully clever.
I must commend you both.
I'm truly humbled, sir.
Ribbit, ribbit.
It was all thanks to me.
So Tokoyami and Asui
passed their exam.
I'm not surprised.
[TENYA] We're running
out of places to stand.
Mr. Power Loader can do this?
What now, Class Rep?
[TENYA] The topography gives
our opponent the advantage.
In order to keep injuries
to a minimum and defeat him,
I think our best choice
right now is to go and find
a hero who is better
suited to take him on.
So in other words,
we should run.
One thing.
[OJIRO] There are traps
between us and the gate.
Not to mention we have no
idea where Mr. Power Loader
will attack next.
[TENYA]
We can still make it.
As long as we work together.
All right!
[TENYA]
Fusion!
I can only imagine how
stupid we look right now.
[TENYA]
Here we go, Ojiro! Reciproburst!
[OJIRO] We're outrunning
the traps he set.
If we keep this up...
[POWER LOADER]
Uh-uh-uh. Not so fast.
Not good!
[OJIRO yelps]
We're gonna fall!
[TENYA] Find the best
solution, Tenya! Come on!
[TENYA] Quick, wrap your
tail around my leg!
[TENYA grunts]
Recipro... Extend!
[POWER LOADER]
I've got you!
[ANNOUNCER 34A]
Team Iida and Ojiro
have passed the final.
Nice one, man!
[POWER LOADER]
Heh.
It was kind of a risky move, but
it put a quick end to the match.
And, you managed to get
your friend out of the ring
without getting
yourself injured.
All in all, not bad.
You pass. Congrats.
[TENYA]
Thank you very much.
They're both amazing!
I promise I will strive
to be the perfect hero.
[IZUKU]
Iida... You're so cool!
[TENYA]
Also, I'm completely stuck.
[IZUKU]
Uh, well. Sometimes at least.
[TODOROKI]
It's our turn now.
Let's go.
Yaoyorozu.
[gasps]
What's wrong, are you nervous?
Oh. No.
It's okay.
With our opponent,
I don't blame you.
But, I have a plan
in mind for us.
Uh--
[buzzer sounds]
[ANNOUNCER 34A]
Team Todoroki and Yaoyorozu.
Practical Exam.
Ready, go!
[TODOROKI]
Yaoyorozu.
Listen, I want you to keep
making small objects.
When you stop being able to,
it means Mr. Aizawa's close by.
[PRESENT MIC]
And, I'm back!
That's Class 1-A's
homeroom teacher,
Shota Aizawa.
He can erase the Quirks
of whoever he sees,
but the effect ends
when he blinks.
[TODOROKI] Our success will
depend on which one of us
finds the other first. Once we
spot him, I'll draw him to me.
Then you can run
to the escape gate
and win this thing for us.
Just stay close
to me until then.
C'mon. Hurry up and
start making things.
Sure. No problem.
[TODOROKI]
Um.
I guess those work okay,
but what are they?
Oh, these, things?
They're just
Russian nesting dolls.
[TODOROKI]
Right.
Let me know if you notice your
Quirk acting strangely at all.
[YAOYOROZU] I'd expect nothing
less from you, Todoroki.
[TODOROKI]
What do you mean?
[YAOYOROZU] You were able
to come up with a plan
to use against
Mr. Aizawa so quickly.
You knew exactly what was
best as soon as we started.
[TODOROKI]
This is nothing.
[YAOYOROZU]
No. You're wrong.
[YAOYOROZU] As students
who got into UA through
recommendations, we started
from the same place.
But in terms of the practical
skills that a hero needs,
I haven't really managed to do
anything that stands out.
During the cavalry battle,
I just followed your orders.
And then when it was
my turn to fight,
I failed before
I could do anything.
[gasps]
Yaoyorozu. You're not
making those dolls!
[YAOYOROZU gasps]
--[TODOROKI] He's coming!
--I'm sorry!
[AIZAWA] If you know I'm here,
then you should be acting.
I would suggest that
you prioritize evasion
since I've taken your
power from you.
Yaoyorozu. Go!
[gasps]
Is that what your plan is?
[grunts]
[AIZAWA]
Then this will be simple.
I was always going
to catch you first
since you're the team's offense.
[TODOROKI]
You think you've caught me?
This is nothing.
I can burn or freeze these
restraints in an instant.
[AIZAWA]
Do whatever you want.
Just be careful where you land.
[TODOROKI]
Caltrops? This is your strategy?
You pretending to be
some kind of ninja?
[AIZAWA] This is very different
from when you faced
the Hero Killer.
I know about your Quirks
and what you can do.
I'm perfectly prepared
to defeat you both.
Your plan places most
of the burden on yourself.
It's nice you tried to be
considerate to the girl,
but maybe you
should have actually
talked this over with her.
[TODOROKI]
Talked it over?
[panting]
[YAOYOROZU] How much farther
until I'm at the gate?
Is there a shorter
route I should take?
I-Is Todoroki okay?
Is this right?
Should I take the time
and make something
to help me go faster?
Can I make it?
Will I be able to pass this way?
Wait. Where am I running to?
Can I do this? Or am I
going to fail us?
[AIZAWA] She obviously
lost her confidence
after the sports festival.
[gasps]
[YAOYOROZU]
Mr. Aizawa!
Does that mean
Todoroki's been--?
No!
[AIZAWA] I'm gonna hit
you where it hurts!
Let's see which
of us is stronger!
[YAOYOROZU] I don't have a
chance against my own teacher.
What? My Quirk's not erased.
Creation!
[YAOYOROZU]
I'm so sorry, Todoroki!
[AIZAWA]
Changing direction?
She let him make
all the decisions.
Comparing herself to Todoroki,
she decided that he was
the superior student.
For better or for worse,
he never seems to hesitate much.
And she's lost her ability
to trust in her own
instincts and reactions.
Emotionally, she's still
a child of 15.
I'd like to help her
regain her confidence.
But that's not my job right now.
[AIZAWA]
Maybe you should have actually
talked this over with her.
[TODOROKI]
Now that I think about it,
she looked like she
had something to say.
[YAOYOROZU panting]
[YAOYOROZU]
Todoroki! Todoroki!
[TODOROKI]
Yaoyorozu!
I'm sorry I came back.
I couldn't--
[TODOROKI]
Hey! Watch it!
Mr. Aizawa's coming!
[gasps]
[YAOYOROZU]
Should I save Todoroki?
Or run? What's the right answer?
What should I do?
Yaoyorozu. You've got
a plan, don't you?
Sorry, I should've asked before,
and not told you what to do.
But you have an idea, right?
Your plan didn't work,
so there's no way
mine will be any good.
We're both gonna fail.
Spit it out already!
I'm saying that you're
the one who's better
at this kinda stuff, not me!
When we were voting
for class rep,
you had two votes, remember?
One of those votes was mine!
Because I thought you would be
best at leading our class!
[YAOYOROZU]
I'm pathetic, but maybe...
[AIZAWA]
Giving up?
[YAOYOROZU]
Not yet.
Todoroki, close your eyes!
What are these?
[AIZAWA]
Flash grenades?
You're right. I have an idea.
A plan for us to win!
This final exam isn't over.
We can still beat Mr. Aizawa!
So, you've got a strategy.
Yes.
I've been thinking about
it from the beginning.
His weakness.
All right, just tell
me what to do.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA]
As a result of my injuries.
I can't use my Quirk
for as long,
and I have to rest more
in between erasures.
If she chose her attack
because she noticed that,
she's pretty smart.
Yaoyorozu!
[TODOROKI]
Fire!
Crap. He erased it!
Todoroki. We have to hide.
Together!
Since he was injured, his
Quirk has become unstable!
[TODOROKI] Because of what
happened at the USJ?
So, we're going to exploit that.
Not yet.
For now, we just need to get
out of his field of vision.
It's all a matter of timing.
We're going to pass this final.
Timing?
How is getting out of his sight
gonna help us with that?
He can still take our
Quirks whenever he sees us.
[YAOYOROZU]
Just do as I tell you.
Keep checking to see if you
can use your ice power, okay?
Not fast enough, kids!
[YAOYOROZU] He's wrong
to think he'll be able to
keep our powers erased
the whole time.
There will definitely
be a single moment...
A brief interval when
Mr. Aizawa blinks
before he can use
his Quirk again.
[TODOROKI]
This is it.
[YAOYOROZU]
And I'll be counting on you
in that moment to attack.
Like you did at
the sports festival.
A giant ice wall!
[AIZAWA]
Todoroki's biggest move.
They were waiting for this.
[AIZAWA] They took advantage
of their opponent.
Hit me where it hurts.
[TODOROKI] I blocked him
with the wall the moment
my Quirk came back.
We can use our powers again.
So can you tell me the
rest of your plan now?
Is that Aizawa's
scarf you're making?
It is.
I don't know the
material it's made of
or precisely how
it's constructed,
so it's not exactly the same.
But I created my own version
with a special material
woven into it.
Since this is
a residential area,
we must keep collateral
damage to a minimum.
And he moves his own
restraining bonds so quickly.
It makes it difficult
to catch him.
So, you see, here is my plan.
[OCHACO] Huh, why isn't
Mr. Aizawa going after them?
[IZUKU]
He might have overused his eyes.
[YAOYOROZU]
What do you think, Todoroki?
I believe this has the
highest chance of success.
Or, at least, it's better
than trying to run.
[YAOYOROZU sighs]
[YAOYOROZU]
We'll only get one chance.
So is this all right with you?
Yeah. No complaints here.
[AIZAWA]
The escape gate is behind me.
It'll be better to watch
the approach from here
than to try and chase them.
[YAOYOROZU]
I have a plan for us to win!
We can still beat Mr. Aizawa!
Let's see it.
Disguises.
I can't use my Quirk
if I can't see them.
But they're at
a disadvantage, too!
[AIZAWA] The upper halves
were just mannequins!
[YAOYOROZU]
Now, I just have to launch it.
[YAOYOROZU gasps]
[AIZAWA]
A catapult?
It's a diversion!
Todoroki! Blast your flames now!
[TODOROKI grunts]
[AIZAWA]
He's not aiming for me. Why not?
[YAOYOROZU] I'm not sure
we have a chance of beating
you in a full battle,
Mr, Aizawa, but that's okay.
[YAOYOROZU]
Nitinol alloy.
Have you heard of it?
When heated, it returns to its
original shape in an instant.
It's a metal with shape memory!
[AIZAWA]
Well, isn't that impressive.
[TODOROKI] It went exactly
according to your plan.
It was almost a
little too smooth.
Honestly, it shouldn't
have worked out.
When I was about to
trigger the catapult,
I made a big mistake.
Mr. Aizawa noticed,
but still jumped away.
Even though he could
have stopped me easily.
I think he allowed
himself to be captured
by my plan on purpose.
I was just trying to see
what Todoroki would do.
You were in my sights,
but he still
had a cloth over him, remember?
I thought he'd try to freeze me.
So I decided it would be
best for me to back off.
In doing so, it looks
like I ended up
playing right into your hands.
[sighs] It really was
just a matter of timing,
like you said, huh?
Thanks, teammate.
[whimpers]
[TODOROKI]
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
[YAOYOROZU]
No. It's nothing, really!
If you feel nauseous,
there's a pressure point
--you can press on--
--[YAOYOROZU] No, I told you,
[YAOYOROZU]
I'm fine.
[AIZAWA sighs]
[RECOVERY GIRL]
My, my.
Turns out that man's
a big softie after all.
[buzzer blares]
[ANNOUNCER 34A]
Team Todoroki and Yaoyorozu
have passed the final exam!
[IZUKU] The fifth match
is currently in progress.
Team Uraraka and Aoyama
against Thirteen.
It's almost over.
Ah! Oh, man, but we
were so close!
[THIRTEEN] There's no way I'll
let you get away that easily!
[OCHACO]
It's getting even stronger
the closer Thirteen gets!
[THIRTEEN]
I'm not great at combat,
but I am excellent at capturing.
It looks like escaping
from Thirteen's
Black Hole Quirk is
next to impossible.
[IZUKU]
They need a plan to break free.
Ah! I guess you
could say this Quirk
really sucks, doesn't it?
Are you serious right now?
We're in big trouble here!
My costume's not just chic.
[OCHACO]
Huh?
[AOYAMA] It channels blasts
from my belly button
which means...
You've got nothing to
worry about, mademoiselle!
[THIRTEEN]
I'll suck up your laser, too!
[AOYAMA yelps]
[THIRTEEN] And break it down
to a molecular level!
This is no joke.
What is your problem?
I have no flaws!
[OCHACO]
This isn't good. We're trapped.
Gotta figure out how
to get outta this!
Okay. Come on!
What would Deku do
at a time like this?
[AOYAMA]
Hey.
Not right now, I'm thinking.
About Izuku Midoriya?
Ah, how sweet.
Huh?
[AOYAMA]
Is it... because you like him?
[IZUKU] Here's the preview!
The finals continue!
Uraraka and Aoyama
against Thirteen.
Kaminari and Ashido
against the principal.
Koda and Jiro against
Present Mic and Shoji
and Hakagure against Snipe!
Everyone's giving it their
all to become heroes!
[IZUKU sniffles] Sorry, I'm
just really moved right now.
[OCHACO]
Hey, Deku?
[IZUKU]
What's up, Uraraka?
[OCHACO] Um, I know you're
having a moment and all,
but Mineta's running away!
[IZUKU] Next time:
"Stripping the Varnish"!
[OCHACO] Aw, Sero goes
night-night on someone's lap.
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, OCHACO]
Plus Ultra!