Say whatever you
want to about me!
You're still just a criminal
who hurt my brother!
[STAIN sighs] And that's
why you'll die tonight.
[TENYA grunts]
[TENYA]
My body... won't move!
[STAIN]
Goodbye, child.
May your death bring
about a better world.
I won't forgive you!
I'm going to kill you!
[IZUKU]
Smash!
Don't worry, Iida.
I'm gonna save you.
I was almost too late
to stop this guy.
Midoriya? Todoroki?
[TODOROKI]
We can protect them!
[TENYA] Just stop it!
Why are you doing this?
His fight is with me!
[IZUKU yelps]
[TENYA]
I inherited my brother's name.
I'm the one that
should stop him.
The Hero Killer is mine!
I'm sorry, Todoroki.
[TENYA]
You have to run.
I can't... watch this.
You wanna make
your brother proud?!
[gasps]
[TENYA]
Are the two of you familiar
with the Turbo Hero, Ingenium?
I know all about him!
He's a super-popular pro
with 65 sidekicks
working alongside him
at his Tokyo agency!
He's my elder brother!
Ingenium is an
unmatched commander
who honors the hero code.
As the second
oldest Iida son,
I strive to be just like him.
[TODOROKI]
Iida...
Stand up and be Ingenium!
[STAIN growls]
Become the hero
he wanted you to be!
[TENYA] I am Ingenium,
and I will defeat you.
That, I promise!
Can I call myself a hero?
My friends are protecting me.
They're bleeding for me.
[STAIN] Shouldn't you be
worried about saving that guy?
[TENYA]
Stain The Hero Killer.
I took my brother's name
so that I could teach
this villain a lesson.
But I was so
consumed with revenge,
that I forgot about
what really mattered.
I was too focused on myself
to help anyone else.
[TENSEI]
You wanna be a hero, too, Tenya?
Yes! Like you! A cool one!
With robot arms?
There's something I wanted
to ask you, big brother.
What drives you?
Why did you choose
to become a pro hero
in the first place?
[TENSEI]
Hm.
Well, our grandfather and
parents were all heroes.
So everyone kind of expected
I would be one, too.
Staying in the family
business and all that.
Plus, it made sense to me.
I think the coolest
people in the world
are those who do
things for others.
I wanted to be the kind of guy
who helps people in trouble.
Then why not work as a
police officer or something?
Aren't you listening to me?
Think of what I'm saying.
[TENSEI] You take things at
face value a little too much.
But you're a hard
worker, and definitely
smarter and more athletic
than me back when I was a kid.
Wait a second.
That's my secret!
Knowing you look up
to me makes me better.
I have to be sure
I make you proud.
[laughs]
[STAIN] Both of you are
nothing but fakes.
[TENYA whimpering]
[TENYA] You spoke
the truth, Hero Killer.
Watch your right!
[TENYA]
These two are different from me.
I'm immature.
I can't hold a candle to them.
But still...
[STAIN]
Ice and fire.
[TODOROKI] Just try and
dodge this, villain!
[STAIN]
Hasn't anyone ever told you
you rely on your Quirk too much?
Makes you a careless fighter.
[TODOROKI]
He's a monster.
Todoroki!
[TENYA]
If I don't stand up right now,
I'll never be able
to be as good as them.
[TENYA] I'll never live up
to my brother's name!
[STAIN]
Damn it.
My Quirk timed out.
[TENYA]
Recipro burst!
[STAIN]
He's fast!
Iida!
You're free, too?
Guess his Quirk isn't as
great as I thought it was.
[TENYA]
Todoroki... Midoriya...
This has nothing to do with you.
I apologize.
Come on. Not this again.
I'm okay.
And I won't let
the two of you shed
any more blood for me!
[STAIN] It's no use trying
to pretend you're a hero now.
A person's true nature doesn't
change in just a few minutes.
You'll never be
anything but a fraud
who prioritizes his own desires.
You're the sickness
that's infected society
and ruined the name "hero."
Someone must teach you a lesson.
You're a fundamentalist lunatic.
Iida, don't listen to
this murderer's nonsense.
[TENYA]
No. He's completely correct.
I have no right to call
myself a hero... at all.
[gasps]
[TENYA]
Even so...
There's no way I can back down.
If I give up now, then the
name "Ingenium" will die!
Pathetic.
[TENYA grunts]
[NATIVE]
Idiots!
The hero killer is only after me
and that kid in the white armor.
Stop fighting back--
just get out of here!
I don't think he'd let me
run even if I wanted to.
Something clearly changed
in him just now.
He seems rattled.
[TODOROKI grunts]
[TODOROKI] His Quirk alone
isn't especially powerful.
The issue of blood type
makes it unpredictable
and it doesn't last long.
Plus, he has to get in close
if he wants to use it.
It must be difficult
for him to take on
multiple opponents at once.
[TODOROKI] He's desperate,
trying to kill Iida
and this other hero
before the pros show up.
Such tenacity.
[STAIN growls]
[TENYA]
Crap. My engines are shot.
Did I break the radiator
with that kick?
[gasps] Hey, Todoroki.
Can you regulate
your temperatures?
Not well with my left,
but, yes, I can.
You gotta freeze my leg for me,
without plugging the exhaust!
[STAIN]
You're in the way.
[TENYA grunts]
No, Iida!
Why won't you stay down?
[TENYA grunts]
--[TODOROKI] Iida--
--[TENYA] Just do it, hurry!
[IZUKU]
I can move!
[IZUKU] My leg's no good.
But... that's okay.
[TODOROKI]
It's done.
[TENYA grunting]
[TENYA]
Thank you, Todoroki.
I will fight...
...with or without my arms.
[TENYA]
Recipro Extend!
[IZUKU]
One For All Full Cowling!
[TENYA]
If I just...
[IZUKU]
Go, guys.
[TENYA]
...use my leg...
[IZUKU]
...use my arm...
[STAIN growls]
[TENYA, IZUKU] ...that's all
I need to beat this guy!
[GRAN TORINO] He's fast,
but not faster than me.
[YOUNG MAN]
No, stay away!
[YOUNG WOMAN screams]
Stop it, you stupid beast!
[grunts]
[ENDEAVOR]
Thanks, old timer.
I'm afraid I don't know you...
Huh?
[ENDEAVOR] ...but I can
handle this from here on out.
Whoa, look!
Why is he in Hosu?
It's because I'm a hero.
[ENDEAVOR] That was only a
low-temperature warning shot.
But, still, it always
KO's my opponent.
Something's not right.
This guy is--
Your Quirk's
absorption and release,
but you still took damage
from my flame, didn't you?
Not a very impressive power.
What's he doing?
Watch it, Todoroki.
I think this guy's
got multiple Quirks.
[ENDEAVOR]
I see. So that's how it is.
[GRAN TORINO] Those two
bystanders got away, right?
Good.
[FOUR-EYED NOMU groans]
Didn't mean to damage the road.
I might be more outta
practice than I thought.
Huh. Nice work.
You're not bad, old man.
[rumbling]
[ENDEAVOR] That must be where
the rest of the heroes
are gathered. It's been
two or three minutes.
They should've taken
care of things by now.
We need to tie this guy up.
The cops will take care
of him from there.
Then we can help out.
[ENDEAVOR growls]
[ENDEAVOR]
Shoto! There's trouble ahead.
I'll show you what
it means to be a hero.
[cell phone vibrates]
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya...
[ENDEAVOR]
Dammit!
--All he sent was his location?
--You should be watching me.
Hey! Wait!
Where the hell are you going?
[TODOROKI] An alleyway
at 4-2-10 Ekou Street.
If you finish what you're
doing or see extra pros,
send them there.
I'm leaving you here
to take care of this trouble.
I'm sure you can
handle it yourself.
[ENDEAVOR]
Huh?
[TODOROKI]
My friend might be in danger.
Shoto...
[ENDEAVOR]
Leave him to my sidekicks.
They'll make sure
the cops take him.
[GRAN TORINO]
Hm?
[ENDEAVOR] There's an
address that I need you
to investigate for me.
I am Endeavor.
I can take care of
the rest of this myself.
Go, guys!
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU]
Crap, did I use too much power?
I don't think it's broken...
Is it?
[TODOROKI] They managed
to land two attacks.
My turn.
I will defeat you, Stain!
Because you are a criminal.
Don't let him get away!
[TENYA]
And I am a hero!
[STAIN groans]
[gasps]
[TENYA, IZUKU yelp]
Stand up! Keep fighting!
He's gotta be knocked
out after all that...
Right?
[sighs] Then, let's restrain
him and get him to the street.
Maybe we can find some rope.
[IZUKU]
Yeah.
And we should probably
take all his weapons, too.
[TODOROKI]
Good idea.
He's too damn strong!
Crap.
Everyone attack at once!
[HEROS]
Right!
Damn it. Can't see!
[HERO 30B]
Where is he?
[gasps] Watch out!
Huh?
[ENDEAVOR grunts]
[gasps] Endeavor!
So, you can regenerate.
Well, then...
Let's see you
come back from this.
Incinerated cells
can't regenerate.
[HERO 29F]
Above you!
[ENDEAVOR] Any hero whose
Quirk isn't suited for this,
go help on Ekou Street
in District Four.
[HERO 30C]
Another villain?
I don't know. Just do it.
[ENDEAVOR]
He's quick! That's fine.
[growls]
[WINGED NOMU groans]
You won't get away.
[IZUKU]
Native, can you move?
[NATIVE] Yeah. I think
I'm good as new now.
[sighs] You sure?
I saw you hurt
your leg back there.
At least let me do this for you.
[sighs] Thank you very much.
I should be thanking you.
[TODOROKI]
Huh.
We're lucky someone threw
this in the dumpster.
Todoroki. I can
drag him from here.
Are you forgetting
your arms are messed up?
[NATIVE]
I have to apologize.
I'm supposed to be a pro,
but I was useless back there.
No, I don't think any one person
could take the Hero Killer on.
Not with that
weird Quirk of his.
He's too strong.
The three of us
barely won against him,
and even then, it was
because of his own mistakes.
He was getting riled
up and desperate
and forgot all about Midoriya's
quick recovery time.
Then he wasn't able
to block Iida's
last Reciproburst or
Midoriya's assault.
Right, let's get him to
the police as fast as we can.
[GRAN TORINO gasps]
What are you doing here, boy?
[gasps] Gran Torino!
I was only--
I thought I told you
to stay on the bullet train!
Who's this?
Gran Torino, the hero
I'm interning with.
I don't get it.
How'd you find us?
I was told to come
here by someone else.
I have no idea what's going on,
but I'm glad you're
not dead, at least.
Me, too. And, I'm sorry.
Tch.
[GRAN TORINO] Jeez, this
side of him reminds me
so much of Toshinori.
[HERO 29K]
Around the corner!
Who's that?
[HERO 30B] Endeavor told
us there was a request
for help here, but...
[HERO 30C]
Children?
Those injuries look bad.
I'll call an
ambulance right away.
[HERO 30D gasps]
Hey, look.
[gasps] Is that...
the Hero Killer?
[GRAN TORINO]
What?
[HERO 30B]
I'll get the police on the line.
[HERO 30D]
Can you walk?
[IZUKU] If you prop me up,
then I think so.
[HERO 30D]
Okay, and you?
[TODOROKI]
Only minor injuries.
But, Iida...
[HERO 30C]
You're bleeding badly.
The ambulance will be
here soon, but until then...
[TENYA]
You guys...
You were both hurt
because of me.
I'm truly sorry.
I was just so angry.
I couldn't see anything else.
I'm sorry, too, Iida.
You were going through
so much by yourself.
But I couldn't tell
anything was wrong.
Even though I'm your friend.
[whimpers]
Hey, pull yourself together.
You're the class rep.
[TENYA sniffs]
Right.
[IZUKU]
All things considered,
our fight against
the Hero Killer
probably only took
about ten minutes.
But for the three of us,
it felt like we were
in that alley forever.
Get down!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
--[IZUKU] Hey! Let go!
--[TODOROKI, TENYA] Midoriya!
It's bleeding.
It must be trying to escape!
[GRAN TORINO]
Shoot. If he takes him too high,
I won't be able to reach
him with my Quirk.
[yelps]
[STAIN] The word "hero" has lost
all meaning in this society.
The world is overrun by fakes
and criminals like you
who chase pretty dreams.
[STAIN]
You must all be purged.
[gasps]
[STAIN]
That idiot's making a move.
And he's so noisy.
I'll dispose of him later.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Everything that I do...
...is to create
a stronger society.
[SHIGARAKI]
Hey, hey, hey, what the hell?
This is no fair!
Why'd he have to
go and kill that Nomu?
And why is that brat here?
I'm so mad, I don't
even know what to say.
This is a mess!
Why do things never go
the way I want them to?
[HERO 30C]
Did he just save that kid?
[HERO 30D]
He took him hostage, idiot.
He killed that guy
with no hesitation.
Everyone be on your guard,
we've got a fight on our hands.
[ENDEAVOR] Why are you
all standing like fools?
The villain must have
flown this way, right?
[HERO 30C]
You took care of the rest?
Mostly, things got a
little rough at the end.
Hold on. Don't tell
me that man is--
[IZUKU]
Let go!
[pants]
Endeavor.
Hero Killer!
Wait, Todoroki!
[ENDEAVOR]
Huh?
[STAIN growls]
[grunts]
You false hero.
I'll make this right.
[STAIN] These streets must run
with the blood of hypocrites.
[STAIN]
Hero! I will reclaim that word!
Come on! Just try
and stop me, you fakes!
There is only one man
I'll let kill me.
He is a true hero.
All Might is worthy!
[gasps]
[ENDEAVOR]
I think...
...he's out cold.
[TENYA, TODOROKI grunt]
[sighs]
[IZUKU] It wasn't until later
that I heard what happened.
A Quirk didn't stop
the Hero Killer.
One of his broken ribs
pierced his lung.
He hadn't managed
to lick anyone's blood.
But still, in that moment,
none of us could
bring ourselves to
stand against him.
Only the Hero Killer
had any fight left.
[ALL MIGHT]
The preview is here!
[GRAN TORINO]
Yeah! And I am here, too!
[ALL MIGHT] U-Uh-- Why is it
you and not Young Midoriya?
[GRAN TORINO]
Who are you?
[ALL MIGHT]
I'm All Might.
[GRAN TORINO]
One more time?
[ALL MIGHT]
I said, I'm All Might.
[GRAN TORINO]
Toshinori?
[ALL MIGHT]
Yes, that's me.
[GRAN TORINO]
And what's your name?
[ALL MIGHT]
Oh! That's enough.
I can't do this all day.
Next time: "The Aftermath
of Hero Killer Stain."
[GRAN TORINO]
That young man named Todoroki
will now be called
"The Hand Crusher"!
[ALL MIGHT]
Go beyond!
[ALL MIGHT, GRAN TORINO]
Plus Ultra!