[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
with 80 percent of us
possessing some uncanny ability.
Cities swirled with
chaos and confusion
following the appearance
of these powers,
and a new profession emerged.
We call those who
fight for justice
and help others
in need, "heroes."
Oh, by the way,
this is the story
of how I became
the world's greatest hero!
[OCHACO]
I'm gonna become a pro.
I'll sign with a good agency
and make plenty of money.
Then I'll be able to let
my parents have an easy life!
You're wonderful, Deku.
I keep seeing that
over and over again.
During the cavalry
battle, I told you
it was good to
team up with friends.
But now that I think about it,
I might've been trying
to rely on you to get by.
That's why,
when Iida said that he was
trying his best to beat you,
I actually felt
embarrassed for myself.
Uraraka...
[OCHACO]
Everyone's facing their future
and giving this their best.
That means we're all rivals.
Even you and me, Deku. So...
Guess I'll see you
in the finals.
[PRESENT MIC]
The eighth and final battle
in the first round of matches.
He was kind of a hot shot
in middle school.
And just look at
that determined face!
From the hero course,
Katsuki Bakugo.
Versus, the one I'm
personally rooting for,
also from Class 1-A,
Ochaco Uraraka!
[CROWD cheers]
You're the one who screws
around with gravity.
Right, Pink Cheeks?
Pink Cheeks?
Well if you're gonna
give up, do it now.
'Cause I'm not gonna
hold anything back.
[TENYA]
Midoriya.
Huh?
I'm curious. What was that
strategy you came up with
that would give Uraraka
an advantage against Bakugo?
Honestly, it wasn't
really much of a plan.
Kacchan's so strong.
When it comes to close combat,
he almost never
has any openings.
And the more he moves,
the more he sweats,
which just makes his
Quirk more powerful.
He's gotten really good
at using his explosions
to move around in the air.
But, if Uraraka is
able to touch him,
she can use her Quirk
to make him float.
She could send
him out of bounds.
That's why, it's obvious
what Uraraka needs to do
to get the upper hand.
Let the eighth match begin!
[IZUKU]
Strike first!
Giving up isn't
an option for me!
Wow, look at her go!
That's a good start,
and all she has to do
is touch him one time!
But it won't be easy.
You know Bakugo's not gonna
let her get too close to him.
Which is why he won't dodge.
He'll focus his energy
on counterattacking.
And now you die.
[IZUKU]
Kacchan.
You always use a big
right hook to start a fight.
[OCHACO]
There!
Here it comes!
[OCHACO]
If I can dodge this move...
[BOTH]
Uraraka!
[JIRO gasps]
He blasted her.
Ugh, looks like Bakugo's
not planning on
showing her any mercy.
Stupid.
Saw it coming and I still
couldn't get out of the way.
You shoulda dropped
outta the match.
There's no way you can beat me!
[gasps]
Whoa! She flew her
jacket over as a decoy!
What incredibly quick thinking!
[OCHACO] This is my chance,
I can make him float!
[KATSUKI yells]
[OCHACO yelps]
Look at that reaction time!
Seriously, the dude's insane.
You can't get the drop on him.
And since Uraraka
can't use her Quirk
unless she touches him,
his lightning-fast reflexes
put her at a huge disadvantage!
Too slow!
[gasps]
I've got you!
Is she okay?
[JIRO]
I can't watch this.
Like I always suspected,
Bakugo's a total sadist.
This isn't over yet!
[OCHACO grunts]
Looks like she's not
resting between attacks
despite being exploded.
The poor girl.
[IZUKU]
Uraraka...
Her feint earlier didn't work,
so now she's getting desperate.
You idiots. Look closer.
[HERO 22C] Hey, shouldn't one
of the teachers step in?
[HERO 20A]
Yeah, this is too rough.
[OCHACO panting]
[HERO 22D]
This is shameful.
Listen, kid, you really
wanna be a hero?
Then stop acting like a bully.
If you're so good,
just send her out of bounds.
Stop toying with the girl
and end this match!
Yeah, you heard the guy!
[AUDIENCE HEROES booing]
[PRESENT MIC]
The crowd is now booing Bakugo!
And honestly, I kinda agree
with what they're sayin--
Hey, whoa-- What the crap?
[AIZAWA] Where is the man
who started this uproar?
Are you a pro?
Huh?
[AIZAWA] Because if you're
being serious, you can go home
and hang up your cape.
I'd suggest looking
into another career.
You know what
he's talking about?
[AIZAWA] Bakugo's fierceness
is an acknowledgement
of his opponent's strength.
He knows she deserves
to have made it this far,
so he's making sure he does
whatever it takes to keep her
at bay and come out on top.
[KATSUKI exhales]
[KATSUKI]
We're not finished.
She's still standing.
She's not dead yet!
[OCHACO]
I think it's about time.
[KATSUKI gasps]
[OCHACO]
Thank you, Bakugo...
...for keeping your
eyes focused on me!
What?
[MONOMA] I don't blame
Bakugo for not noticing,
but it's embarrassing for
a pro to boo and not realize
what's going on from the stands.
She kept low to the
ground as she moved,
which meant Bakugo's blasts
tore up the floor of the ring,
creating weapons for her.
And then she kept
him focused on her
by attacking relentlessly,
without rest.
Rendering him oblivious.
[yells]
A meteor shower!
[AIZAWA]
Now you notice.
Hey, she had a plan all along!
[OCHACO grunts]
[OCHACO] With this much debris,
whether he's evading
or counterattacking, there will
definitely be an opening!
In that moment, I'll
finally get close to him!
[OCHACO]
This is it! My shot.
I'll win and be just like Deku!
[OCHACO grunts]
[CROWD yelping]
[OCHACO grunting]
[KATSUKI] I figured you'd have
some sorta stupid plan
to beat me. You are friends
with that damn nerd, after all.
It took him one shot.
[gasps] Bakugo bangs out
a huge demonstration of power!
He blasted apart
Uraraka's finishing move
and remains untouched!
[pants] That was close.
[OCHACO] I put everything
I could into that,
but I wasn't good enough.
[IZUKU]
Oh, man.
[gasps]
[OCHACO]
I can still stand, though.
All right, then.
Time for us to get serious.
Uraraka!
[OCHACO] If Deku were in the
ring, he wouldn't give up yet!
[grunts]
[PRESENT MIC]
Uraraka is down!
[OCHACO]
No.
Come on. Get up.
I want to keep going.
It's too much.
Yeah. She's way past her limit.
[OCHACO] I can do this.
I can still fight.
I can!
[OCHACO] When I grow up
all big and strong,
I'll help you and Mommy
out any way that I can.
I appreciate you wanting
to help us, Ochaco.
But, as your father,
I'd be happier if you achieved
your own dreams. That'd make
us perfectly happy!
And, well, if you do make money,
just take us on a vacation.
[OCHACO]
I'll become a hero!
Daddy...
Uraraka is KO'd.
Bakugo advances
to the second round!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD cheering]
[MIDNIGHT]
Take her to Recovery Girl.
[PRESENT MIC] And, that's it
for the first round.
[sighs] I was really
pullin' for her.
Oh, yeah, I guess
Bakugo's moving on.
[AIZAWA] You're supposed
to be unbiased, you know.
[PRESENT MIC] Let's try to
forget that depressing outcome.
[AIZAWA]
Or not.
[PRESENT MIC] With that,
the first round is complete!
We're taking a quick break
and then we're back
with more matches!
[CROWD cheers]
Guess I'll see you
in the finals.
[IZUKU]
I'm so sorry.
[grunts]
[yelps] Hey, Kacchan!
What the hell are
you doing here?
Oh, well. I'm up next,
so, you know.
I was gonna hang
in the waiting room.
Um, also congrats
on winning your match.
See you 'round.
[KATSUKI]
It was your idea, wasn't it?
That stupid,
desperate plan of hers.
You would come up with something
that annoying. If we end up--
[IZUKU]
You're wrong.
That plan.
Uraraka came up with it
all on her own,
I didn't know anything about it.
If that battle was harder
than you thought it would be,
then it's because of
her strategy, not mine.
[growls]
[SERO] Hey, Bakugo!
Playin' the villain, huh?
Musta been tough.
Even if it was just because of
who you were up against,
you did make a pretty
convincing bad guy.
Shut up, you idiots. Or else!
For real, dude.
I don't know how you were
able to aim a powerful blast
at a frail girl like that.
I couldn't help but hold
back against Shiozaki.
She completely
overpowered you, Kaminari.
Can't you just let me have this?
[KATSUKI] Hmph. I definitely
wouldn't call that girl "frail."
[door clicks]
Man, I lost. Too bad.
Uh-- Huh?
Guess I got a little
carried away at the end
thinking I had it
in the bag. Dang it!
[IZUKU] You seem fine.
But weren't you injured?
Yeah! Recovery Girl
took care of me.
She was really
careful not to drain
my stamina too much, though.
So, I've still got a few
scrapes and scratches.
Jeez, I didn't realize how
powerful that Bakugo was!
He wiped the ring with me.
Now I realize how much
more training I have to do!
Eh?
You sure you're good?
Oh, yeah, totally.
I'm better than I expected!
[phone vibrates]
Even if you've lost,
you always keep
looking ahead to
what's next, Deku.
This just means that I
have to work harder now.
That's true...
[PRESENT MIC]
Wa-hoo!
We're finally about to learn
who the true winner is
from the seventh match!
Kirishima or Tetsutetsu!
Whoever prevails in this
arm wrestling match
will advance to the
second round! Let's go!
[TETSUTETSU groans]
[yells]
Kirishima is the winner!
Add him to the bracket.
[KIRISHIMA]
Yeah!
[PRESENT MIC] Kirishima earns
a spot in the second round!
Ah, damn my metal deficiency!
Shoulda eaten more
iron this morning!
Hey, man. You put
up a good fight.
Ha!
Oh! So chivalrous!
[PRESENT MIC] Now we've got
a full roster for the next round
of the tournament. Let's get
the party started now, ya dig?
[sighs] Already?
Later.
[OCHACO]
Oh, I'm sorry, Deku!
You weren't able to
prepare since I was here!
Nah. This was perfect.
I'll be watching.
Good luck out there.
Thanks.
[phone ringing]
[OCHACO] Sorry for not
picking up earlier, Daddy.
[OCHACO'S DAD]
No, no, it's fine.
Sorry for calling
when you're busy.
Your mom and I
watched you on TV.
You almost won!
You were amazing!
[OCHACO] It wasn't that close.
And I wasn't very good.
I rushed it too much at the end.
I didn't have a backup
plan for what I'd do
if that big move
didn't work out.
[OCHACO]
I failed.
[OCHACO'S DAD]
You lost.
But that doesn't mean you
can't still be a pro hero.
I know I don't have
the best understanding
of how all this works, but
there's always next year, right?
This isn't the end.
[OCHACO] I know, but I
wish I coulda gone further
in the festival so I would
have had more chances
to show what I'm made of.
The scouts barely saw me do
anything this time around.
[OCHACO'S DAD] What're you
in such a hurry for, huh?
[OCHACO]
It's just...
I want to help you guys
out as soon as I can.
[OCHACO sniffling]
[OCHACO'S DAD] Ochaco, there's
no need for you to rush.
[OCHACO'S DAD] The very fact
that you feel that way
shows me that you'll make
a kind, caring hero one day.
I am so proud of you.
[IZUKU]
Uraraka must be so upset.
I thought I could
help her in some way.
But in the end, I didn't
do anything for her.
Instead, she's cheering me on.
She's got my back.
I'll be watching.
Good luck out there.
[IZUKU] She's the one
encouraging me. Again.
[yelps] Endeavor?
Ah. I was looking for you.
Oh, yeah, hi.
So, uh, what are you
doing back here?
I watched your fight against
the brainwashing guy.
Your power is pretty impressive.
To create so much wind pressure
just by flicking your fingers.
It reminds me of another Quirk.
You seem to have much
in common with All Might.
Oh. Well, I--
I guess I never thought
about it that way.
Sorry, but I should get going.
[IZUKU] Is it possible
that Endeavor knows
about One For All?
No, he probably would
have mentioned it.
He's one person I can't let find
out about All Might's secret.
[ENDEAVOR] It's my Shoto's
duty to surpass All Might
as the number one hero.
[ENDEAVOR] And his match
with you will be a good
testing ground for how
much training he has left.
So hit him hard.
Don't disgrace yourself
or him by holding back.
[TODOROKI] I refuse to rely
on my old man's fire Quirk.
You see, I'm going
to show him that
I reject his power and take
first place without using it.
[ENDEAVOR]
That's all I wanted to say.
I apologize for bothering you.
[IZUKU]
Endeavor. I am not All Might.
What? What are
you talking about?
And the same goes for Todoroki.
He may be your son,
but he isn't you.
[TODOROKI] Midoriya, you've got
All Might in your corner,
helping you out.
[IZUKU]
Todoroki...
[ENDEAVOR] It's my Shoto's
duty to surpass All Might
as the number one hero.
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya.
[ENDEAVOR] Let me assure you
of one thing, All Might.
I will mold that child into a
hero that surpasses you one day.
[OCHACO]
So the match hasn't started yet?
Ura--!
Oh, good!
[TENYA] Something horrible's
happened to your eyes!
You need to go
see Recovery Girl!
[OCHACO] I already did.
This is from...
...something else.
Ah, of course!
If I were you,
I'd be frustrated, too.
It's no time to wallow.
Use this next fight as
a source of encouragement.
Will do.
You're so wise.
[PRESENT MIC] I can feel the
anticipation in the stadium!
And that's because the
second round's first match
is gonna be epic!
It's the guy who
won his last fight
by a landslide and literally
left half the audience frozen.
The hero course's,
Shoto Todoroki!
And this kid almost walked out
of his first matchup,
but made a stunning comeback
by showing off
some impressive moves!
Also from the hero course,
Izuku Midoriya!
So here we are.
And only one of us can win.
Tokoyami. How do you think
this match will go?
It depends on whether
or not Midoriya
is able to get in close to him.
Yeah. That's the problem.
How will Deku avoid the ice?
[MASTER] Pay close attention
to them, Tomura Shigaraki.
These two could prove to
be formidable obstacles
to you one day.
Ha. I'm not worried
about a coupla kids.
[IZUKU'S MOM sobs]
[THIRTEEN]
Oh, right.
Those two students tried to save
you at the USJ, didn't they?
Yeah.
[ALL MIGHT] They may have more
in common than they realize.
They both have such an
intense vibe about them.
[PRESENT MIC] Both of the
heroes-in-training have been
frontrunners in
the Sports Festival!
But which one of these rivals
will advance to the next round?
Prepare for...
...Midoriya versus Todoroki!
[PRESENT MIC]
Begin!
[IZUKU]
Here it is.
Todoroki and I are
finally being pitted
against each other one-on-one.
[TODOROKI]
This will be over quickly.
[IZUKU] Your ice is so
powerful, if you would just
use your left side, too, then...
[TODOROKI]
I told you.
I will win without
using that man's Quirk.
I will completely
reject his wishes.
[IZUKU] Hey, I'm your
opponent here, not him!
[TODOROKI]
What?
[IZUKU] Next time:
"Shoto Todoroki. Origin."
Todoroki will remember
words he hasn't thought of
in many years.
[TODOROKI]
Go Beyond!
[TODOROKI, IZUKU]
Plus Ultra!