[REPORTER A] Okay. Can you
hear me in the studio?
I'm reporting to you live
from skies over Hosu City.
It's unclear what's happening
below, but take a look!
Large clouds of smoke
and fire are rising
from different
locations in the area.
Is this due to a
series of accidents?
Or have villains
taken the streets?
Currently we have no info
on the situation here,
but our station will
continue reporting
as this breaking story unfolds.
[CAMERAMAN A]
And cut!
Don't you dare stop filming.
Wait... What in
the world? Look.
Uh? At what?
Right there.
Check out the building with
the water tower on top.
Zoom in.
[CAMERAMAN A]
There's people--two of them!
Bystanders? How did
they get up there?
[SHIGARAKI]
We're leaving.
[KUROGIRI] Are you satisfied
with the results,
Tomura Shigaraki?
[SHIGARAKI] Depends on
tomorrow's headlines, moron.
[TODOROKI]
Did you sleep, Midoriya?
[IZUKU]
No, not really.
[TODOROKI]
I figured. Me neither.
Thinking about that fight now,
we did something pretty amazing.
Yeah, I agree.
After everything that
happened back there,
it kinda feels like a
miracle we're even alive.
With my leg messed up,
I was an easy target.
He probably could've killed me
if he really wanted to.
Yeah.
Seems to me he let us
both live on purpose.
I'm impressed by
you though, Iida.
He was actually trying to
murder you, but you stood tall.
That's not true.
I was--
[door opens]
Oh, so the injured
youngins are awake.
Gran Torino!
And Manual, too.
Idiot.
I could yell at you
for hours right now.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
[GRAN TORINO] But before I do,
you've got a visitor.
[gasps]
[GRAN TORINO]
This is Hosu's chief of police.
Kenji Tsuragamae.
[IZUKU]
Tsuragamae? The-The Chief?
[TSURAGAMAE]
No, please, stay seated, woof.
[IZUKU]
"Woof"?
[TSURAGAMAE]
So, you're the UA students
who brought down
the Hero Killer, huh?
We are.
[TODOROKI] The police chief
came all this way. Why?
Stain has some serious injuries.
Severe burns and
several broken bones.
Right now he's in the hospital
under strict guard, woof.
Here's a lesson you should
have already learned.
When Quirks became the norm,
the police force sought to
maintain the status quo.
They decided we wouldn't
use Quirks as weapons.
That's when heroes came in.
They could do what we couldn't,
if they were licensed,
of course, woof.
It would be impossible
for the police
to condone the use
of deadly Quirks.
After all, we're here to stop
such harm from being done.
The only reason pros can
use their powers now
is because of the
strict code of ethics
that the early heroes
chose to abide by.
That's why it's against the law
for uncertified people
to use their Quirks
to cause injury.
Whether you were up against
the Hero Killer or not,
none of you had the authority
to harm the villain.
That means the three of you,
and your supervisors--
Endeavor, Manual,
and Gran Torino--
should receive harsh punishments
for this gross abuse
of your powers.
Now wait a minute.
If Iida had not stepped in,
Native would've been murdered.
--And if not for Midoriya,
--[TENYA] Todoroki--
--both of them would be dead.
[TODOROKI]
No one else even realized
that the Hero Killer
was in Hosu.
Are you saying we
should've just stood by
and watched people die?
[IZUKU]
Calm down.
[TSURAGAMAE]
So it's okay to break the law
as long as it goes your way?
[gasps]
But, sir, isn't it a hero's
job to save people?
This is why you're not
a full-fledged pro yet.
It's obvious UA and
Endeavor haven't been
teaching you near enough.
What a shame.
You damned mutt.
Todoroki. Listen, he's right.
Stop there, kid.
You'll wanna hear him
out till the end.
[TSURAGAMAE] What I've said
is the official stance
of the police department.
But any punishment
would only be necessary
if this went public.
If it did, you'd
probably be applauded
by citizens everywhere.
But there's no way
you could escape
from being reprimanded.
On the other hand,
we could say Endeavor
saved the day.
Stain's burns would support
this story completely,
and we could pretend you
weren't involved, woof.
Thankfully, there were
very few witnesses.
This could be the last you
heard of any punishments.
It would mean no one would
know about you, though.
You'd receive no acclaim at all.
The choice is yours.
Personally, I know
where I stand.
I don't wanna damage any
promising young careers.
Not for a mistake like this.
Either way, we'll need
to take responsibility
for being negligent
as supervisors.
I'm sorry. I should've listened.
Yeah! You caused us
a lot of trouble.
Remember that,
and don't do it again.
[TENYA]
Sir!
And... I apologize as well.
Me, too. We'll leave it to you.
[TSURAGAMAE]
I know it's not fair.
You won't enjoy any
of the fame and praise
you probably would've
received otherwise.
But at least... allow me,
as the chief of police,
to thank you.
You know. You could've
started with that.
Todoroki.
[IZUKU] None of us knew
we'd end up fighting
in that back alley.
And in the end, no one
else would find out.
But the implications
of that battle
would continue to eat at us.
Even after our
wounds had healed.
[STUDENT A] Whoa, they arrested
the Hero Killer! Awesome.
[STUDENT B]
Seriously? Who took him down?
[STUDENT A]
Endeavor!
Just what you'd expect
from the number two hero.
[WORKER A] His spree was
exciting in a weird way.
[WORKER B]
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Now, our continuing coverage.
Three villains were captured
in the Hosu riots.
Their identities and
motives are yet unknown.
Based on their distinctive
appearance, however,
and the presence of two people
our reporters filmed nearby,
many are speculating
they're connected
to the League of Villains that
attacked UA High last month.
The Hero Killer Stain
claimed many lives.
In fact, he has more victims
than any other criminal
since All Might burst
into the scene.
With his arrest,
everyone in the country
can rest a little
easier tonight.
[REPORTER A] The seriously
wounded Hero Killer
is currently receiving
treatment at a hospital
under heavy police guard.
Officials are awaiting
the recovery of several
of his victims before
further investigating
the villain's motives.
[DJ A] We're back talkin'
about the criminal
who has surely left
his mark on Japan,
if not the world.
The Hero Killer Stain!
Why did he do it?
What did he hope to gain?
Don't be shy, we're taking calls
and wanna hear your thoughts.
[REPORTER B]
I'm coming to you live
from Ekou Street in Hosu City.
Last night, just after 8pm,
the Hero Killer Stain
was arrested by Endeavor
on this very blo--
[SHIGARAKI]
He's all they're talking about.
What about my Nomus?
[SHIGARAKI laughing]
[SHIGARAKI]
Once this night is over,
the world will've forgotten
you ever existed.
[SHIGARAKI] Not only
have they not forgotten,
but we didn't even
make the front page.
[BEST JEANIST] Let's take
a moment to talk about
the incident last night in Hosu.
The Hero Killer Stain
was arrested.
There were also
incidents with villains
who resembled Nomu
from the UA attack.
You're likely worried how
this all stitches together.
Well, I, too, am concerned.
People tend to come apart at
the seams in times like this.
That's why we heroes must
remain calm despite our fears.
Don't let chaos tempt you
into thoughtless overreaction.
Remember, we're here to protect
others, not seek out vengeance.
It'll be business
as usual today.
Standard material.
May your minds and bodies
be as sharp as your jeans.
[SIDEKICKS]
Thank you, Best Jeanist!
[KATSUKI] Dammit. I'm so ready
to get out of this place.
[KIRISHIMA]
Uh! Midoriya wrote me back!
That location he sent
was in the middle
of the action in Hosu.
That's why he messaged us.
Man am I glad I reported it.
[TETSUTETSU]
Hey!
Put that down before
Fourth Kind sees you.
We're gonna be late.
[KIRISHIMA]
One sec. I wanna reply.
[thud]
What did I say
about punctuality?
[BOTH]
Right. Sorry, sir!
[FOURTH KIND]
Come on. Time to patrol.
[KIRISHIMA, TETSUTETSU]
Yes, sir!
[UWABAMI] No matter how
damaged your hair is,
our new formula is sure to
deeply penetrate each strand.
Such shine! Such volume!
Such luxury.
Easy curls with just one spritz!
Uneri hair spray.
Come on, ladies. Ride the waves.
They sure put that
together fast.
This is just the first cut,
so it'll be another
month before it airs.
It needs lots of CGI.
So weird. We'll be on TV.
We're heroes. This is just
what it takes to be a pro.
So, how 'bout we go patrol.
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH]
Yes!
[OCHACO]
Oh my gosh! That's so scary!
Well, I'm just glad
you guys are okay.
I got really nervous when
the only thing you sent
was your location.
[IZUKU]
Yeah, sorry about that.
But it's all I really
had time to send.
Don't worry, sounds like
you went through a lot.
You get some rest.
I wanna hear everything later.
[IZUKU]
Thanks.
[GUNHEAD]
Uravity. We're about to start.
[OCHACO]
Oh! Sorry.
I'll see you back at school.
I hope I didn't bother
you much. Bye!
[GUNHEAD]
Was that a boy?
Um, yeah, but it's
not like that.
[IZUKU] I can't believe I talked
to a girl on the phone!
It's like she was
whispering in my ear!
[IZUKU]
Oh, hey, Iida.
I just talked to Uraraka.
Midoriya.
Iida just got his
test results back.
[TENYA]
My left hand
might have damage
that's permanent.
[IZUKU]
What? Permanent?
Permanenet damage?
[TENYA] Both my arms
were pretty torn up.
But the injury to my left arm
was especially severe.
There was damage to
my brachial plexus.
Which just means... I'll have
trouble moving my fingers.
And my hand might
have some numbness.
Apparently, there's a
chance it could be healed
with nerve transplant surgery.
When I came across
the Hero Killer,
I stopped thinking rationally.
The first thing I should've
done was call Manual.
But I got lost in my own anger.
[STAIN]
You're completely blinded
by a selfish desire for revenge.
You're about as far away from
being a hero as I can imagine.
I hate him so much,
but I can't deny
he spoke the truth.
That's why, until I'm able
to call myself a real hero,
I'll leave my left
hand as it is.
Are you sure?
[IZUKU] Maybe... if I'd been
a better friend back then...
No. Stop it.
He's already accepted
what happened.
It would be selfish
to make this about me.
[IZUKU]
Iida, I feel the same way.
My hand is a reminder, too.
Let's get stronger. Together.
I feel kind of bad.
About what?
Whenever I'm involved, someone's
hand gets all messed up.
Is something wrong with me?
Am I cursed?
[IZUKU, TENYA chuckling]
[IZUKU] Todoroki, I didn't know
you had a sense of humor!
[TODOROKI]
This isn't a joke.
I'm like "The Hand
Crusher" or something.
[IZUKU, TENYA laughing]
[IZUKU]
"The Hand Crusher"!
[ALL MIGHT]
A phone call is here!
A phone call--
Yes, hello?
[AIZAWA] He can't possibly be
serious with that ringtone.
Wha--? Hi, sir!
[GRAN TORINO] You coulda warned
me about Izuku Midoriya.
I know it probably
couldn't be helped,
but thanks to him,
I'm getting a pay cut
and my teaching license is being
suspended for six months.
His tendency to jump into
situations without thinking
is just like yours, Toshinori.
I humbly apologize, sir.
It's because of my
insufficient teaching.
I can't believe my protegé
caused you so much trouble.
Oh, man, this is bad.
[GRAN TORINO]
Well, I don't care about
my teaching license anymore.
You're the only reason I got it.
And that was so I could
keep my promise
to your predecessor, Shimura.
[ALL MIGHT] And I truly
appreciate all you did for me.
It's only because of
your wisdom and guidance
that I'm the number
one hero today.
[GRAN TORINO]
If that's true,
then why don't
you ever visit me?
[ALL MIGHT]
Well, it's just that
my new life as a teacher
keeps me so busy.
[GRAN TORINO] I actually called
to talk about the Hero Killer.
I saw him only
briefly in person,
but in that short
amount of time,
he shook me to my very core.
There is such hatred
inside of that man.
[ALL MIGHT]
I can't believe he was able
to frighten someone
like you, Gran Torino.
He must have already been
tied up, so what scared you?
It probably stemmed
from his fanatic ideology.
There was something
very intimidating
about his obsession.
I'm not trying to
praise him or anything,
but he's got the same
determination as you
when it comes to your
"Symbol of Peace" thing.
There're similarities.
What do you mean?
[GRAN TORINO] To put it simply,
you've both got charisma.
As the investigation continues,
his ideology and opinions
will be all over the media.
Everyone will wanna
know his motives.
The age we live in,
for better or for worse,
is one of suppression.
There will be people
across the globe
who are influenced
by these new ideas.
[ALL MIGHT] If that's true, and
he inspires copycat villains,
they'll probably strike
out on their own.
Heroes will be able
to stop 'em,
just like they did this time.
That's where the League
of Villains comes in.
The Hosu incident suggests
that Stain and the League
are connected somehow.
That means... the League will
go from being thought of
as a bunch of juvenile
delinquents that attacked UA
to being recognized as
a group with an ideology.
In other words, these new
converts will seek them out.
Even if each individual
is insignificant,
if that evil gathers
under one banner,
it'll swell to
unstoppable proportions.
If the villain in charge
knew this would happen
from the beginning, then he
is a brilliant strategist.
He's steadily getting rid of
any obstacles one by one,
trying to create conditions that
will favor his own purpose.
[ALL MIGHT]
When I heard from Tsukauchi
that Nomu had multiple Quirks,
I had a bad feeling.
What if he's back?
[GRAN TORINO] You're concerned
it could be the man
who killed Shimura,
my sworn friend, your master,
and the previous holder
of One For All.
The man who opened that
hole in your stomach.
You're afraid the villain
named All For One
is on the rise again.
For him to've survived
such injuries, though...
I don't wanna
imagine it's possible.
[GRAN TORINO]
Toshinori.
That child admires you
so wholly and fiercely.
You should find the time
to tell him everything
concerning you and One For All.
Be honest. He deserves
to know the truth.
[IZUKU] Two days after
the Hosu incident,
the Hero Killer's
identity and motives
started being dissected
from various angles.
[BROKER A] Y'know, lately,
it's been hard finding people
to do business with.
My buddies all complain about
not being able to sell stuff.
It's a real pain.
[INTERMEDIARY A] That's
'cause it's a serious crime
to develop or sell support
items and costumes
if you don't have a license.
On top of that,
there've been rumors
that legit support companies
have actually been selling
extra gear on the
black market to people
who aren't certified heroes.
Ugh! Man, I miss the
days before All Might.
And I was still
small-time back then.
Remember when villains
were wild and impulsive?
Everyone thought they
could take over the world.
It was a real good time.
But when All Might showed up,
everything changed and
got so damn boring.
Can't have any fun when that
pillar of justice is around.
Maybe it's time for me
to finally call it quits.
Don't be rash.
Listen, just between you and me,
I know of a way to
make some real cash.
Keep this on the down low,
I'm only telling you
because I know your guys
have quality goods to sell.
Have you seen this yet?
Huh? What's that?
It's a video of the Hero Killer.
He's hot right now.
[VIDEO NARRATOR]
The Hero Killer Stain.
Real name, Chizome Akaguro.
As a child, he was greatly
inspired by All Might's debut.
He enrolled in a private
hero high school,
but was dismayed
by what he viewed
as the educational system's
skewed understanding
of what it meant to be a hero.
Throughout his teenage years,
Chizome advocated for a return
to the early days of heroes,
but quickly realized that
words had no power.
For the next ten years, he
trained in killing techniques
in order to fulfill his
self-appointed duty.
During this time his
parents passed away,
in what police eventually
ruled as a tragic accident.
His focus was on a
return to the old days.
He believed heroes should
not seek compensation.
That one should epitomize
the idea of self-sacrifice.
He believed that present-day
pros were frauds.
Through his violent purges,
he hoped society would
eventually side with him.
[STAIN] These streets must run
with the blood of hypocrites.
Hero! I will reclaim that word!
Come on. Just try and
stop me, you fakes!
There is only one man
I'll let kill me.
He is a true hero.
All Might is worthy!
[gasps]
[INTERMEDIARY A]
This keeps getting uploaded
and immediately
taken down online.
But they can't stop it.
It's not hard to see.
This guy is really stirring
something in people.
From villains with
countless convictions,
to felons on the run,
all the major players,
including me, are watching.
It's infectious. Do you feel it?
I don't think the heroes
realize what's awakening.
The evil that was once
quiet and scattered
now has a rallying cry
that's calling out to it.
Individual criminals are
seeking out the organization
that the Hero Killer Stain
was connected to.
They're all headed to
the League of Villains.
[IZUKU]
Now, the preview!
I wonder how everyone's
internships went
while I was stuck
recovering in the hospital.
[TSUYU]
You're curious, Midoriya?
[IZUKU]
Asu-- I mean, Tsu!
[TSUYU] We can totally
catch you up to speed
by showing Class 1-A in
action at their internships!
[IZUKU]
Yeah, I'd love to see that!
[TSUYU]
But that means your role
in the episode'll
be pretty small.
[IZUKU]
Huh?!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit, ribbit.
[IZUKU] Next time.
"Everyone's Internships."
[TSUYU]
I hope you enjoy these stories
created especially
for the anime!
[IZUKU]
Yeah! Go beyond!
[IZUKU, TSUYU]
Plus Ultra!