You'll all be interning
with pros. Got it?
Even those of you who
didn't get any offers.
[ALL MIGHT] You've received
an offer from a hero
who'd like to take you on.
The hero's name is Gran Torino.
He taught at this school back in
my day, but only for one year.
In fact, the man was
my homeroom teacher.
Hello, I'm here from UA High.
It's Izuku Midoriya. I'm
really looking forward to--
[gasps, screams]
[IZUKU]
Holy whoa, he's dead!
I'm alive!
[screams] He's alive!
[sighs]
[GRAN TORINO]
Whoopsy.
I was carrying a nice big plate
of sausages covered in ketchup
when I accidentally
tripped and fell down.
Clumsy me.
[IZUKU]
Okay, that's a little weird.
Now, who did you say you were?
I'm Izuku Midoriya.
From UA High School!
You're who, now?
I'm Izuku Midorya.
So, what's your name, boy?
[IZUKU]
Oh, great.
He was All Might's teacher,
so I knew he had
to be pretty old, but I didn't
expect him to be bonkers.
Ah--
[GRAN TORINO]
I could really use some food.
Some food?
Toshinori?
Midoriya!
Heh... Excuse me.
I just need to
make a phone call.
[IZUKU] I should probably
let All Might know
the state this guy's in.
He's not fit to mentor.
[yelps]
[IZUKU]
Hey, uh, wait, that's my stuff!
[GRAN TORINO]
Why don't you fire off
a One For All smash at me?
[gasps]
I wanna know
how far you've come
in terms of handling its power.
[IZUKU] Is this even
the same guy as before?
[GRAN TORINO]
This is a pretty good costume.
Now, where's that attack?
But, sir...
Hey, what are you doing here?
[IZUKU]
What the heck is with this guy?
I'm here because I need to learn
how to control One For All.
I have to get so much
better at it, and fast.
I'm also here
because I don't know
if All Might has much time left.
[IZUKU] I'm sorry. But I
can't waste my whole week
messing around like this, sir.
I hope you'll excuse me.
[GRAN TORINO]
As I thought.
[gasps]
[sighs]
It's time for you to
show me what you can do,
ya newbie. He, he, he!
I watched the UA Sports
Festival on television.
The way you used your power
was unthinkable. Reckless!
He's not training you well.
He may be the symbol of peace
and the number one hero,
but All Might's a total novice
when it comes to teaching.
I can only imagine what a
blunder he is in the classroom.
Now. Shall we get started,
you buncha newbies?
[IZUKU] Hey, All Might
called us newbies, too.
And he has two sides,
sometimes playing dumb.
This really is his teacher!
I can't stand to watch you
use your Quirk that way,
so I suppose I'll
have to teach you.
Now, hurry and get
your costume on.
I'm ready. Teach me everything.
[IZUKU]
Instructions?
[COSTUME DEVELOPER 27A]
"Dear Izuku Midoriya.
As we made repairs to your
costume, our designers decided
to make a few changes in regards
to materials and appearance.
Thank you for understanding.
But trust me, it's gonna
look a whole lot cooler!"
[IZUKU]
Huh?
I can't believe the support crew
changed stuff around
without asking me.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised
after seeing Hatsume at work.
Well, whatever the case.
This will be my first
battle in the new version
of my mom's suit!
All right. Let's get started.
Show me a smash.
Uh. You're sure
this is a good idea?
I'm kind of worried since I've
never used this suit before.
Plus, you know,
this place is small.
And, if I accidentally fired
a smash at 100 percent, then--
your body wouldn't
be able to handle it!
Good grief, kid.
A chatterbox, aren't ya?
[GRAN TORINO grunts]
[GRAN TORINO]
I'm losing patience!
[IZUKU grunts]
Okay, that really hurt.
[gasps]
[GRAN TORINO laughs]
[IZUKU yelps]
[GRAN TORINO]
What? You didn't realize
my true strength earlier?
[gasps]
I can't believe
you're the ninth holder
of this great power.
All Might's hardly
taught you anything.
Guess all that fame
doesn't translate
into being a good mentor.
[gasps, grunts]
[IZUKU] He's too fast!
How does his Quirk work?
[IZUKU]
Come on, think!
There's no place for me to hide,
and he's not giving
me any openings.
It's no use trying to
figure out where he is.
I need to stop him
from moving somehow.
Imagine the egg in the
microwave, not exploding!
[IZUKU] He's passed behind
me twice. That means...
Clever analysis, newbie.
[IZUKU]
Smash!
Nice try. But you're
a little stiff!
And there's discord
within your mind.
That's why I bested you.
Crap, I thought for sure
I was gonna land that punch.
[GRAN TORINO]
Listen to me.
The way you used One For All
in the cavalry battle
and the tournament showed
that you're adjusting
to the Quirk. You
understand its fundamentals.
But your admiration
for All Might
and sense of loyalty to him
are shackles on you.
"Shackles"? But how?
[GRAN TORINO] It's true that
you need to get stronger,
and quickly. Time
waits for no man.
Real villains don't care
if you've reached
your full potential yet.
And you think One For All is
more special than it really is.
Then... what should I do?
[GRAN TORINO] Think about
that on your own time.
Meanwhile, I'll go
buy us some grub.
Clean this place up
while I'm gone.
[IZUKU]
Huh?
[IZUKU] My admiration for
All Might... is a shackle?
[MANUAL] On a normal day,
I'd just be waiting
for client calls to come in.
Not really exciting.
But things've been fairly
hectic here lately.
[TENYA] So you're using street
patrols to suppress crime.
Yeah, exactly.
Man, I kinda can't believe
Ingenium's little brother
is interning at my agency.
I'm sure you had
offers from pros
with much bigger
followings than mine.
[TENYA]
The Hero Killer.
So elusive he's managed
to avoid capture
for his deplorable crimes.
I know that I might not
find him. But still...
[TENYA] I have to try
to track the villain down.
Because I can't forgive him
for what he's done.
[STAIN]
Now I get it.
You must be the ones
who attacked UA.
And you wanna
recruit me to build up
your little group again.
[SHIGARAKI]
Yeah.
It'll be great, you've
got so much experience.
And what's your mission?
[SHIGARAKI]
For now?
I really just wanna
kill All Might.
I like to destroy anything
that pisses me off.
Like this little brat here.
Game over.
I was a fool to think
you could offer me anything.
It turns out, you're
the type of person
I hate most in this world.
[SHIGARAKI]
Hm?
The goals of your "league"
are those of a child.
What meaning is there to killing
if you don't have
real convictions?
[KUROGIRI]
The Hero Killer Stain.
Tomura Shigaraki cares
only about wanton violence,
so we brought this man
in to guide him.
Perhaps we made a mistake.
[KUROGIRI]
Master. Should I step in?
[MASTER]
Let it happen.
It's possible this is the only
way he'll learn anything.
He needs to think about
the ways he must grow.
How he can mature.
Only then will he
reach his potential.
[IZUKU] My admiration for
All Might is a shackle.
I understand the fundamentals,
but there's discord in my mind.
I believe One For All
is more special than it is.
Is that what's making
my movements stiff?
What does "stiff" even mean?
Okay, look at all this
in a different way.
What makes a movement flexible?
[gasps] I know!
How I think about it,
One For All--
Those big smashes are
like my special moves.
But I saw him use it up close.
Why didn't I notice then?
Now I see.
Quirks are just extensions
of our bodies. So then...
I need to start thinking of
One For All as being part of me.
That's it! I get it!
[GRAN TORINO] Well, at least
he's mentally adept
and forward-thinking. For a kid.
But I already knew that
from the festival.
You found a good one,
huh, Toshinori?
Or should I say, All Might?
[BEST JEANIST]
To be perfectly frank,
I don't like you very much.
Huh?
[BEST JEANIST] I know full well
why you chose my agency.
Because I'm one of the top
five most popular heroes.
Hey, look, you're the one
who made an offer for me.
[BEST JEANIST]
Yes.
Recently, all my recruits have
been perfect little angels,
so you certainly stood out.
I watched the way you fought
at the sports festival.
You have a good handle
on your powerful Quirk,
and a decent grasp of
its application as well.
[BEST JEANIST]
You're an outstanding talent.
I'd say you're already good
enough to take on as a sidekick.
However, you do
have a fatal flaw.
You believe you're the best,
and you display that belief
without regard for how it
reflects on you or your image.
You have a ferocious nature.
Don't tell me you
brought me here
just to give me a lecture!
Ah--
[BEST JEANIST] I have to
correct people like you.
It's part of my duty to society.
Heroes and villains are
cut from the same cloth.
So your job here is to watch me.
I'll show you what
makes someone a hero.
What in the hell are you doing?
[BEST JEANIST]
Isn't it obvious?
I'm educating you on
becoming an exemplary pro.
That includes being aware
of the way you speak,
your appearance, controlling
your emotions, your morals.
There are countless things
you need to learn,
but in the brief
period of one week,
I will stitch these things
into the fabric of your being.
[TETSUTETSU, KIRISHIMA]
Whoa!
Tetsutetsu?
Kirishima!
[BOTH] Hey, man, what
are you doin' here?
We were able to put in
two offers this year.
Let's begin right away.
[BOTH] I look forward
to working with you.
I was impressed by
the guts both of you
showed at the sports
festival. I like you two.
However, being a
hero isn't easy,
and you can't rely
on brute force alone.
So this week, you'll learn
from my experience.
That's the chivalrous hero.
He's so manly!
Wait for me to finish speaking.
[BOTH]
Yes, sir! Apologies!
[FOURTH KIND]
Seems I'll have to teach you
proper manners, too.
[BOTH]
Thank you very much, sir!
First, let's talk about
why we're even here.
Pros receive wages
from the government,
so we're civil servants.
But, there's more
to it than that.
With the Quirks we offer, our
responsibilities are different
from regular workers.
Now, regarding
our actual duties.
[GUNHEAD] Basic hero goal:
control crime. Right?
When a crime occurs,
the police will contact us.
These requests come in all
at once, filtered by district.
We file reports on the
services we provided.
Assisting with arrests,
rescuing people, et cetera.
Then a special agency looks
at our work and decides
how much we should be paid.
You'll catch on quick, kiddo.
[OCHACO] I didn't expect
him to be so friendly.
[UWABAMI]
Additionally, heroes are allowed
to have side jobs.
There were a lot of
arguments about this
when the world of pros was
first being established,
but the heroes ended up
being so popular
that the public demanded it.
For example:
I'm about to film a commercial.
Stick around, okay?
Um, well.
I was kinda hoping
I'd see something
a little more action-y.
[YAOYOROZU]
No.
This sort of attention is
something you can't avoid
if you're a pro.
Besides,
she was kind enough
to offer her wisdom
to an unworthy, student.
So I'll take every
lesson she has to give!
[KENDO]
She's really into this.
Okay.
But isn't there
anything else we can do
while you film this
commercial, or whatever?
[UWABAMI] Do you know why
I chose to recruit you two?
Any thoughts?
[KENDO]
Well, I guess...
[YAOYOROZU] It must be
because you saw such
heroic potential in us!
[UWABAMI]
Of course I did.
But there's another reason.
You're both very
cute young ladies.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[DEATH ARMS] Heroes must
practice and train constantly.
You can't take a break,
even when you're on patrol.
Right! Kay!
[JIRO]
Aw, man.
This is so much
harder than class.
You know what's a useful skill?
Knowing how to pass the
time while you're waiting
to be called out to
rescue someone. Got that?
[MINETA]
Uh, sure.
[MINETA] This is not the kind of
role play I was hoping for.
[whistle blowing]
[ENDEAVOR] I've been
waiting for you, Shoto.
You're finally ready to walk
down the path of the mighty.
[TODOROKI] I have no
intention of following
any path you've created.
Only I can decide my future.
Heh. Is that so?
You should go get ready.
We're going out.
Where to?
It's time I show you
what it means to be a hero.
[GRAN TORINO snoring]
I'm snoring! I'm snoring!
[IZUKU]
He can't be serious.
The first day of training down,
and all he did was test me once.
No actual hero work
or field training.
He just passed out after
coming back with food.
Gran Torino...
I didn't get any hits when
I searched for that name.
A UA teacher for just one year.
He's one big mystery.
[IZUKU] I need to change
the way that I think
about One For All.
It's part of me.
My classmates use their Quirks
as if it's completely natural.
But I still think of mine as
something I have to call upon.
If I could use even
five percent of my power
like it was nothing.
I'd be able to
move like Kacchan.
Mr. Aizawa and Kirishima
said the same thing.
If I can just master my Quirk,
I'll be able to do
so many things!
But first, I need to be
able to use it instantly.
All right! I'll try this out.
Five percent should
be enough here.
One, two, three, the roof.
That shouldn't be
too hard, right?
[IZUKU] Imagine the egg not
exploding in the microwave!
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU]
I was afraid that would happen.
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU] I need to brace
myself, and use my arms
to cushion the impact.
Which means,
for the second jump,
I need to put power into
both my arms and my legs.
But if I don't do it quickly
enough, then I'll end up
breaking my bones in the fall!
I can't take the time
to visualize the result
like I normally do.
But I have to try it.
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU]
Gotta put some power in my arms.
[IZUKU growls]
[IZUKU]
This time I'll switch faster!
[IZUKU yelps]
Faster, stupid! Do it faster!
Is it a villain?
[IZUKU grunts]
Let's go, it's not
our problem, honey!
[IZUKU]
Faster!
Good morning.
What's wrong? You look beat.
Well...
I was training on my own
yesterday and went too far.
I tried to take
everything you said to me
and put it into practice,
but it was just no good.
Heh. Obviously I still
have a long way to go.
It's your first time trying,
so it's to be expected.
That is how training works.
Of course, I suppose All Might
can't wrap his mind around that.
He was pretty much able to use
One For All right off the bat,
so I taught him in a
very different manner.
'Course he had the
body going for him,
so there's that.
Whoa, All Might
as a student, huh?
Come on, what was
he like back then?
[GRAN TORINO]
Hm? Huh...
It was all combat
training for him.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[groans]
[ALL MIGHT groans]
[IZUKU] No wonder All Might
was so scared of this guy!
The training was difficult,
but I couldn't hold back on him.
He was entrusted to me
by a sworn friend
who had just passed away.
Oh, All Might's predecessor?
So, can you tell me
anything about the guy?
Huh?
[doorbell rings]
[DELIVERYMAN 27A]
Package for you!
I-I'll take care it for you.
[GRAN TORINO]
So you haven't told him about
the seventh holder
yet, eh, Toshinori?
[IZUKU]
Got it. Thanks!
A microwave?
Yeah, for some reason,
mine broke yesterday.
Heh. So I bought a new one.
[IZUKU] I can't tell if
he's being serious or not.
So whaddaya think,
how 'bout we eat
some of that frozen food
I bought? It'll be good!
But the only thing you
bought was dessert.
What can I say, I like
the finer things in life.
[IZUKU] Using my Quirk needs to
be as easy as taking a breath.
Thinking about it
objectively, everyone else
has had 15 years to get
into that kind of mindset.
But not me, and time
waits for no one.
At this rate,
in order to draw out
more than five percent
of my power,
I'll need to put in
the kind of commitment
I did on the beach.
[microwave dings]
Oh, yeah, look at
these delicious babies.
Come and get 'em
while they're steamin'.
My time is limited.
What do I focus on?
Why the long face, boy?
Just focus on these pipin'
hot pastries for now.
Still frozen!
Ah-- No way!
I'm positive that I microwaved
them like it said to.
What're you an idiot?
You stuck a huge plate
in there, didn't you?
If you do that, there's
no room for it to turn.
So only one part of it gets hot.
Have you never done this before?
[IZUKU]
Oh, ours isn't the turning type,
so, no, I guess not.
I'm sorry that--
[gasps]
[IZUKU gasps]
I've got it!
Whoa. Gran Torino!
I see now! The frozen pastry
in my hand is me!
No, it's not. Are you okay?
Uh, I don't mean literally.
I'm not really a dessert.
But I get it.
Up until now, I've just been
summoning One For All.
Only when I really need it.
In the places I need it.
Like flipping on
some kind of switch.
But if I do that that,
my reaction time gets
slower and slower
with every move.
Which means...
I shouldn't be flipping
the switch off.
I just have to leave the
power on the whole time.
Imagining the energy
that used to be focused
in one place spreading
throughout my entire body!
[GRAN TORINO] Didn't take
him long to figure that out.
Good.
[IZUKU] I need One For All's
power surging through
all of me, continuously!
The five percent that I can use!
Visualizing a pastry
in the microwave
is pretty boring, kid, you
sure you're okay with that?
[IZUKU] All Might said that
about my egg already,
and it was fine with me.
So tell me, can you
move in this state?
I don't know for sure.
Wanna give it a try?
Yes. Let's do this!
[SHIGARAKI] So you finally
called me in for a preview, huh?
[IZUKU]
Whoa. Tomura Shigaraki?
[SHIGARAKI]
It took you long enough,
don't you think, Midoriya?
[IZUKU] But I don't have
anything to do with this--
[SHIGARAKI]
Oh, really?
Then starting this week,
I think I'll be in charge
of all these stupid previews.
[IZUKU screams] Somebody help!
Where's All Might?
[SHIGARAKI] Next time:
"Midoriya and Shigaraki."
The League of Villains
is going wild.
I'll destroy every
last one of you,
whether you're a hero
or a hero killer.
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[SHIGARAKI]
Not this time.
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[SHIGARAKI]
I said no!