[TODOROKI]
My father is the hero Endeavor.
He's the number two hero.
You must know him.
[ENDEAVOR] It's my Shoto's
duty to surpass All Might
as the number one hero.
So if you are somehow
connected to All Might,
the number-one hero,
then that would mean...
...I have even more
reason to beat you.
[TODOROKI]
In every memory of my mother,
I only see her crying.
I remember she called
my left side unbearable
before she poured
boiling water on my face.
[TODOROKI]
I'm going to show my old man
that I don't have to rely
on his damned fire Quirk.
I'm going to show him
that I reject his power
and I can take first place
without using it.
[TODOROKI] I suppose your
relationship with All Might
doesn't actually matter.
I will defeat you using
only my right side.
[IZUKU]
I can't lose this, either.
I owe it to everyone who's
supported me to try my best.
I will beat you.
[TODOROKI sobbing]
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
But, honey, you do still wanna
be a hero, don't you?
Just remember,
stay true to yourself.
[TODOROKI]
I had forgotten...
...so much of what
she said in those days.
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC] It's the first
match of the second round!
These two heroes
in training have both
been frontrunners in
the sports festival!
It's Midoriya!
[CROWD cheers]
[IZUKU]
He'll start with an ice attack.
Versus, Todoroki!
[TODOROKI] I can't allow him to
use that power of his too much.
[PRESENT MIC] But which of
these rivals will advance
to the next round?
[IZUKU, TODOROKI]
So, as soon as we start--
Begin!
[TODOROKI]
Now...
[IZUKU]
Smash!
[TODOROKI grunts]
[CROWD gasps]
[AUDIENCE 23A]
Whoa! So cold!
[AUDIENCE 23B] Feels like this
wind is gonna freeze me solid!
[TODOROKI]
Hpmh. Just as I expected.
He's prepared to injure
himself to counter me.
[PRESENT MIC] Wow! Midoriya
managed to break Todoroki's
insane opening move!
[ALL MIGHT] He had no way
of knowing how powerful
Young Todoroki's attack
was going to be,
so he abandoned restraint and
fired off a shot at 100 percent.
It's true that this was
likely the only thing
he could do against the
ice barrage. However...
[IZUKU]
Smash!
[PRESENT MIC]
He countered again!
[IZUKU] I don't know much about
Todoroki's fighting style.
His attacks are so
fast that it's hard
to collect data on him.
So, during this fight,
I need to focus
on finding an opening somewhere.
The ice behind him is
probably how he plans
to keep from being blown
out of bounds by my smashes.
Which means...
I was right to break my fingers.
If I'd spent my whole arm
on a full-powered smash
and the ice held up,
I'd be doomed.
[IZUKU]
I can figure this out.
Come on. Find a weak spot.
I've only got six more chances.
Let's continue.
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU]
Five more chances.
Oh, no, crap!
I'm missing it!
[KAMINARI]
Hey, nice job making it
to the second round, Kirishima.
Thanks, man.
Looks like I take
down Bakugo next.
I'll kill you.
Heh. Yeah, sure. In your dreams.
No, but, seriously.
It's crazy how you and
Todoroki both have moves
that blast the whole stadium!
Must be pretty nice.
Plus, you don't have to
pause between attacks.
It's not as easy as
you think, ya morons.
[KIRISHIMA]
Hm?
If you overuse your muscles,
you risk tearing them apart.
If you sprint too much,
you run out of breath.
[KATSUKI] We all have
a limit to how much power
we can produce.
That's why I designed
my costume the way I did--
so I'd be able to
fire off bigger blasts
than my body usually
allows me to.
Quirks are physical
abilities, too.
They can get worn out.
You can't just use them nonstop.
It makes sense when
you put it that way.
I wonder if that's how Midoriya
thinks he's gonna beat Todoroki.
[TODOROKI]
You want an endurance match.
But I'll end this quickly.
[IZUKU]
Smash!
[IZUKU] That's all the
fingers on my right hand!
[PRESENT MIC] Todoroki
withstood Midoriya's power
and is now rushing
his classmate!
No!
[IZUKU]
Oh, no. Not good!
[IZUKU grunts]
[screams]
[grunts]
[TODOROKI]
That was much more powerful
than any of your
previous attacks.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI] You're trying
to keep me away. Smart.
[IZUKU pants] It's not just
that his Quirk is powerful.
His judgment,
mobility, reasoning...
All of his abilities...
...are incredible.
[exhales]
[AUDIENCE 23C]
That kid's already better
than the average pro.
[AUDIENCE 23D]
Guess that's what you can expect
from the son of
the number two hero.
[TODOROKI]
What's the matter?
Are you really that worn out
from defending
against my attacks?
[IZUKU] He's shaking. Is he
reaching some kind of limit?
I've got to keep fighting!
I'm sorry about this,
but thanks for drawing it out.
Look at him. He's furious
I'm not using his power.
[grunts]
[TODOROKI] I don't have to
rely on his damn fire Quirk.
[TODOROKI]
You see,
I'm going to show that bastard
that I reject his power,
and take first place
without using it.
[TODOROKI]
With your hands like that,
you can't fight
anymore, can you?
Why don't we end this?
[PRESENT MIC]
Whoa! Todoroki continues
his overwhelming attacks!
Could this be his
finishing move?
[IZUKU]
I am not done yet!
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[TODOROKI grunting]
[TODOROKI]
Dammit.
With your broken finger?
Why are you going this far?
You're trembling, Todoroki.
[gasps]
It's easy to forget that
Quirks are physical abilities,
and that means there's
a limit to the cold
your body can take, right?
I get it.
Usually you'd make up for
the drop in temperature
by using the heat
from your left side.
But you refuse to do that now.
Listen. We're all
giving it our all...
...to try and win.
To make our dreams
into a reality.
To become number one!
[IZUKU] You think you can win
with half your strength?
Look at me, Todoroki.
You haven't managed to put
a single scratch on me yet.
[TODOROKI growls]
So come at me
with all you've got!
You think you can win
with half your strength?
Look at me, Todoroki.
You haven't managed to put
a single scratch on me yet.
So come at me
with all you've got!
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya...
[ENDEAVOR]
Hmph.
He may be your son,
but he isn't you.
[ENDEAVOR]
That boy...
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya...
What are you trying to do here?
You want my fire?
What, did my monster of a dad
bribe you or something?
[TODOROKI]
Now I'm mad.
[IZUKU]
His movements are...
[KATSUKI]
...slower.
Is it because he's got
so much frost on his body?
Maybe his Quirk is like a
magic meter in a video game.
If that's true, he could
be running on empty.
Did he waste all his energy
fighting against Tape Arms?
[TODOROKI]
In close quarters,
there's no way he'll
be able to dodge me.
[TODOROKI gasps] The instant
I lifted my right foot...
He's coming!
Imagine the egg
in the microwave.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
It won't explode. I've got this.
Come on, I've got this!
[PRESENT MIC]
A solid punch!
[PRESENT MIC] That's the
kind of action I like to see!
[screams]
[CROWD gasping]
[AUDIENCE 23C] Whoa!
He landed a hit on Todoroki!
[AUDIENCE 23D]
Even though Midoriya looks
way more beat up at this point.
I can't believe he went
on the offensive there!
[IZUKU grunts]
[coughing]
[TODOROKI]
Why?
[IZUKU] The ice attacks
aren't moving as fast now.
[grunts]
[grunting]
[CEMENTOSS]
Should I step in, Midnight?
Midoriya knows
that Recovery Girl
will heal his wounds
after the match,
so he's being reckless
and hurting himself.
He's full of adrenaline.
He probably doesn't even
realize how much pain he's in.
But those injuries are bad.
They probably can't
be healed in one go.
Even if he wins,
he might not be able
to fight in his next match.
He's sacrificing himself.
At this rate, he might end up
with permanent damage.
Work harder.
And don't give me
the excuse that you
don't have control
over your Quirk.
[AIZAWA]
His power has lessened,
but he's gained some control.
It's not that he's
fighting recklessly.
He's just doing everything
he can to win the match
within his current skill level.
[AIZAWA]
But, man.
Even if it can be healed,
to go through such intense pain
and still be putting up a fight
requires an absurd
amount of resolve.
[AIZAWA] What's driving him?
Why's he so intent?
[IZUKU] He's the greatest hero,
and I wanna be just like him.
In order to do that,
I have to be strong enough
to become number one.
I know my motivation might
seem stupid compared to yours.
[IZUKU]
I can't make a fist, but...
Smash!
[TODOROKI] Why are you putting
yourself through this?
[IZUKU] I wanna live up
to people's expectations.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] I wanna be able to
smile while doing something
good for them. I wanna be a pro!
Whatever it takes to be a hero!
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
Shoto.
[TODOROKI grunts]
[IZUKU yells]
[TODOROKI groans]
[IZUKU] That's why I'll give it
my all just like you should be!
[IZUKU]
There's no way I can know
what you've gone through,
or why you're even here.
Your life has been so
much different than mine,
but right now...
Stop screwing around!
If you wanna reject
your father, fine,
but you don't have the
right to be number one
if you aren't going
to use your full power.
[TODOROKI coughing, gagging]
Now stand up. If you
get hurt that easily,
you can forget about
beating All Might,
or even a small-time villain.
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
Please, stop pushing him.
He's only five years old.
[ENDEAVOR] He can take it.
Get outta my way.
--[blow lands]
--[TODOROKI'S MOTHER yelps]
Momma?
[TODOROKI]
Shut up.
[TODOROKI sobbing]
[TODOROKI]
I don't want to, Mom.
Please, I--
I don't wanna be
the kind of guy he is.
someone who bullies you
and hurts people, Momma!
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
But, honey, you do still wanna
be a hero, don't you?
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
Just remember,
stay true to yourself.
You can be the kind of hero
you want to be when you grow up.
That's why I'm
going to win this!
I'll surpass you!
[CHILDREN laughing]
[ENDEAVOR]
Ignore them, Shoto.
They live in a different
world than the one
I'm training you for.
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
Mom?
I feel like I'm going crazy.
I can't take it anymore.
Every day, the children
seem more like him.
And Shoto.
That child's left side sometimes
looks unbearable to me.
All I can see is his father.
I can't raise him anymore.
I want to run away
from this life.
Mom, what're you saying?
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER gasps]
[TODOROKI]
I remember.
[thud]
[ENDEAVOR]
Moronic woman.
To hurt you at such
an important time.
Where did Momma go?
[ENDEAVOR]
Huh?
Oh, she hurt my masterpiece,
so I put her in a hospital
to keep you safe.
[TODOROKI]
That was your fault.
Huh?
You're the one who
made her hurt me!
[TODOROKI]
I will reject you.
I refuse to use my left side.
It's yours! Your Quirk, not his!
[gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Yes. That's right.
Children often do inherit
Quirks from their parents,
or develop similar power sets.
But the most important
thing to remember
is that a Quirk is
what you make of it,
regardless of your history.
You decide how you'll use it.
That's what I mean
when I say "I am here."
Only you can decide to
become a hero, no one else.
Take this to heart,
kids! You've got it!
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER]
Honey, you do still wanna
be a hero, don't you?
Just remember,
stay true to yourself.
[TODOROKI] I didn't realize
how much I'd forgotten.
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER] You are not
a prisoner of your lineage.
It's okay to use your power
to become who you want to be.
[PRESENT MIC gasps]
Is that...?
He's using his fire!
[TODOROKI] When I'm in battle,
I never use my left side.
Incredible.
[ALL MIGHT] You made him
use his father's power.
Midoriya. Don't tell me
you were trying to save
Young Todoroki this whole time!
[TODOROKI]
You're helping your opponent.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI]
You fool.
Even though you wanna
win this battle.
Now which one of us
is screwing around?
[IZUKU gasps]
I want it, too. I'll be a hero!
Yes, Shoto!
Huh?
Have you finally
accepted your purpose?
That's it. Very good.
This is the dawn
of a new era for us.
With my blood in your veins,
you'll surpass me.
You will live up to the
reason I created you!
[PRESENT MIC]
Endeavor suddenly shouts
words of... encouragement?
What a doting father.
Amazing.
[TODOROKI]
Why are you smiling?
With those injuries...
In this hopeless situation...
You must be crazy.
[IZUKU grunts]
Don't blame me
for what happens next.
That's it, Midnight.
One of them could be killed.
His body won't hold up!
[IZUKU] Gotta try and get
close and give it everything!
Come at me with your
full power, Todoroki!
I see now, Midoriya.
[TODOROKI]
Thank you.
[MIDNIGHT grunts]
[MINETA yelps]
Holy crap balls!
This is crazy!
What's happening down there?
[CEMENTOSS] Having a
great power doesn't mean
you'll be a good hero.
But these two are amazing.
[PRESENT MIC]
What happened just now?
What the heck is up
with your students?
[AIZAWA] The air around the
ring had been thoroughly
cooled down, and then rapidly
expanded when heated up.
Wait, that's what
caused the explosion?
How hot did that fire get?
Jeez, I can't see a thing!
Is the match still
going on, or what, huh?
[MIDNIGHT grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[MIDNIGHT]
There.
Midoriya is...
...out of bounds.
Todoroki wins!
He advances to the third round!
[CROWD cheers]
[TENYA]
Attention!
I'm Tenya Iida, the
resentative for Class 1-A!
I'll be responsible
for this preview!
[IZUKU]
That's the same way
you introduced
yourself last time.
[TENYA] Midoriya,
I swear that I will win
this next match and advance.
For both of us.
[IZUKU]
Yeah! I believe in you!
[TENYA]
I've come this far.
I have to keep going and become
number one for my family.
[IZUKU]
Next time: "Fight On, Iida!"
[TENYA]
Hello, Mother?
What do you mean it's Tensei?
How could this have
happened to my big brother?
[IZUKU]
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!