Welcome back to our live show.
For our next topic--
is it really necessary
for heroes to dress sexily?
Let's ask our very special
studio guests what they think.
She's the rookie hero
who debuted just this year.
It's Mt. Lady!
And she's a pro who's currently
teaching at UA High School;
the incomparable Midnight!
Thank you so much
for joining us!
Please, have a seat.
Let's start with you, Midnight.
When you first debuted,
your revealing outfit
caused quite a stir.
In fact, it eventually led to
the "Regulations for Exposed
Skin in Costumes" bill being
taken before the legislature.
You're a hero whose
sexiness changed
the very laws of the country.
Her costume's still pretty racy.
Now I rely on
ultra-thin fabrics.
Because of the nature
of some people's Quirks,
clothing can restrict
their abilities.
Sexiness isn't just
an aesthetic--
it's sometimes needed
so we can do our jobs well.
Besides, what's more
attractive than a hero
who can get the
job done quickly?
I think you just
like the attention.
What's with you, Lady?
Are you trying to start a fight?
[MT. LADY] Of course not!
I look up to you!
I think you're amazing!
For someone of your age.
You can act like the
blushing ingénue all you want,
but you're not that
young yourself, you know.
All I'm saying is if the
older pros try too hard,
then the rest of us
have to go even further!
[MIDNIGHT]
You little--!
[MT. LADY]
Hey, watch your hands!
[MIDNIGHT] Watch yourself!
That almost hurt!
[MT. LADY]
You're ripping my suit!
Ah! Thank you!
[school bell rings]
[AIZAWA] All right.
That's it for class today.
There's only one week left
before your final exams begin.
I'm sure you're all
studying constantly, right?
Don't forget to keep training.
The written exam
is only one element.
There's also the practical
portion to worry about.
Good luck.
[BOTH] I've barely even
taken notes this semester!
[KAMINARI] And with the
sports festival and internship,
I didn't have time
to read the textbook.
It's true that we haven't had
very much free time lately.
We'd barely learned anything
when we took our midterms
so they didn't seem
all that hard,
but I'm kinda worried
about these.
We've been through a lot,
and they probably won't pull
any punches when it
comes to testing us.
As someone ranked in the
top ten, I'm not that concerned.
[KAMINARI, ASHIDO] What?!
You were ninth in the midterms?!
Aw, man, and here I thought
you were one of us!
Don't you know weirdo
little creeps like you
are only likable if
they're kind of stupid?!
Who's going to love you now?!
Everyone. Trust me.
[IZUKU] Ashido, Kaminari!
We've still got time to study!
That way, we'll all get to go
to the training camp together.
Right?
Yes!
As class rep, I have high hopes
that we'll make UA proud.
It's pretty hard to fail
if you just pay attention
in class, isn't it?
Why you gotta cut
me down like that?
Hey, don't worry
about it, you two,
I can catch you up to speed
on the important
topics, if you want.
[BOTH]
You're the best, Yao-momo!
I'm afraid I won't be
any help when it comes
to the practical, though.
[TODOROKI]
Hm?
I've been studying, but...
could you help me out, too?
I'm having some
trouble understanding
quadratic functions.
Really?
Tutor me, please! Classical
Japanese is killin' me!
--[YAOYOROZU] Ah...
--Is there room for one more?
I'm afraid I'm falling
behind a little.
[JIRO, SERO, OJIRO]
Pretty please!
[gasps]
Wonderful!
Yes, let's do it!
[GROUP]
All right!
Okay, then. We can hold a
study session at my residence
over the weekend.
[ASHIDO] Seriously?! I can't
wait to see your fancy digs!
Oh! I must call Mother
and have her prepare
the great hall for us to set up;
it'll be the perfect spot.
[JIRO, KAMINARI]
"Great hall"?
What kind of tea
does everyone like?
I'll have her make
sure we're stocked.
[OJIRO, SERO]
That's overkill.
[YAOYOROZU]
In my family,
we always drink
Harrods or Wedgwood,
so if you have any other
preference, let me know!
When we're finished,
you'll all be model students!
I'll make it my personal duty
to push you forward.
[KAMINARI]
Is she humble bragging?
Or does she not even
realize what she's saying?
[JIRO] She's so excited and
bouncy that I don't even care.
About that tea--I'm not
so sure about the hairy one.
[YAOYOROZU]
No, it's from Harrods.
Sounds like I should
be studying with her.
You think I don't know enough?!
Maybe I should beat
the lessons into your skull!
[KIRISHIMA]
I'm counting on it.
Hah. Everyone's
panicking right now,
but it won't do them any good
to cram this late in the game.
[SHOJI]
Shouldn't you be more concerned?
You didn't do very well
in the midterms.
Are you talking about moi ?
I did just fine, thank you.
[IZUKU] I'm kinda scared
about the practical.
I have no idea
what it's gonna be.
Hard to believe they'd
give us anything too crazy.
The written exam questions will
all be stuff from class so...
...I should at least
be able to do those.
Do you really think
it's going to be that simple?
It's driving me nuts.
I just wanna know
what they'll have us doing.
[HAGAKURE] It's a comprehensive
test of everything
we learned this year.
Yup, and that's about all we
could get Mr. Aizawa to tell us.
Okay, so then it'll cover combat
training and rescue training.
Oh, and basic training.
We can't just study--we have to
stay in great physical shape--
[yelps]
[MONOMA]
Oh, sorry.
You're head's so big
that it's hard to miss.
[IZUKU]
You're from Class 1-B.
Um... Monoma, right?
That really hur--
[MONOMA] I heard you guys
stumbled across the Hero Killer.
[gasps]
Just like in the sports
festival, Class 1-A isn't happy
unless they're the
center of attention.
But you do realize you're not
in the spotlight because
people think you're
good heroes, right?
It's just that you keep
getting into so much trouble.
Here's food for thought:
Someday, the rest of us might
get caught up in your mess,
and then we'll all become
unwitting victims as well.
What kind of horrible villains
will you bring down upon us?
What demon--
[MONOMA grunts]
[KENDO]
That's not funny, Monoma.
You heard what happened
to Iida! Chill out!
[TENYA]
Kendo.
I apologize for him.
I'm pretty sure there's a hole
where his heart should be.
[IZUKU]
I think he's out!
[KENDO]
Mm. So I was listening...
I know you're all worried
about what's going to be
on the big final practical.
I heard it's gonna be
combat against robots,
like the entrance exam.
--[OCHACO] Huh?
--What? Really?
How do you know that?
One of my friends who's
a few grades up filled me in.
I know. Cheating. But oh, well.
[IZUKU]
No, I don't think so.
I'm sure gathering
information ahead of time
is also part of the test.
I definitely should've found
an upperclassman to ask.
Darn it, why didn't
I think about that before?
What kind of idiot
are you, Kendo?
You just gave away our
whole strategic advantage!
This was our chance
to finally pull ahead
of that class full of idiots.
[grunts]
[KENDO]
They're not the idiots!
[IZUKU] She's like their
class's big sister, huh?
[KAMINARI, ASHIDO]
All right!
This'll be super easy
if it's just robots!
Such awesome news!
Why do you sound so happy?
You both have a hard time
controlling your Quirks.
Yeah! But I can
let loose with robots!
And melting them'll
be a cinch for me!
Now you just need Yaoyorozu
to help you study
and you'll be all
set for finals.
[ASHIDO, KAMINARI]
We'll definitely be able
to go to the training camp now!
[ALL MIGHT]
As its holder, you may one day
have to fight against
this great evil yourself.
[IZUKU] In order
to be prepared for that,
I have to make everything
count from now on.
[KATSUKI] It shouldn't matter
if it's robots or actual people.
Why are you morons so excited?
Hey, who are you
calling a moron?!
Shut up! You need to learn
how to control your Quirk!
Ya got it?!
Hey! Deku!
[gasps]
I don't know what's
goin' on with your power,
but I saw the way you're using
it now, and I want you to know--
it's seriously pissing me off.
Uh-oh.
He must mean how Deku was flying
around like him the other day.
Oh, yeah, totally.
I won't have another half-assed
win like the festival.
We'll be getting individual
scores in the upcoming finals--
New rankings.
So we'll all know exactly
where we're standing!
I'll show you how
much better I am.
And, Todoroki?
I'll kill you, too.
It's been a while since
I've seen him that worked up.
Think it's impatience?
Or hatred?
[AIZAWA] Bakugo... You're
getting worse than I thought.
Wow...
I knew her family had cash, but
I didn't know she was this rich!
[door bell rings]
[YAOYOROZU] I've been
waiting for you, everyone!
Please, come in!
I could not feel any more
out of place right now.
[SERO]
Yeah, me, too.
Is something wrong?
[ALL]
No, everything's perfect!
All right, put your
pencils down.
The last person in each row,
bring the answer sheets to me.
Thanks so much
for all your help!
I didn't leave anything
blank at least!
[IZUKU]
Just like that,
our three days of
written exams were over.
Now it was time
for the practical.
Now then. Let's begin
the last test.
Remember, it's possible
to fail this final.
If you wanna go to camp, then
don't make any stupid mistakes.
Uh. Why are all
the teachers here?
[AIZAWA] I expect many of you
have gathered information
and believe you have some idea
of what you'll be
faced with today.
We're fightin' those
big ol' metal robots!
Fireworks! S'mores!
Here we come, camp!
[NEZU]
Actually, this year's tests...
...will be completely different,
for various reasons.
[JIRO, OJIRO, SERO]
Principal Nezu!
You're changing things?
The tests now have a new focus.
There will be Hero
work, of course.
But also teamwork and
combat between actual people.
So what does that mean for you?
You students will be
working together in pairs
and your opponents will be one
of our esteemed UA teachers!
Isn't that fabulous?!
We're... fighting the teachers?
[AIZAWA] Additionally, your
partners and your opponents
have already been chosen.
They were determined
at my discretion
based on various factors,
including fighting style,
grades, and interpersonal
relationships.
First, Yaoyorozu and
Todoroki are a team.
Against me.
Then we have Midoriya
paired with Bakugo.
[BOTH gasp]
[AIZAWA]
And their opponent is...
[IZUKU, KATSUKI gasp]
I am here to fight!
[BOTH]
We're up against All Might?!
You're going to have
to work together, boys,
if you want to win.
[KATSUKI growls]
[ALL MIGHT chuckles]
[NEZU] With the connection
between the Hero Killer Stain
and the League of Villains, it's
possible criminals everywhere
will become much bolder.
[SNIPE] It'd be best if we could
start preparin' for that
before it happens.
As a school, we should be
takin' every precaution.
If fights against villains
are gonna continue
to intensify in the future,
then havin' the kids train
against robots
ain't practical.
Originally, we used 'em
to avoid complaints about
people gettin' injured
in the entrance exams,
but they're just not
challengin' enough.
[AIZAWA]
We can ignore the complaints.
Let people say
whatever they want.
This sounds like it
could be problematic.
I understand why you
want to change the exam,
but having students fight us?
Even if they're in teams of two,
is that a good idea?
[THIRTEEN]
Yeah. I think it's a bit unfair.
If we win too easily,
we won't be able to give them
actual grades, yo.
[SNIPE] Of course, we could
take that into consideration
and give the students
an advantage.
Principal, what are
you thinking?
I believe I agree.
We need to change the
practical exam to reflect
the current times.
How do we ensure the
students aren't put in
life-threatening situations?
The answer is simple.
We must push them.
We make sure that they're
as strong as possible.
[MIDNIGHT]
That makes sense.
[THIRTEEN]
I agree.
[AIZAWA] Right, then let's
talk about the teams.
First, Todoroki. He's doing
quite well, generally speaking,
but relies too much
on brute force.
[AIZAWA] And Yaoyorozu
is an all-arounder,
but lacks the ability to make
spur-of-the-moment decisions
and apply them.
Therefore, I'll erase their
Quirks and take advantage
of their weaknesses.
[TEACHERS]
Sounds good.
[AIZAWA]
Next, for Midoriya and Bakugo,
I'm leaving them
to you, All Might.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
In this case, I didn't
pair the two of them up
based on ability or class work.
I went with relationships.
I know you've got a
soft spot for Midoriya.
Please ensure that
they learn something.
[ALL MIGHT] You're paying
close attention, huh, Aizawa?
And now, let's announce
the teams and the teachers
they'll be fighting in order!
To complete the exam,
you'll have 30 minutes.
In order to win, your objective
is to put these handcuffs
on your teacher.
Or you can win if one of you
manages to escape
from the combat stage.
So we've either got to capture
the teacher or run away.
It's basically like
the combat training.
Yeah, but is it really
okay to just jet?
Yup.
It's gonna be much different
than that combat training
y'all went through earlier.
After all, you're up against
people way better than you!
"Better"? Really?
Wait, aren't you
just the announcer?
Hey, watch your mouth,
girl--have some respect!
[THIRTEEN] This time,
your exam will be very similar
to a real battle.
As strange as it is,
please think of us as villains.
[SNIPE] Assumin' you
come across your enemy.
If you think you can win
against them, then fight.
However...
[AIZAWA] ...in instances
where you're outmatched,
it would be smarter to
run away and find help.
Todoroki. Iida. Midoriya.
I'm sure the three
of you understand.
[NATIVE]
Idiots!
The Hero Killer is only after me
and that kid in the white armor!
Stop fighting back--
just get out of here!
[TENYA] I won't make
that mistake again.
I will pass this test and
prove that I'm a hero!
So we fight to win...
or run to win.
That's right!
It's a test of your
decision-making skills.
But with these rules,
you're probably thinking
your only real
choice is to flee.
That's why the support
course made these
super-clever accessories for us.
[PRESENT MIC] Behold!
Ultra-compressed weights!
[ALL MIGHT] These babies will
add about half our body weight
to our physiques.
It's not much, but they
will eat up our stamina
and make it harder
for us to move around.
[grunts] Oh, shoot... These
are heavier than I thought.
We had a contest to come up
with these designs,
and Young Hatsume
ended up winning it.
Wow, good for Hatsume!
You think we need a handicap
to win against you?
Well think again.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
This'll be fun.
[AIZAWA]
Let's begin.
The teams will take the
practical exam in the order
you were called. We have
a stage prepared for you.
Sato, Kirishima. You're up.
[BOTH]
Yes, sir!
Those waiting their turn to
fight can either watch the exams
or try to strategize together
as a team. It's your choice.
That's all.
[TENYA]
Ojiro.
I'd like to discuss how we
might be able to coordinate
the use of our Quirks.
Great.
Tokoyami? Let's go
come up with a plan.
Agreed.
We've got to figure out a way to
destroy Ms. Midnight's costume!
[SERO]
You are such a little scumbag.
[RECOVERY GIRL]
Well, looks like I have
my work cut out for me today.
--[door hisses open]
--[OCHACO] Oh, Deku.
You're watching, too? Hi.
Yeah. It's not like
we get many chances
to watch students in combat
with teachers, right?
And besides...
...I don't think Kacchan really
wants to talk strategy with me.
[OCHACO]
I can see that.
And, uh, my partner is a
little preoccupied with himself.
[IZUKU whimpers]
You don't say...
[OCHACO] That's why I thought
I'd try and get inspiration
from everyone else's battles.
[IZUKU]
Smart.
[IZUKU] I have to pass this
test, no matter what it takes.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Team Sato and Kirishima.
Practical exam. Ready?
Go.
[KIRISHIMA]
So what do ya think?
We'll definitely get a
higher score for capturing
instead of running, you agree?
Yeah, that'd make sense.
Mr. Cementoss can't
move around very fast.
Let's break through
from the front
and shoot for a high score!
Aw, yeah!
[PRESENT MIC] Rikido Sato.
His Quirk: Sugar Rush!
For every ten grams of sugar,
he's five times as strong
for three minutes.
However, the more sugar
he uses for power,
the more his cognitive
functions suffer.
So you've decided on
a direct frontal assault.
This is it, Sato!
Let's go!
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH growl]
[yelling]
[yells]
[KIRISHIMA yells]
[BOTH yelling]
Not so fast, kids.
Come on, you guys!
You've totally got him!
They're not gonna
win it like this.
Huh?
[IZUKU]
Their Quirks are amazing,
but there's a limit to
how long they can use them.
They won't last forever.
I don't think Mr. Cementoss
has that kind of limit, though.
The more time that passes by,
the more of a
disadvantage they're at.
That's not good.
[IZUKU] It's no coincidence
they were matched up.
Mr. Aizawa's pitting
students against teachers
they'll have a
hard time against.
[gasps]
To pass, we'll have to
recognize our weaknesses...
...and overcome them.
[RECOVERY GIRL]
Exactly right.
So before it's time
for your own final,
you should think carefully
about your compatibility
with the teacher
you're fighting.
[IZUKU]
I knew it...
[yells] Man, this
is never-ending!
No matter how many
walls we break,
he keeps making more of 'em!
[groans] I'm tired...
So sleepy...
[KIRISHIMA]
Now's not the time!
--[SATO] Just a little nap...
--[KIRISHIMA grunting]
[KIRISHIMA grunts]
I'm running outta steam...
[BOTH scream]
[CEMENTOSS]
You're both weak when it comes
to long-term battles.
Listen well.
When your life is on the line,
you need to know exactly how far
you can push your powers.
[buzzer blares]
[ANNOUNCER A] Sato and Kirishima
have been knocked out.
Exam over.
--[ASHIDO gasps]
--Seriously?!
That fast?
Kirishima went down?
[RECOVERY GIRL]
It's only the first match
and I'm already needed.
[OCHACO]
No way... It was that one-sided?
Their Quirks were
too ineffective against his.
[IZUKU]
Crap...
Looks like this exam
is going to be a lot harder
than I thought it would be.
On top of that, we're up
against the number-one hero.
[TOKOYAMI]
I see.
They're starting us in
the middle of the stage.
[TSUYU] In order to escape,
we have to pass through
the designated gate, right?
Which means the teacher's
probably there waiting for us.
[buzzer blares]
[ANNOUNCER A]
Team Asui and Tokoyami.
Practical Exam. Ready? Go!
[ECTOPLASM]
Maybe you didn't understand,
but we teachers are
trying to crush you
with everything we've got.
No holding back.
--[TOKOYAMI gasps]
--[TSUYU] Ribbit!
[ECTOPLASM] Steel your nerves
and show me your resolve.
[IZUKU]
Now, the preview!
Asui and Tokoyami
are up against Ectoplasm!
And Todoroki and Yaoyorozu have
to fight against... Mr. Aizawa?
[AOYAMA] A-ha! This match
is going to end up
being très tragique .
Now hurry up so I can
finally take the stage.
[IZUKU] Aoyama, there's still
Iida and Ojiro's exam...
[AOYAMA] Like that'll last
more than a minute.
[IZUKU]
Why are you sparkling?
[AOYAMA]
Next time, "Yaoyorozu Rising."
I'm going to say something
shocking in the last scene,
so don't miss it.
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[AOYAMA]
Plus Ultra!
[IZUKU groans]