[IZUKU] The first incident
was in Qingqing City.
An extraordinary child was
born who radiated light.
[IZUKU] After that, reports
of people with superpowers
popped up across the globe.
No one knew what was
causing these Quirks.
The world became a
superhuman society,
with about 80 percent of
the population possessing
some uncanny ability.
Our streets looked like
scenes from comic books.
As cities swirled with
chaos and confusion,
a new profession dominated
our collective consciousness.
It was an age of heroes.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Fear not, citizens.
Hope has arrived.
Because I am here.
[yells]
[giggles] He's the coolest
in the whole world!
And once I get my Quirk, I'm
gonna be a hero just like him!
[IZUKU'S MOM] I'm sorry, Izuku.
I wish things were different.
[IZUKU]
I was born without superpowers.
Quirkless.
Just an ordinary kid.
I wanted to be like him
so badly, but I wasn't.
And so, I started to
give up on my dream.
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU] Still--even though my
brain told me I could never
be a pro, in my heart I knew
all I wanted was to be a hero.
And, thanks to the people who
guided me and supported me...
[IZUKU]
I am here now. On my way.
My dream is becoming a reality.
[IZUKU]
And though I've had setbacks,
I keep pushing forward.
[IZUKU]
My journey is just beginning.
You see, this is the story...
[IZUKU] ...of how I become
the world's greatest hero.
[NEWSCASTER 14A]
Up next: an update
on yesterday's
incident at the UA
rescue training center
where hero course students
were attacked by
a gang of villains.
According to new
police officials,
the criminal forces
called themselves
"The League of Villains."
Investigators have reportedly
uncovered that this group
has been plotting to kill
UA teacher and popular hero
All Might since the
spring of this year.
Police arrested 72
villains at the scene,
but the League's leader escaped.
His whereabouts are unknown.
[ALL MIGHT]
Greetings. The air is warm here.
It feels like summer is
just around the corner.
I hope this letter
finds you well, sir.
In good health and
even better spirits.
This semester,
I took a position
as a teacher at UA High School.
Heh. That's right.
I'm now guiding the next
generation of heroes.
I was hoping to
find someone worthy
of inheriting my power among the
elite students at the school.
A hero-in-training with
outstanding test scores
and a powerful Quirk.
However, before I
ever began my tenure
at UA, I met a young man.
Even though he was weak,
and had no Quirk of his own,
he showed incredible bravery.
He rushed into
a dangerous situation
that caused pro heroes,
including myself, to hesitate,
and managed to save
the life of a classmate.
He may not have had
a plan when he acted,
but he knew he had
to do something.
I feel like watching
this young man
spring into action taught
me something that day,
and it reminded me of
the virtues I must embody
in order to call
myself a pro. A hero.
That's why... I meant it
when I said to him:
"Young man. You, too,
can become a hero."
Soon after that, I told
this pupil the secret
of my Quirk, and proposed
that I transfer it to him.
This ability I have,
that's been passed on
from person to person,
cultivated, and made stronger,
the crystallization of
power that binds itself
to a courageous heart for
the good of those in need:
One For All.
He accepted without
hesitation, and I began
training him for the trials
he'd need to overcome
in order to be accepted
into the hero course
at UA High School.
Even though he
sometimes struggled
with his newfound abilities.
he never stopped fighting,
and gave 100 percent
as he tried to
harness One For All.
I don't like to
toot my own horn,
but I believe I found
the perfect person
to pass my Quirk on to.
He has shown me time
and again that he has
what it takes to be a real hero.
I'm still quite new to
the role of instructor.
The day may come when
I must trouble you,
my old teacher, for advice.
I'll be counting
on your wisdom
and patience when
that time comes.
Until then, please
take care of yourself
as the seasons begin to change.
I'll continue to
keep you updated
about what's happening.
Sincerely yours.
[GRAN TORINO] So, Toshinori
has found a worthy successor.
[TSUKAUCHI] Our investigators
are trying to learn
everything they can about this
so-called "League of Villains."
We've made some progress,
but we can't find anything
on this Shigaraki so far.
We've searched our
records for men
in their 20s or 30s who
are registered as having
some sort of
disintegration Quirk,
but so far, we've come up empty.
Same for the Warp Gate
villain, Kurogiri.
So they're not citizens
or they're using aliases.
Hard to find, either way.
So what you're really saying
is we don't know anything.
[SNIPE]
We've gotta track 'em down.
I shot their ringleader, but
once he heals up he'll probably
try pullin' somethin'
like this again.
What a pain.
He did seem like the type.
Is something on
your mind, All Might?
[ALL MIGHT] The attack
on the USJ was too bold.
No sane adult would
ever attempt it.
The ringleader kept monologuing
about the reasons he was there.
And he bragged about
Nomu's many Quirks,
but he never said a word
about his own powers.
When things didn't go his way,
he was visibly upset.
Like he was gonna
throw a tantrum.
Ah, I guess bragging
about Nomu's Quirks
was a quick way to
draw me into a fight.
That might be true,
yes, but strategically,
it was foolish to reveal
his Quirks up front
instead of keeping
them a secret.
[ALL MIGHT] Shigaraki made
wild, immature claims,
but did so with a
completely straight face.
And he talked about Nomu
like he was some kind of a pet.
It seemed like he'd never
been told "no" before--
like he thought things would
go his way no matter what.
He has the personality
of a spoiled little
brat. A man-child.
A child with incredible
power, though.
It's possible he never
got the Quirk counseling
students receive
in elementary school.
[SNIPE] Maybe so, but it
doesn't really matter now.
[TSUKAUCHI]
There were 72 villains arrested
in the aftermath
of the USJ attack.
They were all small-time thugs
who usually lurked
around back alleys.
What worries me is
that this "man-child"
got them all to
follow his crazy plan.
They viewed him
as a real leader.
Criminals are starting
to feel more pressure
now that the world is
brimming with heroes.
That could be why they
were so quick to back
such simple-minded villainy.
Guess that makes sense.
[SNIPE] There are plenty a'
people out there lookin'
for a cause to get behind.
So, what can we do to stop them?
Well, it is thanks to
you heroes that we have
the time to devote
ourselves to this case.
We'll expand our
investigation and continue
searching for the perpetrators
who planned this attack.
A man-child, huh?
In some ways, he shares common
ground with our students.
They both have
so much potential.
And, like our students,
I suppose it's possible
someone is guiding him,
trying to nurture
his malice and villainy.
[ALL MIGHT sighs]
[ALL MIGHT] I don't wanna think
about what that could mean.
[DOG barking]
[IZUKU]
School was closed the day after
the League of Villains
attacked the USJ.
I think they wanted us
to have a little break,
but it was pretty
tough to relax.
[MAN 1A]
Who is he?
The guy's already saved
100 people at least,
and it hasn't even
been ten minutes.
This is-- This is crazy!
I can't believe it!
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[CAMERAMAN 1A]
Look, he's got more!
Fear not, citizens!
Hope has arrived!
Because I am here!
[IZUKU] I'm still so far away
from becoming a real hero.
During the USJ attack,
all my classmates and I did
was slow Mr. Aizawa
and Thirteen down.
If it weren't for
All Might and our teachers,
we never would have stood a
chance against those villains.
[IZUKU]
In order to truly oppose evil,
I have to make
All Might's power my own.
I have to embody
One For All and master
every aspect of it, until
it's second nature for me.
Because... there
isn't much time left.
And because I'm the one he
chose, I'll make him proud!
[knocking]
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Izuku?
[IZUKU]
Yeah?
Lunch time. Your
food's getting cold.
I'll be right there.
Thanks, Mom.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Eat up!
Those new muscles
need lots of fuel.
[HAGAKURE]
You guys!
Did you watch the
news last night?
Yeah.
[HAGAKURE]
It was so cool that we got
a few seconds of screen time!
Though I bet nobody
noticed me hanging out
in the background.
[SHOJI]
Probably not.
It is difficult to stand out
when you're just gloves.
We're totally big deals.
Those news channels love us--
we're basically celebrities.
Yeah, it's kinda crazy, right?
Get over yourselves.
The hero course that pumps
out pros was attacked,
and that's what they care about.
Who knows what
woulda happened to us
if the teachers hadn't shown up.
Why'd you say that?
I'm gonna pee myself
just thinking about it.
Oh, shut up!
Grow a pair, loser!
Did you guys see All Might
fighting the bird guy?
That dude was super strong,
and he still destroyed him!
Yes.
His is strength is truly
a thing of wonder.
Attention!
Homeroom class is
about to begin!
Everyone stop talking
and take your seats.
[KIRISHIMA]
Uh, we're all sitting.
[SERO] Yeah, You're the
only one standing.
Dang it!
Don't sweat it.
Hey, Tsu.
So... Who do ya think's
gonna teach class today?
No idea.
Mr. Aizawa's still
in the hospital
--recovering from his injuries.
--[door scrapes]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[AIZAWA]
Morning, class.
[STUDENTS] Mr. Aizawa,
what are you doing here?
Whoa! What a pro.
[TENYA] Mr. Aizawa.
I'm glad you're okay.
You call that "okay"?
[AIZAWA]
My well being is irrelevant.
What's more important is that
your fight isn't over yet.
Our fight?
Don't tell me...
Not more bad guys!
The UA Sports Festival
is about to start.
Yes!
[STUDENTS] Ugh! Why would
you scare us like that?
[STUDENTS]
The sports festival!
Let's go kick some ass!
Wait a second.
Is it really such a good idea
to hold the sports festival
so soon after the
villains snuck inside?
They could attack once
we're all in the same place.
[AIZAWA] Apparently, the
administration thinks this is
a good way to show that
the threat has been handled
and our school
is safer than ever.
Plus they're beefing up security
compared to past years.
This event is a huge opportunity
for all students at UA.
It's not something we can cancel
because of a few villains.
Uh, I'm sorry, but why not?
It's just a sports festival!
Huh? Mineta, don't you
know how important
this competition is?
Of course I do!
I just don't wanna get murdered.
[AIZAWA] Our sports
festival is one of the
most-watched events
in the entire world.
In the past, everyone obsessed
over the Olympic games.
But then Quirks
started appearing.
Now, the Olympics
have been drastically
reduced in terms of
scale and viewership.
For anyone who cares
about competition,
there's only one
tournament that matters.
The UA Sports Festival.
That's right!
And top heroes everywhere
will be watching.
This is where you get scouted.
Sure, unless you're dead.
She's right.
After graduating,
a lot of people
join pro agencies as a sidekick.
Yeah, but that's as far
as some people go.
They miss their
chance to go indie
and stay eternal sidekicks.
Actually, that's probably
where you're headed.
You're kinda dumb.
[AIZAWA] It's true that
joining a famous hero agency
can garner you greater
experience and popularity.
That's why the festival matters.
If you wanna go pro
one day, then this event
could open the path for you.
One chance a year.
Three chances in a lifetime.
No aspiring hero can afford
to miss this festival.
[AIZAWA] That means you
better not slack off
on your training.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[AIZAWA]
Class is dismissed.
[school bell chimes]
[KIRISHIMA]
That villain stuff sucked, sure,
but I'm pumped for these games!
We put on a good show,
and we're basically
on the road to bein' pros!
Yeah, this is why I'm even
here in the first place.
We get so few chances.
We have to make
the most of this.
[HAGAKURE] Oh, man, Ojiro,
I'm getting kind of nervous
about the festival.
I have to come up with
a way to get noticed!
--[OJIRO] Uh, sure.
--[HAGAKURE] Maybe with a cheer!
Maybe you should be looking at
a shinier costume or something?
Otherwise, you're gonna
have to try really hard.
My, what's a boy to do?
I stand out even when
I'm standing still.
That means the scouts
won't be able
to take their eyes off me!
Don't you agree?
[sighs] You're so lucky, Shoji.
People are bound to
notice your unique Quirk.
[SHOJI] Sure, but what
matters is that I show them
how useful I can be.
No doubt you'll
make a scene, too.
[KAMINARI growls]
This is gonna be nuts!
Everyone's so excited.
Well, yeah, of course we are!
We enrolled at this school with
the sole aim to become heroes.
So naturally, we're
all getting fired up.
Wow, Iida.
Those are some
interesting moves. Ribbit.
You have to be excited,
too, right, Midoriya?
Well, yeah, of course I am!
And also nervous.
[OCHACO]
Deku! Iida!
--[TENYA] Uh...
--[IZUKU] Ah.
Let's do our best
in the sports festival.
[IZUKU] Uraraka, what
happened to your face?
Seriously, what's up?
You're normally, like,
the most laid back girl ever.
PMS?
[OCHACO grunts]
Everyone! I'm gonna do my best!
[TENYA, IZUKU]
Yeah!
[ASHIDO]
I said, I'm gonna do my best!
--[KIRISHIMA] Got it...
--[SATO] Uh...
[KIRISHIMA]
You okay?
Ya kinda look like
you're losin' it.
[IZUKU]
Now that I think about it...
There's something I've
been meaning to ask her.
[IZUKU]
Hey, Uraraka?
[OCHACO]
What's up?
[IZUKU] Why did you
decide to come to UA?
What made you wanna
be a pro hero?
[OCHACO gasps]
Oh...
Well... Because...
Uh-- For the money?
You wanna be a hero
so you can get rich?
If we're cutting to
the chase, then, yeah.
I'm sorry if it sounds greedy.
You two have such
admirable motivations.
I hope you don't
think less of me now.
Not at all!
Your goal is to
support your wellbeing,
which is a perfectly
admirable ambition to have.
[IZUKU] Mm-hm. It's just
kinda surprising.
[OCHACO sighs]
Well, you see,
my family owns
a construction company,
but we haven't gotten any work
lately, so we're flat broke.
Anyway, this isn't
really something I usually
tell other people, but...
Construction, eh?
[gasps] If she got licensed,
I bet she could use her Quirk
to bring costs down a lot.
And they could sell their
heavy-lifting equipment.
She could float everything!
I know, right?
I've been telling Dad
that since I was a kid!
But...
[OCHACO'S DAD]
You want to work for us?
When I grow up
all big and strong,
I'll help you and Mommy
out any way that I can.
[chuckles]
[OCHACO'S DAD] I really
appreciate the thought, Ochaco.
But as your dad,
I'd be even happier
if you achieved your own dream.
That's the way to make us happy.
And if you do make money,
you can take us to
Hawaii or something!
Daddy...
[OCHACO]
I'm gonna become a pro.
I'll sign with a good agency
and make plenty of money.
Then I'll be able to let my
parents have an easy life!
[BOTH gasp]
That's beautiful!
So noble!
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
[IZUKU] She's not here because
of some hero fantasy.
She's more grounded
than any of us.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
Young Midoriya is here!
Whoa, All Might!
What are you doing here?
Lunch! Ya wanna eat with me?
[OCHACO]
That's adorable!
[ALL MIGHT]
Whaddaya say?
Sure thing!
[IZUKU]
Is something wrong?
[OCHACO] I wonder what
he wanted with Deku.
I heard that when
All Might was attacked
by villains during
the USJ incident,
Midoriya tried to
stop them himself.
Perhaps that's what
this is about.
Oh, yeah!
Also, remember what
Asui said on the bus?
That power of yours...
Isn't it a lot like All Might's?
Since their Quirks are
so similar to each other,
it's possible that All Might's
taken a liking to him.
How lucky!
[TODOROKI] All Might and
Izuku Midoriya, huh?
[IZUKU]
Only 50 minutes?
[ALL MIGHT]
Yeah.
That's about how long
I can use my power now.
I overdid it too many times.
That Nomu was a
real tough customer.
He took a lot outta me.
At this point, I can
barely even look like
All Might for an
hour and a half.
I'm so sorry.
I should've just--
--[IZUKU yelps]
--[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[ALL MIGHT] You don't need
to apologize for anything!
Man, we are alike, you and me.
Have some tea.
[IZUKU]
Thanks.
I brought you here to
talk about the festival.
The problem is, you still can't
fully control One For All yet.
So then, what's your plan?
[gasps] Wait, I did once!
When I landed a smash
on that brain villain,
there was no backlash at all!
Oh, that's right,
you did mention that.
What was different
about that smash?
Let's see...
We were facing real villains
and I didn't have
much time to think,
but maybe that's part
of it, since I knew
this wasn't just more training.
[THIRTEEN] I'm sure you're
aware that I have
a powerful Quirk.
It's called Black Hole.
I can use it to suck up
anything and turn it into dust.
But my Quirk could
also very easily
be used to kill.
This was the very
first time, ever,
that I used my power
against a person.
[ALL MIGHT] Hm... Sounds like
you succeeded in subconsciously
putting on the brakes so so you
wouldn't have to kill anyone.
Hey, that's some kind of
progress at least.
[ALL MIGHT]
Tea's gettin' cold.
Oh, right, thank you.
[ALL MIGHT] To be frank,
I don't have much time left
as the world's Symbol of Peace.
Soon, I'll have to
put that title to bed.
No way...
And some villains out there
are startin' to notice that.
Someone has to step up
and keep the people safe.
[gasps]
I gave you my power
for one reason:
'Cause you will be the
hero who takes my place.
[IZUKU] I want to be the
greatest hero in the world!
I want to save people
just like you do.
When they see my fearless
smile, they'll feel safe.
[ALL MIGHT] Do you still
feel the same way you did
when we met? Do you
still wanna be a hero?
Yes.
Excellent.
The time has come
for you to prove it.
[gasps]
This sports festival:
it's something that the pros--
no, the entire country will
be watching very closely.
Uh...
I want you to think
of this sports festival
as your debut. You are the
fledgling Symbol of Peace.
The next All Might!
Izuku Midoriya.
[ALL MIGHT] I want you to
introduce yourself to the world
and proudly say "I am here!"
[ALL MIGHT] The next
episode preview is here!
[IZUKU] The UA Sports Festival
is finally starting!
[ALL MIGHT] The first event
is an obstacle course
everyone participates in.
And, there's no
limit to Quirk use.
[IZUKU] Doesn't that sound
kind of dangerous?
[ALL MIGHT] Regardless,
you must aim for the top!
Show the world that
you're Izuku Midoriya,
the world's next great hero!
[IZUKU] Next time:
"Roaring Sports Festival"!
[ALL MIGHT] Ooh, don't
miss Young Todoroki
pick a fight with
Young Midoriya!
[IZUKU]
Uh, go beyond!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Plus Ultra!