[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
with 80 percent of us possessing
some uncanny ability.
Cities swirled with
chaos and confusion
following the appearance
of these powers,
and a new profession emerged.
We called those
who fight for justice
and help others
in need, "heroes."
Oh, by the way,
this is the story
of how I became
the world's greatest hero!
[CROWD cheering]
[PRESENT MIC] Welcome back
to the finals, everyone!
Sorry for that long wait.
The insane amount of ice
from the second match
has finally been
cleared, though,
so it's time to
welcome new competitors!
Even beautiful flowers
have thorns.
It's the assassin
from Class 1-B.
Ibara Shiozaki from
the hero course!
Versus the boy with
the electric personality!
Another hero in the
making, Denki Kaminari!
[CROWD cheering]
Keep those eyes peeled.
I wanna see a super-flashy
battle this time!
[SHIOZAKI]
Excuse me!
Please pardon the interruption.
I'm not sure why you
called me an assassin.
I've come to the festival
in search of victory,
not to take my opponent's life.
That wouldn't be in line
with the values of
a hero at all, sir.
Right. I'm sorry.
Gentlemen, I didn't
enter UA for wicked
or selfish reasons, but to
deliver salvation to others!
It is my humble quest to spread
true good across this world.
[PRESENT MIC]
Listen, I said I was sorry!
That was my bad, okay?
I thank you for your
kind understanding.
I thought everyone in
Class 1-B was a jerk.
[KAMINARI] Look at those
big beautiful eyes.
And it looks like she
might be strong, too.
Come on, you idiot--remember,
this is a competition.
But, oh, man,
she's so cute, though.
This is terrible. I'm gonna have
to ask this girl out sometime.
[KAMINARI]
Once I win this!
[PRESENT MIC]
So, anyway. Begin!
What do ya say me and
you go out after this?
I'd be happy to
treat you to a bite.
Hm?
[KAMINARI]
And comfort you after your loss.
'Cause this is all gonna be
over in two seconds, honey.
Indiscriminate Shock.
One point three million volts!
[KAMINARI]
Uh?
Uh, what?
[yelps]
[PRESENT MIC] He's immobilized!
That's all, folks!
It was over in an instant!
The winner is Shiozaki!
She advances on!
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIOZAKI] I'm just so thankful
that I was able to make
the most of the opportunity
I was given today.
[PRESENT MIC] Ibara Shiozaki.
Her Quirk: Vines!
The vines on her head can
extend to great lengths.
Plus, they're detachable!
As long as she gets plenty
of water and sunlight,
they can grow instantly!
It's one killer head a' hair.
Oh, yeah! Way to
represent Class 1-B!
Man, she's good.
[MONOMA]
Guess he was right.
That match really was
over in just two seconds.
I wonder if his real
Quirk is the ability
to tell the future.
Hey! Wasn't Class 1-A supposed
to be so much better than us?
[laughing]
[KENDO grumbles]
[MONOMA grunts]
Sorry 'bout him.
[YAOYOROZU, JIRO, ASHIDO, TSUYU]
I hate that guy.
[MT. LADY]
Kamui, did you watch that?
[KAMUI WOODS]
Hm?
[MT. LADY]
Wouldn't she make, like,
the perfect sidekick for you?
[KAMUI WOODS]
Yeah, wish I coulda seen more.
She's great for your brand.
You need someone cute!
[KAMUI WOODS]
Just get back to work.
[HERO 20D] As soon as she
detached her vines, it was over.
No way was he going
to avoid those.
[HERO 20A] Yeah, and his
electric current couldn't
travel through them,
so he couldn't hurt her.
Excellent offense and defense.
[HERO 20B] That binding hold
was really impressive.
Smart girl. Kaminari never
stood a chance against her.
[HERO 20A]
It's tough when someone's Quirk
cancels yours out, but he still
could've put up a fight.
[IZUKU] I've seen Kaminari
in action--he's super strong.
But Shiozaki placed fourth
in the entrance exam.
And those vines.
I wonder if she's studied
Kamui Woods' moves.
Binding attacks can
be really powerful.
I hardly ever see anyone
break out when they're used.
It would be impossible
to get close to her
while avoiding all
those thorns and vines.
You'd have to find
some way to tear them off
or just hack your way
through using brute force.
Oh, but in order to keep
you from doing that,
she'd probably go after
your hands first,
so then what do you do?
Maybe you should
take a sec to relax
before planning too
many matches ahead.
[IZUKU yelps]
Oh, sorry!
Sometimes I don't realize
I'm talking out loud
when I'm taking notes.
t's not every day I get
to see incredible Quirks
from people outside our class!
[OCHACO chuckles]
Uh, actually...
I've been taking notes on
everybody in our class, too!
Here's what I've got
on your Zero Gravity!
Uh--
[chuckles] Y'know, Deku,
I've always know
that you're amazing.
You've got so much drive
and focus in you.
And the sports festival's
reminding me of that.
Uh?
[PRESENT MIC] Let's keep pumpin'
out these hits and move on!
Time for the fourth match!
Get ready to watch two
new players duke it out!
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC] He's the kid
with engines in his legs.
Tenya Iida from the
hero course! Versus...
...a fully-equipped
gadget dynamo.
The support course's
Mei Hatsume!
So it's hero class
versus support.
I have no idea what this
fight will look like.
Uh, what's up with Iida?
[SATO] Where the heck did he
get all that weird gear from?
Hero course students
can't use support gear
unless they have to.
And you didn't fill out any of
the proper paperwork for that.
[gasps] I didn't know
that was the rule!
Aoyama got to wear his belt,
so I thought it was fine.
[MIDNIGHT]
He turned in the proper forms.
I apologize, ma'am.
It's just that,
my heart was moved
by my opponent's sportsmanship.
Even though she's from
the support course,
she wanted this to be as
even a match as possible
since she made it this far.
To have a fair fight!
So, she offered to
give me this equipment.
I respect her integrity.
That's why, to honor her,
I would like to wear this gear!
Such youthful vigor!
[giggles]
I'll allow it.
[PRESENT MIC]
Really?
[AIZAWA] I guess if everyone's
in agreement, then it's okay.
Right?
[IZUKU] Weird, that doesn't
seem like something
Hatsume would do. Unless...
[giggles]
[PRESENT MIC] Well, if
everyone's on the same page,
let's begin the fourth match!
[CROWD cheers]
Bet you love how fast
that gear makes you!
Huh, Iida?
She's got a mic?
Hey, now.
[AIZAWA]
Is she wearing speakers?
[TENYA panting]
[HATSUME] Don't your legs
feel lighter than usual?
That's to be expected.
I designed those leg parts
specifically to increase
the wearer's speed and mobility.
But, of course...
[TENYA yelps]
[HATSUME]
I can easily evade you
with my hydraulic attachments!
[HATSUME] Those are boxes
for support companies.
[HATSUME squeals]
They love my babies!
I've got this in the bag!
[PRESENT MIC]
Mei Hatsume. Her Quirk: Zoom!
If she gets serious, she can
see up to five kilometers away!
Since I've got sensors
in every direction,
it's impossible for an
opponent to sneak up on me!
[TENYA yelps]
What the heck is going on?
Look at how adeptly Iida
just changed his course!
It's all thanks to the ingenious
auto-balancer I created.
This is weird.
[AIZAWA]
She's turning the festival
into one big commercial.
[HATSUME]
There's absolutely no lag time!
[TENYA growls]
[HATSUME]
The auto-balancer is equipped
with a custom
32-axis gyro sensor!
As you can see, it can
keep the user from falling
unless they actually want to.
I thought you said you wanted
this to be a fair fight!
[yells]
[HATSUME cackles]
That's right, I'm practically
flying through the air!
These electro shoes use
electromagnetic induction
on both feet. They're perfect
for evasive maneuvers
or just keeping things light!
As soon as she lands,
I'll stop her!
Huh? What is this?
[HATSUME] A capture gun
to use against villains!
The nets are loaded
into small cartridges.
You can fire up to five
before having to reload!
And all of these
items were developed
by yours truly--Mei Hatsume,
support course prodigy!
So, to any support
companies out there
looking for strong new recruits,
the choice is clear.
You want me!
Again, I'm Mei Hatsume,
that's H-A-T-S-U-M-E.
She's something.
[HATSUME]
And now, let me introduce you
to a few more of my babies.
Wait, there's more?
[HATSUME] Whew! That was fun,
but I think now I've shown off
everything I wanted to.
I suppose it's time for me
to wrap this show up.
Uh, Hatsume stepped
out of bounds,
so Iida advances
to the next round.
[TENYA] I can't believe
I let you trick me!
Sorry about that.
I needed to use you to
make a name for myself.
[TENYA]
I looked like a fool!
Iida's so sincere,
he trusted her motives.
She probably made it sound like
she was doing him a favor.
She's so driven.
Straightforward about her goals.
And from what I can tell,
she'll pretty much do
whatever it takes to reach them.
Amazing.
[CROWD cheering]
[PRESENT MIC]
We're gonna charge right along
to the fifth match.
Let's hope that gaudy belt
serves some kinda purpose.
It's Yuga Aoyama
from the hero course!
Bonjour.
[PRESENT MIC]
Versus...
Is there some kinda
purpose for those things
sticking out of her head?
From the same class,
Mina Ashido!
This match is gonna
be a piece a' cake.
I do believe you're going to be
eating those
words, mademoiselle.
Come on, Mina, you can do it!
[MINETA] Don't show her
any mercy, Aoyama!
Fight like you're in
one of those video games
where everyone's clothes
get beaten off!
[JIRO]
You pervert!
A match between
Aoyama and Ashido.
Let's see. Considering
what their powers are,
Aoyama will probably
keep his distance
and try to attack with
his laser from far away.
So it'll all depend on
whether or not Ashido
can dodge his attacks
and manage to use her power
against him in close combat.
Problem is, there's nothing
much for her to use
as cover in this ring.
So she's at a
slight disadvantage.
Now let's get started!
Fifth match... Begin!
[AOYAMA]
Navel laser, activate!
Think again!
We were on the same team
for combat training,
so I know all about
your Quirk, Aoyama.
I can say the same
thing about you.
Sure, but there's
a big difference.
I remember something you said.
Shooting my beam for
more than a second
can sometimes hurt my tummy.
I know your weakness!
Here's a big one!
Ow. My tummy.
There's my shot!
Oh, no! Oh, no, no, no!
Not my precious belt!
[yelps]
[AOYAMA]
My pants!
For my finishing move...
...an uppercut!
[AOYAMA whimpering dramatically]
[MIDNIGHT]
Aoyama has fainted!
The winner of this
match is Ashido!
Dang, Aoyama went down hard!
That's an indisputable victory
if I've ever seen
one, sports fans!
Wow, Mina is amazing!
[thud]
I got to see panites,
but why were they his?
[JIRO]
Oh, for crying out loud.
[MINETA whimpers]
[sighs]
[IZUKU] The match unfolded
like I though it would,
but I definitely
underestimated Ashido.
Although, now that I think
about it, she did place ninth
outta the class in that
Quirk assessment test.
She has a great
power, but she won
because of her
physical strength.
[PRESENT MIC] Now, let's not
let this hot streak cool.
Time to move on
to the sixth match!
[KAMUI WOODS]
We're not here to watch TV!
[PRESENT MIC]
Offense and defense in one!
The dark samurai and
his darker shadow!
From the hero course,
Fumikage Tokoyami!
Versus...
The great creator!
She was admitted
because of recommendations
and I think we can all see why.
Also from Class 1-A,
Momo Yaoyorozu!
How do you think this
one will end? Any clue?
Timing is going to be
the key thing here.
Oh? How so?
[YAOYOROZU] Present Mic's
description of Tokoyami
was accurate. With Dark Shadow,
he's skilled at both
attacking and defending.
He can also call upon
the creature instantaneously,
so there's little doubt
he'll start the match
with a preemptive strike.
If I can make a simple
shield, I can block him.
But I'll have to
be fast about it,
or else this fight will be
over in a matter of seconds.
Just like that.
Then, if I have
enough time to make...
[PRESENT MIC]
Sixth match... Begin!
Go, Dark Shadow!
[DARK SHADOW]
I've got her!
[YAOYOROZU]
Quickly! A shield!
Now it's my turn to attack!
[YAOYOROZU]
I can't focus on my Quirk!
[yelps]
[YAOYOROZU yelps]
[YAOYOROZU] Why has he
stopped? This is my chance!
[MIDNIGHT]
Yaoyorozu!
You're out!
[gasps]
[MIDNIGHT]
This match goes to Tokoyami!
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC] Yikes! Another
fast, overwhelming victory!
Is it possible that
Tokoyami's Dark Shadow
is the greatest Quirk
ever? I think so!
I lost...
I didn't even... do anything.
Tokoyami is way too powerful.
I can't believe he
forced her out of bounds
by focusing his
attacks on her shield.
He obviously had a
strategy worked out.
Yeah, I guess so.
Maybe he didn't wanna hurt her.
I bet she's really upset
about how that went down.
[OJIRO]
I feel bad for her.
[PRESENT MIC] Okay, let's see
who we've got for ya next.
[PRESENT MIC]
The seventh matchup includes
two completely redundant Quirks!
One of them's a passionate,
manly fighter made of steel.
The hero course's
Tetsutetsu Tetsutetsu!
Bring it!
[PRESENT MIC]
Versus...
...a passionate, manly
fighter made of rock!
The hero course's
Eijiro Kirishima!
Seriously, even our
intros are the same?
Make us proud, Tetsutetsu!
Win just like Ibara did!
[snoring]
Look alive, shorty.
[yelps]
[PRESENT MIC] Can't wait to
see how this one ends!
Begin!
[yells]
[KIRISHIMA, TETSUTETSU grunt]
[TENYA sighs]
[OCHACO] Hey, Iida,
you did great out there.
Oh. Urara--
Whoa, what's with
that face? Ugh!
My face?
Oh, it's nothing!
I guess I'm not great at
hiding how nervous I am.
I get that. You are up
against Bakugo, after all.
Not exactly an easy match.
Yeah, I'm kinda scared.
But, you know, after seeing your
match, I feel a little better.
What's that supposed to mean?
[door clicks]
[IZUKU]
Uraraka!
[OCHACO]
Deku!
Why aren't you out there
watching the matches?
Well, most of them ended
how I expected them to.
And, it's looking
like Kirishima's fight's
going to drag on
for quite a while.
[yelling]
I thought you were
supposed to be strong!
Funny, I heard the
same lie about you!
I'm next.
So this is it. My fight.
It'll be okay!
I don't think Bakugo
would use the full power
of his explosions
on a girl, right?
Yeah, he would.
[OCHACO whimpers]
And besides, everyone's
trying to get the top spot
in these games. Even if she
wasn't fighting Kacchan,
I don't think anyone
would hold back.
You've helped me so much.
It's my turn to help you.
Maybe I can repay you
a little bit with this.
[IZUKU] I've got a plan
for how you can use
your Quirk against Kacchan.
It's not much,
but I did my best.
Hey! Well, all right!
This is perfect!
[OCHACO] Thank you
so much for doing that.
But, no. Sorry.
What?
[OCHACO]
You're wonderful, Deku.
I keep seeing that
over and over again.
During the cavalry
battle, I told you
it was good to
team up with friends.
But now that I think about it,
I might've been trying
to rely on you to get by.
That's why
when Iida said that he was
trying his best to beat you,
I actually felt kind of
embarrassed for myself.
Uraraka...
So it's fine. Really.
[OCHACO]
Everyone's facing their future
and giving this their best.
That means we're all rivals.
Even you and me, Deku. So...
Guess I'll see you
in the finals.
[KIRISHIMA grunts]
[TETSUTETSU grunts]
[TETSUTETSU, KIRISHIMA
grunt, groan]
[yelling]
[PRESENT MIC] Wow, that
hurt me and all I'm doin'
is watchin' these guys!
Is it over?
The hardheads look
like they're KO'd!
But who is the winner?
They're both down! It's a draw!
When the contestants
recover from this battle,
the winner will be determined
by a simple contest.
Perhaps arm wrestling.
Weird, they're basically
copies of each other.
You gotta appreciate the passion
they brought to the ring.
It's inspiring, really.
I could use a good
sidekick like that.
[PRESENT MIC] While we wait
for Tetsutetsu and Kirishima
to recover, we'll move on
to the next battle.
[CROWD cheers]
Ribbit. This might be the
most disturbing matchup.
I know. I almost
don't wanna watch it.
[BOTH gasp]
[IZUKU]
Do your best. You got this.
[PRESENT MIC]
The eighth and final battle
in the first round of matches.
He was kind of a hot shot
in middle school,
and just look at
that determined face!
From the hero course,
Katsuki Bakugo.
Versus...
The one I'm personally
rooting for,
also from Class 1-A,
Ochaco Uraraka!
[inhales]
[exhales]
[PRESENT MIC]
Let the eighth match... begin!
[OCHACO]
Oh, hi, Deku.
I guess we should do
the preview now, huh?
[IZUKU] Uraraka, why do
you sound so down?
Oh, wait, it's because your
first match is against Kacchan.
[OCHACO]
But I can beat him!
I have to so I can get
scouted and become a hero.
Then my parents can
have an easy life!
Deku! I'll meet you
in the final match!
[IZUKU] That's the spirit!
Good luck, Uraraka!
[OCHACO]
Next time: "Bakugo vs. Uraraka"!
[IZUKU] An unexpected meteor
shower could pave the way
for your path to victory!
[OCHACO]
I'm gonna go beyond!
[OCHACO, IZUKU]
Plus Ultra!