[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
with 80 percent of us
possessing some uncanny ability.
Cities swirled with
chaos and confusion
following the appearance
of these powers,
and a new profession emerged.
[IZUKU] We call those
who fight for justice
and help others
in need, "heros."
Oh, by the way,
this is the story
of how I became
the world's greatest hero.
[IZUKU] All three of them
put their trust in me.
This is my responsibility.
We all have our
reasons to win this.
And I refuse to
let the others down!
It was around his head,
where his guard was the weakest.
Midoriya,
you're the one who created
the opening for me,
and ensured our advancement.
[PRESENT MIC] And in fourth
place is Team Midoriya!
These four valiant teams
will advance on
to the final round!
[PRESENT MIC]
Now for a lunch break before
the afternoon
festivities. See ya!
[STUDENT 19A]
Ugh, I'm starving.
[STUDENT 19B]
Me, too.
[STUDENT 19C]
Let's find some food.
[IZUKU]
So, you brought me here.
Now what?
We should probably eat soon.
The cafeteria's gonna be busy.
[IZUKU]
Don't you think?
[gulps]
[IZUKU]
He's all cold intimidation.
Way different from Kacchan.
[TODOROKI]
I was overwhelmed.
[gasps]
And it made me break
the promise I made
to myself a long time ago.
[IZUKU] It would have given
him such an advantage
to use his left side.
And yet... he didn't.
Ida and Kaminari...
Yaoyorozu and Tokoyami...
Uraraka...
None of them felt it.
In that moment,
I was the only one who
could sense your true power.
It reminded me of something...
Experiencing All Might's Quirk.
Oh, yeah? Okay...
Is that all?
I'm saying...
The power coming from you
felt the same as All Might's.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya, tell me.
Are you really All Might's
secret love child
or something?
[IZUKU]
Am I... What?!
I've seen it.
You've got All Might in
your corner, helping you out.
[IZUKU]
Okay. I get why he'd think that.
As insane as it sounds.
[TODOROKI]
Well, are you?
No, no way--
that's not it at all.
But I guess even if I was,
I'd totally say I wasn't,
so you probably won't believe
me no matter what, I bet.
Anyway, I promise,
you've got the wrong idea.
And... Why would you
even think that about me?
"That's not it at all"
is interesting wording.
It suggests there is
something between you two
that you're not
supposed to talk about.
U-Uh...
My father is the hero Endeavor.
You must've heard of him.
Which means you're aware
that he's the number-two hero.
So if you're connected to
the number-one hero,
All Might, in some way...
That would mean...
...that I have even more
reason to beat you.
[ALL MIGHT]
Yo! Long time no see!
Let's catch up,
Endeavor.
[ENDEAVOR]
All Might.
I haven't talked to you since
that press conference
ten years ago.
Been a while.
I saw you and
figured I'd say hi.
Did you now?
Well then, if that's all you
wanted to do, we're done.
[ALL MIGHT]
Huh?
[ENDEAVOR]
Chatting like we're old friends.
What a joke.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
Come on, why the cold shoulder?
[growls]
[ALL MIGHT] You should
be thrilled. After all,
your son's doing
very well out there,
just using half his power.
You must be a great teacher.
Are you implying something?
No. I want to know your secrets.
How do we train the next
generation of heroes?
Do you really think
I'd tell you anything
I've taught the boy?
You're all flash
and no brains as usual.
Outta my way.
Okay.
Let me assure you
of one thing, All Might.
Whatever it takes...
That kid of mine will
beat you, someday.
I'll make sure of it.
That's why I made him.
You did what?
[ENDEAVOR] He's in a
rebellious phase right now.
But he will take your place.
I'll make sure of it.
[TODOROKI]
My old man is ambitious.
He aims for the top.
He used his power to make
a name for himself as a hero.
But he was never able
to best All Might,
so the Symbol of Peace is
living proof of his failure.
He's still at it, though,
trying to take down All Might.
One way or another.
I'm not really sure
what you're getting at.
What are you trying
to tell me, Todoroki?
Have you ever heard of...
...Quirk marriages?
Uh...
[TODOROKI]
They became a problem
in the first few generations
after superpowers
became widespread.
There were those who sought out
potential mates solely
with the intention
of creating powerful children.
Many people were forced
into relationships.
They were simply viewed as
old-fashioned
arranged marriages.
But, clearly, it was unethical.
My father has not only a rich
history of accomplishments,
but plenty of money
to throw at his problems.
He bought my mother's relatives
to get his hands on her Quirk.
And now he's raising me
to usurp All Might.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI]
It's so annoying.
I refuse to be a tool
for that scumbag.
In every memory of my mother...
I only see her crying.
[TODOROKI'S MOTHER sobbing]
I remember she called
my left side unbearable,
before she poured
boiling water on my face.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI] The reason
I picked a fight with you
was to show my old man
what I was capable of doing.
Without having to rely
on his damned fire Quirk.
You see,
I'm going to show him
that I reject his power,
and I can take first place
without using it.
[IZUKU] The life he's led
is so different than mine.
It sounds terrifying.
How strange that we could
be aiming for the same thing
despite such
different childhoods.
You're obviously
connected to All Might.
Even if you won't
tell me about it.
But no matter how fiercely
you come at me in the future,
I will defeat you using
only my right side.
I can assure you of that.
[IZUKU] So this is why
Todoroki's so focused.
He's like a
comic book character.
A hero with a tragic backstory.
Fighting to rise above it.
[IZUKU]
Hey, wait!
[IZUKU] I'm only here because
others have supported me.
I've been really lucky.
In fact, I've had even more
help since I've come to UA.
[ALL MIGHT] Have no fear.
You're safe. I am here.
Can't you just give him
some of my points?
I'll support you with
everything I've got!
[AIZAWA] You can't be a pro
if you only have one trick.
[TSUYU] I guess we passed
the shipwreck zone.
[KATSUKI]
Get the hell outta my way, Deku!
[HATSUME] Team up with me,
person in first place!
It was around his head,
where his guard was the weakest.
Young man,
you, too, can become a hero.
[IZUKU] All Might is
constantly saving people
with a fearless smile.
He's the greatest hero.
And I wanna be just like him.
In order to do that,
I have to be strong enough
to become number one.
I know my motivation
might seem stupid
compared to yours.
But, still--I can't
lose this, either.
I owe it to everyone who's
supported me to try my best.
[IZUKU]
You declared war on me earlier.
Well, right back at you.
I am going to beat you.
[PRESENT MIC] Get those
foam fingers in the air!
It's almost time
for the last round!
But before that:
good news for everyone
who didn't make the finals.
Since this is a sports festival,
we've prepared some
super-fun side games
everyone can participate in!
We even brought in cheerleaders
from America to get
your blood pumping!
[AIZAWA]
Ah--
Hold up.
[AIZAWA]
What are they doing?
[PRESENT MIC]
Looks like Class 1-A is goin'
full-on fanservice!
[KAMINARI, MINETA cackle]
What?! You tricked us?
You're gonna regret this!
Yaoyorozu. Jiro.
Uh-huh, do you need something?
[MINETA] Well, I'm sure
you already know since
you're like, a class rep...
But they said all
the girls have to wear
those uniforms for the big
cheer battle this afternoon.
Huh?!
That's odd. This is the first
I'm hearing about it.
Are you sure?
You don't have to believe me
if you wanna get in trouble.
But this is coming
straight from Mr. Aizawa.
I thought maybe you'd forgotten,
so I figured I'd
remind you, just in case.
[sighs] Why is it that
I always end up falling
for that little pervert's
stupid schemes?
I even used my Quirk
to make these outfits.
Ugh, I hate those guys!
[HAGAKURE] Well, we do have
a little time before
the finals start, and I kinda
like these uniforms, so...
How 'bout we just roll with it!
[JIRO]
Are you crazy?
Wow, Toru. You've got skills.
[PRESENT MIC]
Have fun competing in these
little side games, everyone!
[PRESENT MIC] After they're
over, the 16 students
from the top four teams
will be duking it out
one-on-one in a tournament-style
fighting competition!
[PRESENT MIC]
I promise you're not gonna wanna
miss these epic match ups!
[KIRISHIMA]
Aw, yeah.
Finally getin' the chance
to show what we're made of.
I watch these finals every year,
and now I'm actually in them!
So, wait. Is it
always a tournament?
The final's always a
one-on-one competition,
but they switch
it up every time.
Last year it was a foam
sword-fighting match.
[MIDNIGHT]
Come closer and draw lots to see
who you're up against.
Then enjoy the pleasure
of the recreational games
before we start.
The 16 finalists have the option
of participating in those
activities or sitting out
to prepare for battle.
I'm sure you all want
to conserve your stamina.
I'll start with the
first place team.
[OJIRO]
Um. Excuse me.
Sorry.
But I'm withdrawing.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Ojiro. No way!
But this is a rare chance
for you to get scouted.
It just wouldn't be right.
I barely remember anything
from the cavalry battle
until the very end of it.
[gasps]
[OJIRO] I... think it
was that guy's Quirk.
[IZUKU] Wait, who was
Ojiro with, again? Him?
[OJIRO] I know this is
a great opportunity.
I wish I could
take advantage of it,
but my conscience won't let me.
Think about this.
[OJIRO]
I have, okay?
Everyone gave their
all in round two,
but I was just
someone's puppet. No way.
I don't wanna advance if I
don't even know how I got here.
It wouldn't be fair.
[HAGAKURE] You're making
way too much of this!
Just kill it in the finals
and prove you should be here.
Yeah, what she said.
I didn't do much
in the battle, either.
[OJIRO]
That's not it.
I'm talking about my pride here.
I refuse to give that up.
[BOTH gasp]
[OJIRO]
Also, why are all the girls
dressed like cheerleaders?
[GIRLS groan]
[SHODA]
Nirengeki Shoda from Class 1-B.
I think I should withdraw
for the exact same reason.
Regardless of how strong I am,
this isn't how
I wanted to get here.
It would go against
the values of the festival
to advance without
earning my spot.
Listen to these guys!
They're so manly!
Well, now.
Here's another weird
turn of events.
[AIZAWA]
We'll have to see what Midnight
has to say about all this--
she's the one in charge.
This sort of talk is
incredibly naive, my boys.
That turns me on! Shoda! Ojiro!
You're withdrawn!
[STUDENTS]
Did she say it turns her on?
Don't worry.
I'll win it for you.
Now, let's see...
We'll have to
move up two students
from the fifth-place
cavalry team
so we have enough contestants.
We were frozen most of the time.
Honestly, we barely did anything
in the cavalry battle.
Isn't that right?
Uh-huh.
Girls?
You should choose from the group
that kept fighting
the whole time.
Team Tetsutetsu.
Kendo!
I'm not doing this as
a favor. It's just fair.
Seriously, you guys!
Thank you!
[MIDNIGHT]
And so, Tetsutetsu and Shiozaki
have advanced to the final!
Take a look at the
bracket, my dears.
These are your opponents!
[CROWD cheers]
[KIRISHIMA, TETSUTETSU]
Seriously?
How does this keep happening?
I'll give it my all.
Good. That's all
that I ask of you.
Ma cherie .
I'm afraid it's the end
of the road for you.
I can't wait to melt your butt.
[IZUKU] I'm the first match
of the first bracket.
Which means I might
fight Todoroki next.
Great.
[IZUKU]
First things first.
I have to worry about
this Shinso guy.
That is you, right?
Izuku Midoriya?
[IZUKU whimpers]
[IZUKU yelps]
[IZUKU]
It's him!
If any of us do well
in the sports festival,
the teachers can
decide to transfer us
to the hero course.
[IZUKU]
From General Studies!
A pleasure. So you excited?
Uh... Ye--
Not so fast.
Heh.
Ojiro. What's the deal?
You can't say a word to him.
Huh?
[TODOROKI]
He could be my second match.
You must advance, Midoriya.
So I can beat you with one hand.
[KATSUKI]
Uraraka? Who the hell's that?
[gasps]
Hey, legs. You're Iida, right?
[TENYA]
Hm? Correct. I'm Tenya Iida.
Oh! That's perfect!
I have something nice for you!
Okay.
Let's press pause for
a momentary interlude!
Before the battles begin,
it's time for some
pulse-pounding side games!
[HAGAKURE]
Woohoo!
[PRESENT MIC] First,
how about a scavenger hunt?
Hey, anyone up there
got a bag they can give me?
[SATO]
A cat?
--Anyone sneak a cat...
--[KAMINARI] Anybody got...
What in the heck?
[MONOMA]
What a joke.
They're actually taking these
dumb side games seriously?
As usual, those Class 1-A
idiots really need
to get their
priorities in check.
[KENDO]
Monoma!
If you're not playing,
come with me.
Okay?
[MONOMA] Uh... I think you may
have the wrong impression
of me, Kendo.
Trust me. This fits.
[IZUKU] Even though
we were told to have fun,
those of us in the
tournament couldn't relax.
Some tried to come up
with a strategy.
Some tried to rest their bodies.
There were those who
prepped for the fight.
Or tried to hype themselves up.
And others still
who just focused on
trying to calm their nerves.
[IZUKU] We wanted to be
ready for anything.
And before we knew it,
the finals began.
That's it. I'm pretty
much done here.
[PRESENT MIC]
Thank you, Cementoss!
Hey, sports fans. Are ya ready?
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC] After all the
action you've already witnessed,
it's time for the
real battles to begin!
Can ya feel the excitement?
Our competitors are
on their own now!
Sometimes, heroes have only
themselves to rely on!
Heart. Skill. Strength.
Wisdom. Courage.
They'll have to use all of these
things to rise to the top!
[ALL MIGHT]
Hey.
[gasps]
Sorry I haven't said hi.
You've been great.
You harnessed One For All!
No, not really.
I'm... still worried
about using it.
I imagine the
egg in the microwave
or how it felt
to hit that villain.
But I'm still not in control.
It feels so unpredictable,
like I might be ripped apart
if I'm not completely focused.
Besides, I'm still not ready
to fully wield it, I can tell.
Even after so much training,
my body is weak.
It just can't handle
your power at 100 percent.
Yeah.
If we're talkin' about
how much of One For All
you'd be able to
use at this point,
I'd say my closest guess would
be around five percent or so.
[IZUKU]
What--only five percent?
Wow, okay.
I guess I really have
only been getting by
because of luck and
my friends helping me out.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
All I wanna hear you say
is that you'll
do your best, dammit.
There's no such thing as luck.
You're never gonna
become the hero you want
if you believe in
somethin' like that.
Ah...
[ALL MIGHT]
Listen.
Whenever you're scared
or nervous about a fight.
Just try and deal
with it by smiling!
You've made it this far, kid.
Even if you're worried,
you must stand tall!
Don't forget that
I'm counting on you,
and cheering you on!
[PRESENT MIC]
All right, audience!
Let's cut to the
good stuff and not delay
these finals any longer.
Welcome our first fighters.
Whoa, he looks kinda scared
in that picture, doesn't he?
It's Izuku Midoriya from
the hero course versus...
Hitoshi Shinso from
general studies,
who really hasn't done
anything to stand out yet.
The rules are simple.
Immobilize your opponent
or force them outta the ring.
You can also win by getting
the other person to cry uncle!
Bring on the injuries,
'cause we've got
our very own Recovery Girl
waiting on standby!
So put your morals aside and
don't be afraid to play dirty!
But of course, no
life-threatening crap, folks.
It's not allowed!
Real heroes use their power
to throw villains in jail,
not kill them.
I'll stop anyone who
tries to get too rough.
[sighs]
[SHINSO]
So you can just give up, huh?
[gasps]
[SHINSO]
In a way, this is a test
of how strong your spirit is.
If you know what you want
your future to hold for you,
you can't worry about
what other people think.
[PRESENT MIC]
Ready?
That monkey was going on
about his pride earlier.
[PRESENT MIC]
Begin!
[SHINSO]
But I just think he's an idiot
for throwing away
his chance like that.
[gasps]
[growls]
Don't you talk about
him that way!
[SHINSO]
That's it. I win.
[groans] I warned him
not to say anything!
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
[PRESENT MIC] Huh?!
Hey, hey, what's the dealio?
This is the first match!
It should start out with a bang!
[PRESENT MIC] The fight has just
begun and Izuku Midoriya is...
...completely frozen?
[OJIRO] The finals
are starting, Midoria.
[IZUKU] So, what'd you
wanna tell me, Ojiro?
[OJIRO] It's important you know
about Shinso from Class 1-B.
He's your opponent
in the first round,
and his Quirk
could be a problem.
[IZUKU] Aw, I didn't know you
cared about me that much!
[OJIRO] Uh, yeah, I mostly just
wanted to get to do the preview.
[IZUKU] Oh. Well,
at least you're honest.
Next time: "Victory or Defeat."
[OJIRO] Get ready for
a quick match that leaves
the whole stadium
feeling bad for the loser.
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, OJIRO]
Plus Ultra!