[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
with 80 percent of us
possessing some uncanny ability.
Cities swirled with chaos
and confusion following
the appearance of these powers,
and a new profession emerged.
We call those who
fight for justice
and help others
in need "heroes."
Oh, by the way,
this is the story
of how I became
the world's greatest hero!
[AIZAWA] The UA Sports Festival
is about to start.
It's true that joining
a famous hero agency
can garner you greater
experience and popularity.
It's something that the pros--
no--the entire country will
be watching very closely.
Think of the sports
festival as your debut.
You are the fledgling
Symbol of Peace.
The next All Might!
Izuku Midoriya.
You must introduce yourself,
and proudly say, "I am here!"
[PRESENT MIC] The first-year
students are rocketing through
this obstacle course in hopes
of moving on in the festival!
Who would have imagined
at the beginning
of this race that
the climax would be
a non-stop mega-mix
of surprises?
The first competitor
to make it back
into the stadium will be
the first-place winner!
Izuku Midoriya is our champion!
[CROWD cheers]
[MIDNIGHT] Forty-two of you
qualified to move on
to the next round.
Gird your loins and prepare
for your next test.
A Cavalry Battle!
Those of you at the top
will suffer the most.
Of course, that's something
you'll hear over and
over again at UA.
Show us what "Plus Ultra" means!
Izuku Midoriya placed
first in the qualifier.
He'll be worth ten million!
[heartbeats]
[KATSUKI]
You'd never be able to hang
with the best of the best.
You're just a Quirkless wannabe!
[IZUKU] Things have changed
so much since junior high,
but I'm still a target.
I'm only in first
place right now
because of some good luck.
Not that that matters, I guess.
[ALL MIGHT] Now you know
the burden of being the best.
[IZUKU]
What they say is true.
It's hard being at the top.
Right, All Might?
First years!
These are the rules
that you'll abide by.
The game itself
will last 15 minutes.
Individual point values
will be added together
to reach your team total.
Everyone will know
how much you're worth
thanks to your headbands.
Swipe as many headbands
as you can to raise
your team's score.
Stolen headbands must be
worn from the neck up.
So the more you steal, the
harder it'll be to manage them.
And another thing.
Even if your headband gets
stolen or your team falls down,
you can keep playing
until time's up.
It's anyone's game, then.
[SATO] And since there
are 42 contestants,
there'll be ten or 12 teams
fighting on the field
the entire time.
[AOYAMA]
Sounds hard.
So, if you lose your
headband at the beginning,
you have more time
to make up a plan.
I dunno, Mina. Maybe we
should wait and see
how the teams turn out
before we start strategizing.
This is going to be rough.
You may use your Quirks
as much as you like.
But there are still rules!
Make a team fall on
purpose and I'll slap you
with a red card.
You'll be disqualified!
Tch.
[MIDNIGHT] Now, you've got
15 minutes to build your teams.
I recommend you get started.
[IZUKU] It doesn't
matter how many points
my teammates have
since I've got so many.
I just need to make sure
I pick the right people.
Okay, I know who I want!
[DEATH ARMS] The sports festival
isn't really about seeing
how prepared they are
at being heroes.
It's more about
simulating the competition
they'll face if they go pro.
[MT. LADY]
Huh? What are you talking about?
We both know this
country's overrun
with agencies right now.
If you wanna put
food on the table,
you've gotta be willing to
step on top of other heroes.
That was the whole point
of the first round.
[MT. LADY] That's such a sad
way of looking at our jobs.
[KAMUI WOODS]
Seriously?
You've never had a problem
stealing the spotlight.
But, on the other hand--
even if you're battling
each other for popularity,
there are plenty a' cases where
you have to work together.
Huh. You're right, it's just
like this cavalry battle!
Every point you score
is not just for you,
but for your teammates as well.
Plus, you have to
think about how Quirks
work together and who
you're compatible with.
[KAMUI WOODS] It's kind of
like coordinating with
your sidekick or doing Quirk
training with other agencies.
I'm sure at least
some of the kids
are thinking about all this.
If they become pros,
it'll be their way of life.
[MT. LADY] They've still got
a long road ahead of 'em.
You should team with me!
No, you definitely
want me by your side.
I don't wanna beg, but please.
Wait, remind me what
your Quirks are again.
And your names.
You're kidding!
We're your classmates.
Can you really be
that self-centered?
[ALL MIGHT]
He's a hot head,
but he came in third
and he has 200 points.
And considering how
versatile his Quirk is,
I'm not surprised people are
trying to join up with him.
[KIRISHIMA]
Bakugo!
I was gonna try Todoroki,
but he already picked a group.
So, hey! We should team up.
Hey, Dumb Hair.
My name is Kirishima!
And my hair's not that
different from yours.
Come on. You wanna
be the rider, right?
So you're gonna need
a strong front horse
who won't be hurt
by your blasts.
That'd be me.
[KATSUKI]
Hm...
I need someone with guts.
My Quirk was made for this!
I got you covered, man!
Let's go charging
into battle together.
[KATSUKI]
Ah--
Ten million.
Bring it.
[growls]
[MINETA]
Shoji! Shoji!
[SHOJI]
Hm?
None of the girls
wanna team up with me!
Please, be my partner!
I'm super tiny,
so I can't be a horse,
but for some reason
no one wants me to climb
on top of them
so I can be a rider!
With your huge body
and those tentacles,
you could cover me completely,
so no one'll take my headband!
Right? Please?
Good idea. Let's go.
[IZUKU]
Just like I expected.
Everyone's sticking to the
people in their homeroom class.
It's too much of a gamble
to partner with someone
if you don't know what
their Quirk can do.
I need to find a team
of my own and fast.
But everyone's
totally avoiding me
since I'm worth so much!
Oh, hey. What's up, Ojiro?
Sorry.
[yelps]
[IZUKU]
It makes sense.
No one's worried about
keeping their own headbands
the whole game. It's a
better strategy to steal
as many points as
you can at the end.
And unlike Todoroki or Kacchan,
I didn't use my Quirk
in the first round,
so no one has any
confidence in me!
[OCHACO]
Hey, Deku!
Let's team up!
Uraraka! Are you sure?
Everyone'll be after me and
my ten million stupid points!
Tell me you're not kidding!
If we run away the whole time,
then we'll win, right?
Um, you're either
overestimating me
or underestimating
everyone else here.
Phooey!
Anyway, it's better to
team up with people you like!
[OCHACO] Is something wrong?
You look so gross.
No, I just thought my chest
was gonna explode for a second.
Actually, I wanted to
team up with you, too.
Thanks a lot.
You're right. For a
game that requires
so much teamwork,
it's smart to find people
you communicate smoothly with.
In fact, if we had your
Quirk and one other person...
You know what--I think
I might have a solid plan.
Huh?
[IZUKU]
Iida.
[TENYA]
Hm?
[BOTH]
Ha!
[IZUKU]
The three of us would be horses,
with Iida in the front.
Using Uraraka's Quirk,
Iida and I would be way lighter,
so we'd be able to maneuver
around really easily.
No one could catch us.
Good idea!
[IZUKU]
The only thing is...
We'd still have to find
a pretty strong rider.
I don't know who could do it.
I know it's not much,
but it's the only evasive plan
I could think of this fast.
[TENYA]
A good strategy, but I'm sorry.
Uh...
[TENYA] I'm afraid I must
refuse your offer.
--[IZUKU gasps]
--[OCHACO] Huh?
Since this all started,
I've been losing to you.
Please don't take
this as an insult.
You're a great friend, but if
I continue to follow you,
I'll never get stronger.
Bakugo and Todoroki have
challenged you already,
but they aren't the only ones
who see you as a rival.
[TENYA] Midoriya, I'll try
my best to defeat you.
Whoa, Iida...
[IZUKU]
So, it's already begun.
Everyone's an enemy.
I'm at the top, and they'll
all be coming for me.
I can't rely on anyone.
Not this time.
[HATSUME giggles]
Oh, perfect, you're still alone.
And you're the star.
Team up with me,
person in first place!
So close! Who are you?
[HATSUME chuckles] I'm a
student in the support course.
Name's Mei Hatsume!
Oh! You're that weirdo
from the obstacle course.
We haven't met,
but I'd like to use
your current fame to
my personal advantage.
[IZUKU]
That's straightforward!
If I team up with you,
then I'll be in the spotlight!
Part of the team that everyone
is keeping their eyes on.
That means my
super-cute little babies
will inevitably be seen
by the big company CEOs
who're tuning into
the Sports Festival.
And following that
line of reasoning,
this is the best way for me
and my marvelous gadgets
to get recruited.
Could you slow down a minute?
Did you bring babies
here, or... I mean...
[HATSUME] Plus, you two
will definitely benefit...
[OCHACO]
Oh, she doesn't care about me.
[HATSUME] The support course
specializes in creating
equipment that helps heroes deal
with their Quirks and
enhance their skills.
[HATSUME cackles] I packed
a ton of powerful babies
to bring with me,
so I'm sure you'll find
something you like
floating around my arsenal!
Oh, I see one's caught your eye.
Uh--
I based this on a
certain hero's backpack.
Though, of course,
I added my own twist.
Wait, I recognize that!
Air Jet, the Buster Hero
has one of those.
[HATSUME laughs]
I love that guy!
Isn't he awesome?
[IZUKU]
Mm-hm! His agency's close by...
[OCHACO]
Huh. They sure get along well.
[IZUKU] Not being able
to team up with Iida
was a definite blow. I've got
Hatsume and Uraraka now.
But...
I still need one more.
[IZUKU]
Looks like pretty much everyone
is on a team already.
That's fine. We can
work with that.
In fact, I know exactly what
power our team is missing.
[IZUKU] And the person
who can fill that spot is...
Where're you going?
Join me!
[MONOMA]
Almost everyone in the audience
is foaming at the mouth
for Class 1-A. Why is that?
They're so full of themselves.
Just like Tetsutetsu said
earlier. Why are they stars?
The only difference
between us and them
is that they fought
a couple of villains.
Just because we're
Class 1-B doesn't mean
we're second rate or
can't win this whole thing.
So, let's step it up
and show those jerks
what we can do. Are ya with me?
Oh, goody. It's time to
get this party started.
[PRESENT MIC]
Hey, hey, look alive!
[AIZAWA]
Mm?
After 15 minutes
to pick teammates
and talk strategy, 12 cavalry
teams are preparing
to go head-to-head!
[AIZAWA] I see some unexpected
student combinations.
[PRESENT MIC] Come on, everyone
get your hands in the air!
It's time for an arena-thumping
UA battle royale!
Let me hear ya scream!
[DARK SHADOW growls]
[IZUKU]
You ready?
Yeah!
[IZUKU]
Hatsume?
[laughs]
[IZUKU]
Tokoyami?
Yes.
Let's do this.
[CROWD cheers]
[TODOROKI] I chose the three
of you because I believe
we'll make for the most
stable formation possible.
Kaminari's our left wing.
He can use his Quirk
to keep enemies at bay.
Yaoyorozu, you'll take
the right wing.
Focus on insulation and defense.
Iida, you'll take the front.
We'll rely on you for mobility
and physical defense.
[TENYA] And you'll be attacking
and creating diversions
of ice and fire. Is that right?
Not quite.
When I'm in battle...
[TODOROKI]
I never use my left side.
[CROWD cheers]
[PRESENT MIC]
Okay, all you first years!
I hope you're happy
with your chosen teams!
[MONOMA]
Tetsutetsu.
[TETSUTETSU]
Huh?
No hard feelings, okay?
Right!
Let's get this party started!
One final countdown
before the game starts!
Three!
Get 'im.
[PRESENT MIC]
Two!
He's ours.
[PRESENT MIC]
One!
Begin!
[IZUKU whimpers]
It's basically one big battle
for ten million points!
[HAGAKURE cackles] I'll be
taking that headband, Midoriya!
They're not even giving
us a chance, huh?
Such is the fate of the pursued.
[OCHACO]
This is it.
Make your choice, Midoriya!
Here they come!
That's easy.
We're running away!
Don't think so!
Yeah!
[ALL yelp]
[OCHACO]
What's happening?
[IZUKU]
We're sinking!
It must be that guy's Quirk!
[OCHACO]
No good--I can't get out!
Uraraka! Hatsume!
Watch your faces!
He flew? Damn support course.
After them!
[HAGAKURE]
Jiro, now!
I know!
Stupid bird!
Good work.
Please, continue to watch over
our blind spots, Dark Shadow.
[DARK SHADOW]
Got it!
Wow, that is seriously cool.
Your shadow is just
what we needed.
It'll take care of
our omnidirectional
mid-range defenses!
Tokoyami. You're amazing!
You are the one who chose me.
We're landing.
[IZUKU]
Uraraka's Quirk is awesome!
She's floating everything
but her and the equipment.
So what do you think
of my babies?
Aren't they just precious?
Cuteness can be
manufactured, you know.
Excellent mobility!
Your babies are
amazing, Hatsume!
Aw, thanks!
I'm the one who's
making us float.
[HAGAKURE]
They're not that far away!
Come on, Jiro! Full speed ahead!
Hey, wait! Hagakure!
Your headband's gone!
[HAGAKURE]
Huh?
What? Who--? No!
Well, that was easy.
[PRESENT MIC]
Wow!
Barely two minutes have
passed since we started,
and it's already
a total free for all!
Yeah! Watch those headbands!
You can even ignore
the ten million points
and go after the
other chart toppers!
[MINETA cackles]
[MINETA] This is too easy.
It's not a fight.
It's more like a massacre!
It's Shoji! Is he
all by himself?
Where's his team?
What we need
is breathing room.
We can't get caught trapped
between multiple opponents!
Uh-- Ah!
Oh, no!
What, is something wrong?
Yeah, I'm stuck!
[IZUKU gasps]
That's Mineta's ball.
But where did it come from?!
[MINETA] From right
over here. Hi, Midoriya.
[IZUKU]
What? Is that even allowed?
Judges say yes!
[yelps]
Impressive moves as usual.
[IZUKU] Oh, man. You've
got Asui in there, too?
I told you to call me "Tsu."
[PRESENT MIC] Team Mineta's
coming in like a tank,
making clever use of how
compact their members are!
Quickly. We must move!
[grunts]
[sobs] My baby's ruined!
[IZUKU] Sorry! But at least
we got away from them!
[IZUKU]
Kacchan!
[KATSUKI] Don't think for
a second that you're safe.
[yelps]
[KATSUKI]
I've got you!
Tokoyami!
[TOKOYAMI grunts]
--[DARK SHADOW growls]
--[KATSUKI grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
Whoa!
What the hell's that?
[PRESENT MIC] Bakugo has been
separated from his horses!
Whoa, nice catch.
[PRESENT MIC]
Is that even allowed?
He never touched the ground,
so technically, it's okay.
[OCHACO yelping]
Nicely done, Uraraka!
It's hard to control
where we're going
with just one foot.
I understand.
[IZUKU] With that busted boot,
our movement is limited.
We can't risk taking
to the sky again.
That means, to survive,
we'll have to rely on
Tokoyami's Dark Shadow,
and our increased mobility,
thanks to Uraraka's
Zero Gravity.
[PRESENT MIC]
As expected, everyone's after
the first place team,
giving them no time
to catch their breath.
What a show this is!
Wow, those Class 1-A
guys are pretty good.
[AUDIENCE 17A]
With all those flashy Quirks,
I can't decide who
I should be watching!
[AUDIENCE 17B] Looks like
the experience fighting
villains made that class
level-up superfast.
[PRESENT MIC]
Now who wants to take a look
at each team's points so far?
It's been seven minutes,
so let's get those rankings
thrown up on the screen.
[AUDIENCE 16C]
Huh? Uh...
Hold on here.
This is an unexpected turn.
Other than Midoriya,
Class 1-A's not doin' so hot.
[PRESENT MIC]
Even Bakugo is losing!
Your class is too small
minded. Think bigger.
He got us!
What did you say?
Come back here!
[MONOMA] Midnight said the
obstacle course was just
the first game, and we
figured they wouldn't
cut that many of us right
off the bat. Would they?
Huh?
Assuming they'd keep
at least 40 contestants
for the next event, all we
had to do was make sure
we stayed within that
group as we ran.
From our spots
in the middle ranks,
we could fully
observe the Quirks
our rivals had and judge
their capabilities.
Only a fool would
obsess over winning
the preliminary rounds,
wouldn't you agree?
You planned this as a class?
It wasn't totally unanimous,
but I'd say it's
playing out well.
Hey, they're coming.
[MONOMA] It's better than
chasing after a temporary
frontrunner like a horse with
a carrot waving in his face.
Oh, while I have your attention.
You're kinda famous, aren't you?
For being attacked by
that sludge villain.
You'll have to tell me
about it sometime.
It must be strange
to always find yourself
in the role of the victim.
Kirishima, we have
a change of plans.
Uh--
[gasps]
[MONOMA]
Hm?
[ASHIDO, KIRISHIMA,
SERO whimper]
Before we take down Deku,
we're gonna kill every last
one of these B-list idiots!
[IZUKU] Holy, whoa. Class 1-B
had a long-term strategy
that involved throwing
the qualifier.
I guess that could help them
leave a bigger impression
with the audience. Everyone
does kinda love an underdog.
But...
If they're playing
the long game here,
they might not even bother
coming after my headband at all!
Everyone, don't worry,
I think we're okay.
[pants]
[PRESENT MIC]
And now we've reached
the halfway point of the game!
Whew.
I thought we had it made.
Guess I was wrong.
[PRESENT MIC] As the cavalry
battle enters its second half,
it's anyone's game! Class 1-B
has made an unexpected showing,
but who will wear the ten
million points in the end?
That's the real
question, sports fans!
I'll be taking that, now.
[TENYA]
Attention!
I'm Tenya Iida, the
representative for Class 1-A.
I'll be responsible
for this preview!
[IZUKU] Yeah, sure, let's
talk about the next episode.
[TENYA]
I'm to challenge you, Midoriya!
[IZUKU]
Please don't!
[TENYA] I will defeat your
team in the cavalry battle,
and the result will bring
honor to the Tenya family.
My older brother,
Tensei, will be proud!
[IZUKU]
What about everybody else?
[TENYA] Next time:
"Cavalry Battle Finale"!
[IZUKU] Iida's calves
flip into overdrive
and get super revved up!
[TENYA]
I'll go beyond!
[TENYA, IZUKU]
Plus Ultra!