Previously on "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure".
Come out. It's time to go home.
Get lost. I didn't ask you to come here.
You really think you can help me?
I'd like you to meet an Egyptian
friend I met a few years ago.
Say hello to Avdol.
Red bind!
Huh? What the...
And now for the truth.
This may seem like an evil spirit, but it's far from it.
Jotaro, this thing you believe has
possessed you is actually a powerful vision
created by your own life energy.
This vision will always appear standing by your side,
and because of that, we call it a stand!
That coffin's a hundred years old,
and four years ago, it was pulled out
of the Atlantic off the coast of Africa.
Okay. So?
I did a little research.
My grandfather, Jonathan Joestar,
your great-grandfather, died while at sea.
Turns out this exact same coffin
was on that boat with him when he died.
When they discovered it four years ago, it was empty,
but I know exactly what was inside it.
Avdol and I are trying to locate him as we speak.
That person is evil incarnate,
and his name is Dio!
And now that he has been awakened
from his hundred-year slumber,
it is our fate to fight that man!
From the neck of this bastard on down
is Jonathan Joestar, my grandfather!
This son of a bitch took over his body!
Jotaro, don't leave yet.
You forgot something important.
Silly boy.
Here is your goodbye kiss.
You're such a bitch.
Stop clinging to me like I'm still a little kid.
Okay. Have a nice day.
What a giant pain in my ass.
Hey. Look, it's JoJo.
What? JoJo?
You're right. It is JoJo.
JoJo.
Hey, JoJo.
What's up, JoJo?
Hey there, JoJo.
What's going on JoJo?
So tell me, JoJo, where have you been?
You haven't been to school for four days.
Uh...
Hey!
Who do you think you are grabbing on to JoJo like that?
I don't like how friendly
you're getting with him. Stay away.
What the hell, ugly?
I'd be careful there, no boobs.
Ugly.
No boobs.
Shut up! You're freakin' annoying!
He totally said that to me!
Nuh-uh, me!
JoJo, wait.
What the hell?
JoJo!
Those branches.
JoJo.
Oh, no.
JoJo fell so far down the steps.
Look. He can still move.
The branches must have broken his fall.
Did a branch slash open my leg?
No. Wait a sec.
That's not what caused me to fall down the stairs.
This cut is what came first. But how?
I see.
Looks like he's able to summon a pretty fierce stand.
I get it now.
Impressive.
No wonder he wants me to get rid of him.
But still...
He is no match for the power of my stand.
You really scared me.
Are you okay, JoJo?
You think you're hurt anywhere?
You're lucky. If you had landed just few inches off,
you'd have cracked your head right on the flagstone.
Nasty accidents happen on those steps all the time.
Tomorrow when you go down these
steps, you really should hold my hand.
Here.
Your leg seems to be cut.
You might wanna wrap it with this
handkerchief to help stop the bleeding.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
Hold it.
Hmm?
I forgot to say thanks.
I haven't seen you before. You go to our school?
I'm Noriaki Kakyoin.
And, yes, I just transferred here yesterday.
See you around.
Oh.
So his name's Kakyoin. Seems pretty cool.
You think so?
I still like JoJo way more than him.
Yeah, me, too.
Same goes for me.
At that time, I was very weak.
Lacking a body made me vulnerable.
If I had not taken Jonathan Joestar's body...
If it hadn't been for his energy
to augment my own limited source,
I couldn't have survived at the
bottom of that ocean for a hundred years.
But still...
This body has like a bond between a parent and a child.
It ties me to his kin.
They seem to know of my existence...
And of this power I've gained
from taking Jonathan’s body...
The stand.
It is the stand that reaches out
to the bodies of his descendants.
There are always advantages and
disadvantages to every situation.
I will eliminate them all.
The Joestar clan must be destroyed soon.
Why is every single room in
this house so tiny and cramped?
This is exactly why I hate Japan.
Avdol, how the hell can you stand being here?
I find it quite fascinating,
especially the tea ceremony.
Ceremony, schmeremony.
Instant coffee will do just fine.
By the way, about Dio...
Mr. Joestar, if you and I are aware of his existence,
would it not be safe to assume
that he knows about us as well?
Hmm. But if we don't know what he's going to do
or, for that matter, even what powers he has...
Gah!
Japanese coffee is absolutely vile!
That's American coffee.
Hmm?
That's a horrible cut, JoJo.
How'd you get it? Let me guess. You
got into another fight, didn't you?
Show some respect, and take off that hat.
It's poor manners.
Would you stop that?
Seriously?
Has JoJo ever been hurt in a fight before?
That's not what cut him, I'm sure.
No way.
Well, you do have a point.
Then I'll assume you were being clumsy, you big klutz.
Hey, hold on. What are you gonna do?
Cut your pants, of course.
Like hell, you are.
Well, if I'm gonna treat that wound, I must.
You'll ruin 'em. I'll take 'em off.
Didn't know you were so thrifty.
So while JoJo's taking off his pants,
I'm gonna take your temperatures and
prove you're nothing but a bunch of fakers.
Come on. We really caught a cold.
Totally. Now just let us go home already.
Not gonna happen.
Oops.
What the hell is this?
K-Kakyoin?
Hey, doctor.
What are you trying to do?
What does it look like?
I'm just shaking out the thermometer to reset it.
Th-that's not a thermometer you got in your hand.
Yeah, that's a pen.
Ah, come on. Did you just say, "pen"?
You think I'm dumb? Does this look like a pen to you?!
Tell me something.
Just how stupid are you two boys?
If you honestly think this thermometer
I'm holding looks like a pen to you...
Then maybe you need to take a closer look!
What the...
My eye! My eye!
JoJo...
What do you have to say?
You're not gonna stand there and tell me
this thermometer looks like a pen, too, are you?!
What the hell is going on? Such strength.
This is no mere woman.
Wait.
I saw something weird crawlin' up from the floor.
Was it a stand?
Noriaki Kakyoin...
Was he the one who started this?
Did he cut my leg on the stone steps?
Yes, it was me.
So it is you.
Hey. Long time, no see.
So my stand is currently possessing
and controlling that doctor.
If you attack my stand,
you'll hurt her, too, JoJo.
You bastard. Who are you?
I told you. I'm Noriaki Kakyoin,
and the name of my stand here is Hierophant Green.
I am human, but I have pledged loyalty to him.
That's why I'm gonna kill you.
I have zero intention of hurting her.
Heh.
Now that I've dragged it out,
I see it for what it is, just a sleazy
stand whose only ability is to possess people.
So this is your stand, Kakyoin?
This green, stripy thing looks like shiny melon.
You're gonna regret doing that.
Dragging that out of her was a mistake, JoJo.
Don't act tough.
I can see my finger marks on your forehead.
If I decide to crush your
stand's head like the melon it is,
then I'm guessin' your head'll get crushed, too.
I'm gonna keep a tight grip on you for now.
We're gonna pay my gramps a little visit.
I'm sure he'd love to meet you...
And I'd like to know more about Dio myself.
What the hell?
What's that green liquid coming out of his stand's hand?
You should have listened, JoJo.
I told you you're gonna regret this, didn't I?
This is the attack of my stand, Hierophant Green.
No weird moves, Kakyoin!
Emerald splash!
So what do you think?
Did you like emerald splash?
That fluid you saw in Hierophant Green
is actually a surge of destructive energy.
It tore straight though your stand's chest,
and your insides have now been torn to shreds.
And as for that doctor over there...
Why?
I know I took that stand out of her, so how?
I told you already,
but let me reiterate.
I tried to warn you that by attacking my
Hierophant Green, it would hurt her as well.
My stand can travel farther than yours,
but it dislikes open spaces.
Without exception, it prefers to hide within something.
If you drag it out, it gets angry.
That's why, when you ripped it out of her throat,
it hurt her along the way.
You're the one who did this to her.
This is entirely your fault, JoJo.
You must be held responsible.
Look at what you've done.
All you had to do was let me kill you, and
the doctor would have walked away unharmed.
And still you get up.
You are so pathetic.
You're nothing more than a sandbag
about to be pummeled by a skilled boxer.
Why even bother standing up?
I'm just gonna knock you down again.
Look...
No one ever said Jotaro Kujo was a nice guy.
I beat the crap out of people more than I have to.
Some are even still in the hospital.
I've had idiot teachers who liked to talk big,
so I taught them a lesson, and
they never came back to class.
If I go to a restaurant and the food's bad,
I make it a policy to stiff 'em with the bill.
But even a bastard like me
can spot true evil when he sees it.
True evil are those who use the weak for their own
gain, then crush them underfoot when they're through...
Especially an innocent woman.
And that is exactly what you've done, isn't it?
And your stand gets to hide from the
victim, the law, and the consequences.
That's why...
I will judge you myself.
I'm evil?
See, that's where you're wrong.
Evil is always the loser.
It's the victor who has justice,
the victor being the last man standing.
And how you win in battle is irrelevant!
See, the loser is always the evil one.
Time to finish you off.
Really? The loser's evil?
Emerald splash!
Then, let me show you...
What?
There's no way.
No one can just deflect the emerald splash.
...just how evil you are.
Ora!
I'll teach you justice
with my stand!
Your stand has incredible power.
You caught me by surprise earlier
and scratched its chest a little.
I'm glad my stand isn't weak,
but sometimes it feels like it
can get more savage than I am.
That was a close call.
She'll be fine once her wounds are treated.
Hmm?
Did a gas pipe just burst?
It came from the doctor's office.
Everyone, stay in the classroom!
I'll leave the cleanup to them.
I've had enough school for one day.
This guy needs to talk.
I wanna hear everything he knows about Dio.
I just had the most amazing
connection with my son right now.
Jotaro must be thinking about
me at school this very second.
I'm not thinking about you.
Jotaro!
Why aren't you at school?
And who is that boy on your shoulder?
Is that blood that he's covered in?
Wait a sec. Please don't tell me you did that.
None of your business.
I need to find the old man.
Finding someone in this big house really sucks.
I think you can find him with Avdol right now.
They're both in the tea room.
Oh, Jotaro, you never tell me anything.
All that does is make me worry about you all the time.
But still, I know that, deep
down, you really do mean well.
You're a very sweet little boy at heart.
Hey.
Yes?
You're lookin' a little bit pale the morning.
You all right?
Yay!
I'm fine! Thank you!
I knew it.
Well, I hate to say it, but it's too late for him.
There's no way he'll make it.
He's got a few days before he dies at most.
Jotaro, this is not your fault. Trust me.
Do you want to know why this
man swore his allegiance to Dio
and came to your school to kill you?
Look right here, and I will show you!
What the hell is that?