I'm sure it's quite the traumatic
experience being eaten alive by your own sister.
Then again, when a man uncovers his deepest
desires, all of his weaknesses are laid bare.
You gave nary a thought to the depraved nature of
bringing someone back to the world of the living.
Everyone desperately wants to believe that
their loved ones are still alive somewhere.
More than anything else, your
hope is that, by some miracle,
they'll suddenly pop in tomorrow and say, "good morning."
Oh, before I forget,
I believe you said something about a third wish,
but, if I'm not mistaken, you've already made said wish.
You mean...
You wished for Avdol to come back to life!
Hail 2 U!
No. He's...
Avdol, it's me!
Av-Avdol, why?
My fingers, they've crumbled to pieces.
On your feet, Polnareff!
I blame you for all of this.
Because of your idiotic bumbling, I...
Polnareff, because of you, I ended up like this!
Avdol, you're right.
The person to blame for this...
is me!
Mark my words. You'll pay for this, Polnareff,
and you'll do it with your flesh!
I'll get better if I eat, right?
Well, am I right? Huh, big brother?!
What's the matter, brother?
S-Stay away! Stay away from me!
Both of you!
Please go back to your graves!
But why? You're the one who brought us back, aren't you?
The time has come for you to enter your grave!
I-I'm so panicked that I forgot to summon Chariot.
How could I have been so caught up in
my wish that I neglected to use my stand?
Leave me alone!
Get away from me!
Please, just stay away!
What the...
"Please"? Oh, no, no, no!
You don't have any wishes left, remember?!
I've already granted your three wishes.
And I'm sorry to say you don't get any more!
Stop it! Get off!
Hail 2 U!
Go ahead. Writhe and scream to
your pathetic heart's content.
Since you're in the middle of nowhere,
your friends by the shore won't hear you.
No one can save you now!
It's no use.
This is the end.
I'm going to die. I'm finished.
Sherry, Avdol...
I suppose you're giving me what I deserved.
It's only fitting.
It's like you said.
You died because of my actions...
And so I've accepted my fate.
Huh?
What? My vision must be going.
I'm seeing double.
It looks like there are two Avdols.
Huh?
Of course there's not another one.
If I'm starting to see things,
guess it means the end is near.
The blood loss is taking its toll.
I'm hallucinating.
All right, this is it.
I'll have to tap out early.
Goodbye, Mr. Joestar, Kakyoin, Jotaro.
I pray for your victory.
As for you, Avdol,
I'll atone in the next world.
Hmm?
What? Impossible!
Huh? I was right!
I just knew I saw another Avdol!
My eyes weren't playing tricks!
Besides the dirt and dust version
Cameo made, there's another Avdol!
Magician's red!
But how?! He's supposed to be dead!
It's impossible! He was stabbed
by the Hanged Man, Centerfold!
How the hell is he alive?!
Tsk, tsk.
Are you really Mohammed Avdol?!
Yes, you had better believe I am!
Is it really you?
Tsk, tsk.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
I-Is it the real you, I mean?
Polnareff, you haven't changed in the slightest.
You still lose all common sense when it comes to
your sister and never stop to think of the consequences.
I simply refuse to accept this! Mohammad Avdol is dead!
I was told Hol Horse put a bullet between your
eyes after Hanged Man sunk his blade into your back
and you died on the spot!
You're correct about me being shot,
right in the forehead.
That said, because I was stabbed in the
back, for a moment, my face was looking up,
and the bullet only grazed me.
I suppose this is what one
would call a blessing in disguise.
Hol Horse didn't realize it, but his
bullet never made contact with my brain,
so he didn't inflict a mortal wound.
He was only able to scratch my skin and bruise my skull.
Although I did completely lose consciousness.
So you call yourself Cameo of the judgment card.
Hell is near, so prepare...
For hell 2 U!
I know it was only the third wish, but still...
It's really him.
It came true!
Mohammed Avdol is indeed alive and well.
I would call this bad news.
That being the case, shouldn't you scurry away to inform
Dio and your fellow stand user
compatriots about my return?
Well, shouldn't you, Cameo?
That's right!
I have to tell them!
I have to let Mr. Joestar, Kakyoin,
and Jotaro know! Avdol's back!
This is very surprising news, to be sure,
but the way I see it, I can spin it this way.
Not only did judgment's Cameo slay the idiot Polnareff,
but also succeeded in eliminating
Avdol, who was actually alive!
Oh, I can't wait to tell them the splendid news!
Magician's red!
Whoa, there.
Avdol!
This stand...
It's far more powerful than I expected.
Be careful. It's not just his power.
This guy's got incredible speed, too.
Come now, Avdol. Is that the extent of your abilities?
If so, then sharing my good news
will be even easier than expected.
May fortune...
Be with you both!
What now?!
Hail 2 U!
Big brother...
No, stop this charade. You're not the real Sherry.
My Sherry is gone, dead!
You're nothing but...
A hunk of dirt!
But, brother...
Polnareff.
Apologies. I would like to take back
what I said about you not changing.
No, you were right about me all along.
I'm the one who should apologize.
This battle has already been decided.
Tell you what, Avdol.
Before you head off for that magic lamp in the sky,
I'd like to hear your three wishes.
I'll grant them before I put you to rest for good.
Go ahead. You may as well give it a shot.
As I said, you get three wishes.
Quel salaud. He's making fools of us!
Just ignore him, Avdol.
You don't have to make any wishes!
Avdol, are you listening to me?
No good.
I want four wishes!
Huh?!
What?
My wishes. Can't you hear?
I'm asking you to grant my wishes,
only I want four instead of three.
Tsk, tsk.
Avdol, you can't be serious.
Are you denying my wish?!
Cameo, you're the one who offered to grant them!
I'm going to make sure you keep your promise!
You still insist upon this futile contest of power?
Your kicks are nothing!
What?!
That's the way! Super!
Tsk, tsk.
You should probably know that my first
wish was to make you cry out in agony,
and it came true.
This is madness.
How can you be so much stronger than before?
The wound left behind after I was stabbed by
the Hanged Man hasn't completely healed yet.
Because I was so focused on guarding my wound
from an assault, I had to hold myself back a little.
What?
It was only three days ago that
I was finally able to stand again.
But since I took a plane here
from India, the trip was very easy.
That's Avdol, still the best.
And now for my second wish!
I wish for you to scream out in utter terror.
And while you're at it, grant my third wish!
Cry in regret!
That bastard!
He's running away!
Wait, damn it! Get back here!
Shh. Polnareff, quiet.
With that kind of power and speed,
given the rule of stands, the user must be hiding
somewhere nearby, supplying his stand with energy.
Is he here?
Yes, he should be hiding out very close to us.
Hey, could that be...
Shh.
Has this user really resorted to hiding underground?
Damn coward.
How dare you use my sister like some pawn in a game?
For what you've done, I think I'll show you hell.
Hell 2 U.
Connard.
I can think of a few things to drop down this tube,
like dirt and sand...
A spider...
Ants, too...
And a match.
Bastard. I hope you're ready,
because your suffering has barely begun.
Hey, Polnareff.
I do believe it's time for me to drain the snake.
Huh?
How about it, my friend?
Shall we engage in the timeless ritual of male bonding?
Hmm. Tsk, tsk.
Huh?
Oh.
Somehow I made it out of that mess alive.
Huh?
Come on, Polnareff. Let me hear you laugh!
Uh...
I want to hear the heartiest laugh that you can muster!
Avdol, I might be wrong about this, but
it seems like you're the one who's changed.
Before the incident, you would have never
thought of doing something quite so perverse.
This...
This isn't a result of you being shot in the head, is it?
That's it! Aim that thing!
Right!
Huh?
What the...
Please I beg you, forgive me!
Huh?
Last, but not least, my fourth wish is to not
grant you a single one of your pitiful wishes.
My magician's red forgives no one, especially not you.
Ba-dum-tss!
Hey! You guys'll never believe it!
Guess who I ran into while out and about?!
Polnareff, we were worried about you.
Where did those injuries come from?
Some kind of enemy?
My wounds are nothing compared to my news!
Now listen up, and don't be too shocked, Jotaro!
And you're gonna have to promise you won't
throw your back out in surprise, Kakyoin.
Who do you think I met out there, Mr. Joestar?
Huh?
Now prepare to be blown away!
Tum-ta-da-da!
Here he is!
That sly bastard Avdol was still alive! Isn't that great?!
Well, we should probably get going.
Here. Allow me to help you carry your luggage.
Avdol, how you been doing?
It's been a while. How goes it?
So, Avdol, is the wound on your back healing up all right?
It's fine, though my joints
do get a little stiff sometimes.
Hey!
Has it really been two weeks since we last saw each other?
We're lucky to all be alive.
Jotaro, you're still wearing your uniform?
Don't you ever get hot?
Hey, just hold on a second, guys!
Didn't you hear me?! I told you
to hold on a second, you assholes!
What's the deal with those laissez-faire attitudes?!
A man we thought was dead just waltzed onto the beach!
How the hell can you just brush it
off and act like nothing has changed?!
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry about that, Polnareff.
When I told you I'd taken it
upon myself to bury Avdol in India,
I may have lied.
Wh-wh-what the hell?!
Mr. Joestar and Jotaro were
the ones who tended to the wounds
on my head back in India
after I was shot by Hol Horse.
You assholes have known Avdol was alive the entire time,
and never once did it cross any of
your deceitful minds to let me know?!
I'm most surprised at you, Kakyoin!
I only found out the day after it all happened.
But it was imperative to not let the enemy know,
and since you have such a big mouth, I suggested...
Pardon.
What I meant to say was since it's not easy for you to
lie on command, I suggested we keep it a secret from you.
If you'd let the secret slip,
Avdol wouldn't have been able to recuperate in peace.
We were planning to let you know the
very moment we knew that he was safe,
but we didn't think you'd run into him first.
Oh, yeah. Avdol, we found your
dad living in a hut on this island!
Come on. Let's let him know you're here!
Oh, that was just me in disguise.
Say what?!
Then you were in on it from the very start?
Everything that happened was a ruse you created?
Don't talk to me! No one ever comes to
visit when they have good news to report!
Just shut up!
Don't go there. Avdol's death wasn't your fault.
You didn't have to go that far!
How dare you leave me out of the loop?!
I think that's the cruelest thing you've ever done to me!
Now, now, chin up. There's no reason for you to cry.
I'm sorry, Polnareff. I truly
didn't think you'd be this hurt.
I apologize as well,
but I had a very good reason for
coming to this island in disguise.
Yeah? What is it?
It was partially so the enemy wouldn't find out,
but I also had Avdol do some
shopping for me while he was laying low.
What kind of shopping?
Since it was a very conspicuous acquisition,
I disguised myself as a wealthy Arab gentlemen.
All right, everyone, let's climb aboard and head out!
Come on, Polnareff. For the love of
everything that's sacred, cheer up already.
Huh?
It's almost here. Look.
I don't understand. What's almost here?
I don't see anything!
What?!
Whoa! A submarine?!
That's right.
From here on out, we're riding to Egypt in this.
Y-You've gotta be kidding!
How did you afford this?!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian