Enyaba, there's something
I'd like to ask you.
What does it mean to live?
It's to obtain all that one desires.
If you were to distill life into
its essence, that is what it would be.
A lust for riches, a desire
for fame, food, love, and lovers,
that is life's goal.
But one must always fight to get what one wants.
Isn't that correct, Enyaba?
Indeed.
And if the battle is lost and one
fails to obtain what one desires most,
the result is frustration, pain, and a sense of failure.
One carries the wound into the
future, into the next fearful battle.
I believe conquering that fear once
and for all is what it means to live.
The one who stands at the
pinnacle is the one who has no fear.
Do you understand, Enyaba?
I was the one who told you about the
existence of your stand and how to use it.
Also you have an immortal body.
Is there anything you could possibly fear?
Perhaps, old woman.
Hmm. What burdens you, my lord?
The Joestar bloodline.
Hmm? Joestar? They worry you?
Those worms are mere trash.
Your enemies are no match for your stand.
Yes, but I must believe it's destiny
when the lives of those worms are
so thoroughly entangled with mine.
It is a fate that has been written
for us all from the very beginning.
Let me be clear.
It is not the Joestars that I fear,
but the fact that I can never
underestimate their bloodline.
In order to obliterate all fear,
I have decided that I must remove
the Joestars from the cogs of fate.
You want to go and eliminate them yourself, simply
because you feel that they cannot be underestimated?
Yes.
Foolishness!
You should never engage in such trivial
matters! They are beneath someone of your stature!
I have sent seven stand users to command...
The empress, the wheel of fortune, the hanged
man and temperance, the emperor, and the devil...
All of them on the move and
ready to strike whenever you.
Thanks to these allies, you need
not take any action yourself, lord Dio.
A freighter.
I didn't see it at all.
Jotaro, something's bothering you, isn't it?
Are you worried there might be
another stand user on this freighter?
It's not ideal, but we could handle it.
Not quite. Strange they lowered the stairs,
but there's not a single soul
to be seen around here anywhere.
Eh?
This ship came all this way to rescue us.
There has to be some sort of crew on board.
Even if they're all stand users, I'm getting on this boat.
I'm done drifting in circles.
Hmm?
Take my hand, kid. I'll help you get up.
Um...
Blehh!
Good grief.
Hey, what's with this ship?
There's no captain in the control room,
there's no engineer in the radio room.
There's no one anywhere. And yet, look at this.
All the gauges and machinery are
working properly, just like normal.
Maybe they're just all in the
bathroom with a bad case of the runs.
Hey! Isn't anyone around?!
You have to see this. Come here! Quick!
Eh?
An ape. There's an ape inside that cage.
It's an orangutan.
Who the hell cares about a friggin' ape?!
Let's split up and find whoever's been feeding this thing.
Well?
Hmm.
It doesn't appear to be broken, but...
Uh...
Eh?
Avdol!
That sailor! Watch out!
Oh, good grief.
That isn't any way to greet a lady
you've never met before, now, is it?
But no one was touching the controls.
I saw that crane move,
even though there was no one operating it.
I don't believe in ghosts, but what the hell?
I saw it, too. That crane impaled him all on its own.
Keep your guard up. There's someone hostile here.
Hey, don't touch the machinery. You got that?
If it moves or runs on electricity,
don't lay a finger on it.
If you want to live, then you'll
do exactly as I tell you. Understand?
Get into the cabin below, and stay
there until I tell you otherwise.
Did any one of you see even a glimpse of a stand just now?
I didn't.
My apologies. I was the closest to
the crane, and yet I felt nothing.
I should have been able to sense something.
All right. I'll send Hierophant
Green to take a look around the ship.
I have no idea what's going on,
but scary things keep happening
whenever you guys are around.
Could you guys be jinxed?
I've heard about people who cause
disasters that endanger everyone.
If that's what you are, I'd better stay away.
I have just one bit of truth for you, so listen closely.
Whatever happens, we're on your side.
Uh... huh.
Stay safe. Make sure you stay with the others. Got it?
Mm-hmm.
Do you want me to open the cage for you?
But I can't. I have no idea where the key is,
and you're too big to let out.
You're giving me an apple?
But it doesn't make any sense.
This apple's been cut with a knife,
and the color hasn't really changed yet.
It looks totally fresh, like it was cut a second ago,
so I guess there really must be
someone hiding somewhere on this boat.
Where is the person who feeds you?
Has he gone off and left you here?
Huh?
Mmm.
Whoa. You're a pretty smart
monkey. Who trained you to do that?
No way. A monkey like you is actually into looking at...
Pinups of girls?
Hey, kid, be careful there.
They say an orangutan has five
times the strength of a normal human,
so it could easily rip off your arm.
Come on. Stay with us in the room on the other side.
Don't go off by yourself.
Oh, okay.
It's inconceivable.
I've had Hierophant Green search every inch of this
ship, but I can't find a single sign of human life aboard.
We've searched every pipe and
crevice, but still came up empty-handed.
Anything?
It's no use. I can't get a connection.
Well, try again, damn it.
Ehh, gross. I feel sticky from the salt water.
Huh? Hmm.
Huh?
Hey.
JoJo!
Take your lock, you stinking ape.
Seems that this ape...
Isn't your run-of-the-mill monkey.
Could it be that he's the one?
Ora!
Wait.
Who the hell ripped out that fan?
Had to be him.
So this ape's a stand user, but where's the stand?
I should be able to see the damn thing, but I can't.
Doesn't make any sense.
What the...
The steel propeller bent on its own, like it's alive.
JoJo.
Hey, what's going on here?
Son of a bitch.
There's no stand in sight, and somehow the window broke?
Star Platinum!
What's with this thing?
The ape just sank into the wall and disappeared.
Hey, you saw that, right?
Stay close to me. Something bad is going down.
The ape vanished into the wall,
but that orangutan has to be the stand user.
When I touched it earlier, I felt
a stand's energy coming from it.
I have no doubt that he's the one we're looking for.
Doesn't make any sense.
Why can't I see the stand, like I always do?
Wait.
What if I'm seeing it already?
What's happening?
Whoa. What's going on?
This isn't good.
It's swallowing us.
Is the freighter trying to... is
it possible the ship itself is...
So the stand is actually the freighter.
Damn. You son of a...
All of it,
this ship itself and everything
on it, is a gigantic stand!
The entire ship?
So there are stands that non-stand users,
like that girl and the crew members, can see?
The only possible explanation
for that is that its immense energy
is making it possible to be seen with the naked eye.
But all this must demand a tremendous amount
of energy to operate a stand as huge as this.
Kakyoin, send Hierophant Green to Jotaro.
He can help get us out of this.
I... can't do that.
It's got a firm hold on my stand, and I'm stuck.
This is what it means to face
death. We fell for this trap,
and now we're hopelessly
ensnared with no way to escape.
The pressure keeps increasing.
At this rate, our bodies are going to be pulverized.
We... will be...
Damn. We were careless.
We've got to...
The word that the was pointing to was "strength."
It means force, energy, power, or aid,
and it is the eighth card of the tarot deck.
It suggests challenge, a strong will, and hidden powers.
Damn ape. Thinks he's won already, huh?
"This entire ship is my stand, and you've lost.
"You're totally outmatched and
helpless, and there's nothing you can do."
Jotaro needed no explanation.
He knew exactly what the ape was saying.
Over here, monkey.
That button's not part of your stand.
Are you angry?
I guess it wounded your pride, since
you thought you'd already beaten us.
No, it's not hurt at all, is it?
Because apes like you don't have any pride.
That's exactly what makes you an ape and not a
man. What's going to hurt now... is your head!
Good grief.
I've heard that, when frightened, animals show
their stomachs to signal their submission to the enemy.
So you're asking me to forgive you?
I'm afraid your actions have already
gone beyond the rules of the jungle,
so I don't think so.
Ora!
What the... the pipes and walls are
distorting. The whole ship is twisting up.
Hey, be surprised about it later.
This ship is about to sink.
It's time to leave. Get back to the lifeboats.
Wow, I can't believe it.
The ship's shape is changing. It's
turning into a shabby little boat.
If I hadn't seen it myself, I wouldn't believe it.
That ape was traveling the sea on his own stand.
What terrifying power. That was the
first time I've encountered such energy.
Hate to say it, but we were
completely overwhelmed this round.
If Jotaro hadn't figured it
out, we would have been done for.
Are we going to encounter even more
stands with crazy, unknown powers from now on?
We'll have to be ready for anything.
Hey, you want some gum?
So we're going to be drifting again.
Good grief. My cigarettes are soaked.
There'll be plenty of sun and
time for them to get dry, JoJo.
We'll have to pray that we get rescued
and reach Singapore safely and soon.
It's been four days since we left Japan.
There are 46 days until time runs out for the Joestars.
My lord, it would appear that Strength has been defeated.
But have no fear. The remaining six stand users
are all very powerful and each deadlier than the last,
and one of them is my son. His
right arm shall crush our enemies.
The Joestars will not pose a
threat when he's finished with them.
You are a strange old woman.
What is it that you desire the most?
Oh, but I've told you many times. My
only wish is to stay by your side, my lord.
Your guardian spirit has unbelievable power.
Your ability to escape trouble and
your strange life are the result of that.
I would like to see your life
unfold. It's the only thing I want.
Once upon a time, there was a prince from the land
of Sumatra who traveled the seas seeking new lands.
Eventually he happened upon an island inhabited by
lions called Singas, an island he named Singapura.
Today, its straits bustle with ships
and tankers from around the world.
This nation that shares both western and eastern
heritage, thanks to free trade, is tropical Singapore.
Good grief. We finally made it to dry land.
We'll clean up and get some rest at a hotel. Once
we've recharged, we'll figure out our route to Egypt.
All right, let's stay at that one.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian