No way! We got it. That treasure's been at
the bottom of the ocean for a hundred years,
and now whatever's in it is ours.
Hey, stay calm.
We gotta get it on the boat before we start celebrating.
Yeah, I know. I know.
Up we go.
That thing looks too long and
narrow to be a treasure chest.
Just do your job! You're lifting it too high.
Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
All right.
Come on. Crack it open already.
Hold on. Wait. This is bizarre.
It seems like this thing was locked from the inside.
Who the hell cares? Just bust it open.
Just give me a sec. Something's written on it.
D-I-O, "Dio."
Is that someone's name?
I don't care!
Just freakin' open it up!
The sun's about to go down, and don't
wanna be countin' treasure in the dark.
Okay, I hear you.
I'm gonna go get the blowtorch.
And then we can start dividin' up our loot.
On a day like any other, a motorboat
was found adrift and abandoned.
The craft was largely undamaged
and showed no signs of struggle.
In the galley, three cups of coffee sat half full,
and on deck, an iron chest, its
lock melted away, lay open and empty.
But the chest's unusual shelter-like chambers
baffled discoverers,
who believed it to have once contained a vast treasure.
But interest waned, and before
long, the chest was forgotten.
Jotaro Kujo, 17 years old and 195 centimeters tall.
His father is a Japanese jazz musician, currently on tour.
His mother is an American of British decent.
Yes, all of that is correct,
and Jotaro is definitely my son.
It seems like all his friends call him JoJo.
Guess they decided to take the Jo from his first
name and the Jo from his last name and combine 'em.
Ah, man, that's really lame.
I... I need to know.
Exactly how many people did Jotaro kill?!
No! I take it back! I don't want to know!
Settle down. Nobody said
anything about him killin' people.
He got into a fight. That's all.
The truth is, the thugs he tangled with
were all armed with nunchuks and knives.
He fought four punks, one being an ex-boxer, and he
broke 15 of their bones, and he busted their balls.
Sorry if that was crude.
He put all of them in the hospital.
Things could have gone a lot worse. He's
gotta be shown the severity of his actions.
Okay.
The real issue is what happened afterward.
Copy this, and pass it around.
Yes, sir.
I gotta tell you, that son of yours is a strange one.
Huh?
Okay, follow me. I'll show you the way.
Thank you for everything.
Look, you can thank me by takin' your kid home.
So then, does that mean you're releasing him?
Well, we can't keep him in here forever.
Okay.
By the way, ma'am, I have to tell
you your Japanese is really quite good.
Just how long have you been livin' in Japan?
For 20 years now.
Well, that explains it, then.
Good work, men.
This place has been overrun lately.
We got an entire backlog of criminals
that we aren't even able to find cells for.
We're almost there, ma'am. Your son's just up ahead.
Jotaro!
Jotaro, throw the ball to mom.
That's it. Good boy.
Do your best at that track meet tomorrow.
I will.
Jotaro.
You did it. Let's go out to eat and celebrate.
Nothing's as good as your cooking, mom.
Jotaro.
Jotaro!
Shut up!
Get out of my face, you bitch!
Okay!
I promise you he's a very sweet boy.
He's just not capable of doing something so appalling.
Hey, on your feet, Kujo!
You're being released. What part
of "go home" don't you understand?
Hmph.
Listen, mom, you can leave.
I'll be stayin' here for a while.
Huh?
Seems I've been possessed by an evil spirit,
and I've no idea what he'll make me do next.
During that fight, it took all I had just to stop it,
so do everyone a favor, and leave me in this cage.
Jeez. For crying out loud. Do
you see what I'm talking about?
We're trying to release him, but he refuses to go.
I'm sorry to have to ask you this, but are you
sure everything's all right with your boy upstairs?
This isn't a hotel, you know, ma'am.
Come on! Let us change cells! Please!
He's not lying about the evil spirit thing.
All right, all right! That's enough! All of you, shut up!
Is he... seriously?
What are you doin' with a beer in a jail
cell?! How did you even get that in there?!
I told you. I've got an evil spirit,
and sometimes it likes to bring me things.
They're still in, still in.
What the hell?! He's reading "Shonen
Jump" while listening to a radio!
Sir, I... I mean, how is this even possible?
We have a major problem here!
Hold it.
This might not be enough to make
you guys keep me locked up in here,
but I'll show you how evil this spirit is anyway.
Maybe then you'll see why
lettin' me outta here is a bad idea.
That's my gun he has in his hand. But how'd he...
That's really bad.
You didn't see it just now?
Well, if you guys didn't see
my evil spirit, then watch this.
No! Jotaro!
It's like there's someone behind me.
It bound itself to me not long ago.
Jotaro's grandfather Joseph has strange powers...
But what's happening to my son?
Papa!
Hmm?
Over here, papa! Over here.
Holly! Outta my way.
Oh, I can't believe you're here.
Thank you for coming.
Hey, you're my one and only daughter, and
if you tell me you need me to be somewhere,
then just give me a day, and I'll cross the globe.
Did mom come?
She didn't like me leavin',
but I just told Suzie that it was official
Joestar corporation business and I had to go.
Thanks, papa.
Holly, hey.
The greeting's over. Let go of me already.
No. I don't wanna.
It's been forever since you've held me.
Look at yourself.
Come on. You're a 45-year-old woman. Let go.
Oh, now you've done it.
I'm gonna tickle you. Tickle, tickle, tickle.
Hey, stop that!
No!
Goochie-goochie goo.
Hmm?
Hey, what are you clowns staring at?
Mommy.
Don't look.
I'll take your bag.
By the way, Holly, about Jotaro...
You sure he used the word "evil spirit"?
Oh, my poor little boy.
Yes. The policemen said they couldn't see
it, but I saw it. It's like he had a third arm,
and then he reached out and grabbed the gun.
And when this arm came out, no
one else there could see it but you?
That's right.
And aside from Jotaro saying that
he's been possessed, you're okay?
Did anything happen to you?
I feel totally fine, but what do I do about Jotaro?
He says he won't leave that cell
until he finds the cause of all this.
What am I gonna do, papa?
There, there, my darling daughter.
You've got Joseph Joestar with you now.
No need to worry.
Thank you.
Now let's go see my grandson.
Jotaro can explain this himself.
It's gettin' spookier.
He's got more stuff in his cell now,
and he's violent.
If something is possessing him,
it's definitely not something nice.
If word of this gets out to my superiors,
I'll lose my job in a heartbeat for sure.
He's no longer your problem.
I'll be taking my grandson home now.
Your grandson?
Hold it. That's far enough.
You're better off just staying where you are.
It's dangerous. Convince him to leave
from where you're standing, or I can't...
I'll take my chances.
Now step aside, and leave him to me.
We won't be held responsible.
Move it!
Jotaro, this is your grandfather.
Whatever's happened, he'll be able to help you.
Please come out and talk to him.
Come out. It's time to go home.
Get lost.
I didn't ask you to come here.
You really think you can help me,
an old man like yourself?
Sorry you came all the way from New
York, but nobody can help me, gramps.
Huh?
Wait.
That's the pinkie from my prosthetic left hand.
When was he able to take it?
So did you see it or even feel it?
That's the evil spirit.
Stay away from me, or you'll
lose what's left of your life.
I've never seen anything like this.
He was able to deceive me right off the bat.
That's unbelievable.
I'm afraid I know exactly what Jotaro's evil spirit is,
but I don't think explaining it to him will do any good.
He'll understand his situation much
better if he sees it with his own eyes.
Actually, in order for him to
truly know the danger he faces,
he needs to experience it physically.
All right, Avdol.
It's your turn now.
I'd like you to meet an Egyptian
friend I met a few years ago.
Say hello to Avdol.
Hmm?
Do what you need to.
Just get my grandson to leave this damn cell.
Back off.
You look strong enough,
but do you really think I'd let someone chase
me outta here just 'cause you told them to do it?
I don't work like that. In fact,
all you've done now is made me wanna stay here even more.
I'm afraid this may get a little bit rough.
But in a few minutes, he'll be riddled with so much pain,
that he'll be begging you to let him out of here.
Just do what you gotta do.
Papa, you can't be serious.
W... wait a sec. We can't let you turn this...
Zip it, pig!
Yes, sir!
This is...
Heh. That's right.
Avdol also has what you'd call an evil spirit,
an evil spirit under the complete
command of Avdol's will, and his name is...
Magician's Red!
It's hot. I feel like I'm on fire.
My arms, they're burning.
What are these evil spirits?
What's Kujo doing? Why's he
flattened himself against the back wall?
Yeah, I don't get it.
But do you feel how hot it's gettin' in here?
Look at those numbers.
That's insane! What's happening?!
Aha! There it is!
It's finally shown itself, and the fact that
it's so clearly visible means it's incredibly strong.
Let's do this.
I can't believe he's able to
make it manifest so distinctly.
Well done.
Your evil spirit is impressive, too.
So tell me, grandpa, you know about these evil spirits?
Of course I do.
Mr. Joestar, when you asked me to help
get your grandson out of this jail cell,
I had planned on going easy on the boy,
but in light of his tremendous
power, I'm reconsidering that.
Just one misstep could put us all in danger.
Tell me if you want me to stop.
If not, I'll resort to a use of force
that could land your grandson in the hospital.
Like I said, do what you gotta do.
Yes, sir!
Red bind!
Huh? What the...
What's up with this heat?
Yeah, what the hell's going
on? None of this makes any sense!
Papa, that's enough! What are you doing to Jotaro?
Holly, be a good girl, and let
papa finish what he started, okay?
I can't breathe.
The evil spirit is withdrawing.
The heat is restricting his breathing,
which causes the evil spirit to weaken.
And now for the truth.
This may seem like an evil spirit, but it's far from it.
Jotaro,
this thing you believe has possessed you is actually
a powerful vision created by your own life energy.
This vision will always appear standing by your side,
and because of that, we call it...
A stand!
A stand?
Remember Aesop's fable.
The cold wind made the traveler pull his coat tighter,
but the heat forced him to admit defeat.
Ready to leave your cage now, JoJo?
I said it before. I'm stayin'.
I keep hurting other people
without even knowing I'm doing it.
Until that stops, I'm stayin' here.
It's nice to meet someone like me,
but if you keep this up,
you'll die.
Huh?
He just broke the damn toilet.
Hey, that's destruction of property!
You had your chance.
All right, bastard.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
What the hell?
Why'd you suddenly turn your back on me?
We're not done.
Mr. Joestar, he's left his jail cell.
I've accomplished what you asked me to do, right?
So now what? You got me, huh?
Not exactly.
I did have every intention of sending you to the hospital,
but you're stronger than I had expected.
And if I had kept going with this steel rod,
just what would you have done?
Do not underestimate my stand, Magician's Red.
It could have easily melted that
rod midair into a worthless puddle.
The power Avdol has is exactly the same as yours.
If you want to know more about this evil spirit,
you'll need to leave this jail.
Thank you. Thank you, Jotaro.
I'm glad you finally left that awful jail cell.
Why are you such an annoying bitch?
Okay. I don't know.
Hey, how dare you address your own mother that way?!
And what kind of language is that?
And stop smiling, Holly. You'll only encourage it.
Okay.
Hey, grampa, one question.
There's something that I can't quite wrap my brain around.
You seem to know all about this...
Evil spirit, the stand, whatever you wanna call it,
but how do you know this?
Hmm. How do I know?
I guess I did come all the way
from New York to explain it to you.
But in order for you to fully understand the
whole history of it, I must start from the beginning.
This is part of the legacy of the Joestar family.
Take a look at these pictures.
What are these about?
That coffin's a hundred years old, and four years ago,
it was pulled out of the Atlantic off the coast of Africa.
Okay. So?
I did a little research.
My grandfather, Jonathan Joestar, your
great-grandfather, died while at sea.
Turns out this exact same coffin
was on that boat with him when he died.
When they discovered it four years ago, it was empty.
But I know exactly what was inside it.
Avdol and I are trying to locate him as we speak.
Hold on. Did you say, "him"?
Are you suggesting there was a person inside that thing?
Come on. How could a human being stay
buried underwater for a hundred years?
Because that person is evil incarnate,
and his name is Dio!
And now that he has been awakened
from his hundred-year slumber,
it is our fate to fight that man!
What the hell does that face mean?
And don't you turn your back on me
like this has nothing to do with you!
Look, you old man, this face means your
story is so lame, I don't know what to say.
What? "Old man"?
Avdol, was it?
I don't know you, but you are one arrogant bastard.
And as for you, old man...
Huh?
Did you really expect me to fall
for an unbelievable story like that?
Heh. I know the story sounds far-fetched,
but wouldn't you also say our evil
spirits are equally unbelievable?
Think what you want,
but soon you will have no choice but to believe it.
If you want me to tell you how I know that
Dio exists and why I've chosen to go after him,
the best way to explain it is to show you.
See, the truth of it is I myself had a rather
startling revelation that prompted all of this.
About a year ago, I suddenly obtained a stand of my own.
What did you say?!
Gramps, what did you...
Get ready.
Let me introduce...
My stand!
Did you see it, the thorns that came out of my hand?
This is my stand.
It can reveal faraway visions and place them on film.
The only downside is I have to bust a
30,000-yen camera every time I use it!
Excuse me. Is everything all right here?
We're fine. Now go on. Run along.
Of course.
In a matter of seconds, a vision
will appear in this photograph, Jotaro,
and it will reveal your very destiny!
What are you talking about?
Jotaro, Holly,
have either of you ever taken the time to
look carefully at the back of your necks?
What does that mean?
You each have it, but you
probably never thought much about it,
a birthmark shaped like a star.
It turns out that we all have it.
I'll say it again. What the hell does all this mean?
My father died when I was young, so I asked my
mother about it, and she said he had one, too.
It seems that everyone from the Joestar
bloodline is born with this exact same birthmark.
All right, and just what the hell
is gonna turn up in that photograph?
It's our destiny, a path that until now has been unknown.
Papa.
I'm losing my patience. Just
show me the damn photo already.
Dio. He shows up in all my spirit photos,
and look what's just above his shoulder.
From the neck of this bastard on down
is Jonathan Joestar, my grandfather!
This son of a bitch took over his body!
A hundred years ago, there was
an incident in the Atlantic ocean.
All I know is what I've learned
from my grandmother, Erina.
Somehow, Dio took over the body
of my grandfather and survived.
And this much I know is certain...
This bastard is currently hiding somewhere on the globe,
plotting something.
It's four years since he's revived,
and the reason my spirit photography
and your evil spirit have manifested
since is most likely connected to Dio.
To society in general, our gifts
are considered a kind of psychic power.
I've had my stand since the day I was
born, but your powers seem bound to Dio's body,
or, rather, Jonathan Joestar's body.
There's some sort of invisible
string that connects you all to him.
His rebirth is also your own,
awakening your sleeping powers.
Avdol, does this photograph give you
any indication to where he might be now?
No, nothing.
There's hardly anything of note in the photo at all.
I see.
I'll take a closer look later.
Thank you. Hmm?
Oh, Holly.
I'm sorry I sprang this all on you out of the blue.
Let's head home now.
All right.
I think I'll be sticking around for quite some time.
You mind if I stay at your place while I'm here?
No, of course not, papa. Let's go, Jotaro.
Again...
Just now...
A most intense feeling like
someone somewhere is watching me.
It is Jonathan's descendants.
This body is sending out some kind
of spiritual signal to his offspring.
Fine. It must be my fate.
But fate must be purged.
It's all set.
I've taken the first step.