That piercing noise...
What is this place?
An amusement park?
I've never been here before.
W-Why in the world am I riding
on a ferris wheel in my pajamas?
How'd I get here?
The desert.
I remember being in the desert,
riding through Saudi Arabia on camelback.
But where are the others?
Did they abandon me?
This isn't making any sense.
There's not a soul anywhere in the amusement
park, so why do I hear the cries of a baby?
And for that matter, where is it?
Th-this card is...
Death 13..
Oh, no! The card is moving!
Kakyoin. Kakyoin!
Hey, take it easy.
Stop screaming and shaking the bed
like that creepy girl from "the exorcist."
You're weirding me out.
Where are we?
Don't ask stupid questions.
Now come on, and get up already, would you?
After breakfast, we're gonna take to the skies.
Looks like another scorcher today.
I had a terrible nightmare.
It was truly horrifying.
You don't say? Lay on the
details. I wanna hear all about it.
Well, the thing is, I can't remember.
I've forgotten it all.
Come again?
Regardless, it was petrifying,
but when you woke me up, you pulled me out of it.
Wish we could talk more about
it, but we've gotta get a move on.
Let's go.
Hurry up, and get ready.
There's a cut on my hand.
But how'd it get there?
Jotaro and Mr. Joestar are already headed
to the plane, so we'll meet them there,
and the way I hear it, we're
traveling 500 kilometers today.
No! This can't be happening!
Please, not my poor dog!
My dog is dead!
Who would do such a thing?!
A dog? Dog?
I could have sworn...
That I saw a dead dog not too long ago.
Whoever did this is sick, but
there's nothing we can do about it.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Hold on a dang second there, mister!
What exactly do you mean, you can't sell us the plane now?
I seem to recall you taking my money
last night and saying it was a done deal.
You'll get a full refund, but first
we need to see to a baby with a fever.
It's 39 degrees Celsius.
Huh?
There's no doctor in this town, so we have no
choice but to take the baby somewhere else to get help.
Okay, then, what do you say to
us taking that plane over there?
I'm sorry to say that one's
broken, and the others are out...
What's up? Some kind of argument?
Yeah.
A baby?
A baby.
I remember hearing a baby's cries...
But where?
You'll be able to use the plane
after it gets back tomorrow night.
We can renegotiate and talk prices then.
Did you say, "tomorrow night"?
Our group has someone's life on
the line, just like you guys do.
We can't afford to spend two
days pissing around this place.
So what you're telling me is
you'd rather let that baby die?!
Well, I...
Excuse me.
I have a suggestion.
We can kill two birds with one stone by having
these gentlemen take him to the doctor on their way.
Uh, nice idea, but...
The Cessna is built to carry four, but
surely there's enough room for a baby.
I could have sworn I just saw it smile
and that the child already has teeth.
You sure about this, lady?
Do you really want to leave your baby with these guys?
Eh, just a minute. We can't do that either.
It's too dangerous for the baby to come with us.
I told them this would be dangerous.
Hey, just try and take it easy, Mr. Joestar.
There's no way a stand could catch a
plane flying hundreds of kilometers an hour.
I mean, we even made sure the plane itself wasn't a stand.
I'd say we're good to go.
I'm far more worried about the old man's
flying than I am an attack from enemy stands.
Oh, thank goodness. What a relief.
By the way, I wonder who that baby belonged to.
Huh? Are you saying you're not
the mother of that child, miss?
Oh, no. I found it by the well this morning.
Though, from the moment I heard the
baby's crying, I wasn't able to help myself.
I felt I had to put him on that plane.
What could happen?
Maybe it's just me, but I always
get so tired when I get on a plane.
If it's all right with you, Mr. Joestar,
I think I'm gonna take a 30-minute catnap.
Sure.
W-What is this?
Hey, Kakyoin, where the hell are we?!
Where'd Mr. Joestar go?!
This is the same dream I had this morning,
but now it seems we're both inside the dream.
What? A dream?
Yes.
That's a relief. It's just a stupid dream.
I was worried for a second, but if it's
only a dream, who cares if the dog is dead?
Polnareff, you can't be serious.
Dreams are only as scary as you make
'em. That's kind of the way it goes.
Oh. Just try and relax.
How can I relax when we're having the same dream?!
I suppose you have a point there.
This is kinda weird.
But in a dream, isn't anything possible?
Oh, boy! Would you look at that?
This dreaming thing is great.
So good.
See? All you have to do to make
your dreams fun is think they're fun.
Listen. Do you remember seeing
the dog's carcass this morning?
Obviously, the dog and I had the same dream, and
in that dream, that dog was unmistakably slaughtered.
Once I was awake, I found this cut on my hand.
Eh? Where from?
From the enemy's stand, Death 13...
The enemy stand?
Oh, I get it now. You're paranoid,
'cause you had a dream about stands.
Hah! Man, you have got to take it easy.
You're wrong! It wasn't a dream about stands.
A stand was in my dream. That's what I said.
You were having a dream about stands.
You still don't get it, do you?
Lali-ho! Tell me, does it hurt being that stupid?
Oh, for the love of...
Let me spell it out for you!
I'm saying that you're slow on the uptake, Polnareff!
I-it's coming from the dog's wound.
Lali-ho!
Allow me to welcome you to my humble abode.
This is a dream, and I'm the grim reaper!
It's a megaphone?
What the... what is that thing?!
Polnareff, stay on guard, and watch
closely. That fiend is Death 13..
W-w...
Come forth, Hierophant Green!
Hierophant, attack!
Chario...
Why can't I summon Hierophant?
What is this?
I can't get my stand appear either.
Is it because we're in some kind of twisted dream?
Lali-ho!
It's romantic, wouldn't you
agree, being able to die in a dream?
Lali-ho.
Eh, Jotaro, do you sense that?
Yeah, clear as day.
Are you stupid?
Surely you know by now that
only a stand can defeat a stand.
It's time for you to enter your eternal sleep, Polnareff.
Lali-ho.
Polnareff!
Die!
Polnareff.
Hey, Polnareff, wake up.
It would appear our little traveler has wet himself.
Do us all a favor, and change his diaper.
Eh, curses.
Someone must have woken the fool from his slumber.
He's quite lucky.
Lali-ho. I suppose it's no matter.
Even if he wakes up, he won't remember a single thing.
I'll just have to finish him
the next time he falls asleep.
Which means your death has been moved up.
Lali-ho!
Hey, there, Polnareff, have you woken up yet?
I'd like that diaper changed this year.
All right. I'm up. I'm up.
Man. I feel like I had some kind of terrifying nightmare,
but I... I don't remember what happened at all.
I've completely forgotten.
After you change the boy's diaper, you can
head back to dreamland to finish your business.
I won't wake you up again.
Merde! Hold on a second, guys. What the hell is this?!
The kid took a dump in his
diaper. Just look at the size of it.
Well, he is a baby, you know. That's why he wears diapers.
You're kidding me! That's why?!
C'est degueulasse.
What a vile, disgusting creature.
And he's gotten it all over the place!
Would you stop yapping and change
the damn diaper already? It stinks.
How are you not embarrassed?
Do us all a favor, and grow up already.
Does this look right to you?
Well, it looks good to me.
Jotaro, I need you to hold on to the
edge there. I'm gonna try and pin it.
Okay. Like this?
Yeah, I think so. Now hold on to the baby.
Lali-ho!
Stop it! Stop it!
Kakyoin, what's wrong?
Hey!
What's going on?
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
Damn it!
I've lost control!
Wait. Are you saying that we're gonna crash?
Stop!
Kakyoin, what's the matter with you?
He's been this way since he woke up!
I don't care. Just calm him down.
Old man, if you don't regain control
of this thing, we're all done for.
Kakyoin, you need to pull yourself together,
pronto. We're about to crash because of you.
Lali-ho.
Talk about a restless sleeper. At this rate,
you'll kill us both, you and my user, that is.
Y-your user is that baby? How
in the world is that possible?
No way. He's only about six months old.
Wrong. I'm 11 months, almost a year old.
It may also interest you to know that I'm a genius.
I may poop in my diapers, but I know
a hell of a lot more than you fools!
Lali-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
And with that, you've lost your ability to scream.
A stand within a dream.
I have to find a way to let Mr. Joestar and Jotaro know.
What are you doing? Mr. Joestar!
Damn it. Level us out.
Just calm down.
Can't you see I'm working on that
while trying to stay cool and collected?
I'm not waking up.
Lali-ho. Looks to me like no one's going to notice
if you're cutting your arm with a
knife that's smaller than my wee-wee.
Besides, you can hurt yourself all you
want in this dream, but it won't wake you up.
As long as you're asleep, I completely
control every iota of your precious mind.
My stand, Death 13, infiltrates the minds of its
slumbering victims when they are at their most vulnerable.
Damn it. Stop.
What's wrong, old man?
We're crashing.
I'll control it with Hermit Purple.
I did it! I lifted the plane just in the nick of time!
What a close one.
It would seem we managed to avoid crashing.
That was too close for comfort.
Now, then, what do you say to me killing
you by crushing that heart of yours?
That way, Joestar and the others will think
you had a heart attack and died of natural causes.
Die, Kakyoin.
Did you guys see that? How do you boys
like them apples? My flying's not too shabby.
Well done.
Hey.
Hmm?
What? Why the hell is there a
palm tree all the way out here?
Good grief. Damn.
I knew you'd do this.
Is this enough, Mr. Joestar?
Yeah. Thank you.
We survived, but
Kakyoin, what's going on, man?
This is all your fault, you know?
I'm not sure.
I feel like I just endured a horrible dream,
and when I awoke, I was utterly exhausted.
I think there's something wrong with me.
Try and cheer up. It's probably a case of fatigue.
It's been about a month now since we left Japan,
and the enemy's been attacking
us nonstop ever since that day.
Hey. It looks like the baby's fever has finally gone down.
Thank goodness he's safe and sound.
If anything were to happen, to this
little guy, I'd never forgive myself.
Peek-a-boo. Bleh!
Peek-a-boo. Bleh.
He has such an adorable smile, don't you think?
I really don't get what's so funny.
You're not even making any
jokes, just faces. What an idiot.
Oh, put a sock in it.
This isn't my idea of a perfect night, either.
Hey, old man, the radio survived. What should we do?
Should we send out an S.O.S?
That'll mean Dio can find us, but...
We have to.
Let's call for a rescue, for the baby's sake.
I thought I was feeling twinges of pain.
I'm bleeding.
Wait. Did I cut it when we crashed?
What's this? The cuts form letters.
"Baby... stand"?
But how did they.
I don't know what it means,
even though it's my handwriting.
I can't remember anything.
Did I do this to myself?
There isn't any blood on my knife, but it
seems the cuts were made with this blade.
Wait a minute, could I have really
forgotten violently cutting my own arm?
Damn it. I was told that he was clever,
but I never got he actually carved letters
into his arm while trying to wake himself.
What was that look on the baby's face just now?
It's as if he deliberately looked
away the moment I met his gaze.
Baby...
Stand.
Baby stand.
I hate to say it, but I might be losing my mind, because.
I'm starting to think...
That this baby is a stand user!
Hey, Kakyoin, what do you think you're doing?
Come on, now. That is way too rough.
You could strangle the boy. What's wrong with you?
My apologies.
There, there. Everything's all right.
Let's have something to eat, shall we?
He should calm down once he has some food in him.
Hey, Jotaro, it looks like poor Kakyoin's
really starting to lose it out here.
There, there...
I wonder if he'll make it through the rest of this trip.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian