Tokyo, Hong Kong, Singapore...
So the Indian leg of our journey is finally upon us.
But, well, I'm a little bit worried.
I mean, is there anywhere to get a cheeseburger there?
I've always heard India was a land
of curry, disease, too many people.
I know. I'm worried my stomach
won't be able to handle the culture gap.
That assessment is rather distorted.
You needn't worry.
It's a country of extraordinary people.
That, I assure you, my friends.
Well, we've reached Calcutta.
Let's get going.
Let me carry that for you!
Want a tattoo? You're very pretty.
Need some anti-venom? It won't hurt your stomach.
Stay at our hotel!
Calcutta, India,
in the 20th century, its population is 11 million.
Calcutta buzzes with a bustling energy
that will pull you in and never let you go.
I don't need any.
I stepped in some cow shit! Damn!
Seriously, thank you.
Aw, crap. Somebody's already stolen my wallet.
Tip! Tip! Tip!
If you don't give me tips,
you won't go to heaven, sir.
Hey, kid, don't put your nose all over my stuff!
Avdol!
So this is India?
See? Great country, isn't it?
They're what makes India great, don't you think?
Here. Try this.
This is chai. I think you'll find it to your liking.
Chai, one of India's most popular drinks,
a sweet concoction made by boiling
black tea, sugar, and ginger with milk.
At last, a little peace.
Be patient with India.
Once you get used to it,
you'll see how wonderful this country is.
You know, I kinda like this place. It's pretty cool.
What, Jotaro? You cannot be serious.
It's a hell of a lot of culture shock, though.
Guess I'll like it once I get used to it, huh?
Well, I guess people adapt to
their surroundings eventually.
Where's the John?
It's right over there, sir.
Polnareff.
Yeah?
Aren't you going to order first?
Pick for me.
It better be something amazing,
something gorgeous and sophisticated
that suits a Frenchman such as moi.
Which means it doesn't matter, he'll eat anything.
Let's see. What's something he'll like?
Excuse me.
Pardon me, sir. Could you please wait?
Eh?
Huh?
Please use this while you're in here.
Hmm?
What am I supposed to do with this? Hey!
Hmm? Hmm.
Hmm.
Ooh la la.
I must say, the toilet looks weird, but at
least it's a lot cleaner than I had expected.
A gentleman like myself has certain standards
and won't stand for it when a bathroom is dirty.
Sir, is something wrong?
D...d...d...d...don’t "is something wrong?" Me!
Th...th...th...th...the toilet...
The toilet...
There's a pig sticking its head out of it!
Why, yes. No need to be frightened.
He's actually quite friendly.
The builders constructed the pigpen down
below higher than they were supposed to,
so when the pigs get hungry,
they come up for more. That's all.
But that's not even what I'm asking you about!
No. Wait. What?
So you're telling me...
That this pig's food is...
That's what it's there for?!
As I told you, sir, here. Use this stick,
like this.
See? Now you can do your business while the
pig's knocked down. Though some like the pig.
Our manager gets the pig to lick his
buttocks and always sings the pig's praises.
He gets it so clean.
Feel free to take your time.
Hey, monsieur, don't leave me alone!
I don't think I could ever get used to this,
no matter how much I tried.
I'll wait until we get to the hotel.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh.
Crap, the food.
Hmm?
Where is he?
No way. Too weird.
I know I saw someone out there.
Huh. I must have imagined it.
I guess I can't help it.
I mean, there was a pig in the John, for god's sake.
Oh, well. Nothing there.
What's a little monster in the mirror, anyway?
So this is what they mean by culture shock here.
Wh...what the?!
Huh?
What the hell is going on here?!
I can only see this damn thing in the mirror!
This must be the mirror stand Jotaro talked about.
Merde, this is not good.
Mon dieu! This is so not good!
Ah! Silver Chariot!
Huh? Where did that bastard go?
Damn it.
Huh?
A stand!
Hmm?
But where's the user?
Who is it?! The man with two right hands.
Too many people.
Damn it.
What's the matter, Polnareff?
What is this about?
If that was it,
if that stand belongs to who I think it does,
then...
That means I've finally found him.
Jotaro, the stand user who uses the mirrors, he's here.
The bastard who killed my sister.
My angelic sister.
The scum who heartlessly trampled
my sister's life, soul, and pride,
who destroyed the world's most pure heart,
finally,
finally we meet.
Are you absolutely sure it's him?
It's settled.
Mr. Joestar, I'll be traveling on my own from here on out.
Wha?!
With my sister's murderer finally within reach,
I'll be damned if I'm going
to wait for him to come after me.
I'm screwed if he gets the drop
on me, and that's just not my style.
I'll find him first and kill him.
But we don't even know what he looks like
or what his stand is.
He's got two right hands. That's enough for me.
And don't forget, he knows that I'm coming after him.
That should put him on the defensive
and give me the advantage.
See ya.
Tough talk for a man who's digging his own grave.
And that means?
Just as it sounds, my friend.
Are you implying that I'm gonna lose?
Yes.
Can't you see? The enemy attacked in order to isolate you.
He's exploiting your biggest weakness!
I won't let you go alone, Polnareff.
Listen up. I'm only gonna say it once.
This whole time, I never once gave a damn about Dio.
Hmm?
I told you in Hong Kong that I would go
along with you so that I could get my revenge.
Mr. Joestar and Jotaro already know this.
I've been alone from the beginning.
I've always been fighting alone!
You selfish fool!
Did you forget that you were brainwashed by Dio?
Are you so foolish you forgot
that he's the root of all of this?
You have no idea how it feels to have
your sister murdered, so shut the hell up!
I heard, the last time you met Dio,
you pissed yourself and ran away.
A coward like you would never
understand why I need to do this!
What did you say?
Don't touch me!
You just got lucky the day you beat me in Hong Kong.
Enough with this lecturing.
How dare you?
Oh, did that offend you?
But don't forget! I'm a lot angrier than you are right now
and with a hell of a lot better reason.
You can just keep being yourself
with your holier-than-thou attitude, Avdol!
Why, you...
Mr. Joestar!
That's enough. Just let him go.
Now that his mind is made up,
I doubt that anybody could stop him.
Yeah?
I've lost all respect for him, that's all.
My impression of him was completely wrong.
You are correct in that I did run in fear from him.
You see, I'm certain that foresight will let us win.
Rushing in without thinking will get us killed.
Oh?
Then I'll say this with certainty, too.
Your precious little divination will be wrong.
Time to get off.
I'm here to see a friend of mine.
Now get gone, girl. You're on your own.
Please make me your wife.
I'll do anything you want.
Hmm?
My life will belong to you.
Just say whatever you wish of me, my love.
Please, let me stay with you.
Let me be by your side forever.
Oh, come on now. Don't be stupid.
You're still only 16.
I'm old enough to marry.
I love you.
Listen. I'm just a no-good drifter, baby.
I live each day like it's my last,
and one day, the end will come for me.
Shh.
This is no life for a lady,
and you have royal blood.
We can't have a fairy-tale marriage,
no matter how much we might love each other.
Really? You've never said that before.
You love me?
Yeah. You're the only woman I've ever loved.
That's just it.
It's 'cause I love you that we can't marry.
I want you to be happy and have something better.
You understand, don't you?
I know, sweetheart.
This breaks my heart just as much as it breaks yours.
But I'll come back to see you
and hold you like this whenever I can.
That's enough to make me happy.
Okay.
Goodbye. Love ya, darling.
Hmm?
You know, it's bad manners to eavesdrop.
You think I spend too much time on romance, don't ya?
Well, when you've got girls like her
all over the world at your beck and call,
well, you've always got an ally, a partner.
They'd do anything for me,
even throw away their own lives.
You are aware of how I work, aren't you,
Mr. Centerfold?
By the way, about this Silver Chariot's Polnareff,
seems that he left the group
and is looking for you on his own.
What do you wanna do?
He totally fell for your plan, hook, line, and sinker.
Heh. Shall we go and kill him first?
Huh?
Hmm.
Let's go.
You know, between your Hanged Man and my Emperor,
I have no doubt that we can kill 'em all, no sweat,
this'll be a hell of a ride.
So he really didn't come back after all.
What? You've seen him?
Are you absolutely sure you
saw a man with two right hands?
Where?!
Huh?
Eh? I just saw him.
I don't understand it.
He was just right there.
What?
There. He was with that man in the street.
The gun is mightier than the sword.
Eh?
Mm, not bad, if I do say so myself.
Wait. What?
Who the hell are you, buddy?
Hmm.
Hol Horse,
that's what they call me.
I'm a stand user just like you
are, and my card is the Emperor.
Lord Dio paid me to get rid of you guys,
so say your prayers, and get ready for a beating.
Look here, cowboy, I don't give
a rat's ass who you say you are.
Hmm?
Where is the man with two right hands?
That was pretty rude.
You asked who I am, so I answered you.
Well, whatever.
I came here with that guy.
He's nearby.
What?
Where is he?!
There's really no point at all
in you asking that.
I, Hol Horse, will have the pleasure of snuffing you out.
Arrogant morons like you always talk trash,
and it always ends up the other way around.
Oh, was that funny?
Lord Dio had you pegged.
"Polnareff has the fatal habit
"of underestimating his opponents.
Beating him into a corpse won't be any trouble for you."
He was exactly right, so I couldn't help but laugh.
If I can't face him until I defeat you,
then that's just what I'll do, chump.
Bring it on.
Ever heard of military chess?
The tank is stronger than the soldier,
and the tanks are weak against the mines.
See, it's pretty much the basics of battle.
My Emperor is stronger than you,
so I thought I'd be a gentleman.
I'll let you know my stand's abilities
before we fight so we're square.
The gun is mightier than the sword.
Heh. Such a brilliant quote.
What are you trying to say, exactly?
That I have a stand that shoots,
and a sword simply can't beat that.
So, what? A peashooter?
Prepare to die!
You underestimated me!
And now, Polnareff, you're dead!
If I take off my armor...
I can knock down a bullet!
Wait. What the?!
That's impossible!
It bypassed my sword!
Oh, crap!
The bullet is also my stand,
and underestimating me just cost you your life.
Polnareff!
What? Avdol!
I've been worried about you,
and now look where you are!
Your ego will end you, Polnareff.
You're worried about me?
Damn you! You came here to lecture me again?
The enemy already knows everything about you!
You said you're a loner, but from now on,
you won't be able to win alone!
Hmph.
What bad timing for an outsider to interfere.
Polnareff, move! The bullet's coming back!
Go, Magician's Red!
I'll melt it down!
Damn that Avdol.
He went after Polnareff himself.
Where are you, Mr. Avdol,
Polnareff?
I have a terrible feeling.
Hey, there's a weird fight going on over there!
The puddle...
What the?!
Mr. Avdol!
Man, today must be my day.
My gun and Centerfold's mirror don't do
very well against Avdol's flames, you see.
We were sure he'd be our most formidable enemy.
Talk about luck.
With him gone, the game is in the bag!
Mr. Avdol!
H... He's just hurt. That's all.
It's just a minor wound. See?
He's going to start speaking.
He'll open his eyes in a moment.
Right, Mr. Avdol? Right?
You're going to wake up, right?
Mr. Avdol, you gotta wake up!
No, please! Mr. Avdol!
That seemed awfully easy.
It was too quick.
That's what he gets for lecturing people.
Look at him now.
W... What did you say, Polnareff?
Mr. Avdol was worried about you.
Who asked him for help? Because I never did.
He likes to meddle in other people's business,
but he's slow as hell, so they got him.
Guys like him just get in the way and screw up.
That's why I said I was going it alone.
You bastard.
He saved your life. How dare you?
Huh?
I am sick of it...
Having people up and die on me.
Polnareff.
I'm so sick of it.
You hear me?!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian