Polnareff, I shall savor killing you.
To avenge my dear son, I shall
rip out your insides while you watch.
But I can't let him find Hol Horse's
body, or else my chance will be lost.
She's not behind the counter, either.
It'll be even worse if the other three show up.
I need to kill them one by one, damn it.
Stay back. Go away.
Oh, madame, are you here?
I thought I heard some kind of
crash back here. Are you okay?
Hmm.
I'm coming in, madame.
Oh, no! What happened?
Oh, it's nothing. It's only a tiny
fall. Just bruised my hip a little bit.
You fell down? You can't be falling now.
And you burned your left hand?
You're being much, much too careless.
Oh, thank you, dear boy.
I'm fine.
No problem. I promise.
Get out. Get out. Get out!
Who said you could come in here, damn it?
I'll spare you my wrath for now,
but when the time is right, I'll kill you
just like I killed that bastard Hol Horse.
All it takes is just a tiny, little
wound, and then you're finished.
I'll turn you into my very own puppet of Justice.
Hmm?
Eh?
Oh? Cool.
Here. Your staff.
Madame, you seem to be sweating a lot.
It's nothing. Don't concern yourself with me. I'm fine.
Just go to your room, and get some rest.
Well, if you insist.
So I was wondering, are you running
the entire hotel all by yourself?
Don't you have some family around to help, like a son?
Huh? Sorry. Did you say something?
Uh, I was just saying I've gotten used to living alone.
Ah, I see.
Sounds lonely to me.
Just think, life with the son and daughter along.
Your grandkids could run around and play in the lobby.
They'd definitely cheer this place up.
It'd be a little noisy, but
that's what makes families great!
If you had a son, he'd probably be older than me, right?
Hey, what's the matter?
Did you have a son who moved away or something?
N-No. He passed away.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
That was terribly insensitive of me.
You're the one who killed him, you monster. I despise you.
I'll slaughter you. I'll slaughter you.
Please, sit down and rest.
I'll give you a nice back rub.
I know how it feels to be alone.
I lost my mom when I was still just a kid.
Isn't this great? Ah, the memories.
Tonight, you can think about me...
as if I'm your own beloved son.
Ask me for anything, okay?
You rotten little brat. I should
just kill you right now, you fool!
Wow, you're really tense.
I guess living alone has been pretty tough on you.
Hmm?
Huh? What's that guy doing there?
Hol Horse? How is he still alive?
That miscreant must have made his stand vanish
as soon as it shot the bullet into his mouth.
What? No! That face.
Hey. Look behind you, Polnareff.
Behind you, you fool!
No way! You're Hol Horse!
What are you doing?
Getting my vengeance!
I'm the mother of Centerfold, who
you mercilessly murdered in cold blood!
Chariot!
So you were a stand user all along!
Dare play a part in murdering my boy,
and I'll make sure you'll pay for it!
Mr. Joestar, I need help!
Hah.
It's too late. I'm afraid your trusty
friends will never hear your cry, my dear...
Because...
I've summoned my own allies.
Who the hell are you guys?
Wait. It's you.
B-But you're dead.
You were dead when we got here.
You're the one from India!
Holy shit. We've got zombies.
Behold the terrifying power of Justice, my stand.
One can only have one stand, but Justice, the fog
stand, can transform the dead into my personal army.
It can control hundreds of
corpses, even thousands of them.
Aren't you taking this grudge a bit too far?
To think that such a twisted stand user was after us.
I had no idea.
This whole godforsaken town's got it in for you.
And if you get any kind of wound,
she'll turn you into her personal puppet.
I need only to give you a little
scratch. It doesn't take much, you know.
Soon you'll be mine.
Then my stand, Justice, will take care of the rest.
You're dead!
Get him!
I'm outta here!
Polnareff!
Don't leave me here, please.
Oh, shut up.
Did you forget about shotting my friend Avdol?
Now, why in the hell should I save you?
You're on your own, pal.
You can't escape my righteous vengeance, Polnareff!
I'll yank your brains out through your nostrils!
I'll snap your spine in half and shatter your bones!
I'll crush your balls 'til they pop!
My vengeance comes now!
She's psychotic.
How can an old crone like her possibly run so fast?
Take this.
Damn it. That filthy coward ran into the back room.
After him, you fools!
Break down that door at once!
Merde. Just my luck.
This hallway leads down to the basement.
I'm so far away from them now,
Mr. Joestar and the others will never hear me.
I don't think those creepy zombies can beat me, but
if I get even a single scratch, I'll be in trouble.
She'll take control of me, just like Hol Horse.
D-Damn it. Isn't there any way outside?
And of course the windows have iron bars on them.
Damn it!
I'll hide in this room.
Crap, they broke down the door.
At this rate, I'm going to have to fight them.
I just have to keep these freaks
as far away from my skin as possible.
And now they're coming down the hallway.
They must be checking every room.
Damn it. They're getting closer and closer.
Wait a minute. Oh, come on.
Did I run into another bathroom?
Why am I always getting ambushed in bathrooms?
Damn it. The toilet is so dirty.
All right, just try it.
But the second you walk in,
my Chariot will chop up the
four of you in a single breath.
Huh?
What's going on?
Now it's totally quiet out there.
Creepy.
Damn zombies, that old hag,
what the hell are they doing?
Aren't they going to break down the door?
What's taking them so long?
Come on. Do something, damn it.
Hmm?
Ahh! They were looking through the keyhole the whole time!
What the hell?
Merde! This is not good.
The bastard stabbed me in the tongue!
Perfect! You've finally fallen under my
Justice's control, you shitty little brat!
And now, if you don't open that door
and come out on your own this second,
I'm going to slowly crush your
face and pull you through the keyhole!
Laugh now.
How pitiful, Polnareff. Very pitiful, indeed.
This isn't even close to the level of
torture you put my Centerfold through.
Because of your cowardice, my
precious son died in unimaginable agony.
Now, then, how about we have you clean the bathroom, eh?
Sound like a plan to you?
Lick the toilet until it sparkles like new.
Don't be shy.
Lick it 'til it's shiny, like this.
No, not that.
Anything but that.
Oh, god, help me!
Oh, you startled me.
You must learn to knock, my young man?
What can I do for you?
I'm here looking for Polnareff, and I did knock.
Maybe you didn't hear me, because
you were too busy doing something else.
I wonder what.
I'm looking for Polnareff, but I can't find him.
Seen him, grandma?
Damn. Now what?
Unlike Polnareff, this Jotaro is clever and knows
the right questions to ask to get what he wants.
I have to be careful.
Playing dumb will just make him
more suspicious. I need something else.
What a troublesome brat.
I know. I'll tell him where he can find
Polnareff, and as soon as he turns his back,
I'll turn him into a pincushion with these.
Then he'll be easy pickings for my Justice.
Yes, of course I can help you.
I know exactly where he is, Mr. Jotaro.
He and I were just having a lovely chat.
Oh?
This isn't good.
Jotaro has no idea a tiny scratch will spell his doom.
S-Stay back.
Tell Mr. Joestar and Kakyoin.
That hag is the enemy.
He's in the bathroom, but he's
been in there for quite some time.
Of course he's taking a shit.
Through this door here?
Yes, that's right. Once you're
through the door, make a left turn.
The bathroom is at the very end of the hall.
What an incompetent fool. You are a child after all.
Murdering Polnareff will delight my son's soul,
and spilling your blood, Jotaro, will
send lord Dio in Egypt into jubilation.
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
You have a second?
I got a question.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Did you trip, or are you just that clumsy?
You should be more careful.
That was too close.
Yeah. Could have been real bad.
It could have gone into your eye or
cut a huge chunk out of your scrawny neck.
You're pretty damn lucky.
Sorry to ask before you even get
up, but I have a few more questions.
First on the list, how did you know my name is Jotaro?
I never told you my name.
No one has, not since we got here.
Huh?
I find that strange.
Well? Come on, tell me.
You know, it's funny.
Maybe it's because I watched "Columbo" as a kid, but
it's little details like that that keep me up at night.
Oh, you're beginning to hurt this old lady's feelings.
It's the guest book.
You wrote your name in the guest book earlier.
Don't tell me you don't remember.
It's so dry. You wrote "Jotaro Kujo," yes.
Oh, then I guess you mean...
This guest book here?
Yes. That's it.
See? Your name is right here.
"Qtaro Kujo"?
"Jotaro" isn't written anywhere in this old thing.
Calling me Joestar when we
first met was your first mistake.
I've suspected you since.
I told the others not to use my name,
and yet, you know it, which could only mean...
Cut the crap, you old hag.
I already know you're one of the stand
users that's after us. The jig is up.
What's the matter now?
Aren't you going to show me your stand and fight?
You're looking right at it.
My stand, Justice, always prevails.
All it needs is one small scratch,
and then your life is as good as forfeit.
You've fallen into my trap, Jotaro.
Polnareff.
Jotaro, it's me, Hol Horse, remember?
Enyaba's stand is made entirely out of fog.
It'll split your wound right open and start flowing
through your body. That's how she controls you with it.
It'll even control corpses.
Shut your mouth, Hol Horse!
Ora!
Can you punch the fog with your fist or cut the fog
with your sword or shoot it with a gun? I don't think so.
Absolutely futile.
There's nothing you can do but accept your fate.
It's the biggest, toughest, fiercest stand there is.
Ours are puny by comparison. We're no match for it.
Nothing stands a chance against Justice.
Lovely. Keep it coming, Hol Horse.
Your fearful praise is music to my ears.
Now I'll control you, too, Jotaro.
Quick, run away, Jotaro.
She's gonna turn you into a puppet!
Good grief.
I don't need to run.
Before that old hag takes another breath,
I'll defeat that stand and send her packing.
Huh? What was that? I could have sworn you just made some
idiotic proclamation about defeating me, you little brat.
Before I take another breath, is that right?
Well, I'll do that...
I'll do that right...
What did you do to me?
Huh?
Jotaro's Star Platinum is sucking in her entire stand!
No, no, please stop.
I can't breathe.
And he's holding it in!
He's suffocating that bitch.
Huh. You see that?
Looks like her head is in a bit of a fog.
You ask me, that's Justice at its finest.
I'm so angry.
What do you mean, "what have I been
licking?" You ask such stupid questions.
I honestly don't see why that matters.
The toilet.
Eh? You were licking what, again?
I couldn't hear you very well.
Who cares what it was? Now I
need to disinfect my tongue, okay?
Give me the medicine already.
Hmm? I thought I just heard the word "toilet."
What are you giggling about?
Actually, I already knew about that, but I
couldn't resist picking on him about this first.
Hold on!
Jotaro already told you what happened, didn't he?!
You shitty old man!
You were just messing with me!
Forget the medicine.
All right, all right. I'm sorry, come
here, and I'll fix you up, Polnareff.
If you don't take care of that, it'll get infected.
Ahem.
Toilet.
You licked it real good.
Jotaro, Kakyoin, come on. Let's
just get the hell out of here.
Everyone, come outside.
Eh?
Huh?
Hmm?
What on earth?
We step outside of the hotel, and this place is a...
It's a graveyard.
She was using her stand's fog to make
this graveyard look like a town and a hotel.
So the whole time we were here,
we were talking to some corpses six feet under?
You wanna take her with us?
Are you serious?!
Sure am.
We need to know how many more stand users are out there,
what their powers are,
and wherever Dio's dug a hole for himself in Egypt,
as well as what his power is.
If we get the hag to tell us,
it might finally give us the edge that we need.
That's worth the risk of dragging her around.
I highly doubt she'll be willing
to share that information, though.
We just need to use my Hermit Purple.
I'll project everything she's thinking onto a TV screen.
Great idea!
We'll hop over to the next town and use a TV there.
Hmm?
Hol Horse, you slimeball!
That's our car!
Sorry, boys. I'm stickin' with Dio after all.
Catch you all later,
provided you all don't die before then, that is!
A little advice for y'all...
you better put a bullet between
that old lady's eyes real soon,
or else you'll find out just how terrifying
Dio really is, and you do not want that.
Hmm?
See ya!
Does anyone know what he's talking about? 'Cause I don't.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh.
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian