With Enyaba in tow and a new carriage to boot,
JoJo and crew arrived in the coastal town of Karachi,
Pakistan's industrial and financial
center located in the Indus river delta.
Oh.
Hey, a doner kebab joint.
Let's stop and get something to eat.
The doner kebab, it's been called
the hamburger of the middle east.
A slab of meat is placed on a spit,
its outer layer roasting as it turns.
Before long, the meat is cooked, sliced, and
served with any number of sides and condiments.
Excuse me, sir. I'd like five of those.
That'll be 1,000 yen.
1,000 yen?
In the middle east, Japanese and western
business practices are by no means universal.
Namely, prices change and are open to negotiation.
With no understanding of how to
haggle or how to value goods for sale,
first-time visitors can become
easy targets for exploitation,
but here, people don't see
such exploitation as a bad thing.
The swindled are deserving of the label fool, not victim.
Haggling takes guts and ingenuity.
Really?
The first step is the art of the bluff.
Make it clear you see through the trick.
Let him know you're no slouch.
Don't mock me now. That's far
too much for a handful of kebabs.
A hearty laugh always helps. Then...
How much would you buy 'em for?
The merchant will test the waters.
Make it 250 yen for five.
In return, you throw out a price so
low, you can't help but blush. And then...
He'll act as if you have no sense at all.
Catching on?
If I sold them for that cheap,
I'd be out on the streets, and my wife
and seven children would starve to death.
Then he'll gesture the old throat slash,
but you can't give up the fight just yet.
Then maybe I'll just buy them somewhere else.
Pretend that you're leaving.
Okay, friend, you win.
I very much like foreigners.
I'll sell you five for 700 yen.
He'll try to stop you.
Then make it 300.
Let the haggling begin!
600!
350!
550!
400!
450!
425!
I'll take 'em.
All right. I got them for less
than half his original price.
Take that. I made out like a bandit.
And just as you think you won.
I usually sell five for 150 yen.
Bye-bye. Thank you, sir.
Huh?
Holy crap!
Turn around! That old lady's awake.
I... I promise you
I haven't said anything to any of them, I swear.
Wh-why are you here?
What could you possibly want with me?
Did you think I would actually tell
them the secret of lord Dio's stand?
I am and shall always be his loyal servant.
Eh?
Gross.
What are they? Some kind of worms?
Why? I have done nothing wrong!
Why have you come here to kill me?!
Lord Dio places his trust in no one,
not even you, Enyaba.
That is why.
And it's my job to make sure that you never speak again.
As for the rest of you...
The only way you're leaving is in pieces.
Memere!
What?
You can call me Dan,
Dan of Steel.
My stand represents the one and only lovers card.
I will see to it that you all meet the
same fate as that pathetic witch Enyaba.
How could you?!
That old lady was one of your own, you son of a...
Memere!
Lies. Lies.
These are all lies.
This isn't happening. Lord Dio would never do this to me.
I am his loyal servant, loyal.
These things coming out of her body
they're definitely not some stand.
Don't you see it? They're actual tentacles.
I have dedicated everything to him.
Lord Dio would never do me such harm.
He'd never plant a flesh bud in me.
What did she say?
Lord Dio is my only reason for living.
We trust each other wholeheartedly.
Hold on!
See that?
The sun just disintegrated them!
The flesh bud, it's made out of Dio's own cells.
Precisely.
I must say you are quite the perceptive one.
Since you're so astute, I'll continue.
This is what a full-grown flesh bud looks like.
I want to kill her, not control her,
so I just grew it inside the old bag.
Enyaba, you may be the very one
who told lord Dio about the stands,
but you're a fool to think that a man with such complete
power would ever trust a feeble old woman like you.
Unfortunately, it's a point you failed to realize.
Old lady!
What's the true identity of Dio's stand?
Tell us!
You placed all your hope in Dio.
You trusted him with your life and your son's.
And now after all you've sacrificed, you
know he's not the man you thought he was.
You know I'm right.
We must defeat Dio, no matter the cost.
You have to tell us.
We need to know!
Tell us what we need to know about
Dio's stand before it's too late!
D-Dio...
My lord.
He believes in me, so I'll serve him even in death.
I won't betray him.
Oh, god!
How pathetic.
It's laughable how sad that old woman was.
But the very depth of her trust
in him should tell you something.
Lord Dio's evil charm is more
powerful than you can imagine.
The old woman may have had it out for us,
but she was misled and sure as
hell didn't deserve that death.
I'll see you join her.
Four against one, but we won't hold back.
Prepare yourself, Dan.
On your feet.
Hey, jackass,
stop trying to act cool, and get up and fight.
This is going down, whether you want it or not.
Go ahead.
But you can't touch me.
I'm Dan of Steel, and none of you can
take me down. You don't have what it takes.
Ora!
What the?
W-What happened, Mr. Joestar?
He flew back just like that guy.
You're an utter fool. I was about
to explain my powers when you hit me.
That impatience nearly killed your
grandfather. I suggest you listen next time.
Huh?
Listen. My job's not over. I have
other important business to attend to.
You really think I would show
my face here just to kill Enyaba?
You... you damn bastard. You told us that
your stand is the lovers. Isn't that right?
So tell us! What the hell does it do?!
What's the point in telling you now?
The battle's already begun, Mr. Joestar.
You're all simpletons.
You do know, no matter how hard you
look, you won't be able to see my stand.
Hey, half pint.
You want some cash? It's all yours if
you can hit me in the leg with that broom.
Whoa.
Oh.
Wha?
What? But why would he...
Now hit me!
The hell? Now what?
It... it hurts!
I don't get it! It's like I broke my leg!
You mean you still haven't figured
it out? That's so disappointing.
My stand can't be seen, because
it's rooted firmly inside you.
The moment Enyaba died, it entered you.
It got to your brain through your
ear, and that's how I'll get to you.
What?!
My stand and I are connected, just like yours.
If my stand gets hurt, so do
I, and the reverse is also true.
You're utterly helpless. If you so much as scratch me,
in that instant, my stand will react
to my pain by going berserk in your head
and inflicting the same agony on you.
Not only that, it will deliver
a pain several times greater.
Now I'll say it once more.
Alone or together, you won't be
able to lay a single finger on me.
Plus, the lovers has taken one of
lord Dio's flesh buds into your body.
It's growing in your brain as we speak.
Just like it did to Enyaba, it'll
devour you from the inside out.
I don't recall asking you to strike
me again, you stupid little brat!
Well, to be honest, my stand, the lovers,
isn't as strong as you might think it'd be.
It doesn't have the strength to
move even a single strand of hair,
making it the world's weakest stand.
However...
Power isn't necessary if all you
want to do is kill your opponent.
Do you understand, gentlemen?
Say something fortunate happens,
like I get into an accident, a
baseball hits me, or I just trip and fall,
how do you think that would affect you, Mr. Joestar?
I might get banged up some, but your
body would suffer far greater pain than mine.
What the? How?
How am I feeling your knuckles
cracking in my prosthetic hand?
You've got 10 minutes, old man.
Then your brain will be eaten through,
and you'll be a corpse like Enyaba.
Jotaro, calm down. Don't do anything rash.
Sorry, but no.
I'm gonna kill this damn tool so quickly,
he won't have enough time to feel pain.
Kill me before I feel it, huh?
Sounds interesting. Do it, then.
I wanna see what happens.
What are you waiting for, Jotaro?
Come on. Let's see it.
Just what were you planning to strike?
Tell me. My face? Or maybe my throat?
What? You mad?
Let's see what'll happen.
Don't back down on me now, man.
Why don't you try busting a hole through my chest?
Or how 'bout you give up on using your
stand, and crack my head open with a rock?
This one looks like a prime specimen.
It sure looks big enough for the job.
You do not want to underestimate me, pretty boy.
When I say I'm gonna do something, I do it.
Jotaro, don't do it!
We've already seen how effective his power
is. Are you trying to kill your own grandfather?
Uh, this is Jotaro we're talking about. He might be.
You dumb, good-for-nothing punk.
Oh?
Jotaro!
Don't you toy with me, you bastard.
After the geezer kicks the bucket, you're next.
Look out!
It'll be your brain that I send the Lovers in to kill.
Stop. What the hell do you think you're doing?
This is just insane.
My grandson is being beaten up to save me.
We're completely at this guy's mercy.
I can't do anything while it's in my brain.
I remember when that poison ring
was placed around my aorta long ago,
but think, Joseph. There's got to be something you can do.
H-hey!
Jotaro, keep him away from Mr. Joestar at all costs!
We're gonna try and get as far away from him as possible!
I see. So that's your plan?
Putting some distance between me and the old man
might make my stand's power vanish without a trace?
Sorry, but my stand's physical
weakness is made up for in other ways.
The Lovers may be physically weak, but its
range is farther than any stand in existence.
It doesn't matter how far they run. Their
lives are forfeit as long as it remains in a host.
What's up?
Hey, Jotaro, I'm talking to you.
It's impolite not to look at
people when they're speaking to you.
Look at me!
What's wrong?
You sound like you're starting to lose your cool.
What's your plan?
Follow me around 'til grandpa
Joseph keels over? Sounds like a blast.
Dan of Steel, was it?
I'll make you pay for this. Just a matter of when.
Well, if you're gonna stick around for a
while, I might as well help myself to your wallet.
Nothing but chump change, huh?
Though I didn't expect a guy
like you to be sporting a tag heuer.
I'll be borrowing this.
There!
An electronics store. Mr. Joestar, they have TVs.
Yeah, so? Why does that matter now?
Come on, Polnareff. Did you
really think we were running away?
I'm going to fight this blasted
stand that's inside my head.
Fight? Mon dieu, non.
We only have a few minutes, and we're
gonna need your help to pull this off.
Huh?
Hermit Purple!
That's it!
Oh, no!
I hoped he was bluffing.
How the hell did he get inside my brain so damn quickly?
Wow. If I hadn't seen it myself,
I wouldn't have believed it.
At least now we know for sure that it's in there.
But I still don't see how
we're going to destroy the thing.
By having our stands enter Mr. Joestar's
ear canal to find and destroy the monster.
Are you crazy?
Stands are simply materializations of energy.
We should be able to shrink them.
You don't know that.
Hey, try not to break anything while you're in there.
There's no time. We're going in now, Polnareff.
A-all right.
Hierophant Green!
Silver Chariot!
Smaller.
Get smaller.
We're going to be entering a blood vessel.
R-right.
A drainage ditch.
This could be fun.
I'd try to jump it, but if I trip and twist my ankle,
it could be real bad for old man Joestar.
Walking all the way to that bridge would be such a bother.
I've got an idea.
Lie down across this ditch,
and make yourself into a bridge.
I'll just walk on you to get across.
What now?
You don't want to be my bridge or something?
Shut up.
The hell do you keep yammerin' about?
I said make yourself into a bridge!
You good-for-nothing, arrogant prick!
What?! What's the matter?
Mr. Joestar.
M-my leg,
i-it's going numb.
Damn it, Jotaro.
What the hell are you doing?
Aw, don't look so upset, Jotaro.
Come on.
I don't have all day, you know.
Good.
You're a rather sturdy bridge, aren't you?
Boing, boing, boing.
Impressive.
Hold on.
Almost there.
Mr. Joestar, I think the stand is here.
Hiding around the thalamus makes the most sense.
That's the point where the nervous system begins.
Polnareff and I will enter a blood
vessel from inside your inner ear,
then swim through the veins toward the brainstem.
But to do that, we need to
tear the wall of the blood vessel.
Hey, hold on.
You're using your stands.
Can't you just slip through it without cutting me?
At this size, it's not possible.
The blood vessel's wall is too thick.
The slit will be microscopic, so
there'll be no hemorrhaging to worry about.
The only other issue is time.
Cutting through a blood vessel or nerve
right now will take several minutes at least.
Otherwise, the Lovers would have
already done its damage by now.
Though, in all probability, it may have already started.
Keeping our stands this tiny is really exhausting.
It's taking a ton of stand power
just to get where we can fight.
On y va!
Oh, my god!
I-I really don't feel so well.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian