What a nice bridge you make, Jotaro.
Oh, hang on. Jotaro, I have a very nasty itch.
Scratch it.
Just a little lower.
Even lower.
Ah, yeah, that's it.
But not too hard, mind you.
Huh?
Mr. Joestar?
Hey, what's the matter?
It honestly feels like someone's tickling my back.
I can't concentrate much longer like this.
Whah! Whah! Whah! Aah!
Calm down!
Enough already!
Just perfect. We've got quite the captive audience.
Mr. Joestar! Keep your voice down. People are staring.
Keep this up, and they'll think you've gone nuts.
You... you think I'm screaming for the hell of it?
Oh, no!
That poor man.
Why don't we give him some change?
W-Why are they throwing money?
I pity 'em.
Older relatives like that can be tough.
That is so true.
Kakyoin, go buy the TV. Let's get out of this crowd.
Right.
Is this your store?
Uh, yes, it is.
I'd like to buy that TV.
Unbelievable.
Kakyoin's Hierophant and Polnareff's Chariot made
themselves microscopic and infiltrated Joestar's body.
They intend to fight me. I can see them.
They're traveling through the bloodstream
and heading toward the brainstem,
right to my Lovers.
Quickly. We don't have long before the flesh
bud in Mr. Joestar's brain eats clean through.
Hurry, you two!
Allez hop!
All right.
Do it, Mr. Joestar.
Right. Hermit Purple!
Th-these are...
The flesh bud's tentacles.
Great. We're finally at the brainstem, but
the flesh bud's already taken over. Damn it!
It's him!
Just look at that fiend.
He's using those weird claws of his to knead
Mr. Joestar's brain cells into a gooey mash,
and I bet he's going to feed it to the flesh bud.
We have to destroy him and tear out all
the flesh bud's roots as fast as we can,
or else they'll completely devour his brain.
D'accord. I'll julienne him to ribbons!
You know, on second thought, I
think a finer cut should do the trick.
I'll turn you into a lump of pate!
No, you don't!
Now!
He did it!
No, not quite.
I gotta say, Kakyoin, that thing's pretty fast.
But, luckily for us, I've already figured him out.
If that's all the little beast
has, then he's no match for...
Polnareff...
Who are you talking to?
Wha... huh?
Polnareff, that's not me,
and that wasn't the real stand.
Look. It's melting away.
What the?!
I'm the Lovers.
Polnareff.
He disguised himself using the
brain cells, Mr. Joestar's brain cells.
Somehow, that thing was able to use
the collection of kneaded brain cells
to disguise himself as my Hierophant Green!
And since he can mold his cells at will, all you
destroyed was a decoy made of those brain cells.
You hit the nail on the head.
And you dummies completely fell for it.
Come on.
Pull your head out of your ass, would you?
You better shine those shoes right, Jotaro.
I'm in such a good mood, I can hardly stand it,
so I'm gonna need you to keep polishing these shoes
until they're shining as brightly as I feel right now.
Do you think you can handle
that, my little sycophant?
You can stop polishing when that magnificent
sun up in the sky makes these puppies sparkle.
Also, I want you to use your tongue to shine them.
Hey, you bastard,
what are you writing in there?
You're looking at your tab,
and you're gonna pay in full.
I wrote it down so I won't forget.
You're a scoundrel, Jotaro.
Heh.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It'll all be meaningless in the end.
Whoa! Kakyoin, look!
Check out the decoy's head that I just opened.
What?
What the hell's going on?
Somehow he's splitting in two.
Listen up. Here's some advice.
To win in life, one must thoroughly know oneself.
It's like Aesop's fables,
when the unassuming tortoise beats the hare.
The tortoise outruns the hare, because he knows
himself and his abilities better than anyone else.
Of course, the same applies to me.
I'm no fool. I know perfectly well I
don't possess the power or speed necessary
to mortally wound either of you one-on-one,
but remember this.
The spoils belong to those who admit their own weaknesses!
Emerald splash!
Did it work?
What? More decoys are forming out of the brain cells.
They're multiplying.
But a person can have only one stand,
which means only one of them is real.
That said, where's the real one?
Right here!
Emerald splash!
Well, that's not good.
Any closer, and I would have been killed.
The more decoys we hit, the more they multiply.
No, no. It's me. It's me.
It's me. It's me. It's me.
It's me. It's me. It's me. It's me.
They're all me. Can't you tell?
Polnareff, that's enough.
Withdraw your stand now.
I can't just watch you get hurt,
even if you are trying to save me.
No way in hell! I can't stand the thought
of giving up and watching you die like this.
Are you trying to die? Withdraw your stand.
Do as I say. It's over.
You can't quit, Mr. Joestar. We'll fight till the end.
Damn. They all look the same.
Which one is the real one,
and which one of them is the stand?
I can't tell them apart.
The world's weakest stand is...
The most, the most, the most, the most,
the most, the most, the most, the most,
the most, the most, the most, the
most, the most, the most, the most,
the most, the most, the most, the most,
the most powerful of all!
Hey, now, take a look at this, Jotaro.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I would wager an expensive gift like this
would make any girl fall head over heels.
Jotaro...
You see that space there in the glass?
Use your stand to sneak through and steal the bracelet.
Steal it.
What don't you understand, moron?
Get a move on, if you know what's good for you.
I mean, I don't mind breaking the
glass and taking the bracelet myself.
Then again, if I'm caught, I
could be beaten to a bloody pulp.
Old Joseph would surely die from the pain.
Hurry, would you?
Do it while the salesman's looking the other way.
Oh, no! This guy is shoplifting!
Son of a...
Do something! This guy's shoplifting!
Come on, salesman!
I'll go and get some help!
Please, sir, don't let him get away!
Sure thing.
Bastard.
All right, boys, where is this thief at?
Who's the culprit? Is it that guy there?
You talkin' about that Asian kid?
You know, back where I come from,
when someone steals somethin'. We chop their fingers off.
Hey, Jotaro...
You better not use your stand against civilians.
Punk!
Take this!
Despicable!
You dirty thief!
Now you get the hell out of our country,
and don't come back. Good for nothin' asshole.
You do that, and we'll allow you to
leave here with your fingers intact.
That was great. Nicely done, my friend.
Thanks to the commotion you caused,
I was able to get my hands on
something even better than that bracelet.
Jotaro, what the hell are you laughing about?
What's so damn funny?!
Nothing. I'm just a bit excited.
I was laughing, because your punishment has doubled,
and I've been waiting a while for this moment.
It's just about time for payback,
and I gotta say it's really got me tingling.
Why, you...
It would seem...
That we have something of a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry to say, but your old
man isn't long for this world.
That's the reality you're facing.
How sad. You don't know us very well, do you, friend?
And I see you don't know Kakyoin at all.
Come again?
It seems to me you're obsessed
with the notion of knowing oneself.
Yes, that makes sense.
I suppose I'm inclined to agree.
But before you continue pontificating,
think on this for a moment.
There's another adage, "know thy
enemy," that's nothing to scoff at.
Can't you see? My Hierophant has a certain ability.
It has the power to stretch out its feelers,
and I've been inspecting every single one of you.
Gah! How could I have not noticed something touching me?
So you're the stand.
Emerald splash!
Success!
Well, well, what do we have here?
Looks like Kakyoin got you pretty damn good.
So I'm wondering, will I get my payback once he's done?
He realized that he's out of his league,
and now he's trying to escape into the artery.
He's trying to escape from Mr. Joestar's brain.
Huh? Did you say he's leaving?
All right. That's great news, isn't it?
Mr. Joestar, hurry, the flesh bud.
Right.
Time for overdrive!
The flesh bud's vanishing.
Thank god it's gone.
Well, if you ask me, this whole experience has
done a lot to bring our group closer together.
You're incorrigible, Polnareff.
Hold on a minute. If that thing's
really trying to leave my brain...
Then wouldn't that imply that the stand is...
The bastard is returning to its user!
This is bad. Jotaro's has no way of knowing.
What's wrong?
Why are you backing away from me?
Aren't you going to tell me
more about my grandfather's death?
I'd really love to know.
Hey, wait a minute.
What's with the big hurry?
We weren't done talking yet.
No, it couldn't be.
You're not actually trying to run away, are you,
after all you've done?
Please Jotaro, sir, forgive me.
I admit it. You win.
I'll lie down and lick your boots.
I know I did a bad thing, and I wanna change.
You can pummel me as much as you'd like.
Hit me, kick me, but, please, don't
kill me. I'm begging you to spare my life.
Lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick...
Soon, very soon, the Lovers will return to me,
and this idiot Jotaro doesn't have a single clue.
Just you wait. This time, it'll enter your brain.
Kakyoin can't help you from hundreds of meters away.
I'll make you suffer pain so horrible,
you'll wish you were never born.
Heh. It's here.
It's here. It's here. It's here. It's here.
Now, enter his ear.
Ora!
I kinda figured you'd go and
try something shitty like this.
Don't you know my stand, Star Platinum,
possesses excellent eyesight and precise reflexes?
You're pathetic.
Didn't you check up on us at all, even a little bit?
No, no, no, no, no.
Believe me, I wasn't planning anything,
not against your stand's immense power.
Did you just say, "your stand"?
Only "your"?
Let me explain.
W-What I meant to say is that your awesome
and powerful stand is far superior to any other.
I knew it didn't stand a chance, so I had it come back.
Just look at what you've done.
You've already shattered my arm and leg to pieces.
I can't possibly fight anymore. I can't even move.
In that case...
I guess I'll take pity on you and
accept your arm and leg as payment
for all the low blows you took out against me,
but only if you swear that you'll never
show your ugly mug in front of us again.
I'll do whatever you say. I promise.
I'll head for some deserted island,
or I'll go to the ends of the
Earth and never return to bother you.
You'd better not be lying.
The next time I see that face,
it'll get a thousand punches.
I'm not lying. I would never, ever lie to you.
Get lost.
Let's play soccer over there.
Jotaro.
You're an utter fool.
Just take a look at that girl.
Well, I wanna play over here.
It might interest you to know that my stand,
the Lovers, just went into that girl's ear.
Now he's heading for her brain.
You better not move, Jotaro.
Here's what's about to happen.
I'm gonna stab you in the back with this knife
and make sure that you're never able to move again.
Attack me with your Star Platinum,
and this girl's pathetic life ends right here and now.
But you would never allow such an
innocent child to die, would you?
Oh, good grief. Go ahead, and stab me, then.
Huh?
Hey, now, did you not hear me? I just told you not to...
I told...
You not... to move.
What's the matter?
Didn't you say something about stabbing me?
Like this, right?
My... my body won't move!
W-Why?
What the...
What is this thing wrapped around me?
I see you didn't notice.
As your stand was trying to make its escape,
Kakyoin tied Hierophant's tentacle to its leg.
And seeing as those tentacles stretch all the
way back to your stand like a string to a kite,
you must have been so
self-absorbed, you didn't even notice.
Please, I'm begging you, forgive me!
Ask for forgiveness from Enyaba, the woman you killed.
But as for me, I never had the
slightest intention of forgiving you.
D-Dio paid me to cause this madness.
Y-you can have it all.
Good grief. I know this is blatantly
obvious, but you really are a piece of work.
What you owe me
can never be paid back with money!
Ora!
Your receipt.
You can keep the freaking change.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian