Ah, my, that looks quite good on you.
In all my years, I've never received
such a strange request for clothing,
but the pleasure was mine, sir.
Here. I gotta go.
Keep the change.
See ya.
Uh, thank you, sir.
Let go! Let go of me!
And don't you dare touch me there, you jerk!
Hey, don't say it like that.
No! I don't wanna! I wanna keep going with you guys! Eh?
Listen, little miss.
We're not vacationing here.
My daughter, Jotaro's mother,
is in grave danger at the moment.
We're on this journey to save my
daughter's life, not to put yours at risk.
Forget this running-away business, and start heading home.
I'm sure your parents are worried
sick wondering where you are.
There.
Fine. I suppose so.
I'll make you look good this time, grandpa.
Huh?
Hmm? What's the matter?
Nothing.
See ya! Life is just a bunch of goodbyes anyway.
I do sort of wish I could have
seen him once more before I had to go.
Huh?
Goodbye, JoJo!
You better save your mom! We're all counting on you!
I'll be cheering you on!
Hmph.
Pakistan is a young country, established
in 1947 following its separation from India.
But when Japan was still a hunter-gatherer culture,
Pakistan was the seat of a highly-developed civilization.
Here in Pakistan, the people carry on the
5,000-year history of the Indian subcontinent.
I gotta say, Jotaro,
I'm impressed you got a Japanese
school uniform made here in Pakistan.
The fit is perfect, too.
It's 100% wool.
Hey, Polnareff, are you okay driving right now?
The fog in this area is getting quite thick.
These aren't exactly the safest conditions.
It's one hell of a drop off the right
side, and there's no guardrail anywhere.
Hmm. The fog looks even thicker up ahead.
It's not even 3:00 yet, but we should head in.
Let's find a place to stay in that town for the night.
Do you think they have nice hotels?
A nice hotel, huh?
That's right, and it'd better have a decent bathroom.
I... I just couldn't get used to the really strange
toilets they have all over India and the middle east.
What the hell? Was that a dead dog?
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Hmm?
Oh. Uh, it was nothing.
Hey, this is a nice little town, don't you think?
There must be at least a few
thousand people living here.
Let's ask about a hotel at that restaurant over there.
But there's a weird quiet about this place.
No matter where we've gone, every
other place has been rowdy and congested.
It's probably because of the fog.
Listen up, guys.
In Pakistan and the rest of the Islamic
world, this is how you greet people.
First, you smile and say...
"As-salaam alaikum."
Eh...
Uh, no harm intended.
No need to close up shop just for us, sir.
We just wanted to ask a question.
Are there any hotels here in town?
Uh...
Anybody home?
I do not know.
Huh?
Good day.
Hey, wait a minute!
What do you mean, you don't know?
Huh?
Huh? What's with that guy? That can't be right.
I must have imagined it.
I'm sure he couldn't understand you,
because your pronunciation's so bad.
Let's just go ask that guy over there.
Excuse me. Sorry, but we're looking for a hotel around
here, preferably a hotel with nice, clean bathrooms.
Do you know any that...
Whoa! Hey, you, what's wrong?!
What the hell?!
He's dead!
With that look of fear on his face.
Wh-what's going on?
Why is he lying dead in the road?
What could have killed him, a heart attack?
A stroke?
It's possible, but look.
What we've got here is no ordinary heart failure.
Huh?
It's a gun.
Wait a minute. This guy's holding a gun!
You just noticed?
Check it out. It's still smoking.
He must have just fired it, maybe two to five minutes ago.
Either way, he must have died
right before we arrived in town.
Do you think he shot himself?
No, I doubt it. His body doesn't seem to have
any visible wounds, and there's no blood anywhere.
Then how'd this guy die? This isn't natural. Look at him!
His face is all twisted, like
he was screaming in utter terror!
Astounding.
You gotta wonder who or what he shot at with that gun.
What exactly happened?
Didn't anyone here see anything?
No one's stopped to help.
Excuse me! Ma'am, wait!
Someone has died here! Please call the police!
Pardon me, young man.
My boils seem to be festering today.
My apologies. You had a question.
What was it that you needed?
I asked if you could please call the police, ma'am.
The police?
What would I do that for?
Look!
That man's dead.
Hmm.
Someone is dead, you say? How terribly unfortunate.
I'm not sure if there is anything I can do about that.
I already asked you to call the police twice.
Of course. Call the police. I think you did say that.
Well, good day, sir.
My boils are infected.
They are so itchy, so terribly itchy.
What is with the people in this town?
There's a man lying dead in the street,
and nobody seems even the slightest bit concerned.
Didn't they hear the gunshot? Nobody's
doing anything. It's like they don't even care.
These people are more oblivious than
the most jaded New Yorker or Tokyoite.
That dog...
This blasted fog just keeps getting thicker and thicker.
It's almost as if the fog is swallowing the town whole.
This is really creepy.
Call me crazy, but doesn't
that part there look like a skull?
What do you want to do?
You don't think it could be the
work of another stand user, do you?
Eh, probably not. There's no motive.
Why would someone who's after us kill a man who
has nothing to do with us before we even got here?
There's no reason for a stand user to kill him.
Who knows?
The way he died is obviously unnatural.
Let's examine the body before the police come.
Just try not to touch it.
Right.
This might be something.
It appears he was traveling, too, just like us.
He has bus and train tickets in his pocket.
And he looks like he might be Indian.
He's carrying Indian money on him.
I'm guessing he's not from this town.
Oh?
Look at this wound.
He's got a gaping hole here, right in his upper chest.
This must be what killed him.
Hang on. Why isn't there any blood coming out?
With a fatal chest wound this big,
there should be blood gushing everywhere.
Unless, of course...
This is no ordinary murder.
Looks like things are about to get messy.
We've gotta get to the bottom of this.
It's time to search him.
Take off his clothes.
What happened to his body?!
There are tons of holes all over this guy!
He's like that cartoon cheese you see on "Tom and Jerry"!
And there's not a drop of
blood anywhere near those wounds.
How on earth was this man killed?
What does all of this mean?
Be careful.
If there wasn't a stand user here
before, you can bet there's one here now.
Everyone, get in the car! We're leaving this town now!
What the...
Hmm?
Impossible!
This isn't the car!
Oh, no!
Hermit Purple!
Hey, old man...
What in the hell are you doing?
You're crazy.
Huh? Oh, no!
What do you mean, what am I doing?
The car was right here just minute ago.
Huh? What are you talking about? We
just parked the car over there and walked.
What?!
But just now, I could have sworn that...
Well, hello, good sirs. I see you are travelers.
I'm afraid, with this fog, it's
dangerous to leave the town now.
There are many cliffs, you know.
I run my own bed-and-breakfast not far from here.
If you'd like, why not stay there for the
night? There's plenty of room for everyone.
I'll even give you a healthy discount.
Finally. We've actually met a normal person for once.
We have to assume a stand user
is hiding somewhere in this town.
With this fog, there's no telling what our enemy could do.
They could be next to us, and we wouldn't know.
We absolutely cannot let our guard down tonight.
You know, guys, I realize no one's attacked
us quite yet, but, damn, this town is creepy.
Come on. This way, master Joestar.
That building over there is my bed-and-breakfast.
Follow me, and I'll show you to your rooms.
Try not to fall behind.
I know it doesn't look like much, but it has history.
About 20 years ago, one of the 007 movies was filmed here,
and when John Lennon of the Beatles visited the country,
he spent the entire time in our little hotel.
What?! Seriously?!
Oh, no, I was just pulling your leg, young man.
Wha...
Still, it is quite a lovely hotel.
I've put my heart and soul into it.
We don't have any other guests at the
moment, so you can pick the dinner menu.
Would you prefer meat? If not,
we have fresh fish available.
Wait a second, grandma.
Before, you called me "Joestar," didn't you?
How did you know my name?
Hmm?
Uh...
Come, now.
That delightful young man next to you said, "Mr.Joestar,"
earlier. I may be old, but my ears still work.
You mean me?
I think I said it, but I'm not sure.
Ah, you did, sir.
When you've been working in this
business for as many years as I have,
you really learn to memorize people's names quickly.
So I'm sure of it.
By the way, ma'am, I just noticed the
bandages. What happened to your hand?
Uh, oh, this? A minor burn, nothing more.
I suppose it's just my old age, but I
accidentally spilled boiling water on it.
Oh, don't be silly, madame. You hardly look
a day over 40, and that's god's honest truth.
What do say you and I get dinner alone?
Oh, you naughty boy. Don't tease an old woman like that.
You damn babbling, pathetic fool.
It is you I despise most, Polnareff.
I'll make you suffer a pain one thousand
times worse than what my son endured.
Then I'll cut off your dick and
rip out your guts to finish you off.
Oh, this doesn't look bad at all.
Here, Kakyoin.
Right.
My autograph's worth as much as Lennon's.
Here.
I'm Paul-nareff, after all.
Make sure you take care of it.
Of course.
I'll make sure it's preserved for all time.
To commemorate the day I murder you.
It's done.
Well, then, allow me to show you to your rooms, gentlemen.
Man, talk about a weird town.
Now, time to hit the loo.
I don't think it's functional.
Oh. If that's the case, I won't be able to
use Hermit Purple to get info on the enemy.
Hey, Mr. Joestar.
What's the matter?
Looks like my room doesn't have a bathroom.
Is there one in here I can use?
Perhaps the bathroom here is communal.
Ah. Of course.
He's so carefree. Good grief.
A stand user could attack at
any moment. He should be on guard.
So the Joestar party is on the third floor?
Maybe me and my six-shooter ought to pay them a visit.
Ah, Hol Horse. So you've come.
That's right. I finally managed to track
those sorry bastards as far as this creepy town,
but finding you is a surprise, Enyaba.
I didn't think you'd come all the way out here yourself.
What's the matter, Enyaba?
Did I say something wrong?
Forgive me. I'm just happy, Hol
Horse. It means so much that you're here.
Thank you for coming to see this lonely old woman.
It is so wonderful to finally see you.
Huh?
Tell me something.
You and my son were friends, were you not, Hol Horse?
Were we friends?
Uh, well, I...
Yes, we were as thick as thieves, ma'am.
So you were close?
Yeah, we were practically brothers.
He was a dear friend and an excellent partner.
What's this all about? You aren't
acting like yourself at all, Enyaba.
His death must weigh heavily on you.
Will you avenge him? Is that why you're here?
Yes! That's exactly it!
I'm gonna make sure those bastards
pay for killing my best friend.
That's exactly what I want to hear!
Because now I can kill you, too, you filthy traitor!
Enyaba, what the hell are you doing?!
Idiot. Isn't it obvious?
You abandoned him to save yourself.
I swore I would kill you the moment I saw
you again. You deserve the same as the Joestars.
How dare you call yourself his best friend? Cretin! Judas!
Wait! You got it all wrong.
By the time I got there, Centerfold
was already a goner, honest.
You wretch.
You're as unforgivable as that bastard, Polnareff.
I'll have you die at the hands of my stand, Justice.
Wait. Have mercy!
Only a few have seen the terrifying power of my stand,
and now you will join all of them in death, Hol Horse.
Huh? What the hell is happening to the blood in my arm?!
It's like it's all just evaporating.
It made such a fine wound, did it not?
That's right. This is Justice, a stand that's made of fog.
Any wound my stand happens to graze
becomes a gaping hole, and then...
Justice wants to dance, Hol Horse.
My stand's fog has entered your arm, like a string, and
now you're a helpless puppet I can do with as I please.
You will die by your own hand, Hol Horse!
Damn it.
You shouldn't get so damn cocky.
Emperor!
Die, you crazy old hag!
Justice prevails.
Huh?
What the hell was that noise?
Sounded like an giant explosion.
It came from the room at the back of the downstairs lobby.
Is something wrong, Polnareff?
Huh?
We heard something strange and came to investigate.
Same here. I was about to check downstairs.
I'll look in the lobby first.
Call me if you find anything, okay?
Hmm.
Your time's finally come, Polnareff.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian