My son, my precious boy has been murdered!
I can sense the misfortune that has befallen my son.
The bond between mother and son has spoken!
My precious, beautiful boy, you died
covered with wounds like this? Those bastards.
I can feel it. I suffer the same pain you felt!
You were utterly magnificent as you
fought for lord Dio, my dear Centerfold.
How? How did they do it?
To kill such a noble and pure soul like you,
they must have done something underhanded!
Damn them!
The bastards!
I will make sure they pay a
terrifying price with the empress card!
They'll regret the day they were born!
Move!
I won't stand idle.
This is the time for action, a time for
vengeance with the stand that brings a slow death!
Oh, the anguish, the pain!
I shall kill them all!
JoJo and crew head to the sacred city, Varanasi.
Listen up.
I don't usually get on a soapbox like this,
but stupid people are just that.
You could repeat something a million
times over, and they still won't listen.
You know the type, don't you?
There's just no helping the poor souls.
But you know, uh... hold on. I never got your name, did I?
Nena.
Nena! That's a great name.
Daughter of a wealthy family in the sacred
city Varanasi that we're passing through, right?
You're good-looking, and you've got
an equally good head on your shoulders.
I have an eye for people...
which leads me to my point.
Hol Horse is a horrible, lying bastard, understand?
He was manipulating you.
Think how your parents would feel.
You hear me?
You can't end up like this, okay? I
know it's easy when you're in love,
but you can't afford to see
the world with such a narrow view.
Take a step back, and look at the whole picture.
Hey.
Eh?
We're almost there...
The city of Varanasi.
The sacred river, the Ganges...
A place for holy men, the old and the sick,
where domestic animals and food for human consumption
lie alongside human waste and corpses for cremation.
The river embraces all.
From birth unto death, its holy
waters form a microcosm of life.
It is said that visitors of the sacred city of
Varanasi remain transfixed, never wanting to leave.
Perhaps the landscape that is this sacred land
is a mirror unto the soul.
Hmm?
Man...
This thing isn't getting any better.
What's wrong, old man?
You don't look well.
Uh-uh.
Looks like my bug bite just got a lot worse.
This thing must be infected.
It's definitely swollen.
It would be best to have a doctor
look at it before it gets worse.
Hey, doesn't that sort of look like a person's face?
Stop kidding around, Polnareff. That's creepy.
Sorry about that.
Want me to go to the hospital with you?
No! Stop treating me like an old man.
Hmm.
I'll just lance this.
Huh? What did you say?
It's definitely infected now.
It'll get worse if we don't drain the fluid.
Hey, hey, hey. Can't we just put medicine
and a bandage on it and call it a day?
Don't worry, my friend.
We'll numb the area so it won't hurt.
No problem. No problem at all.
Come, now. Lie down.
Sir, I studied medicine in England.
I can do appendectomies, too.
Uh-oh. It's a little rusty.
Eh?
Well, that's no problem.
All right.
Let's slice it open.
Eh, come on. I don't wanna watch
it being cut open. Have a heart.
It'll be fine.
Hey, are you done yet?
Can I open my eyes now?
Huh?
What the...
Hey, doctor...
Trying to cut me off?
That's a pretty stupid move, you old fart.
Chu-mi-min!
What the... what the hell is this?!
I am the Empress, as in the empress card, old
man Joseph, and now, I'm gonna bloody you up good!
When did you get on me, damn it?!
No way! This thing's got teeth?!
Damn thing's strong.
No! It grabbed the scalpel!
Oh, no!
Thank goodness that was my artificial hand.
Bastard! Think you can just cut me?
I'm a part of your body now, old man Joseph.
You can't get away from me,
honey, no matter how hard you try.
You know, I bet I can tell you what's
going through that thick skull of yours.
You're probably thinking something
like, "Only a stand can beat another stand.
"My stand, Hermit Purple, has the
power of clairvoyance and remote viewing,
but how am I supposed to fight
something like this with those powers?"
"How can I destroy something
that's growing out of my own arm?"
So, honey, was that spot on?
Where's the user?!
How in the hell could you have infected me?!
You moron, I won't tell.
Disgusting freak.
Running off to your friends?
We'll see how that goes, won't we?
Doctor, your next patient is waiting for you.
Doctor!
Uh, hey, don't get the wrong idea. I didn't...
I killed him!
I'm Joseph Joestar, an American.
I'm staying at hotel Clarks.
What?
And by the way, girlie,
I have a thing for hot young nurses like
yourself. I think I should give you an exam.
What?!
M-Murderer!
Wait! It's not true!
Oh, no.
Now you can't go back to the hotel.
You're all alone now, honey.
I can kill you without anyone interfering.
You little...
you're pissing me off!
I'll crush you to tiny bits!
What?
Hey, this is your own arm.
Take care of it, you shitty old man.
It grew arms.
How much more could it grow?
Eh?
What the hell?
Let go of it! I mean it, freak, now!
Not a chance.
Hey, officer, the murderer's over here!
He's right here!
It's been a while since it's come to this.
Hey, what are you doing?
Overdrive!
Eh?
Moron!
It's your arm, remember?
You think your hamon would work against your own body?
Hands up! Don't move!
Then how about Hermit Purple?!
Y-You're crushing me.
I can use it this way, too, so how does it feel, ugly?
I told you not to move. Now freeze!
Stop, criminal!
Damn it.
What are you doing? I can't see.
Shit. Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
Do you get what I'm telling you, Nena?
Real men don't have to talk a big
game like your six-shooting boyfriend.
That's how you figure out who's a
liar and who's the genuine article.
Damn cops have run me in the wrong direction.
I'm nowhere near the hotel now.
If I had known this would happen, I
would have taken Polnareff with me.
Instead of a petty guy like Hol Horse,
why not be with me? Am I not your type?
Hmm.
Come on.
I don't dwell on the past like some.
I don't care who you were dating before, even Hol Horse.
What's important is the future.
We just need to understand each other, right?
Oh, look over there, Polnareff.
Hmm.
That place is a hotel run by a
nice Japanese woman named Kumiko.
Huh?
She manages it with her Indian husband.
We can probably get a cheap room.
Oh, really? Huh.
Tell me more about this hotel.
Huh?
Wha...
What the hell are you doing?!
Huh?
Chu-mi-min!
I'm eating, Joestar.
A growing girl needs her food.
You stole those at the market, you quick little bastard.
Ahh!
Eh? Why, you...
Chu-mi-min.
Look how big I've gotten.
It's tough having another mouth to feed, isn't it, daddy?
Chu-mi-min.
You disgusting little cow!
I'll show you that nobody has the experience or
the smarts to take down the great Joseph Joestar.
You don't stand a chance, you bastard.
Now how the hell am I gonna do that? Damn it.
Here goes nothing.
Hermit Purple!
Oh, daddy dearest, you've done
a wonderful job of raising me.
But you know, you shouldn't tie your children
down, or they won't grow. It only smothers them.
You should raise them to be
free. If not, they might rebel.
Oh, no!
It's no use.
If I had a camera, I could use Hermit Purple
to get a picture of the stand user's location.
Damn it all!
Come on, think, Joseph. Think.
At this rate, it won't just be my arm.
She'll take over my whole body.
Huh?
I've already grown enough that I
could easily end your pathetic life.
See? My hand can reach your throat now, old man.
I just have to bust your carotid artery, and
you'll crumple over like a sack of potatoes.
Oh, no!
What's he doing?
Bastard!
He's lost his mind.
Look at that.
Some very strange man has a strange growth on his arm.
Damn it!
Where the hell's the stand user?
I have to tell you something.
Huh?
I need a reliable man, a good
man like you to take care of me,
and I... I love you, Polnareff.
Such a kindhearted, trustworthy man you are.
Uh, really? But it's all so sudden.
This is happening. I have
finally found one. Eeh! Lucky. Eeh!
Huh?
Hey, Joseph Joestar,
you idiot, you keep getting farther
and farther from Jotaro and the others.
Do you really think I'm just running around town randomly?
I'm not doing this just to wear myself out, you know.
Wha?
I'm running so I can kill you!
This is the end of the line!
See that?
You're going in! Have a nice soak!
Hah!
You senile, old fool!
A nail?
Yeah, I picked it up earlier when you were
rolling around on the ground like an idiot.
Now I can shove it right in your carotid,
and you'll bleed out like a stuck pig.
Did you actually believe I'd suffocate
if you stuck me in here, you fool?
Die!
I may be made of your flesh, but I'm nothing like you.
Forget the rules already, chump?
Only a stand can hope to defeat another stand.
Oh, yeah, didn't you say you were gonna
show me all that fighting experience you have?
Was I supposed to be impressed? Some plan.
You're just a helpless geezer who's
gotten too old to help anyone, even himself.
My prosthetic hand, it was on the
verge of breaking from her attack earlier,
and now I can't get any strength into it.
Just one more push.
Your life as an invalid is about
to come to an end. Chu-mi-min.
There's not a single way you can defeat me.
You might as well surrender.
Eh?
What the hell is this?
Huh?
I might as well what now?
I'm sorry. My hearing isn't exactly what it once was.
Run that by me one more time, will you?
It's coal tar!
That was your plan all along.
It wasn't to suffocate me.
You were trying to keep me from moving!
But how?
How did you know there was coal tar in there?
With my stand's power. Hermit Purple told me everything.
H-Hey, everyone, look.
What is this?
The ashes that foreigner spilled
everywhere when he wrecked the place.
They've formed into a perfect map of the city.
You drew a map with Hermit Purple?
That's how you found the tar, a map out of incense ashes?
Yeah.
Now I think even a glorified pimple like you
should see the difference in our fighting experience.
When your opponent starts boasting, he's already lost.
That, shrew, is a line from my wilder days.
Like a fine wine, I guess I just get better with age.
And now...
A stand will defeat another stand.
Next you'll say, "please stop it. I beg you."
Please, just stop it. I beg you!
This will hurt me as much as it hurts you,
but children can't depend on their parents forever.
Once you've grown up, you've
gotta learn to live on your own!
Now then...
I wonder where that thing's stand user is hiding.
Uh, so what do you say, Nena, darling?
Shall we seal our new love with a sweet kiss?
What the hell is this?! It's nasty! Ugh!
What's wrong, Nena?
So she was the empress's stand user all along.
Huh?
She was an ugly old troll.
She attached her stand to me as a tumor with a human face
and camouflaged herself as a beautiful woman.
You were careless.
She played you like a damn fiddle, Polnareff.
And here I thought we'd finally
be able to sleep in a bed for once.
If the old man hadn't screwed up, we
wouldn't be out here hiding from the cops.
I took care of things.
We can take this car.
Polnareff, you do the driving.
What?
Don't tell me you're still in shock.
I was the one who was attacked by the stand.
Sure, but I think I'd rather have gone through that.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian