Is anyone else here getting nervous?
Try to stay calm.
Times like these require us to keep
our heads on straight and be prepared.
Oh. Putting this stuff on with only one
hand is a lot harder than I thought it'd be.
All right, before we leave, has
anyone here ever scuba dived before?
Not me.
No.
No, I haven't.
You have to teach us how to use this equipment right now.
That thing is going to attack us in any second.
Try and calm yourself, Avdol.
You must never panic, no matter what.
That is the most important rule when scuba diving.
When you're traveling underwater, for
every ten meters you go below the surface,
the corresponding pressure increases along with you.
The surface pressure starts at one atmosphere,
and since we're 40 meters below the surface,
we'll endure five atmospheres of pressure.
If we surface too quickly,
the pressure'll cause our
lungs and blood vessels to burst.
We have to rise slowly so our bodies can adjust.
Since we're nearing the Egyptian coast,
it's best to ascend along the seafloor.
Okay, I'm letting the water in.
Now pay very close attention.
What you're looking at is a regulator.
The valve inside only allows air
in from the tank when you inhale.
The air you breathe out exits
through the piece on the left.
Wait a second. What about spit?
What happens if I need to drool or
have to hock a loogie or something?
Stuff like that just comes out of the opening here.
By the way, this should go without
saying, but we can't talk underwater.
Instead, we'll use hand signals.
Let's keep things simple and only use two.
When things are going smoothly,
we'll use this to say, "okay."
But when they aren't, use this.
Mr. Joestar, couldn't we just use
our stands to communicate underwater?
Huh? Oh, yeah. I didn't think about that.
Aww, man. And I was just about to say
that I know a really good hand signal.
He says, "your underwear is showing."
Yeah, nice.
We could be attacked and killed at any time!
Stop fooling around, and let's go!
This room is about to be filled to the brim with water.
Put on your masks and regulators
while you still have time.
P-Polnareff!
But when did it...
That's it.
The stand had already integrated with the regulator.
That bastard.
It's gonna rip him apart from the inside.
We've gotta drain the room while we still can.
It's too late.
It must have been lying in wait for just this moment.
Ora!
Damn it.
It's already burrowing down his throat.
We can't just stand here and watch him like this.
What should we do?
Hierophant Green!
Hermit Purple!
What are you doin...
I was able to grab it before it could damage his organts.
Me, too.
Let's pull it out before it transforms.
Success.
All right, keep it just like that.
Look! It's transforming into something else.
You gotta be kidding me. It turned into a spear gun.
Emerald splash!
Silver Chariot!
Let's get moving.
It's already reloading.
It doesn't quit.
H-Hurry.
Move it, old man.
Yeah, I'm coming.
That was too close for comfort.
It's too soon for us to relax,
especially since that bastard knows
exactly how to hit us where it hurts most.
Polnareff, are you all right?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
You guys saved my life back there.
Merci beaucoup.
Wow, just look at how beautiful it is down here.
This would've been a spectacular
place to visit on vacation.
This isn't time to plan your next getaway.
We have to surface before we run out of oxygen.
Think we're safe?
I believe so.
The High Priestess can transform into metals and glass,
but it can't take the form of bubbles
or fish, so I doubt it'll come after us.
Just keep your eyes peeled.
If it pursues us, it'll probably
transform into a screw on our gear to do it.
Be careful of moving pebbles and stones, too.
Hmm?
Look up there!
I think it's a sea tunnel.
We're at seven meters.
We've finally reached the Egyptian shore.
We can swim along these rocks to get to the surface.
What?
Is that the...
Yes, it's definitely the stand.
It merged with the seafloor, and it's gargantuan!
Damn! There's no way we can fight this pull.
This is impossible!
How is it so gigantic?
What the hell?!
It was so small earlier.
What's this stand's power?
Merde, I'm so confused!
You boys are so slow on the uptake.
Didn't it ever cross your minds
that if the rocks are mineral,
it would mean the seabed is mostly mineral as well?
Yes, of course.
That's why the stand has suddenly gotten stronger.
It's user must be nearby, and I'd
wager she's closer than we think.
You guessed it, and to be more precise,
I'm seven meters above you on the shore.
But since you're about to be
ground to bits by my High Priestess,
you'll never have the chance to see my face.
So long.
It's so dark in here.
I can't tell what part of the stand we're in.
Seems like we're still inside its mouth,
but luckily we weren't sucked down its gullet.
Yoo-hoo, Jotaro.
Believe it or not, you're actually my type,
so this is going to be as painful for me as for you,
but despite my feelings, I still have
to make the High Priestess digest you.
Huh?
How sad.
If only our encounter had been
under different circumstances.
But if I kill you,
lord Dio will no doubt shower me with praise,
so don't hate me.
Good grief. Do I have to?
Would you just say it?
Come on. Hurry up, and get on with it.
Say what?
Huh?
Ah, I see.
It's a shame things turned out this way.
I would have liked to have
seen your face, if only this once.
You might have been my type, too,
and if you were, well, I just might have fallen for you.
Oh, hey, you know what, guys?
I bet she's a beauty.
I can tell from that gorgeous voice of hers.
She comes across as an elegant woman.
My fortuneteller's instinct senses it.
Well, if you ask me, she sounds just like Audrey Hepburn.
Man, if I were only 30 years younger.
You bastards didn't mean a single word of that!
I'll kill you all!
Holy shit!
Everyone, look!
What is that?
It looks like a tongue, the stand's tongue to be exact.
Here it comes!
Jotaro!
No! Jotaro's going to land in...
He... he landed right on the molars.
Jotaro, get out of there now!
You're about to be crushed!
Ora!
Ooh!
You want to pit your strength against mine, do you?
Damn, what ridiculous power.
Oh, give up, Jotaro.
Those teeth are as hard as diamonds.
You'll never be able to break them.
It's time for you to meet your end.
We have to save Jotaro!
Stay out of my way!
That damn tongue again!
Magician's Red!
We're out of time!
We have to free him!
Jotaro!
J-Jotaro.
No. Those giant teeth pulverized him.
Jo..Jotaro.
We didn't make it in time.
Hmm? Hold on a sec.
I think I can hear something.
It's definitely coming from rather far away.
Listen again. I think it's getting closer.
Wait. That voice belongs to...
The teeth. It's coming from inside the teeth!
Huh?
Everyone, get down, and brace yourselves.
Those teeth were hard as diamonds,
but he managed to punch his way out.
Oh, my god!
And would you look at that? He's
breaking the other teeth while he's at it.
That showoff.
His stand's immense power never ceases to amaze me.
Come on. I'm getting us out of this hellhole.
Ora!
Ah, good grief.
Well, you were right about those teeth
being sturdy, but they weren't sturdy enough.
Too bad. I guess your so-called
diamonds were a little low on calcium.
You couldn't pay me to do that again.
Hmm?
Hey, there's a woman passed out over there.
I assume it's Rose, the user of the High Priestess.
She doesn't seem dangerous. Should we just leave her?
I think I'll go see if she's hot or not.
From the looks of it, she's got a pretty nice body.
Let's see.
How's it going over there, Polnareff?
Nothing to see here, folks! No comment whatsoever!
Trust me, you don't wanna see her. Her teeth
are all ugh, so there's no point in looking.
I see.
It hasn't been easy, but we finally made it to Egypt.
Indeed. A trip that would have taken a mere 20
hours by plane ended up taking a whopping 30 days.
It's been quite the adventure.
We've gone inside a brain and even inside our dreams.
Our dreams?
What do you mean, Kakyoin?
Why are you talking about dreams?
It's morning. Wake up already.
Oh, right. You guys don't remember that.
Huh?
Whatever. Let's go.
Four mysterious and otherworldly stands powered
by the mystical and symbolized by the tarot.
Joseph Joestar once described their
journey as "around the world in 80 days."
From Tokyo to Hong Kong, they faced Tower of Gray.
In Southeast Asia, they tackled
Dark Blue Moon and Strength.
In Singapore, they encountered
Ebony Devil and Yellow Temperance.
In Calcutta, India, it was Hanged Man and Emperor.
In Varanasi, India, the Empress,
and near the Pakistani border,
they fought Wheel of Fortune.
In the mountains of Pakistan, they battled Justice.
In Karachi, Pakistan, the Lovers.
In the desert of the United Arab Emirates, the Sun,
and in Saudi Arabia, Death 13.
On a small island in the red sea, Judgment.
And now, on the Red Sea floor,
they've just defeated High Priestess.
With several of Dio's assassins vanquished,
they have finally arrived in Egypt.
Only a few of the tarot cards still remain.
But little do JoJo and company know new threats
lie ahead in Egypt ready to take our heroes on.
That's...
One, two, three...
Nine.
There are nine in all, both genders.
Eh?
What the...
What the hell was that?
Have the meddlesome flies swarming around been swatted?
That Speedwagon foundation,
for pity's sake, I can't let my guard down for a minute.
I must say I've gotten quite used to this body.
Tell me, Jonathan, can you feel it?
Your descendants are inching ever closer.
It can be so cruel and unforgiving,
this wretched little world of ours.
So that's what's been going on.
Why didn't you just tell me Jotaro
was helping you with your work?
That's fantastic.
The boy still has a long way to go, compared to me.
So this work is important enough for you to ask for help?
That's right.
It's my most important mission yet,
and it's imperative that we don't mess up.
But as long as we work together, we
should get it done without too much trouble.
Hmm.
Say, Joseph, could I speak to Jotaro?
Eh? Sure, but what do you want to talk to him about?
Nothing much. Is it wrong that I want
to hear my darling grandson's voice?
Well, no.
Jotaro, it's for you.
Hmm?
Hey, it's me.
Grandpa told me everything, Jotaro.
Work hard, and take care of your grandfather for me.
Will do.
I know in my heart if you work together, you Joestar men
can overcome just about any hardship that comes your way.
Eh?
I truly believe that.
Grandma Suzie, you...
What's the matter? You sound so serious all of a sudden.
It's nothing.
All right, I'm hanging up. I
look forward to good news. Ciao.
Madam.
Hmm?
It's hard for me to believe it,
but at this point, it's already been 30
years that I've worked for the Joestar family,
but I can honestly say that we've
never faced something of this magnitude.
Oh, come now. You're overreacting.
Didn't he say it was just a little business trip?
Ah. Well, I suppose so.
It's so troublesome when men act
selfish and refuse to tell us anything.
But I've grown accustomed to it.
The Joestar family has been
like this for an entire century.
I'm sure if she were here, she'd say
the same thing and laugh it all off.
Hmm?
What's the matter, Jotaro?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Hmm?
All right, it's time to head out.
After a century, it's time for us Joestars
to bring an end to Dio's grip on our family.
We don't have to do it alone.
Hey, Mr. Joestar!
We got the car that you asked us to buy!
Let's hurry, and hit the road.
We should probably get to where
we're going before it gets too dark!
Well, old man?
Okay, you're right. Guess we're pretty lucky, huh?
Yeah, yeah, hold your horses! We're coming!
This is the land of Egypt, a nation that's 97% desert.
However, thanks to the blessings of the Nile,
beautiful, fertile green spreads
across the entirety of its riverbanks.
In addition to the culture of the ancient Egyptians,
Egypt is also home to Persian, Greek, Roman, Muslim, and
Arabian cultures, and all have left their indelible marks.
What bizarre adventures and challenges
await Jotaro and the others in this eternal land
as they continue their perilous journey?
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian