How could this have happened?
I can't believe...
We totally fell for it.
Having managed to halt the
Lovers' horrifyingly invasive attack,
Jotaro and company choose to avoid
the political unrest in Iran and Iraq
and instead cross the Arabian sea at
Karachi to arrive in the United Arab Emirates.
Now then, if you'd be so kind as to sign this document,
everything will be squared away, sir.
Right here, yes?
Man, oh, man.
You know,I'm the kinna guy who do almost
anything for a pretty girl, even buy a car.
My, aren't you sweet?
How would you feel about the
two of us having dinner sometime?
Sorry, Polnareff.
I hate to interrupt when you're obviously so busy, but...
Mr. Joestar!
Come on. It's time to leave.
Seriously, try not to mess with the hair.
Do you know how hard it is to make it look this good?
As if anybody cares about your hairdo.
You're driving.
Right-o.
Au revior, mademoiselle.
Hey, Mr. Joestar,
I don't get why we're riding in such a
fancy, expensive car in this sandy death trap.
Wouldn't it be better for us to
get an off-road vehicle instead?
Oh, there's a method to my madness.
C'est magnifique! This country's amazing.
Are you guys seeing what I am here?
It's like every house is a crazy mansion or something.
Yeah.
In Tokyo, a house like one of these,
would cost three or four billion yen.
However, for most people in
this country, it's standard living.
It wasn't but 20 years ago that
this place was a barren desert,
though, thanks to a thriving oil industry,
it's grown into a playground for the rich.
The sun is merciless, but at least with air conditioning,
it's perfectly comfortable inside the car,
so no complaints here.
What's wrong, Kakyoin?
It's nothing. I was just
thinking about how open it is here.
I know we could spot anyone following us,
but I just can't shake the feeling
that there's someone out there watching.
Yeah, can't say that I blame you.
Well, back to business.
I've given a bit of thought to the route we should take.
About 100 kilometers northwest
is a village called Yarpline.
The desert and mountains make
taking a direct route near impossible.
It normally takes two days to reach by car,
so to expedite the travel time,
the locals use a Cessna to get there.
If you want my opinion,
we should go to the village and buy a Cessna
in order to cross the vast Saudi Arabian desert.
You know, I've been apprehensive
about getting anywhere near a plane.
If a stand user attacked and the plane went down,
we'd be putting innocent lives in harm's way,
but if we had a Cessna, I could be the pilot.
We'd be able to save a couple of days for sure.
Flying in a Cessna with a man
who's been in three plane crashes,
yeah, that seems like a perfect idea to me.
That comment notwithstanding,
our priority should be crossing the desert
and hightailing it to the village of Yarpline.
It'll take us one day on camelback.
Camelback?
A Cessna is one thing, but on camelback?
I've never ridden a camel in my life!
Just leave everything to me.
I know these creatures well,
and I'll teach you how to ride them.
You boys sit back, and watch the magic happen.
You want camels, you say?
Sure, I have them, but they're gonna cost you, my friend,
and they need a gentle touch.
We're kind of in a life-or-death situation here,
so we need them, whatever it takes.
As for payment, how about a trade for that car?
I couldn't possibly accept such a generous offer!
Yeah, Mr. Joestar!
And besides, you literally just bought that car!
What other reason did you think I
had to buy such a fancy, expensive car?
It's true an off-road vehicle would perform better here,
but we're not in the big city.
We can't just write a check in this place,
and cash isn't accepted here.
In my experience, trading is far
more effective in places such as these.
If you try to buy safety for cheap in a time of emergency,
you'll find yourself even worse off in the end.
Besides, I don't know about you, but
I think we've suffered enough already.
Hey, mister!
I take it this seals the deal?
Oh, hey, you know what?
To make things a little more even,
I'd like the water in those tanks, too.
It's the most important thing when you're in the desert.
But the water isn't nearly as valuable as your car, sir.
You are very strange indeed, sir!
All right, everyone. Let's get ready, shall we?
Crossing the desert will be no
easy task. Brace yourselves, men!
Merde! That stinks!
Hey, Mr. Joestar, how the heck are we
supposed to get on one of these things?
It's, like, three meters tall!
Allow me to demonstrate the proper way to mount a camel.
You have to make them sit first, and then you get on.
Like I said, make them sit, and then get on.
You see? Just like this!
You make 'em sit, and then you get on 'em!
Give me a minute! Any second, this
beast is gonna sit and let me saddle up.
Hey! Sit down, would you?!
Damn it, you stubborn animal!
Mr. Joestar, you have ridden
one of these before, haven't you?
I will have you know that I've watched "Lawrence
of Arabia" three times now from start to finish!
I know all too well how to ride a camel!
Although, two of those times, I slept through half of it.
You learned to ride from a movie?!
So you're saying you've never actually ridden one before?
The saliva makes great sunscreen.
The more you know...
Listen up. When you're handling an animal,
it's absolutely imperative to
understand exactly how it feels,
and I mean exactly.
Here. Doesn't this yummy apple
look absolutely scrumptious?
It's really good!
Come on. Come on.
There's a good boy.
You see? I made the camel sit down. If you
just take the time to get inside its head,
it'll sit down for you for sure!
Whoa! I did it!
Whoa. It's so high off the ground.
By the way, did you know camels can
close their nostrils to keep the sand out?
And before I forget, you're forbidden
from making stupid camel jokes.
Is that understood?
Your turn. Now you greenhorns get to
learn the finer points of riding a camel.
Listen up.
The first thing you need to know is that
camels don't walk anything like horses.
The front and back legs on either side move
forward together, so these things can sway a lot,
but don't let that throw you off.
If you find a way to ride with the
camel's rhythm, I know you'll be just fine.
For example...
Yah! Hey, wait!
You're going too fast! Slow down!
Listen to me, damn it!
Yah! I didn't tell you to go that way!
Yaah!
Okay, then.
Now that everyone's gotten the hang
of mounting and riding their camels,
All right, we have a desert to get through!
The time has arrived, men!
Onward toward the northwest!
Hey, now! Wait just a minute! Hey!
Something's wrong.
I still haven't been able to shake the
feeling that someone out there is watching us.
Kakyoin, don't you think you
might be worrying a bit too much?
I mean, the palm leaves will erase our tracks.
Plus, we can see for kilometers in all directions.
If someone were here, we'd know.
Actually, I think he's onto something.
I feel some sort of presence, too.
Hey, Jotaro, why don't you go take a look?
How about it? Do you see anything suspicious out there?
No, nothing,
nothing whatsoever.
Even so, something's not right here, but what is it?
Hey, let's hurry up and go.
Yeah.
Let's get as far away as we can.
We'll keep pressing forward until
the sun goes down this evening,
then stop to pitch our tents.
It's much too dangerous for us to travel at night.
I only wish we could get out of this freaking heat.
Just look at this. It's reading 50 degrees Celsius.
Yeah, it is hot out here.
But then again, the weather is
at its hottest right around now.
Huh? 8:00?
Wha?
Jotaro, check your watch. What time does it say?
It's 10... Past 8:00.
Hey, old man!
My watch is correct.
We lost track of time,
but what the hell's going on?
According to my watch, it's past 8 P.M.
So why isn't the sun setting?
This is impossible.
The thermometer is jumping to 60 degrees Celsius!
No, the sun isn't setting at all. It's actually...
It's actually rising higher in the west!
Wait. Could it be that that sun is really...
A stand?
I don't understand how such a thing is even possible.
How could this sun actually be a stand?
Quickly, take cover behind those rocks!
How the hell could that sun be a stand?!
We're such fools. How did we miss this?!
I knew that we were being watched, but I never
thought this is why I couldn't see our stalker.
At this rate, that Sun is gonna burn all day...
No, all night long. Ah, nom de dieu!
It's going to roast us like a bunch of
rotisserie chickens. We're totally screwed!
Yeah,
though I doubt it'll take that long.
The thing is a sauna can dangerously
raise the body's temperature in minutes.
Okay, then, how do we fight it?
C'est des conneries! It's 70 degrees Celsius!
And to add insult to injury, we
can't tell if the stand is close or not!
The distance is impossible to judge!
Our only option here is to
quickly take out the stand user.
Indeed, the user.
He has to be nearby.
We have to find him.
He must have a way to conceal himself,
and somehow he's been following us all this time.
Hang on a minute.
What if it's like the Lovers we encountered in Pakistan?
Maybe this guy has a stand he can use from far away.
That's not the case this time.
Sure, a weak stand can be controlled from a distance,
but this Sun is just too strong.
The energy it's emitting is incredible!
The stand user has to be nearby.
Hey, check it out.
The camels are starting to
collapse from exposure to the heat.
And this waiting isn't getting us anywhere.
I'll use Hierophant to do some
reconnaissance around the area.
Kakyoin.
I'm only searching for the stand's rough location.
Once we know how far away it actually is,
we might just be able to locate the user.
20 meters. 40 meters.
60 meters. 80 meters.
100...
Something's not right.
Kakyoin, have Hierophant come back!
There's something's coming right at us!
Before that happens,
Emerald...
No! Kakyoin!
The camel!
You bastard!
I'm gonna bust a hole in the ground, everybody get in now!
Ora!
You okay, Kakyoin?
Yes, I am.
I was in the middle of initiating my Emerald Splash,
so that protected me from any major damage.
More concerning is this intense heat.
I feel like it's gonna drive me insane.
Did any of you notice that
attack was perfectly aimed at us?
And that could only mean that
the enemy has been watching us.
But from where? Where is he?
Polnareff, keep your voice down.
If you keep shouting, the enemy will find us.
Just lay low for now.
We'll sit tight for a while and see what happens next.
Oh, shit!
Things can't go on like this.
Come on. Think, damn it.
It's time for this old-timer
to take the bull by the horns.
But this isn't the most ideal spot.
I can't even use my best technique.
It's crucial that I get more information.
Jotaro.
Yah!
Son of a bitch!
Where the hell are you?!
How are you watching us?! Are you invisible or something?!
Show yourself, you coward! Damn!
Hey, Kakyoin, what's the matter?
Kakyoin!
What the hell are you laughing
about? Hey, snap out of it already.
Control yourself, man.
J-Jotaro!
This is happening to you, too?
P-Polnareff, no!
Not you, too.
Oh, my god, no!
They've all lost it!
This damn heat has driven them all completely insane!
I have my sanity, but what can I do?
Hey, Jotaro! Get a hold of yourself, man!
You have to settle down!
You need to listen to me, Jotaro.
Sometimes things get rough, but when
they do, you have to remain in control. Eh?
Please, please don't get the
wrong idea about this, Mr. Joestar.
Have a look at that rock over there.
It's large enough for someone
to hide behind. Don't you agree?
What? I don't follow you.
Oh, you will.
Now take a look at the rock
that's sitting on the opposite side.
Opposite side, huh?
Um...
You still don't see it, sir?
Have another look.
There's a rock that's shaped exactly the
same way, but it's on the opposite side.
The shadow is also reversed, which means...
What a stupid trick!
Move.
Stay here, old man.
Jotaro! If you go out there now, you're
all but asking for the enemy to attack you!
It's dangerous!
Ora!
How'd a hole suddenly appear in thin air?!
Good grief, old man.
You really are pathetic.
Well, I'll just assume that the
intense heat was too much for you,
or else I'd find it very hard to
believe that you're my grandfather.
Since we defeated the enemy stand, night's finally fallen.
Or maybe I should say it's back to being night.
However you wanna slice it, we're safe at last.
Just how long do you plan on hiding in that hole?
Oh, yeah, right.
Good grief.
It's finally gotten dark around here.
Well, what do you know? It's a mirror.
And look at this.
Check out the little car he's got behind the mirror.
It looks like it's rather comfy.
There's even air conditioning.
Man, I had no clue he was reflecting the desert
and tailing us from behind in this nifty little thing.
He was smarter than I thought.
I see he has a tank of water, too.
How about we take it off his hands?
Oh, and here's a drink.
Let me understand all this.
You mean we've already defeated the stand user?
There's nothing else to do?
We don't even know this guy's name,
but somehow we've already made short work of his stand?
Yes, you've hit the nail on the head.
So this was the sun card's stand, huh?
At first, he was pretty impressive,
but once we figured the guy out, he
actually kinda sucked, didn't he? Heh.
So off to our next destination.
It's pretty chilly in the desert at night, isn't it?
Hold your horses. Traveling at night is dangerous.
If we're not careful, we could lose our way.
Yeah, and with that idiot out of
the way, it'll be sweet dreams tonight.
Ah-choo!
Ba-dum-tss.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don't you know
If they move too quick
Oh, whey, oh
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
Oh, whey, oh
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with the hookah pipes say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blond waitresses take their trays
They spin around, and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
Oh, whey, oh
You drop your drink
Then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
Oh, whey, oh
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Whey, oh, whey, oh
Ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
Walk like an Egyptian